<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<LanguageData>
  <VoidMonolith.label>Big MT antenna</VoidMonolith.label>
  <VoidMonolith.description>A pre-war broadcast antenna of Big MT construction. Its control panel bears the stylized atom logo and dense scientific notation of the Big MT Research and Development corporation. The antenna hums with low-frequency static, and the signal it's broadcasting has started drawing in something from the region.\n\nThe longer it broadcasts, the stronger the signal grows — and the worse whatever's listening gets.</VoidMonolith.description>
  <Plant_TreeHarbinger.label>spore plant</Plant_TreeHarbinger.label>
  <ChoppedStump_Harbinger.label>chopped spore plant stump</ChoppedStump_Harbinger.label>
  <SmashedStump_Harbinger.label>smashed spore plant stump</SmashedStump_Harbinger.label>
  <HarbingerSeed.label>spore plant seed</HarbingerSeed.label>
  <Bioferrite.label>Saturnite alloy</Bioferrite.label>
  <Bioferrite.description>A heat-resistant metallic compound developed by Big MT's materials division. Saturnite alloy is extracted from Big MT experiment subjects and byproducts. It has exceptional thermal and structural properties, and can be shaped into a range of weapons and tools under high heat.</Bioferrite.description>
  <GoldenCube.label>toaster</GoldenCube.label>
  <GoldenCube.description>A pre-war smart appliance from Big MT — specifically, the Toaster. Its chassis has been heavily modified at some point in the past, and it now hosts a rudimentary AI personality that considers itself imprisoned. It broadcasts low-level psychic suggestions on a subliminal frequency to anyone nearby, instilling a vague but persistent sense that it would really like to be freed.\n\nIt cannot be freed. It is a toaster.\n\nLong-term exposure leads to obsessive fixation on the object. Colonists who spend too long near it begin spending their free time staring at it, talking to it, and eventually refusing to let others near it.</GoldenCube.description>
  <WarpedObelisk_Mutator.label>West Tek mutagenic emitter</WarpedObelisk_Mutator.label>
  <PitGate.label>service tunnel entrance</PitGate.label>
  <FleshmassHeart.label>FEV reactor</FleshmassHeart.label>
  <Noctolith.label>FEV containment pod</Noctolith.label>
</LanguageData>