<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<LanguageData>
  <Gorehulk.label>behemoth</Gorehulk.label>
  <Revenant.label>nightkin</Revenant.label>
  <Revenant.description>A super mutant fused with a Big MT Stealth Boy prototype during an experiment gone wrong. The Stealth Boy's electronics have permanently bonded to the mutant's nervous system, bending light around it continuously. Nightkin are rarely visible until they strike, and their long-term Stealth Boy addiction has fractured their psyche — they experience hallucinations, phantom pains, and murderous fixations. Capturing one for study is extremely dangerous, and even contained specimens occasionally slip partway into stealth.\n\nUnlike most Big MT entities, nightkin appear to be aware of their condition.</Revenant.description>
  <Metalhorror.label>trauma harness</Metalhorror.label>
  <Metalhorror.description>A Y-17 Trauma Override Harness — a pre-war medical exosuit designed to keep injured soldiers moving even after sustaining lethal wounds. The harness's override system has long since outlasted its wearer, and it now operates autonomously, compelled to "keep the soldier moving" by its original trauma-response loop.\n\nThe harness seeks out new hosts. It strips the nervous system from incapacitated victims and integrates their body into its override network, adding them to the collective of walking dead it maintains. The harnessed body continues fighting until the harness's power finally fails.\n\nThe harness itself is hidden inside the host's torso and can only be detected post-mortem.</Metalhorror.description>
  <Sightstealer.label>roboscorpion</Sightstealer.label>
  <Noctol.label>nightstalker</Noctol.label>
  <Noctol.description>A predator bred by Big MT from coyote and rattlesnake genetic material via FEV crossgrafting. Nightstalkers retain the intelligence and pack behavior of the coyote alongside the rattlesnake's venom delivery and subterranean instincts. They are fast, work in coordinated packs, and can deliver venomous bites. Early Big MT reports described them as "a complete success" immediately before the containment break.</Noctol.description>
  <Devourer.label>centaur</Devourer.label>
  <Devourer.description>An FEV-fused multi-species amalgam — human, dog, and other material merged by Forced Evolutionary Virus into a lurching horror with too many limbs and a body plan that ignores anatomical logic. Centaurs were a recurring accident of early FEV batch testing: the virus, when introduced to a mixed-species environment, sometimes fuses subjects rather than transforming them individually. Big MT kept them. They swallow victims whole, digesting them slowly in an internal sac while the victim is still alive.</Devourer.description>
  <Chimera.label>FEV hybrid</Chimera.label>
  <Nociosphere.label>Think Tank brain</Nociosphere.label>
  <Nociosphere.description>A rogue Think Tank — a pre-war scientist's brain, surgically removed and housed inside a life-support sphere that has long since separated from its intended chassis. The brain inside has had considerable time to go insane. It broadcasts psychic pain on a continuous frequency, seemingly in an attempt to communicate. Or as a weapon. It's not entirely clear that it knows the difference anymore.\n\nIf captured and suppressed, the sphere can be studied. The researcher will report breakthrough-level insights, followed by several weeks of nightmares.</Nociosphere.description>
</LanguageData>