<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor.description>A suit of advanced power armor developed by the Enclave. Offers exceptional protection against all forms of damage, enhanced mobility, and complete environmental sealing. Wearing this armor marks its user as a force to be reckoned with on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor.label>Enclave Advanced Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>An advanced helmet designed for Enclave soldiers, offering exceptional protection against ballistic, blunt, and heat damage. Equipped with integrated systems for toxic environment resistance.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Enclave Advanced Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII.description>The MkII variant of the Enclave Advanced Power Armor, featuring improved environmental sealing and enhanced durability for prolonged combat scenarios.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII.label>Enclave Advanced Power Armor MkII</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII_Helmet.description>The Mk II variant of the Advanced Power Armor Helmet, featuring enhanced durability and improved environmental resistance for hazardous conditions.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII_Helmet.label>Enclave Advanced Power Armor Mk II Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Advanced_Power_Armor_MkII_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor.description>Advanced combat armor issued to Enclave troopers. Constructed from reinforced composites, it offers substantial protection against ballistic and melee threats while allowing for mobility in hostile environments.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor.label>Enclave Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor_Helmet.description>PLACEHOLDER</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor_Helmet.label>Enclave Combat Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Combat_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor.description>The Hellfire Power Armor is an advanced Enclave suit designed for extreme environments and frontline assault. Its reinforced plating and advanced heat dispersal systems provide unmatched protection against fire and explosions, making its wearer a walking fortress in the most hazardous conditions.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor.label>Enclave Hellfire Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A heavy-duty helmet for the Hellfire Power Armor, offering unparalleled protection and resistance to extreme environmental conditions.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Enclave Hellfire Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Hellfire_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Cap.description>A distinguished cap worn by Enclave officers, symbolizing authority and discipline. Made from high-quality materials, it offers moderate protection and a professional appearance.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Cap.label>Enclave Officer Cap</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Coat.description>A formal coat worn by Enclave officers, tailored from high-quality materials and adorned with insignia. It signifies authority and provides moderate protection while maintaining a commanding presence.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Coat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Coat.label>Enclave Officer Coat</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Officer_Coat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Boots.description>Specialized boots worn by Enclave scientists, designed with reinforced soles and advanced materials to protect against chemical spills, radiation, and hazardous terrain during field research.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Boots.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Boots.label>Enclave Scientist Boots</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Boots.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Glove.description>Protective gloves worn by Enclave scientists, made from advanced polymers to shield hands from chemicals, contaminants, and the harsh elements encountered during fieldwork.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Glove.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Glove.label>Enclave Scientist Gloves</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Glove.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Helmet.description>An advanced helmet designed for Enclave scientists, equipped with protective visors and integrated sensors to assist in hazardous environments.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Helmet.label>Enclave Scientist Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Outfit.description>A suit commonly worn by the Enclave's scientists, especially when working in the hazardous wasteland. It's a fully enclosed white suit with special polymers woven into it and a helmet with an orange visor made from plexiglass. It comes with a built-in computer system and various scientific instruments to support all manners of intellectual pursuits.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Outfit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Outfit.label>Enclave Scientist Outfit</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Scientist_Outfit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Sturdy_Combat_Armor.description>Advanced combat armor issued to Enclave troopers. Constructed from reinforced composites, it offers substantial protection against ballistic and melee threats while allowing for mobility in hostile environments.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Sturdy_Combat_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Sturdy_Combat_Armor.label>Enclave Sturdy Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Sturdy_Combat_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Cap.description>A practical cap issued to Enclave troopers, providing basic protection and shielding against the elements while maintaining a professional look.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Cap.label>Enclave Trooper Cap</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Uniform.description>A jet-black uniform with a tan jacket and pants that are worn over it. The outer layer is made of a sturdy material designed to withstand the harsh conditions of the wasteland. The uniform comes with a pair of knee-high boots, black gloves, and a utility belt. It does protect well against the elements, less so against bullets.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Uniform.label>Enclave Trooper Uniform</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_Trooper_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor.description>A next-generation Enclave power armor, the X-02 offers formidable protection and advanced environmental sealing. It is lighter and more intimidating than earlier models.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor.label>Enclave X-02 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>The standard helmet for the X02 Power Armor, providing balanced protection and advanced features for Enclave operatives in the field.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Enclave X02 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor.description>A rare variant of the X-02, the Tesla Power Armor is fitted with electromagnetic shielding and energy-dispersing coils. It offers superior protection against heat and electrical attacks, making its wearer a terrifying sight on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor.label>Enclave X-02 Tesla Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A specialized helmet for the X02 Tesla Power Armor, designed to protect against energy-based attacks while maintaining high resistance to environmental hazards.</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Enclave X02 Tesla Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Enclave_X02_Tesla_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Bullet_Plasma_Cannon.label>Supercharged Plasma Bolt</FCP_Bullet_Plasma_Cannon.label>
  <FCP_Currency_Enclave_Platinum_Bullion.description>High-purity platinum coins minted by the Enclave as a reserve currency for high-value transactions. Each bullion coin bears the distinctive Enclave eagle emblem and represents the technological supremacy and economic power of America's shadow government. These precious metal coins are highly valued both for their platinum content and as symbols of Enclave authority.</FCP_Currency_Enclave_Platinum_Bullion.description>
  <FCP_Currency_Enclave_Platinum_Bullion.label>Enclave platinum bullion</FCP_Currency_Enclave_Platinum_Bullion.label>
  <FCP_Enclave_Vertibird.description>Vertibird is a designation for a series of vertical take-off and landing (VTOL) aircraft. These multipurpose tiltrotor aircraft were developed by the United States military and rapidly became a primary gunship and transport aircraft. This one is now in use by the Enclave.</FCP_Enclave_Vertibird.description>
  <FCP_Enclave_Vertibird.label>Enclave vertibird</FCP_Enclave_Vertibird.label>
  <FCP_Enclave_VertibirdIncoming.label>Enclave vertibird (incoming)</FCP_Enclave_VertibirdIncoming.label>
  <FCP_Enclave_VertibirdLeaving.label>Enclave vertibird (leaving)</FCP_Enclave_VertibirdLeaving.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.description>An Enclave refinement of the multiplas design, featuring three independently-controlled plasma generation chambers in a triangular array. Each trigger pull unleashes a devastating barrage of three plasma bolts simultaneously. The advanced targeting computer helps maintain accuracy despite the weapon's aggressive spread pattern, making it a feared close-to-medium range weapon.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.label>Enclave Advanced Multiplas Rifle</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.description>The pinnacle of Enclave plasma rifle technology. This advanced assault variant features an upgraded plasma generation chamber, enhanced magnetic confinement, and superior targeting systems. Significantly more accurate and reliable than standard plasma rifles, it represents the cutting edge of pre-war American military technology.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.label>Enclave Assault Plasma Rifle</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.description>A devastating heavy weapon platform developed by the Enclave for anti-armor and siege operations. This massive plasma cannon generates and magnetically accelerates supercharged plasma bolts with enough energy to melt through bunker walls and power armor alike. The weapon's immense power comes at the cost of weight, slow cycling time, and the need for enhanced cooling systems. Typically mounted on vehicles or power armor, it can be wielded by sufficiently strong soldiers in desperate situations.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.label>Enclave Plasma Cannon</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.description>A compact plasma submachine gun developed by the Enclave for close-quarters operations. This weapon sacrifices range and raw power for a dramatically increased rate of fire, making it ideal for room clearing and urban combat. The miniaturized plasma generation system allows for rapid cycling between shots.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.label>Enclave Plasma SMG</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.description>The Self-Modulating Energy Loadout Efficiency (SMELE) plasma rifle represents the Enclave's answer to the need for versatile energy weapons. This sophisticated platform features adaptive power regulation, allowing it to balance between sustained fire and devastating single shots. Its modular design incorporates both offensive and defensive systems, making it the preferred weapon of elite Enclave special operations units.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.label>Enclave SMELE Plasma Rifle</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>PLACEHOLDER</FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>Standard Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>A Vault-Tec collectors edition lunchbox. It's a little dirty, but still opens and may have something useful inside!</FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>Dirty Vault-Tec Collectors Edition Lunchbox</FCP_Item_Enclave_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_Enclave_Tech_Crate.description>PLACEHOLDER</FCP_Item_Enclave_Tech_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_Enclave_Tech_Crate.label>Standard Tech Resource Crate</FCP_Item_Enclave_Tech_Crate.label>
</LanguageData>