<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFE_Mechanoids_Power.description>Power represents the state of a machine's internal battery. If it gets too low, the machine will stop performing tasks and return to its station to recharge.</VFE_Mechanoids_Power.description>
  <VFE_Mechanoids_Power.label>power</VFE_Mechanoids_Power.label>
  <VBE_Chemical_Caffeine.description>Because of a caffeine addiction, this person needs to regularly consume caffeine to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</VBE_Chemical_Caffeine.description>
  <VBE_Chemical_Caffeine.label>caffeine</VBE_Chemical_Caffeine.label>
  <VBE_Chemical_Tobacco.description>Because of a tobacco dependence, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</VBE_Chemical_Tobacco.description>
  <VBE_Chemical_Tobacco.label>tobacco</VBE_Chemical_Tobacco.label>
  <VME_Anonymity.description>Anonymity reflects on how secretive a person finds their identity and personality to be. A pawn with this belief will feel happier when it’s high and unhappy when it’s nearing depletion. Anonymity slowly rises over time and any social interaction or exposed facial features will lower it.</VME_Anonymity.description>
  <VME_Anonymity.label>anonymity</VME_Anonymity.label>
  <VME_Corruption.description>Corruption reflects a person's desire to give in to the dark, eldritch, and possibly even violent desires deeply embedded within them; a mildly corrupt pawn cannot lose ideological certainty. Corruption slowly fades daily, but can be paused by nearby obelisks and increased by incantation rituals. Upon reaching 100 corruption a pawn will immediately begin mentally breaking, and upon reaching 0 a pawn will easily be swayed to any other ideoligion</VME_Corruption.description>
  <VME_Corruption.label>corruption</VME_Corruption.label>
  <VME_Desserts.description>Dessert need represents the desire to engorge yourself with lusciously sinful confectionery creations.</VME_Desserts.description>
  <VME_Desserts.label>desserts</VME_Desserts.label>
  <GR_ElectroEgg.description>Because of an active mechanites addiction, this person needs to regularly consume mechanoid eggs, produced by mecha-chickens, to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</GR_ElectroEgg.description>
  <GR_ElectroEgg.label>active mechanites</GR_ElectroEgg.label>
  <GR_Chemical_Featherdust.description>Because of a developed Featherdust dependence, this person needs to regularly consume the drug to avoid withdrawal symptoms.</GR_Chemical_Featherdust.description>
  <GR_Chemical_Featherdust.label>featherdust</GR_Chemical_Featherdust.label>
  <VAspirE_Fulfillment.description>Fulfillment represents how happy someone is with their personal achievements in life. If they achieve their dreams and complete their lifetime goals, the fulfillment will increase. Each stage of fulfillment decreases mental break threshold. Achieving maximum fulfillment will result in a final growth moment.</VAspirE_Fulfillment.description>
  <VAspirE_Fulfillment.label>fulfillment</VAspirE_Fulfillment.label>
  <VCEV_FoodVariety.description>Represents the assortment of different foods in a colonist's diet, reflecting their ability to access and consume a wide range of nutrients and flavors, calculated as an average of the variety in meals and the variety in ingredients in those meals.\n\nLow values will cause a mood penalty, while higher values will cause a mood bonus.</VCEV_FoodVariety.description>
  <VCEV_FoodVariety.label>food variety</VCEV_FoodVariety.label>
  <Bladder.description>To prevent the risk of disease it is important to maintain a good level of sanitation by removing or treating waste, and preventing sewage from contaminating you water supply.</Bladder.description>
  <Bladder.label>bladder</Bladder.label>
  <DBHThirst.description>Water is required for many of life’s physiological processes. If this reaches zero then the creature will slowly die of dehydration</DBHThirst.description>
  <DBHThirst.label>thirst</DBHThirst.label>
  <Hygiene.description>Good personal hygiene is important for reducing the risk of disease and keeping colonists happy and healthy.</Hygiene.description>
  <Hygiene.label>hygiene</Hygiene.label>
</LanguageData>
