<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- Apparel_ArchoShuttle -->
  <!-- Apparel_ShuttleComm -->
  <!-- Spaceports_Beacon -->
  <!-- Spaceports_FuelDispenser -->
  <!-- Spaceports_FuelProcessor -->
  <!-- Spaceports_FuelTank -->
  <!-- Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad -->
  <!-- Spaceports_VisitorSpot -->

  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>A bizarre archotech signal flare that calls a vertibird out of nowhere. Whatever intelligence answers it is willing to provide one miraculous extraction.</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>vertibird signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>A single-use field transponder used to request Brotherhood vertibird pickup.</Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>Brotherhood field transponder</Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.description>A long-range IFF beacon and traffic-control mast used by Brotherhood cells and trusted allies to advertise a safe vertibird approach, coordinate landings, and broadcast refueling availability.</Spaceports_Beacon.description>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.label>Brotherhood flight beacon</Spaceports_Beacon.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>A service terminal that sells aviation fuel to Brotherhood vertibirds and other authorized aircraft. It must be placed adjacent to a vertibird pad; once payment is verified, pumps inside the pad draw fuel from tanks on the same power network.</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>vertibird refueling terminal</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>An industrial processor that refines volatile feedstock and water into aviation fuel for Brotherhood vertibirds. It runs best with water access and turns surplus chemfuel into saleable flight stock.</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>aviation fuel processor</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.description>A chilled storage tank for processed aviation fuel. Keep it powered or the stock begins to evaporate away.</Spaceports_FuelTank.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.label>aviation fuel tank</Spaceports_FuelTank.label>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>A hardened landing pad with guidance lights, fueling hookups, and an encrypted transponder for Brotherhood vertibirds. Keep it powered and clear, and visiting patrols, quartermasters, traders, and allied passengers can touch down here.</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>Brotherhood vertibird pad</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>Designates a configurable point where visiting Brotherhood personnel, traders, and allied passengers will gather after landing. If no valid point is found, they will remain near their vertibird.</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>vertibird mustering point</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>
</LanguageData>
