<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorCataphract -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorLocust -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige -->
  <!-- Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige -->
  <!-- Apparel_Coronet -->
  <!-- Apparel_Crown -->
  <!-- Apparel_EltexSkullcap -->
  <!-- Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet -->
  <!-- Apparel_PsyfocusRobe -->
  <!-- Apparel_PsyfocusShirt -->
  <!-- Apparel_PsyfocusVest -->
  <!-- Apparel_RobeRoyal -->

  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy armor used by Whitespring secret service units to break fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>An ornate heavy armor awarded to high-ranking Whitespring secret service operatives. Embedded cryptex threads enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with short-range thrust capabilities for quick movement in urban environments. Urban scouts prefer close-quarters engagements and quick strikes rather than static defense.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>urban scout armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor specialized for cold and arctic operations, fitted with a shoulder-mounted launcher. Arctic marines specialize in breaching cold-climate fortifications.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>arctic marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet used by Whitespring patriots, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>patriot marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of armor used by Whitespring patriots. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and ceremonial, patriot marine armor marks membership and rank. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>patriot marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A beret styled with the Whitespring insignia, worn by enclave personnel of certain ranks.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>Whitespring Beret</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A cap worn by senior Whitespring researchers, denoting a leadership role in cryptid studies.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>Whitespring Scientist Cap</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for cryptid research focus. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>cryptex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for cryptid research focus. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>cryptex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>cryptex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special cryptid-focusing materials. These enhance cryptid sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>cryptex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>cryptex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, formal longcoat used by Whitespring patriots and officers. Embroidered with the enclave sigils, it marks membership and rank.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>patriot longcoat</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
</LanguageData>
