<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- GrandThrone -->
  <!-- MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink -->
  <!-- MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink -->
  <!-- MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink -->
  <!-- Throne -->

  <GrandThrone.description>An ornate grand chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential grand chair grants the occupant a sense of authority and dignity.</GrandThrone.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>presidential grand chair</GrandThrone.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword refined for Whitespring security officers. Its mono-molecular edge cuts through armor with ease, while an embedded cryptex core sharpens the wielder's cryptid insight and stabilizes the weapon's high-speed response.

The cryptex core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once that bond is established, the blade responds with extreme speed and precision and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>cryptex molecular blade</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored officer's sword wrapped in a sheath of captive plasma. Targets are sliced by the inner edge and burned by the surrounding field, giving Whitespring officers a close-range weapon that can cut and cauterize in the same strike.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the sword responds with unusual speed and control and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>plasma officer sword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A Whitespring warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. On impact it discharges a powerful pulse in addition to the physical blow, making it especially effective against power armor, robots, and other advanced hardware.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the hammer tracks the wielder's timing and strike rhythm with unusual accuracy and rejects any hand outside its assigned operator.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>pulse hammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <Throne.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential chair may be used as a focus for certain duties and ceremonies.</Throne.description>
  <Throne.label>presidential chair</Throne.label>
</LanguageData>
