<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.description>A distinguished uniform issued to generals of the United States Army, symbolizing command and tradition. Its immaculate condition and ornate details reflect the prestige and authority of America's military leadership.</FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.label>US General Uniform</FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.description>A winterized uniform issued to generals of the United States Army, symbolizing command and tradition. Enhanced with insulated lining and weatherproof materials, it provides warmth and protection in cold climates while maintaining the prestige and authority of America's military leadership.</FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.label>Winterized US General Uniform</FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.description>The standard-issue US Army Combat Armor of 2077, featuring advanced composite plating and modular design. Widely deployed across conflict zones, it offers robust protection against ballistic and energy threats while maintaining mobility. Integrated with environmental seals and tactical interfaces, this armor represents the pinnacle of military technology in the United States.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.label>US Army Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Helmet.description>The standard-issue US Army Combat Helmet of 2077, designed to complement the advanced composite plating and modular features of the armor. Widely deployed alongside its armor counterpart, it provides robust protection against ballistic and energy threats while maintaining comfort and tactical functionality. Integrated with environmental seals and communication interfaces, this helmet exemplifies the pinnacle of military headgear technology in the United States.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Helmet.label>US Army Combat Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_General_Cap.description>A distinguished cap issued to generals of the United States Army, symbolizing command and tradition. Its immaculate condition and ornate details reflect the prestige and authority of America's military leadership.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_General_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_General_Cap.label>US Army General Cap</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_General_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.description>A United States Army variant of the legendary T-51 power armor. Painted in military olive drab and bearing the insignia of the US Armed Forces, this suit represents the standard issue for Army mechanized infantry units. The T-51's titanium composite shell and advanced servos provided unmatched battlefield superiority during the Resource Wars, making its wearers nearly unstoppable forces of pre-war military might.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.label>US Army T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A United States Army variant of the T-51 power armor helmet. Painted in military olive drab with Army insignia, this helmet provides the legendary protection of the T-51 system while marking its wearer as a member of the pre-war American mechanized infantry.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>US Army T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.description>The ultimate expression of United States Army power armor technology before the Great War. This T-60 variant bears the proud colors and markings of the US military, issued only to the most elite mechanized infantry divisions. Combining superior protection with advanced environmental systems and intimidating presence, the T-60 represented the cutting edge of American military engineering and the backbone of armored operations during the final days of the old world.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.label>US Army T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>The helmet component of the United States Army's T-60 power armor. Bearing the colors and insignia of the pre-war military, this advanced helmet combines cutting-edge heads-up display technology with maximum protection, representing the peak of American power armor engineering before the Great War.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>US Army T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.description>Heavy armor worn by United States Marine Corps personnel. Provides excellent protection against ballistic threats.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.label>US Marine Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Combat_Helmet.description>The standard-issue US Marine Corps Combat Helmet of 2077, engineered specifically for the elite Marine Corps with enhanced ballistic protection and amphibious operation capabilities. Features advanced composite materials, integrated communication systems, environmental seals, and a built-in atmospheric filtration system that provides protection against chemical agents, toxic gases, and environmental hazards. This helmet represents the pinnacle of Marine Corps tactical headgear technology.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Combat_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Combat_Helmet.label>US Marine Combat Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Combat_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Diving_Helmet.description>A specialized diving helmet used by United States Marine Corps combat divers and underwater demolition teams. Features an integrated breathing system, reinforced visor, and communication equipment designed for underwater operations. Provides excellent protection against environmental hazards while maintaining clear vision and communication capabilities during amphibious assaults.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Diving_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Diving_Helmet.label>US Marine Diving Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Diving_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.description>A lighter variant of the US Marine Corps armor, sacrificing some protection for improved mobility and reduced weight. Designed for rapid deployment scenarios and extended field operations where agility is paramount. Still provides substantial ballistic protection while allowing marines to operate with greater speed and endurance.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.label>US Marine Light Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.description>A specialized wetsuit worn by United States Marine Corps divers and amphibious assault teams. Made from advanced neoprene composite, it provides thermal insulation and environmental protection while maintaining flexibility for underwater operations. Designed to be worn under marine armor during amphibious missions.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.label>US Marine Wetsuit</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.description>An elegant formal suit worn by the President of the United States. Made from the finest materials with exquisite tailoring, it represents the dignity and authority of the highest office in the nation. The suit is both comfortable and imposing, suitable for state functions and diplomatic meetings.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.label>President's suit</FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.description>Advanced tactical armor issued to elite United States Secret Service agents tasked with protecting the highest levels of government. Engineered from composite alloys and reinforced plating, this armor provides exceptional ballistic and energy protection without sacrificing mobility. The low-profile design allows agents to blend into formal settings while remaining combat-ready at a moment's notice.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.label>Secret Service Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Helmet.description>An advanced tactical helmet issued to United States Secret Service agents. Featuring reinforced composite construction, integrated communication systems, and ballistic face protection, this helmet provides comprehensive head protection while maintaining situational awareness. The sleek matte-black finish and professional appearance allow agents to remain imposing yet discreet during protective operations.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Helmet.label>Secret Service Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.description>A specialized tactical underarmor worn by United States Secret Service agents beneath their armor plating. Constructed from advanced ballistic weave and moisture-wicking fibers, it provides a baseline layer of protection and climate control. The carefully designed cut ensures full range of motion while maintaining professional appearance under formal attire when needed.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.label>Secret Service Underarmor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.description>The pinnacle of pre-war American power armor technology, the T-65 was developed exclusively for elite Secret Service operatives assigned to the most critical national security operations. Incorporating cutting-edge materials science and engineering far beyond standard military issue, this armor provides unmatched protection and strength enhancement. Its distinctive profile is instantly recognizable to those familiar with the inner workings of the United States government.</FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.label>T-65 Secret Service Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>The helmet component of the legendary T-65 Secret Service Power Armor. This masterwork of engineering incorporates the most advanced heads-up display systems, threat detection arrays, and life support equipment ever fielded by the United States. The multi-layered composite construction provides superior protection against all known threats while maintaining perfect environmental sealing and combat awareness.</FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>T-65 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.description>The winterized variant of the US Army Combat Armor of 2077, featuring advanced composite plating, modular design, and enhanced insulation for extreme cold. Outfitted with weatherproof materials and environmental seals, it offers robust protection against ballistic and energy threats while ensuring soldier mobility and warmth in harsh winter conditions.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.label>Winterized US Army Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Helmet.description>The winterized variant of the US Army Combat Helmet, issued in 2077 for operations in extreme cold environments. Enhanced with advanced thermal insulation, weatherproofing, and an integrated facial protection system, it maintains the robust protection and sophisticated features of the standard model while ensuring comfort and operational effectiveness in harsh winter conditions. The built-in thermal faceguard offers superior coverage against wind and frostbite, while integrated environmental seals and communication interfaces remain standard, making this helmet essential for cold-weather deployments.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Helmet.label>Winterized US Army Combat Helmet</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_General_Cap.description>A white variant of the US Army General Cap, issued  for winter use. It retains the same distinguished appearance and authority as the standard cap, with no additional insulation or weatherproofing.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_General_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_General_Cap.label>Winterized US Army General Cap</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_General_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Currency_USA_Pre_War_Dollar.description>U.S. Dollar bill, standard currency in America. Used for everyday transactions and trade.</FCP_Currency_USA_Pre_War_Dollar.description>
  <FCP_Currency_USA_Pre_War_Dollar.label>U.S. Dollar</FCP_Currency_USA_Pre_War_Dollar.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.description>Constructed from hardened alloy steel and precision-machined components, this 10mm pistol combines reliability and enhanced stopping power with improved durability and armor penetration compared to field-grade sidearms. Favored by security forces.</FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.label>Alloy Steel 10mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Alloy_Steel_10mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.description>Built from hardened alloy steel and precision-machined components, this assault rifle delivers consistent, high-velocity fire under harsh conditions. Balanced ergonomics and a tuned gas system keep recoil manageable, making rapid follow-up shots practical even in heavy combat. Favored by hardened units for its durability and ability to punch through field-grade armor.</FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.label>Alloy Steel Assault Rifle</FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_USA_Alloy_Steel_Assault_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Food_Crate.description>A crate of food from the United States of America, standard issue.</FCP_Item_USA_Food_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Food_Crate.label>US Food Supply Crate</FCP_Item_USA_Food_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_MRE.description>A military Meal Ready to Eat from the United States Armed Forces. Individually packaged and designed for field use, it contains a complete meal with multiple components including an entree, sides, dessert, and accessories. More filling and palatable than standard survival packs, though it will never win any culinary awards. Never rots but can deteriorate if left outside.</FCP_Item_USA_MRE.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_MRE.label>US MRE</FCP_Item_USA_MRE.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Armor_Crate.description>A crate of armor from the United States Army, standard issue.</FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Armor_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Armor_Crate.label>US Army Armor Supply Crate</FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Armor_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>A crate of uniforms from the United States Army, standard issue.</FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>US Army Uniform Supply Crate</FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>A crate of weapons from the United States of America, standard issue.</FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>US Weapon Supply Crate</FCP_Item_USA_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Armor_Crate.description>A crate of armor from the United States Marine Corps, standard issue.</FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Armor_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Armor_Crate.label>US Marine Armor Supply Crate</FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Armor_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Crate.description>A crate of uniforms from the United States Marine Corps, standard issue.</FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Crate.label>US Marine Uniform Supply Crate</FCP_Item_USA_Uniform_Marine_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Shuttle_USA_Vertibird.description>Vertibird is a designation for a series of vertical take-off and landing (VTOL) aircraft. These multipurpose tiltrotor aircraft were developed by the United States military and rapidly became a primary gunship and transport aircraft.</FCP_Shuttle_USA_Vertibird.description>
  <FCP_Shuttle_USA_Vertibird.label>US vertibird</FCP_Shuttle_USA_Vertibird.label>
  <FCP_Shuttle_USA_VertibirdIncoming.label>U.S. vertibird (incoming)</FCP_Shuttle_USA_VertibirdIncoming.label>
  <FCP_Shuttle_USA_VertibirdLeaving.label>U.S. vertibird (leaving)</FCP_Shuttle_USA_VertibirdLeaving.label>
  <FCP_USA_Building_Anchorage_Memorial.description>This grand memorial commemorates the pivotal battle in Anchorage, where our brave US forces, led by General Constantine Chase, overcame the invading Chinese army commanded by General Jingwei. It stands as a tribute to the courage and sacrifice of those who defended our homeland and marks the turning point that secured our freedom.</FCP_USA_Building_Anchorage_Memorial.description>
  <FCP_USA_Building_Anchorage_Memorial.label>Anchorage</FCP_USA_Building_Anchorage_Memorial.label>
</LanguageData>