<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationSequence">
    <operations>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Crashlanded"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
            <description>Your airship tore itself apart over the wasteland and three of you barely made it down alive. The wreck scattered supplies across the desert, and now you have one chance to turn an airship crash site into a home.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Crashlanded"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
            <summary>Three survivors, a crashed airship, and one shot at settling the wasteland.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Crashlanded"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]</xpath>
        <value>
          <li Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog">
            <def>GameStartDialog</def>
              <text>Warning klaxons howl through the cabin as your airship tears itself apart over the wasteland. Three of you barely make it clear before the hull breaks open.

  When the smoke clears, you are alive, armed, and stranded beside the burning wreck of a pre-war aircraft. If you cannot raise shelter from twisted metal and scrap, the wasteland will finish what the crash started.</text>
            <closeSound>GameStartSting</closeSound>
          </li>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="LostTribe"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
            <description>Your tribe was burned out by steel war machines and only five of you escaped with what you could carry. Now you must keep the old ways alive long enough to raise a new home from dust, bone, and scrap.

Note: You begin poor, hungry, and far behind the technology of the wastes. This is a difficult scenario.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="LostTribe"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
            <summary>Five survivors from a ruined tribe try to rebuild with little more than tradition and grit. Difficult.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="LostTribe"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
        <value>
            <text>The old stories were right. The metal devils came in the night with fire, blades, and screaming engines. Your tribe fell before dawn.

Five of you survived the slaughter. Hungry, grieving, and alone, you now stand in a harsh land that offers nothing freely. Build again, and make sure your people do not vanish here.</text>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="TheRichExplorer"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
            <description>You were born behind a vault door, surrounded by safety, soft beds, and old-world lies. Instead of staying buried, you took your best gear and went looking for the real wasteland. Now your pod has dropped you far from any friendly road, alone with vault supplies and no one coming to save you.

Note: Strong gear cannot cover every weakness. This is an especially difficult early game scenario.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="TheRichExplorer"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
            <summary>One well-equipped vault dweller chasing the real wasteland instead of stories. Extra difficult.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="TheRichExplorer"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
        <value>
            <text>Life in the vault was safe, sealed, and dull. You grew up with polished corridors, filtered air, and the promise that the world outside was only death.

  You left anyway. Now the hatch opens onto a raw stretch of wasteland, and all you have are fine weapons, vault provisions, and your own nerve. Out here, no door closes behind you.</text>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="NakedBrutality"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
            <description>Someone stripped you, robbed you, and dumped you naked in the wasteland to die. No gear, no food, no allies, not even a knife. If you live through this, it will be because you refused to become carrion.

Warning: This scenario is brutally unfair. Death can come fast and for stupid reasons.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="NakedBrutality"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
            <summary>One naked wastelander left for dead with absolutely nothing. Extremely difficult and unfair.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="NakedBrutality"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
        <value>
            <text>Your mouth tastes like blood and dust. Whoever beat you, robbed you, and left you naked out here is long gone.

  The sun is rising, the ground is cold, and every living thing around you would happily finish the job. Stand up, find something useful, and prove the wasteland picked the wrong corpse.</text>
        </value>
      </li>
    </operations>
  </Operation>
</Patch>