<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>Das Appalachia Chapter steht am Scheideweg. Abgeschnitten von Lost Hills und gezwungen, unabhängig zu agieren, müssen Sie den Weg Ihres Kapitels bestimmen: Werden Sie „The Chain That Binds“ folgen – der strengen Codex-Doktrin, die vor allem die Erhaltung der Technologie verlangt? Oder brechen Sie mit der Tradition und werden Beschützer der Menschen im Ödland, um zu beweisen, dass die Bruderschaft mehr sein kann als nur Sammler? Ihre Isolation bedeutet keine Aufsicht, keine Verstärkung, sondern völlige Freiheit zu definieren, wofür die Bruderschaft in diesen Ländern wirklich steht.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>Appalachia-Kapitel</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>Paladin</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uphalt their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>Überreste des Stolzes von Lyon</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>The Mojave Chapter of the Bruderschaft des Stahls is a shadow of its former self, forced out of the verborgen Valley bunker and now struggling to survive in the harsh Mojave wasteland. Once a proud and disciplined force, they have been reduced to a scattered group, clinging to their mission of safeguarding humanity's technological heritage. Despite their diminished state, their mastery of power armor and energy weapons ensures they remain a formidable presence in the region.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>Mojave-Kapitel</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the Bruderschaft des Stahls, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uphalt the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>Ausgestoßene der Bruderschaft</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>Schutz</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>Ausgestoßen</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>Ausgestoßene</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>The Bruderschaft des Stahls is one of the altest still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their sEinkaufszentrum numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>Bruderschaft des Stahls</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>
