<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Arktos_FireAnts.description>A divergent insect geneline adapted into aggressive fire ants. They share the same eusocial behavior as the black ant strain, but operate as a separate colony and field only ember-colored castes.</Arktos_FireAnts.description>
  <Arktos_FireAnts.fixedName>Fire Ant Colony</Arktos_FireAnts.fixedName>
  <Arktos_FireAnts.label>fire ant colony</Arktos_FireAnts.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnts.pawnSingular>fire ant</Arktos_FireAnts.pawnSingular>
  <Arktos_FireAnts.pawnsPlural>fire ants</Arktos_FireAnts.pawnsPlural>
  <BigMT_ExperimentFaction.description>Escaped super mutants and other experiments from Big MT research sites. They operate on territorial instinct and broadcast-signal aggression rather than coordinated strategy. Not capable of diplomacy.</BigMT_ExperimentFaction.description>
  <BigMT_ExperimentFaction.label>Big MT experiments</BigMT_ExperimentFaction.label>
  <BigMT_ExperimentFaction.pawnSingular>experiment subject</BigMT_ExperimentFaction.pawnSingular>
  <BigMT_ExperimentFaction.pawnsPlural>experiment subjects</BigMT_ExperimentFaction.pawnsPlural>
  <Ancients.label>controlled vault</Ancients.label>
  <AncientsHostile.label>crazed vault</AncientsHostile.label>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Civil.description>A democratic settlement in the Nova-Arizona desert, where the shadow of Caesar's Legion falls long across the land. The settlers here draw largely from the Nat'L people, whose roots lie in the national park communities that kept to the canyons and monument lands when civilization collapsed. Governance tends toward consensus and elected leadership, though staying small enough to avoid Legion interest is a practical concern.</HHTools_Arizona_Civil.description>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Civil.label>civil Arizona settlement</HHTools_Arizona_Civil.label>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Raider.description>A raider gang roaming the canyons and desert trails of Nova-Arizona. They prey on the trade routes that thread between Legion-controlled territories and independent settlements, targeting those too isolated for any patrol to reach in time. Their speech, dress, and customs carry the echo of the region's native heritage — the wasteland ground it down but never erased it.</HHTools_Arizona_Raider.description>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Raider.label>Arizona raider</HHTools_Arizona_Raider.label>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Rough.description>An autocratic settlement carved out of the Nova-Arizona desert, run by a strongman, elder council, or local boss with no obligations to outside powers. The culture here reflects the deep heritage of the region — generations of hard wasteland survival in canyon country. The Legion is ever-present, but does not control everything.</HHTools_Arizona_Rough.description>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Rough.label>rough Arizona settlement</HHTools_Arizona_Rough.label>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Tribal.description>One of the Nat'L tribal communities of Nova-Arizona, descended from the tourists who visited the national parks long before the war. They move with the seasons through canyon country, carrying oral histories and customs. The Legion considers them a resource to conscript or a nuisance to remove, depending on the tribe's size and location.</HHTools_Arizona_Tribal.description>
  <HHTools_Arizona_Tribal.label>Arizona tribe</HHTools_Arizona_Tribal.label>
  <HHTools_California_Civil.description>A democratic settlement on the Two-California coast, stretching from Baja in the south to northern California. The region was struck hard by the bombs but rebuilt faster than most of the wasteland, largely owing to the influence of the New California Republic. Settlers here live under organized governance, with elected leadership, regulated trade, and access to NCR-affiliated traders and patrols.</HHTools_California_Civil.description>
  <HHTools_California_Civil.label>civil California settlement</HHTools_California_Civil.label>
  <HHTools_California_Raider.description>A raider gang operating along the Two-California coast. The region's trade routes, NCR supply convoys, and established settlements make it a rich target for organized raiding. These gangs stay mobile to avoid NCR response forces, striking at travelers and outlying communities along the coast and inland valleys.</HHTools_California_Raider.description>
  <HHTools_California_Raider.label>California raider</HHTools_California_Raider.label>
  <HHTools_California_Rough.description>An autocratic holdout on the Two-California coast. While the NCR extends its reach across much of the region, this settlement operates outside its law, run by whoever holds authority through force or reputation. The NCR's expansion is a constant backdrop to daily life here, and many such communities navigate a careful balance between independence and annexation.</HHTools_California_Rough.description>
  <HHTools_California_Rough.label>rough California settlement</HHTools_California_Rough.label>
  <HHTools_California_Tribal.description>A tribal community surviving in the margins of Two-California, in the coastal ranges and valleys where NCR influence fades and older ways of living persist. They hunt and gather along coastlands that were once heavily populated, trading with settlers when terms suit them, and keeping to themselves when they do not.</HHTools_California_Tribal.description>
  <HHTools_California_Tribal.label>California tribe</HHTools_California_Tribal.label>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Civil.description>A democratic settlement in the rain-soaked wastes of Cascadia, where the Pacific fog rarely lifts and the coast has been profoundly changed by the bombs and the years since. Settlers here build governed communities against a wilderness that feels older than civilization and indifferent to the concerns of surface dwellers. Trade, elected councils, and communal labor keep these towns functional — and keep their residents occupied enough not to dwell on what moves at the waterline after dark.</HHTools_Cascadia_Civil.description>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Civil.label>civil Cascadia settlement</HHTools_Cascadia_Civil.label>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Raider.description>A raider gang operating in the dense forests and ruined coastal stretches of Cascadia. The terrain works in their favor — pursuit is difficult, disappearances are easy to explain, and legitimate settlements are spread too thin for anyone to come running quickly. The strange things that live deeper in the wetlands are a fact of the landscape that Cascadian raiders have learned to tolerate, more or less.</HHTools_Cascadia_Raider.description>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Raider.label>Cascadia raider</HHTools_Cascadia_Raider.label>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Rough.description>An autocratic holdout in the mist-wrapped wilds of Cascadia, ruled by whoever commands enough fear or loyalty to hold it together. The Pacific Northwest was already an isolating landscape before the bombs; what it became afterward is something that most wasteland travelers describe poorly and revisit rarely. These communities are insular, hard, and deeply suspicious of anyone who arrives out of the fog uninvited.</HHTools_Cascadia_Rough.description>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Rough.label>rough Cascadia settlement</HHTools_Cascadia_Rough.label>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Tribal.description>A tribal community living deep in the Cascadian wilderness, among the flooded ruins and forest-covered remnants of the northwest coast. Their stories are full of things that dwell in the dark water and beneath the roots of old-growth trees that should have died centuries ago. Whether these are genuine encounters or generations of isolation and radiation talking, their traditions treat the wilderness with a reverence that borders on dread.</HHTools_Cascadia_Tribal.description>
  <HHTools_Cascadia_Tribal.label>Cascadia tribe</HHTools_Cascadia_Tribal.label>
  <Empire.description>A militant enclave of survivors claiming to represent the Appalachia scientific division. They pursue research into cryptids and hoard intelligence and technology for the Whitespring Enclave.</Empire.description>
  <Empire.label>Whitespring Enclave</Empire.label>
  <Empire.pawnSingular>Whitespring agent</Empire.pawnSingular>
  <Empire.pawnsPlural>Whitespring agents</Empire.pawnsPlural>
  <Entities.label>cryptids</Entities.label>
  <Entities.pawnSingular>Legendary Shade</Entities.pawnSingular>
  <Entities.pawnsPlural>Legendary Shades</Entities.pawnsPlural>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Army.description>A mixed raiding force of ghouls and super mutants operating together by common interest. Neither group is particularly welcome elsewhere in the wasteland, and their combination makes them considerably more dangerous than either would be alone. They prey on settlements and trade routes, relying on numbers, toughness, and the general instinct of most wastelanders to avoid mutants whenever possible.</HHTools_Mutant_Army.description>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Army.label>raider mutant army</HHTools_Mutant_Army.label>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Ghoul.description>A democratic ghoul settlement — a ghost town community that has outlasted the civilization that built it. The residents are ghouls who have organized themselves into a functioning town, with elected leadership, trade, and shared law. Most wastelanders avoid the place on instinct, but those who stop find it considerably more organized than expected. Ghouls here have had long enough to tire of being feared, and long enough to build something worth governing.</HHTools_Mutant_Ghoul.description>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Ghoul.label>civil ghoul ghosttown</HHTools_Mutant_Ghoul.label>
  <HHTools_Mutant_SuperMutant.description>An autocratic super mutant stronghold, held together by the strength and will of whoever leads it. Super mutants do not govern by consensus — authority here is established by force and maintained by the constant threat of it. What passes for order is a rough hierarchy of strength, with the most capable and aggressive at the top. Such settlements range from functional fortresses to barely-contained chaos, depending entirely on the quality of their current leader.</HHTools_Mutant_SuperMutant.description>
  <HHTools_Mutant_SuperMutant.label>rough super mutant stronghold</HHTools_Mutant_SuperMutant.label>
  <HoraxCult.label>holy Mothman cultists</HoraxCult.label>
  <HoraxCult.pawnsPlural>Devoted Seers</HoraxCult.pawnsPlural>
  <Insect.description>Ruthless and unyielding, the Antagonizer is a force of destruction and discord. Their motives shrouded in darkness, they seek power through chaos, crushing all opposition without mercy. Cross their path, and you’ll know true enmity in the wasteland.</Insect.description>
  <Insect.label>antagonizer</Insect.label>
  <OutlanderRefugee.description>Flesh freed from chains, the Escaped Slaves bear scars both seen and unseen. Bonded by suffering and driven by hope, they struggle for freedom and justice amidst the wasteland’s cruelty. Fierce and desperate, they fight for a life stolen but not forgotten.</OutlanderRefugee.description>
  <OutlanderRefugee.label>escaped slaves</OutlanderRefugee.label>
  <OutlanderRefugee.pawnSingular>Runaway</OutlanderRefugee.pawnSingular>
  <OutlanderRefugee.pawnsPlural>Runaways</OutlanderRefugee.pawnsPlural>
  <Pilgrims.description>Guardians of ancient wisdom, the Wise Mothman Cultists follow the elusive protector as a guide against the wasteland’s creeping horrors. Calm and watchful, they seek balance between man and myth, standing sentinel against the chaos that threatens to consume all.</Pilgrims.description>
  <Pilgrims.label>wise Mothman cultists</Pilgrims.label>
  <PlayerColony.description>A new settlement of various outcasts and wanderers.</PlayerColony.description>
  <PlayerColony.label>new settlement</PlayerColony.label>
  <PlayerTribe.label>new tribe</PlayerTribe.label>
  <ResearchExpedition.label>new cult</ResearchExpedition.label>
  <Salvagers.description>The Enclave Radicals burn with fanatic fire, wielding doctrine like a blade. Purity, dominance, and absolute control drive them to purge what they deem impure. Their zeal knows no bounds, turning even allies into enemies in their relentless crusade.</Salvagers.description>
  <Salvagers.label>Enclave radicals</Salvagers.label>
  <Sanguophages.pawnSingular>Feral Caller</Sanguophages.pawnSingular>
  <Sanguophages.pawnsPlural>Feral Callers</Sanguophages.pawnsPlural>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Critter.description>A tribal community made up of both S'Lanters and Numen who have shared territory long enough that their customs have grown together. They keep to the deep wastes and margins, far from the trade routes and settlements of larger factions. Strangers are met with wariness, and those who follow too closely into their territory tend to lose the trail and not find it again.</HHTools_Mutant_Critter.description>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Critter.label>gentile mutant tribe</HHTools_Mutant_Critter.label>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Numen.description>A tribe of mutated Numen who show an unusual compatibility with the living world. Numen communities are quiet and contemplative, guided by customs shaped around an awareness of nature that most ordinary people do not share. Their origins are uncertain; what is clear is that they are not fully human in the conventional sense, and do not live as humans do.</HHTools_Mutant_Numen.description>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Numen.label>gentile numen tribe</HHTools_Mutant_Numen.label>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Slanter.description>A tribe of S'Lanters — FEV-mutated raccoons that gained human-level intelligence and manual dexterity through pre-War experiments at a military research facility. The escaped subjects eventually settled and multiplied, naming themselves S'Lanter, meaning "Kindred," having long since forgotten their origins as animals. Fast, secretive, and highly territorial, S'Lanter communities organize around clan and kin, with customs passed down through story and ritual.</HHTools_Mutant_Slanter.description>
  <HHTools_Mutant_Slanter.label>gentile slanter tribe</HHTools_Mutant_Slanter.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.description>A democratic settlement in the Nuevo Texico wasteland, where Texan frontier culture and Mexican border tradition have been forged together over two centuries of post-war survival. The Brotherhood of Steel has maintained a presence in the region since the Lone Star chapter established operations in former Texas, and many settlements here have a working relationship with the Brotherhood — whether as trading partners, protectorates, or neighbors who keep the peace by staying out of each other's way.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.label>civil Nuevo Texico settlement</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.description>A raider gang operating across the wide-open scrubland and flatlands of Nuevo Texico. They hit trade convoys and isolated homesteads, moving fast across terrain that offers little cover for either prey or pursuer. Their style reflects the region — bold, loud, and accustomed to living rough in dry country far from the centers of any real power.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.label>Texico raider</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.description>An autocratic settlement in Nuevo Texico, run by a boss, patriarch, or council of hard-minded locals who answer to no outside authority. The culture is a direct hybrid of Texan and northern Mexican traditions: disputes are settled openly, authority is earned and demonstrated, and both the Brotherhood of Steel and any passing raider gang are assessed on the same pragmatic terms.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.label>rough Nuevo Texico settlement</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.description>A tribal community in Nuevo Texico, with roots in the ranching families, indigenous groups, and border communities that survived the war in the hill country and badlands. They carry a culture shaped by Spanish, Mexican, and Texan heritage, worn into something distinctly their own. The Brotherhood of Steel's regional presence is a practical reality they navigate carefully, trading with some chapters and avoiding others entirely.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.label>Texico tribe</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.label>
  <TradersGuild.description>Scattered and hunted, the Enclave Remnants cling to the last fragments of a fallen empire. Proud and unbroken, they uphold their sacred mission: to reclaim humanity through strength and technology. Their shadows stretch long, shaped by secrets and betrayal.</TradersGuild.description>
  <TradersGuild.label>Enclave remnants</TradersGuild.label>
  <GravshipCrew.description>The crew assigned to the Hellion.</GravshipCrew.description>
  <GravshipCrew.label>Hellion crew</GravshipCrew.label>
  <VFEM2_CivilClan.label>disabled clan remnants</VFEM2_CivilClan.label>
  <VFEM2_ClanRough.label>disabled clan remnants</VFEM2_ClanRough.label>
  <VFEM2_ClanSavage.label>disabled clan remnants</VFEM2_ClanSavage.label>
  <VFEM2_KingdomCivil.label>disabled kingdom remnants</VFEM2_KingdomCivil.label>
  <VFEM2_KingdomRough.label>disabled kingdom remnants</VFEM2_KingdomRough.label>
  <VFEM2_KingdomSavage.label>disabled kingdom remnants</VFEM2_KingdomSavage.label>
  <VFEM2_MerchantGuild.description>These post-war traders are not a feudal guild but a loose network of caravan companies, brahmin drovers, guards, and deal-brokers who keep the wasteland moving. They abandon static lordships in favor of mobile camps, barter routes, and temporary markets, hauling scarce goods between isolated communities while armed escorts keep raiders honest.</VFEM2_MerchantGuild.description>
  <VFEM2_MerchantGuild.label>caravan companies</VFEM2_MerchantGuild.label>
  <VFEM2_MerchantGuild.leaderTitle>caravan master</VFEM2_MerchantGuild.leaderTitle>
  <VFEM2_MerchantGuild.pawnSingular>caravaneer</VFEM2_MerchantGuild.pawnSingular>
  <VFEM2_MerchantGuild.pawnsPlural>caravaneers</VFEM2_MerchantGuild.pawnsPlural>
  <SettlerCivil.description>These people have lived here for decades or centuries and lost most of the technology that first brought them to this world. They can still defend themselves with basic gunpowder weapons while going about their daily routine of herding cattle, drinking rotgut, and hunting down bounties.\n\nThey care about trade, trust, and survival.\n\nThis particular group holds civil behavior in high regard.</SettlerCivil.description>
  <SettlerRough.description>These people have lived here for decades or centuries and lost most of the technology that first brought them to this world. They can still defend themselves with basic gunpowder weapons while going about their daily routine of herding cattle, drinking rotgut, and hunting down bounties.\n\nThey are not concerned with trade or trust.\n\nThis particular group believes that no one is created equal, and only strength allows one to survive on the frontier.</SettlerRough.description>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary cell, laying low.</VFED_NewSafehaven.description>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.label>Brotherhood of Steel expedition</VFED_NewSafehaven.label>
  <VFEE_Deserters.description>An organized Brotherhood expeditionary force dedicated to disrupting the Whitespring Enclave.</VFEE_Deserters.description>
  <VFEE_Deserters.label>Brotherhood of Steel expeditionary force</VFEE_Deserters.label>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.label>Enclave splinter cell</VFEE_NewFamily.label>
  <Empire.leaderTitle>president</Empire.leaderTitle>
</LanguageData>
