<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <HHTools_California_Civil.description>A democratic settlement on the Two-California coast, stretching from Baja in the south to northern California. The region was struck hard by the bombs but rebuilt faster than most of the wasteland, largely owing to the influence of the New California Republic. Settlers here live under organized governance, with elected leadership, regulated trade, and access to NCR-affiliated traders and patrols.</HHTools_California_Civil.description>
  <HHTools_California_Civil.label>civil California settlement</HHTools_California_Civil.label>
  <HHTools_California_Raider.description>A raider gang operating along the Two-California coast. The region's trade routes, NCR supply convoys, and established settlements make it a rich target for organized raiding. These gangs stay mobile to avoid NCR response forces, striking at travelers and outlying communities along the coast and inland valleys.</HHTools_California_Raider.description>
  <HHTools_California_Raider.label>California raider</HHTools_California_Raider.label>
  <HHTools_California_Rough.description>An autocratic holdout on the Two-California coast. While the NCR extends its reach across much of the region, this settlement operates outside its law, run by whoever holds authority through force or reputation. The NCR's expansion is a constant backdrop to daily life here, and many such communities navigate a careful balance between independence and annexation.</HHTools_California_Rough.description>
  <HHTools_California_Rough.label>rough California settlement</HHTools_California_Rough.label>
  <HHTools_California_Tribal.description>A tribal community surviving in the margins of Two-California, in the coastal ranges and valleys where NCR influence fades and older ways of living persist. They hunt and gather along coastlands that were once heavily populated, trading with settlers when terms suit them, and keeping to themselves when they do not.</HHTools_California_Tribal.description>
  <HHTools_California_Tribal.label>California tribe</HHTools_California_Tribal.label>
</LanguageData>
