<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationSequence" MayRequire="Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly">
		<success>Always</success>
		<operations>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ResearchProjectDef[defName="BioferriteGenerator"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Build power generators that burn bioferrite as a fuel. Bioferrite keeps its own identity here, but the hardware around it can still read like a desperate late-era Poseidon project.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ResearchProjectDef[defName="AtmosphericHeater"]/label</xpath>
				<value>
					<label>Poseidon home reactor</label>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ResearchProjectDef[defName="AtmosphericHeater"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Build compact Poseidon home reactors that burn bioferrite and drive enormous amounts of heat into the surrounding air.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="BioferriteGenerator"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>An experimental generator that works by pressurizing and igniting bioferrite, then harvesting energy from the resulting heat. The fuel remains bioferrite, but the chassis and control layout read like a harsh Poseidon prototype.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="AtmosphericHeater"]/label</xpath>
				<value>
					<label>Poseidon home reactor</label>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="AtmosphericHeater"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Poseidon home reactor powered by scavenged dark archotechnology. It burns bioferrite to agitate atmospheric gases, raising the outdoor temperature while flooding the area with waste heat.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="BioferriteShaper"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A specialized shaping bench that uses heat and electromagnetic stimulation to temporarily coax bioferrite into a pliable state. The material remains bioferrite, but the surrounding hardware fits cleanly into a Fallout-style industrial workshop.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="SerumCentrifuge"]/label</xpath>
				<value>
					<label>Med-Tek serum lab</label>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="SerumCentrifuge"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Med-Tek serum lab that uses scavenged archotechnology to create single-use injectable serums. Clean, expensive, and morally questionable in exactly the right pre-War way.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
		</operations>
	</Operation>
</Patch>