<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AdvancedGravtech.description>Unlock gravhulks, massive gravships capable of supporting entire colonies. Also allows crafting of gravlite panels, essential ultratech material for advanced gravship construction.</AdvancedGravtech.description>
  <BasicGravtech.description>Refine chemfuel into astrofuel and store it in pressurized tanks. Unlocks the construction of the gravjumper engine, allowing the first steps into gravship travel.</BasicGravtech.description>
  <OrbitalTech.description>Build vac barriers to protect against depressurization, and orbital scanners to detect locations in space.</OrbitalTech.description>
  <StandardGravtech.description>Unlock gravship engines capable of lifting a colony into orbit. Allows construction of control terminals for new gravship systems such as gravtech research and maintenance.</StandardGravtech.description>
  <VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>Construct astrofuel synthesizers that automatically convert chemfuel into astrofuel for gravship use.</VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>
  <VGE_AstrofuelRefining.label>astrofuel refining</VGE_AstrofuelRefining.label>
  <VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>Unlock smaller variants of workbenches designed for gravships. Compact enough to fit into tight quarters without sacrificing essential functions.</VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>
  <VGE_CompactWorkspaces.label>compact workspaces</VGE_CompactWorkspaces.label>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.description>Build gravship-exclusive furniture such as bunk beds, lockers, and medbay beds to keep crew comfortable and functional in long voyages.</VGE_GravshipLiving.description>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.label>gravship living</VGE_GravshipLiving.label>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.description>Construct gravship solar panelling, gravcore power cells, and astrofuel generators to supply energy for gravship systems.</VGE_GravshipPower.description>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.label>gravship power</VGE_GravshipPower.label>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>Construct gravship artillery and point defense turrets to fight other ships in orbit or provide bombardments from the sky.</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>gravship weaponry</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>
  <VGE_HeatDissipation.description>Harvest structural heat generated during gravship launches and dissipate it safely. Excess heat can be converted into usable power. Heatsink capacity and power output is increased.</VGE_HeatDissipation.description>
  <VGE_HeatDissipation.label>heat dissipation</VGE_HeatDissipation.label>
  <VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>Harvest and store oxygen for use on gravships. Unlocks construction of vacsuits and other survival gear needed to operate in vacuum.</VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>
  <VGE_OxygenNetwork.label>oxygen network</VGE_OxygenNetwork.label>
</LanguageData>