<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEA_Isolationist.description>Trust is a resource in low supply, everyone our people meet is an enemy.</VFEA_Isolationist.description>
  <VFEA_Isolationist.label>isolationist</VFEA_Isolationist.label>
  <VME_Angler.description>Serene and therapeutic, placid lakes and lapping shores are criminally underappreciated. With a little time or simple engineering rivers and oceans alike can leave our bellies full of tasty fish.</VME_Angler.description>
  <VME_Angler.label>fishing culture</VME_Angler.label>
  <VME_Anonymity.description>Knowing the names, faces, and backgrounds of your fellow colonists can be both a blessing and a curse.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt;\n - Anonymity severely affects both prisoner and slave interactions: wardens with the anonymity meme will get angry when they have to interact with prisoners. Slaves with the anonymity meme can't be suppressed by wardens, as they will ignore the social interaction. Long story short, don't use an ideo with this meme if you are planning on having lots of prisoners or slaves!</VME_Anonymity.description>
  <VME_Anonymity.label>anonymity</VME_Anonymity.label>
  <VME_Aristocratic.description>Kings and Queens are the true path to prosperity, the mind of the common man is unfit for leadership.</VME_Aristocratic.description>
  <VME_Aristocratic.label>aristocratic</VME_Aristocratic.label>
  <VME_Astrology.description>A careful examination of the stars will unlock mystical powers far beyond our wildest imagination.</VME_Astrology.description>
  <VME_Astrology.label>astrology</VME_Astrology.label>
  <VME_BloodCourt.description>Our leader should be a talented melee fighter and brutal warrior, only usurped by one greater. Bloodshed, corpses, scars are a part of life and a show of strength on this planet.</VME_BloodCourt.description>
  <VME_BloodCourt.label>blood court</VME_BloodCourt.label>
  <VME_Bushido.description>A warrior's code of honor means striking down one’s foes unto death itself. Should one’s spirit falter and cowardice prevail, forgiveness can only be found in the afterlife.</VME_Bushido.description>
  <VME_Bushido.label>bushido</VME_Bushido.label>
  <VME_CityBuilders.description>Our home should feature all the accommodations of a great city, homes, workshops, and places of leisure should all be present and accessible by all.</VME_CityBuilders.description>
  <VME_CityBuilders.label>city builders</VME_CityBuilders.label>
  <VME_CraftCulture.description>One should aspire to feel the ache in their fingers after a long day of craft. A talented blacksmith or tailor is to be dignified.</VME_CraftCulture.description>
  <VME_CraftCulture.label>craft culture</VME_CraftCulture.label>
  <VME_Cultured.description>Reading and passing one's knowledge on is a most scholarly mission, and should be most enthused over.</VME_Cultured.description>
  <VME_Cultured.label>cultured</VME_Cultured.label>
  <VME_Egalitarian.description>Bigotry is absolutely to never be tolerated, helping those in need and respecting their beliefs are rewards in and of themselves.</VME_Egalitarian.description>
  <VME_Egalitarian.label>egalitarian</VME_Egalitarian.label>
  <VME_Elders.description>Age and wisdom often come in tandem, our wise and elderly should be respected on that premise alone and should not be expected to toil.</VME_Elders.description>
  <VME_Elders.label>elders</VME_Elders.label>
  <VME_Emancipation.description>It’s not enough to simply not participate in slavery, we should actively work to fight against those who dare to enslave others and free those who have suffered such inhumanities.</VME_Emancipation.description>
  <VME_Emancipation.label>emancipation</VME_Emancipation.label>
  <VME_ExaltedPriesthood.description>Our leader must also be our prophet, and it’s important that we heed their advice.</VME_ExaltedPriesthood.description>
  <VME_ExaltedPriesthood.label>exalted priesthood</VME_ExaltedPriesthood.label>
  <VME_FireWorship.description>Holy flame breathes life into this planet and many others like it, may it guide us to salvation and may it reduce our enemies to ash.</VME_FireWorship.description>
  <VME_FireWorship.label>fire worship</VME_FireWorship.label>
  <VME_Fleshcrafters.description>Technology should be shunned, unless it serves the flesh. Only through extreme biological experimentation may we unlock our hidden potential.</VME_Fleshcrafters.description>
  <VME_Fleshcrafters.label>fleshcrafting</VME_Fleshcrafters.label>
  <VME_Gestalt.description>There shouldn't even be such a thing as individualism. By acting in perfect synchrony, our society will be more than the sum of its parts.</VME_Gestalt.description>
  <VME_Gestalt.label>gestalt</VME_Gestalt.label>
  <VME_GodEmperor.description>Our leader must be worshipped as a living God, a physical manifestation of our ideals and precepts.</VME_GodEmperor.description>
  <VME_GodEmperor.label>god emperor</VME_GodEmperor.label>
  <VME_HardcoreIndustrialism.description>Work gives a man dignity. Only through hard work and being productive can a person really grow.</VME_HardcoreIndustrialism.description>
  <VME_HardcoreIndustrialism.label>industrialism</VME_HardcoreIndustrialism.label>
  <VME_Healthcare.description>The wellbeing of our bodies and minds is something our people take very seriously. It’s important that we look out for each other and tend to the wounds of our friends and family alike.</VME_Healthcare.description>
  <VME_Healthcare.label>healthcare</VME_Healthcare.label>
  <VME_HolyDiseases.description>To be touched by pestilence is a boon to be coveted. As diseases spread, so too shall our influence.</VME_HolyDiseases.description>
  <VME_HolyDiseases.label>holy diseases</VME_HolyDiseases.label>
  <VME_InsectoidSupremacy.description>The labyrinthine tunnels of the underdark ungulate with a seemingly limitless hive of relentless and brutal insects, we should not fear them, we should revere them.</VME_InsectoidSupremacy.description>
  <VME_InsectoidSupremacy.label>insectoid mastery</VME_InsectoidSupremacy.label>
  <VME_Light.description>Darkness obscures one’s vision as well as one’s mind, darklight is a wicked occurrence and is not to be condoned.</VME_Light.description>
  <VME_Light.label>light</VME_Light.label>
  <VME_MechanoidSupremacy.description>Never tire, never wither, never need for sustenance. Mechanoids are humanity perfected and should be revered as our superiors.</VME_MechanoidSupremacy.description>
  <VME_MechanoidSupremacy.label>mechanoid supremacy</VME_MechanoidSupremacy.label>
  <VME_Nationalist.description>Insubordination and dissent should be quenched to make space for a strong sense of nationalistic pride.</VME_Nationalist.description>
  <VME_Nationalist.label>nationalist</VME_Nationalist.label>
  <VME_Nomad.description>Stagnation is death and as with all things in this world, homes are only temporary. Traveling this world and walking roads unwalked always leads to greater things.</VME_Nomad.description>
  <VME_Nomad.label>wanderlust</VME_Nomad.label>
  <VME_Pacifist.description>While defending oneself is acceptable, we have come too far and evolved too much to ever endorse the premise of warfare or slavery. Even tantrums should only manifest in forms that do not harm others or property.</VME_Pacifist.description>
  <VME_Pacifist.label>nonaggression</VME_Pacifist.label>
  <VME_PartyLife.description>Let us toast to the acts of dance, drink and debauchery. Any free time is a good time, but party time is the best time.</VME_PartyLife.description>
  <VME_PartyLife.label>party life</VME_PartyLife.label>
  <VME_Progressive.description>Machines, factories, drones, a goal to any successful community should be optimizing these devices and shunning the idea of sentient beings performing tasks normally meant for them.</VME_Progressive.description>
  <VME_Progressive.label>progressive</VME_Progressive.label>
  <VME_PsychicFocus.description>Mastering the power of the mind is essential to securing one’s place in the universe. Strength of mind can be achieved only through inner peace, and inner peace can only be achieved through meditation.</VME_PsychicFocus.description>
  <VME_PsychicFocus.label>psychic focus</VME_PsychicFocus.label>
  <VME_Republic.description>Power must be balanced between a select few, lest any settlement or empire fall to inevitable corruption.</VME_Republic.description>
  <VME_Republic.label>republic</VME_Republic.label>
  <VME_Royal.description>We embody the essence of royalty, ensuring our titles and their inherent authority are passed down through generations, forever respected and entwined with our bloodline.</VME_Royal.description>
  <VME_Royal.label>royal</VME_Royal.label>
  <VME_Scrapper.description>Nothing should ever be wasted, not even bloodied or torn clothes. Discarded remains of old civilizations should be kept as treasures and reminders.</VME_Scrapper.description>
  <VME_Scrapper.label>scrapper</VME_Scrapper.label>
  <VME_Structure_Agnosticism.description>The theory that any gods or all-powerful force watches or guides us down to trivialities is either asinine or incomprehensible by mere man, and equally so is the idea that all came from nothing. It is better to ignore such dogma and respect the freedom of those who find respite in such beliefs.</VME_Structure_Agnosticism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Agnosticism.label>agnosticism</VME_Structure_Agnosticism.label>
  <VME_Structure_Authoritarianism.description>Plurality only brings a false illusion of choice, and breeds discontent, rebellion and chaos. With an iron fist we will govern our people and bring prosperity to all.</VME_Structure_Authoritarianism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Authoritarianism.label>authoritarian</VME_Structure_Authoritarianism.label>
  <VME_Structure_Bacchanalianism.description>Man's time on this earth is brief and fleeting, to deny oneself of any of life's pleasures such as lust or gluttony is the one true sin. Throw wide the gates to tireless festivity, live and breathe endless splendor.</VME_Structure_Bacchanalianism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Bacchanalianism.label>hedonism</VME_Structure_Bacchanalianism.label>
  <VME_Structure_ChthonianCult.description>There are ancient entities in this Universe that are more powerful than mere gods. Immensely powerful and utterly indifferent to us humans who can barely begin to comprehend them. Only by worshipping them can we hope to placate their ire.</VME_Structure_ChthonianCult.description>
  <VME_Structure_ChthonianCult.label>eldritch cult</VME_Structure_ChthonianCult.label>
  <VME_Structure_Corporate.description>No Gods or Kings should be worshipped, only man and his unslakable desire for wealth. Colonies should be managed like companies.</VME_Structure_Corporate.description>
  <VME_Structure_Corporate.label>corporate origin</VME_Structure_Corporate.label>
  <VME_Structure_CultOfPersonality.description>It is forbidden to question the crown of a king or queen, even the soil itself is undeserving to feel the touch of our leaders' divine feet. Our leader should want for nothing and through their grand design we will prosper.</VME_Structure_CultOfPersonality.description>
  <VME_Structure_CultOfPersonality.label>cult of personality</VME_Structure_CultOfPersonality.label>
  <VME_Structure_Eschatologism.description>To be cursed to walk this earth is true torture, and whether by means of cataclysm, famine, or pestilence the departure of ones soul from their mortal coil should be celebrated.</VME_Structure_Eschatologism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Eschatologism.label>eschatologism</VME_Structure_Eschatologism.label>
  <VME_Structure_Esotericism.description>The forces that guide this world are not for the faint of heart nor weak of will. Only through forbidden texts, dark pacts and proper initiation can one truly see beyond the veil.</VME_Structure_Esotericism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Esotericism.label>esotericism</VME_Structure_Esotericism.label>
  <VME_Structure_Omnism.description>All creeds and beliefs have both truths and fabrications, a healthy mind will listen carefully and with scrutiny to what tenets say as well as what they choose not to say.</VME_Structure_Omnism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Omnism.label>omnism</VME_Structure_Omnism.label>
  <VME_Structure_Pantheism.description>The Universe is God. There is no God but the combined substance, forces, and laws that are manifested in the existing universe.</VME_Structure_Pantheism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Pantheism.label>pantheism</VME_Structure_Pantheism.label>
  <VME_Structure_SecularSpirituality.description>Putting one’s faith in rituals, prayer or powers beyond only delays one’s personal growth. Enlightenment, happiness, and purpose can all be found from within and through any matter one feels is right.</VME_Structure_SecularSpirituality.description>
  <VME_Structure_SecularSpirituality.label>secular spirituality</VME_Structure_SecularSpirituality.label>
  <VME_Structure_Serketist.description>The true face of gods is found in the bite of a spider, the sting of the scorpion. Let those of many legs crawl all over us.</VME_Structure_Serketist.description>
  <VME_Structure_Serketist.label>serketism</VME_Structure_Serketist.label>
  <VME_Structure_Shintaoism.description>This ideoligion is a descendant of ancient Shinto and Taoism. It may have very different precepts than those of thousands of years ago, but its symbols are similar.</VME_Structure_Shintaoism.description>
  <VME_Structure_Shintaoism.label>shintaoist origin</VME_Structure_Shintaoism.label>
  <VME_SweetTeeth.description>Decadent, velvety, rich--When these words grace our ears, first thoughts are of bars of sweet, sweet chocolate. Tangy yogurts, flaky pastries, and moist cakes aren’t just welcomed--They’re indisputably deserved.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt;\n - Unlocks a "Desserts Need" that will make colonists happier if they consume desserts and chocolate regularly (needs expectation to be moderate or higher)\n - Unlocks sowing the cocoa bush, a cocoa producing plant that is more efficient than the tree and can be grown indoors and on hydroponics\n - Colony receives 15 Chocolate to start\n - Makes colonists immune to VCE's diabetes</VME_SweetTeeth.description>
  <VME_SweetTeeth.label>sweet teeth</VME_SweetTeeth.label>
  <VME_Trader.description>With wealth comes power, going too long without profit means going too long without securing one’s position of power.</VME_Trader.description>
  <VME_Trader.label>wealthy</VME_Trader.label>
  <VME_Vegan.description>Eating meat is barbaric and uncouth, better eaten are the fruits of hard labor and ever-giving soil.</VME_Vegan.description>
  <VME_Vegan.label>vegan</VME_Vegan.label>
  <VME_ViolentConversion.description>Infidels can choose to adopt our beliefs, or die.</VME_ViolentConversion.description>
  <VME_ViolentConversion.label>violent conversion</VME_ViolentConversion.label>
</LanguageData>