<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.description>A reinforced exoskeletal frame designed to support the weight and systems of advanced power armor. On its own, the Power Armor Frame offers basic protection and increased carrying capacity, but it truly shines when fitted with full armor plating. Essential for anyone hoping to operate pre-war power armor suits in the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.label>Power Armor Frame</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45_Helmet.description>An early model of power armor helmet, the T45 offers solid protection against most threats. Its bulky design is a testament to pre-war engineering, providing reliable defense at the cost of some comfort and mobility.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45_Helmet.label>T-45 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.description>The T-45 was the first power armor model deployed in the field, offering soldiers unprecedented protection and strength. Though now considered outdated, its heavy plating and servo-assisted joints still provide formidable defense and enhanced mobility to any wastelander lucky enough to find a working suit.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.label>T-45 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51_Helmet.description>The T51 helmet is a refined evolution of power armor technology, offering superior protection and improved ergonomics over earlier models. Favored for its balance of defense and comfort.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51_Helmet.label>T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.description>The T-51 is a legendary pre-war power armor, renowned for its superior protection and advanced design. Its titanium composite shell and improved servos make it lighter and more durable than earlier models, granting its wearer unmatched resilience and strength on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.label>T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60_Helmet.description>The T60 helmet represents advanced power armor development, featuring enhanced armor plating and improved environmental sealing. Designed for frontline combat in hazardous conditions.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60_Helmet.label>T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.description>The T-60 represents the pinnacle of pre-war military engineering, combining the best features of earlier models with enhanced armor and reliability. Favored by the Brotherhood of Steel, the T-60 offers exceptional protection, advanced environmental sealing, and a menacing presence on any battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.label>T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_X01_Helmet.description>The X01 helmet is the pinnacle of power armor headgear, boasting cutting-edge materials and maximum protection. Its intimidating design and advanced systems make it a rare and valuable asset.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_X01_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_X01_Helmet.label>X-01 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_X01_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor with a paint scheme inspired by the iconic Abraxo Cleaner branding. Clean, crisp, and unmistakable - this corporate paint job brings pre-war advertising aesthetics to the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.label>T-51 Power Paints Abraxo Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-51 power armor helmet with Abraxo Cleaner branding. Clean, crisp, and unmistakable corporate aesthetics.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Abraxo T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor emblazoned with dazzling flame decals that turn heads and strike fear into the hearts of enemies. This iconic hot rod design brings wasteland style to the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>T-51 Hotrodder Flame Job Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-51 power armor helmet emblazoned with dazzling flame decals. This iconic hot rod design turns heads on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Hotrodder Flame Job T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor in bold, vibrant hot pink that makes a statement. This eye-catching color scheme ensures you'll never be overlooked on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>T-51 Hotrodder Hotpink Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-51 power armor helmet in bold, vibrant hot pink. This eye-catching color scheme ensures you'll never be overlooked.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Hotrodder Hotpink T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor with menacing shark teeth painted in the style of pre-war fighter planes. This aggressive paint scheme shows your enemies you mean business.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>T-51 Hotrodder Shark Paint Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-51 power armor helmet with menacing shark teeth painted in the style of pre-war fighter planes.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Hotrodder Shark Paint T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor with colorful Sugar Bombs cereal branding. Sweet and explosive, this playful paint scheme combines nostalgia with intimidation.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.label>T-51 Power Paints Sugar Bombs Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-51 power armor helmet with colorful Sugar Bombs cereal branding. Sweet and explosive nostalgia.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Sugar Bombs T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>T-60 power armor emblazoned with dazzling flame decals that turn heads and strike fear into the hearts of enemies. This iconic hot rod design brings wasteland style to the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>T-60 Hotrodder Flame Job Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-60 power armor helmet emblazoned with dazzling flame decals. This iconic hot rod design turns heads on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Hotrodder Flame Job T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>T-60 power armor in bold, vibrant hot pink that makes a statement. This eye-catching color scheme ensures you'll never be overlooked on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>T-60 Hotrodder Hotpink Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-60 power armor helmet in bold, vibrant hot pink. This eye-catching color scheme ensures you'll never be overlooked.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Hotrodder Hotpink T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>T-60 power armor with menacing shark teeth painted in the style of pre-war fighter planes. This aggressive paint scheme shows your enemies you mean business.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>T-60 Hotrodder Shark Paint Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A T-60 power armor helmet with menacing shark teeth painted in the style of pre-war fighter planes.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Hotrodder Shark Paint T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.description>The X-01 is the most advanced power armor ever developed before the Great War, shrouded in secrecy and rarely seen outside top-secret military installations. Its cutting-edge materials and systems provide unmatched protection, strength, and intimidation, making it the ultimate prize for any wasteland survivor.</FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.label>X-01 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Building_PowerArmorStation.description>A specialized station for storing and displaying power armor sets. Allows quick swapping of armor pieces between storage and use.</FCP_Building_PowerArmorStation.description>
  <FCP_Building_PowerArmorStation.label>power armor station</FCP_Building_PowerArmorStation.label>
  <FCP_Item_Fusion_Core.description>A compact nuclear battery used to power pre-war technology, most notably power armor. These cylindrical power cells contain a highly efficient fusion reaction that can provide energy for extended periods. Extremely valuable and sought after by those who maintain pre-war equipment. Cannot be recharged with current technology.</FCP_Item_Fusion_Core.description>
  <FCP_Item_Fusion_Core.label>fusion core</FCP_Item_Fusion_Core.label>
</LanguageData>