<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.description>The New California Republic is a faction based out of Shady Sands in the former state of California. It is a federal parliamentary republic, similar to the pre-war USA before it descended into authoritarianism. They represent the alt world and its values. Roads, taxes, prisons, elections, and other phenomena long forgotten made a comeback with the NCR’s rise to power. It is seen by its citizens to be the sole haven of civilisation, democracy, and freedom in the wasteland. While there certainly is truth to that notion, the NCR also suffers from widespread corruption and oligarchic tendencies, for much power is held by exceedingly rich ranchers and farm owners. Furthermore, it uses its vast military, well supplied by their industrial centres, to aggressively expand their territory and claim the resources of neighbouring regions to sate the ever-growing hunger of its population.</FCP_Faction_NCR.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.label>Neue Republik Kalifornien</FCP_Faction_NCR.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>Präsident</FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>Neuer Kalifornier</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>Neue Kalifornier</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>A rogue faction of former NCR saltiers and officers who have deserted the Republic. Disillusioned with the NCR's leadership, they now operate as a hostile paramilitary group, surviving through raids and mercenary work. Their organization is loose, but they are led by a cunning Rogue Colonel.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>RNK-Deserteure</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>Schurkenoberst</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>RNK-Deserteur</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>RNK-Deserteure</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>Die New California Republic ist eine demokratische Föderation, die auf den Prinzipien von Recht, Ordnung und Fortschritt basiert. Als RNK führst du eine Kolonie an, die danach strebt, die Zivilisation wiederherzustellen und ihren Einfluss im Ödland auszuweiten.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>RNK-Spielerkolonie</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>Gouverneur</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>Bürger</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>Bürger</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>
