<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.description>Diese grotesk mutierten Nagetiere leben unter der Erde in riesigen Tunnelnetzen. Sie vermehren sich schnell und schwärmen in großer Zahl aus, wenn sie gestört werden. Ursprünglich handelte es sich um einfache Ödlandschädlinge, deren Population in unterirdischen Bereichen explosionsartig zugenommen hat, wo sie ausgedehnte Höhlensysteme anlegen. Sie sind aggressiv, territorial und greifen alles an, was in ihr Reich eintritt.</FCP_Faction_Molerat.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.fixedName>Maulwurfsrattenkolonie</FCP_Faction_Molerat.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.label>Maulwurfsrattenkolonie</FCP_Faction_Molerat.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnSingular>Maulwurfsratte</FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnsPlural>Maulwurfsratten</FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.description>The Bruderschaft des Stahls is one of the altest still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their sEinkaufszentrum numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.fixedName>Bruderschaft des Stahls</FCP_Faction_BoS.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.ideoDescription>Unter Elder Maxson hat die Bruderschaft Disziplin mit Zielstrebigkeit vereint. Wir bewahren die Technologie, wir schützen die Menschheit vor sich selbst und wir zerstören die Abscheulichkeiten, die unsere Zukunft bedrohen. Stahl sei mit uns.</FCP_Faction_BoS.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.label>Bruderschaft des Stahls</FCP_Faction_BoS.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.royalFavorLabel>Ehre</FCP_Faction_BoS.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.description>The Lost Hills Chapter is the original Bruderschaft des Stahls, founded by Roger Maxson in the Ruines of the Mariposa Militärbasis. As the first and founding chapter, Lost Hills represents the purest form of the Brotherhood's ideals - technological preservation, military discipline, and isolationist philosophy. They are the keepers of the original Codex and consider themselves the supreme authority over all Brotherhood chapters. Their fortress in the Lost Hills bunker complex remains one of the most technologically advanced facilities in the wasteland, housing pre-war military hardware and the Brotherhood's most elite saltiers.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.fixedName>Kapitel „Lost Hills“.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.ideoDescription>We are the original Bruderschaft des Stahls, keepers of the true Codex as written by Roger Maxson. Technology must be preserved by those of pure bloodline. Outsiders cannot be trusted with our geheims or our legacy. We are the shield that protects humanity's technological heritage - isolation is our strength, purity is our path.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.label>Kapitel „Lost Hills“.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.royalFavorLabel>Ehre</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.description>The Midwestern Bruderschaft des Stahls broke away from the main order during an airship expedition that crash-landed in the Midwest. Unlike their Western counterparts, the Midwestern chapter has adopted a more pragmatic and expansionist philosophy, actively recruiting tribals and wastelanders into their ranks. They maintain the Brotherhood's devotion to technology and military prowess, but have shed much of the isolationism that defines other chapters. Their territory spans vast stretches of the former American Midwest, making them one of the largest and most diverse Brotherhood chapters, though they remain estranged from Lost Hills' authority.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.fixedName>Bruderschaft des Mittleren Westens</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.ideoDescription>Wir sind die entwickelte Bruderschaft. Als unsere Luftschiffe im Mittleren Westen abstürzten, haben wir gelernt, dass Überleben Anpassung erfordert. Wir rekrutieren die Würdigen – Stammesangehörige, Ödländer, sogar ehemalige Feinde – denn Stärke kommt von der Einheit und nicht von der Isolation. Der Kodex führt uns, fesselt uns aber nicht. Wir expandieren, wir schützen, wir bleiben bestehen.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.label>Bruderschaft des Mittleren Westens</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.leaderTitle>Allgemein</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.royalFavorLabel>Ehre</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>Das Appalachia Chapter steht am Scheideweg. Abgeschnitten von Lost Hills und gezwungen, unabhängig zu agieren, müssen Sie den Weg Ihres Kapitels bestimmen: Werden Sie „The Chain That Binds“ folgen – der strengen Codex-Doktrin, die vor allem die Erhaltung der Technologie verlangt? Oder brechen Sie mit der Tradition und werden Beschützer der Menschen im Ödland, um zu beweisen, dass die Bruderschaft mehr sein kann als nur Sammler? Ihre Isolation bedeutet keine Aufsicht, keine Verstärkung, sondern völlige Freiheit zu definieren, wofür die Bruderschaft in diesen Ländern wirklich steht.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>Appalachia-Kapitel</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>Paladin</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uphalt their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>Überreste des Stolzes von Lyon</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>The Mojave Chapter of the Bruderschaft des Stahls is a shadow of its former self, forced out of the verborgen Valley bunker and now struggling to survive in the harsh Mojave wasteland. Once a proud and disciplined force, they have been reduced to a scattered group, clinging to their mission of safeguarding humanity's technological heritage. Despite their diminished state, their mastery of power armor and energy weapons ensures they remain a formidable presence in the region.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>Mojave-Kapitel</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the Bruderschaft des Stahls, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uphalt the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>Ausgestoßene der Bruderschaft</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>Schutz</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>Ausgestoßen</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>Ausgestoßene</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>The Bruderschaft des Stahls is one of the altest still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their sEinkaufszentrum numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>Bruderschaft des Stahls</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uphalt their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.fixedName>Überreste des Stolzes von Lyon</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.ideoDescription>Elder Lyons hat uns gelehrt, dass Technologie ohne Mitgefühl wertlos ist. Wir sind der Schutzschild des Volkes, Beschützer der Unschuldigen und der Beweis dafür, dass die Bruderschaft mehr sein kann als nur Sammler von Artefakten.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.label>Überreste des Stolzes von Lyon</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.leaderTitle>Ältere</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnSingular>Bruder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnsPlural>Brüder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>Stolz Ehre</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the Bruderschaft des Stahls, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uphalt the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.fixedName>Ausgestoßene der Bruderschaft</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.ideoDescription>We are the keepers of the true Brotherhood mission. Technology must be preserved at all costs. Outsiders cannot be trusted with the power of the alt World. The Codex is law.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>Ausgestoßene der Bruderschaft</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.leaderTitle>Schutz</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnSingular>Ausgestoßen</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnsPlural>Ausgestoßene</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>Tech-Skript</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.0.nameType.name>Caesar</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.0.nameType.name>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.1.nameType.name>Mars</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.1.nameType.name>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.description>Caesar’s Legion is the fearsome group which conquered most of the former states of Arizona, New Mexico, Colorado, and Utah. The Legion styles itself after the uralt roman legionnaires and uses many low-tech weapons such as javelins and crude but effective melee weapons. They are cruel, warlike, and known to frequently commit massacres against civilians, which they view as dissolute and profligate. Caesar, or Edward Sallow as he was once known, leads his slave armies as an iron fisted dictator and pushes them ever forward to claim new territories for their leader, the self-proclaimed son of Mars himself. Before long, the Legion stood at the shores of the Colorado river and set their eyes on the gleaming towers of New Vegas and California beyond them.</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.fixedName>Caesars Legion</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.ideoDescription>Caesar, der Sohn des Mars, erhielt vom Mars den Auftrag, die gesamte Erde zu erobern. Um diese Eroberung zu erleichtern, reinigte der Mars die Erde mit Feuer und brachte die Menschheit auf ihren Tiefpunkt. Die göttliche Pflicht des Cäsaren besteht darin, das Ödland von Chaos und Barbarei zu befreien</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.label>Caesars Legion</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.leaderTitle>Caesar</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnSingular>Legionär</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnsPlural>Legionäre</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.description>Ruthless remnants of the alt world government, the Enclave believe themselves to be humanity’s rightful rulers. Isolated, technologically advanced, and fiercely nationalistic, they seek to restore civilization under their iron-fisted vision—no matter the cost to outsiders.</FCP_Faction_Enclave.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.fixedName>Die Enklave</FCP_Faction_Enclave.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.ideoDescription>Die Enklave stellt die Fortsetzung der Regierung der Vereinigten Staaten dar, die dazu bestimmt ist, Amerika zurückzuerobern und wiederherzustellen. Nur reine, unbefleckte Menschen haben das Recht, die Zivilisation wieder aufzubauen. Alle anderen sind Abweichungen, die beseitigt oder unterworfen werden müssen.</FCP_Faction_Enclave.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.label>Die Enklave</FCP_Faction_Enclave.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.leaderTitle>Präsident</FCP_Faction_Enclave.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnSingular>Bestandteil</FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnsPlural>Bestandteile</FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.royalFavorLabel>Behörde</FCP_Faction_Enclave.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.description>Sie sind Agenten der Enklave, der Schattenregierung, die sich als rechtmäßiger Erbe der Vereinigten Staaten von Amerika betrachtet. Ausgestattet mit fortschrittlicher Vorkriegstechnologie und einem unerschütterlichen Glauben an Ihre genetische und technologische Überlegenheit versuchen Sie, Amerika wieder zu seinem früheren Glanz zu verhelfen – mit allen Mitteln. Das Ödland ist voller Mutanten und Degenerierter, die in dem neuen Amerika, das Sie aufbauen werden, keinen Platz haben.</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.label>Die Enklave</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.leaderTitle>Oberst</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnSingular>Agent</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnsPlural>Agenten</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.description>Die Great Khans sind eine Stammes-Raider-Gesellschaft, deren Wurzeln auf die Biker-Banden Kaliforniens aus der Vorkriegszeit zurückgehen. Einst einer der mächtigsten Raider-Stämme im Ödland, haben sie zahlreiche Konflikte mit der RNK und anderen Fraktionen über sich ergehen lassen, die ihre Zahl dezimiert haben. Trotz ihrer Rückschläge bleiben die Khans stolz und äußerst unabhängig und weigern sich, sich vor irgendjemandem zu beugen. Sie sind zu Experten in der Herstellung von Chemikalien geworden, die sie gegen Waffen und Vorräte eintauschen. Die Khans legen Wert auf Stärke, Loyalität gegenüber dem Stamm und die Freiheit, so zu leben, wie sie wollen – frei von den Gesetzen und Steuern „zivilisierter“ Gesellschaften. Sie sind ein Nomadenvolk und leben in Jurten und Zelten, die schnell eingepackt werden können, wenn es Zeit ist, weiterzuziehen.</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.description>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.fixedName>Großkhane</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.ideoDescription>Die Großkhane leben nach einem Kodex der Stärke, Unabhängigkeit und Loyalität gegenüber dem Stamm. Sie lehnen die Regeln und Beschränkungen der „zivilisierten“ Gesellschaft ab und ziehen es vor, sich das zu nehmen, was sie brauchen, und frei zu leben. Die Starken überleben, die Schwachen gehen zugrunde und der Stamm bleibt über allem anderen bestehen.</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.label>Großkhane</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.label>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.leaderTitle>Papa Khan</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnSingular>Khan</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnsPlural>Khane</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.description>The New California Republic is a faction based out of Shady Sands in the former state of California. It is a federal parliamentary republic, similar to the pre-war USA before it descended into authoritarianism. They represent the alt world and its values. Roads, taxes, prisons, elections, and other phenomena long forgotten made a comeback with the NCR’s rise to power. It is seen by its citizens to be the sole haven of civilisation, democracy, and freedom in the wasteland. While there certainly is truth to that notion, the NCR also suffers from widespread corruption and oligarchic tendencies, for much power is held by exceedingly rich ranchers and farm owners. Furthermore, it uses its vast military, well supplied by their industrial centres, to aggressively expand their territory and claim the resources of neighbouring regions to sate the ever-growing hunger of its population.</FCP_Faction_NCR.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.fixedName>Neue Republik Kalifornien</FCP_Faction_NCR.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.ideoDescription>Die Republik basiert auf den Grundsätzen der Freiheit und Freiheit und setzt diese im Laufe der Jahre in die Praxis um. Die wichtigste Errungenschaft war das Verbot der Sklaverei in den Gebieten der RNK, dank der konzertierten Bemühungen einflussreicher Politiker und der Rangers.</FCP_Faction_NCR.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.label>Neue Republik Kalifornien</FCP_Faction_NCR.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>Präsident</FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>Neuer Kalifornier</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>Neue Kalifornier</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.royalFavorLabel>Servicepunkte</FCP_Faction_NCR.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>A rogue faction of former NCR saltiers and officers who have deserted the Republic. Disillusioned with the NCR's leadership, they now operate as a hostile paramilitary group, surviving through raids and mercenary work. Their organization is loose, but they are led by a cunning Rogue Colonel.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.fixedName>RNK-Deserteure</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.ideoDescription>Once loyal to the Republic, these deserters have turned away from its broken promises and endless wars. Disillusioned by corruption and failed leadership, they now value survival, freedom, and loyalty to their own above all else. Their ideals are forged in hardship, camaraderie, and a deep distrust of authority. They do what it takes to endure in the wasteland, bound together by necessity and shared experience rather than alt world dogma.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>RNK-Deserteure</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>Schurkenoberst</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>RNK-Deserteur</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>RNK-Deserteure</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>Die New California Republic ist eine demokratische Föderation, die auf den Prinzipien von Recht, Ordnung und Fortschritt basiert. Als RNK führst du eine Kolonie an, die danach strebt, die Zivilisation wiederherzustellen und ihren Einfluss im Ödland auszuweiten.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>RNK-Spielerkolonie</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>Gouverneur</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>Bürger</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>Bürger</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.description>Die Volksrepublik China basiert auf den Idealen des Kollektivismus, der Harmonie und des technologischen Fortschritts und ist eine Nation geschäftiger Städte, eines reichen kulturellen Erbes und eines starken Gemeinschaftsgefühls. Unter der Oberfläche prägen jedoch zunehmende Zensur, staatliche Kontrolle und militärische Expansion das tägliche Leben. Die Bürger genießen eine rasante Modernisierung, lebendige Traditionen und Nationalstolz, auch wenn das Gespenst eines internationalen Konflikts immer näher rückt.</FCP_Faction_PRC.description>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.fixedName>Volksrepublik China</FCP_Faction_PRC.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.ideoDescription>Die Ideologie des Jahres des Drachen schätzt nationale Einheit, kollektive Anstrengung und technologischen Fortschritt. Es fördert die Loyalität gegenüber dem Staat, den Respekt vor der Tradition und den Stolz auf das kulturelle Erbe. Von den Bürgern wird erwartet, dass sie zum Wohle der Nation zusammenarbeiten, die soziale Harmonie wahren und Innovationen annehmen, in der Überzeugung, dass Einheit und Entschlossenheit Wohlstand und Stärke bringen werden.</FCP_Faction_PRC.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.label>Volksrepublik China</FCP_Faction_PRC.label>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.leaderTitle>Oberster Führer</FCP_Faction_PRC.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnSingular>chinesisch</FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnsPlural>chinesisch</FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.royalFavorLabel>Sozialkredite</FCP_Faction_PRC.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.description>The Raider Gangs are a loose confederation of bandit groups operating in the wasteland. They are known for their brutal tactics, scavenging, and raiding of settlements. While they often fight among themselves, they can unite against common foes. The Raiders reject the alt world values and instead embrace a survival-of-the-fittest mentality. They are feared and despised by many, but also halt a certain allure for those seeking freedom from the constraints of civilization.</FCP_Faction_Raider.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.fixedName>Raider-Banden</FCP_Faction_Raider.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.ideoDescription>Founded on principles of survival and strength, the Raider Gangs believe in taking what they need by force. They reject the alt world's values and embrace a brutal code of conduct where only the strong survive.</FCP_Faction_Raider.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.label>Raider-Banden</FCP_Faction_Raider.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.leaderTitle>Raider-Boss</FCP_Faction_Raider.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnSingular>Raider</FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnsPlural>Räuber</FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.royalFavorLabel>Trophäen</FCP_Faction_Raider.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.description>Amerika basiert auf den Idealen von Freiheit, Wohlstand und technologischem Fortschritt und ist eine Nation glänzender Städte, Vorstadtkomfort und grenzenlosem Optimismus. Unter der Oberfläche prägten jedoch wachsende Paranoia, Konzerneinfluss und militärische Eskalation das tägliche Leben. Die Bürger genossen fortschrittliche Annehmlichkeiten, farbenfrohe Popkultur und patriotischen Stolz, selbst als der Schatten eines Atomkriegs immer näher rückte.</FCP_Faction_USA.description>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.fixedName>Vereinigte Staaten von Amerika</FCP_Faction_USA.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.ideoDescription>Der amerikanische Traum ist der Glaube, dass jeder, unabhängig von seinem Hintergrund, durch harte Arbeit und Entschlossenheit Erfolg und Wohlstand erreichen kann. Es verkörpert die Ideale von Freiheit, Gleichheit und Chancen, auf denen die Vereinigten Staaten gegründet wurden.</FCP_Faction_USA.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.label>Vereinigte Staaten von Amerika</FCP_Faction_USA.label>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.leaderTitle>Präsident</FCP_Faction_USA.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.pawnSingular>amerikanisch</FCP_Faction_USA.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.pawnsPlural>Amerikaner</FCP_Faction_USA.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.royalFavorLabel>Servicepunkte</FCP_Faction_USA.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.description>SEinkaufszentrum communities of wastelanders who have banded together to survive in the harsh post-war world. These settlers live in ramshackle towns, trading scrap and salvaged goods while trying to maintain some semblance of civilization. They're cautious but not hostile, willing to trade with strangers but always wary of raiders and other threats. Most are just trying to scrape by, growing mutated crops, herding brahmin, and defending what little they have.</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.fixedName>Wasteland Settlements</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.label>Wasteland Settlers</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.leaderTitle>Mayor</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnSingular>settler</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnsPlural>settlers</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.fixedName>Wasteland Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.label>Wastelander Techprint Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnSingular>Wasteland Trader</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnsPlural>Wasteland Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.fixedName>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.label>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnSingular>Wastelander</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnsPlural>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>
