<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 오래된 세계에서 가장 호화로운 미용 클리닉 중 하나의 제품입니다. [PAWN_possessive] 생활 동안 [PAWN_pronoun]은 [PAWN_possessive] 외모에 엄청난 돈을 썼고 더 실용적인 것을 연습할 시간이 거의 없었습니다.</VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ShipsNavigator.title>호송 항해사</VBE_ShipsNavigator.title>
  <VBE_ShipsNavigator.titleShort>항해자</VBE_ShipsNavigator.titleShort>
  <VBE_ShipsNavigator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 황무지와 위험한 구시대 통로를 통과하여 이동하는 장거리 호송대의 경로를 도표화했습니다. [PAWN_pronoun]은(는) 가장 안전하고 빠른 경로를 찾는 놀라운 능력을 갖고 있었지만 [PAWN_pronoun]은 기계적인 작업에 어려움을 겪고 종종 다른 사람에게 맡겼습니다.</VBE_ShipsNavigator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_EngineRoomTech.baseDesc>원자로실 기술자인 [PAWN_nameDef]는 장거리 굴착 장치와 결제 생성기를 계속 가동했습니다. [PAWN_pronoun]는 올바른 도구를 사용하면 거의 모든 것을 고칠 수 있지만, [PAWN_pronoun]는 사회적 상호작용에 능숙함이 부족하고 부드러운 손길이 필요한 작업을 피했습니다.</VBE_EngineRoomTech.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GalacticMedic.title>호송 의무병</VBE_GalacticMedic.title>
  <VBE_GalacticMedic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 장거리 호송대의 의무병으로 일하면서 방사선 질환부터 부서진 고속도로에서의 충돌 부상까지 모든 것을 치료했습니다. [PAWN_possessive] 의학 지식은 타의 추종을 불허했지만, [PAWN_pronoun]는 연구나 복잡한 이론에 대한 머리가 없었습니다.</VBE_GalacticMedic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CargoHandler.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 화물 야적장과 호송 목록을 관리하여 물품을 안전하게 보관하고 재고를 정확하게 추적하는 일을 담당했습니다. [PAWN_pronoun]는 육체적으로 강하고 고도로 조직적이었지만, [PAWN_pronoun]는 자세한 문서화나 학문적 추구에 대한 인내심이 거의 없었습니다.</VBE_CargoHandler.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GalleyChef.title>호송 요리사</VBE_GalleyChef.title>
  <VBE_GalleyChef.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 장거리 호송대에 식량을 공급하여 회수한 재료를 승무원을 위한 풍성한 식사로 만들었습니다. 이동 중에 요리하는 것은 나름의 어려움을 안겨주었지만 [PAWN_pronoun]은 그 기술을 마스터했습니다. 그러나 [PAWN_pronoun]는 기계를 잘 다루지 않았으며 엔진보다 팬을 선호했습니다.</VBE_GalleyChef.baseDesc>
  <VBE_BloodlineFounder.title>창립자의 상속인</VBE_BloodlineFounder.title>
  <VBE_BloodlineFounder.titleShort>후계자</VBE_BloodlineFounder.titleShort>
  <VBE_BloodlineFounder.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 강력한 창립자의 혈통과 [PAWN_possessive]의 연관성을 인정하려는 사람이 아무도 없어 치열한 경쟁을 벌였습니다. 어쨌든 [PAWN_pronoun]는 여전히 옛 정권의 유산을 이어받았고, 그러한 권리가 밝혀지자 갑자기 모든 사람들이 남은 것의 일부를 원했습니다.</VBE_BloodlineFounder.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DeposedRoyalty.title>폐위된 군벌</VBE_DeposedRoyalty.title>
  <VBE_DeposedRoyalty.titleShort>장군</VBE_DeposedRoyalty.titleShort>
  <VBE_DeposedRoyalty.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]는 억압 없이 살 수 있는 [PAWN_possessive] 사람들의 권리를 포기하는 것을 거부하면서 잔인한 갈등을 통해 지역 전체에 걸친 영역을 개척했습니다. 결국 라이벌 세력은 [PAWN_possessive] 규칙을 깨기 위해 힘을 합쳤고 [PAWN_possessive] 경호원은 [PAWN_objective]을(를) 도망치도록 강요했습니다. [PAWN_pronoun]은 [PAWN_possessive]명의 미래를 보장하기 위해 가능한 모든 조치를 취했지만 그들을 보호하지 못한 것은 [PAWN_possessive]의 가장 큰 수치로 남아 있습니다.</VBE_DeposedRoyalty.baseDesc>
  <VQE_TheGeneral.description>[PAWN_nameDef]는 묻혀 있는 연속 벙커에서 Operation: Deadlife를 조정하여 올바른 사람들이 아래에서 버틴다면 폐허가 된 세계가 여전히 통치될 수 있다고 확신했습니다. 폭탄이 떨어졌을 때 [PAWN_pronoun]는 지휘 단지를 봉쇄하고 생존자들을 배급했으며 지휘 체계가 사라진 후에도 오랫동안 계속 명령을 내렸습니다. 방사선, 노화 및 응급 보존 치료로 인해 [PAWN_objective]는 정장을 입고 절반은 약으로, 절반은 집착으로 유지되는 생각하는 구울을 남겼습니다. [PAWN_pronoun]는 여전히 제어실에서 최종 발사 명령을 완료할 준비를 하고 있습니다.</VQE_TheGeneral.description>
  <VQE_TheGeneral.title>감독자</VQE_TheGeneral.title>
  <VQE_TheGeneral.titleShort>감독</VQE_TheGeneral.titleShort>
  <VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.description>[PAWN_nameDef]는 전체 지역 그리드를 복원하기 위한 프로토타입 융합 시스템을 설계한 것으로 엔지니어들 사이에서 유명해졌습니다. 치명적인 전력 부족을 해결해야 한다는 끊임없는 요구에 힘입어 [PAWN_pronoun]은 다른 누구보다 위험한 연구를 더 멀리 추진했습니다. 초기 원자로 시험은 성급하고 불안정했으며, 뒤따른 사고로 인해 많은 생명이 희생되었습니다. 이러한 실패는 결코 멈추지 않았습니다 [PAWN_objective]; 그들은 작업이 완료되어야 한다는 [PAWN_possessive] 믿음을 굳혔습니다. 셀 수 없이 많은 수정을 거쳐 [PAWN_nameDef]는 [PAWN_objective]를 일부에게는 영웅으로, 다른 일부에게는 무모한 선구자로 만드는 프로토타입을 제작했습니다.</VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.description>
  <VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.title>복원 엔지니어</VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.title>
  <Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.description>브라더후드의 베테랑 버티버드 조종사인 [PAWN_nameDef]는 악천후와 총격 속에서도 순찰대, 부상자, 화물, 고위 인사를 수송했습니다. [PAWN_pronoun]는 냉정함을 유지하고, 비행선 규율을 알고, 투덜거리는 소리와 놋쇠 소리와 동등하게 이야기를 교환할 수 있습니다.</Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.description>
  <Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.title>버티버드 조종사</Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.title>
  <Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.titleShort>버티버드 조종사</Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.titleShort>
  <Architect28.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed the construction of buildings. Back home, the technical calculations were handled by automated systems while the labour was done by work crews and machines. This freed [PAWN_objective] up to push the artistic limits of the craft, but also meant [PAWN_pronoun] never had to get [PAWN_possessive] hands dirty.</Architect28.description>
  <ArtsPatron54.description>[PAWN_nameDef] managed [PAWN_possessive] family's investments in the arts.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] chose artists to patronize and worked with them to produce the expressions that most glorified [PAWN_possessive] family, their church, and the ruling order itself.</ArtsPatron54.description>
  <BiosphereManager95.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived in a wealthy sealed resort where robots handled the menial work and the residents devoted themselves to leisure. [PAWN_pronoun] managed the plant and animal life of a sprawling park where guests came to admire nature's beauty.</BiosphereManager95.description>
  <CaveworldIlluminator95.description>Among tunnel-dwellers, those with vision as strong as [PAWN_nameDef]'s were revered as guides. [PAWN_pronoun] led the way through the dark, marking good digging spots with fungus lanterns and warning others of danger.</CaveworldIlluminator95.description>
  <CaveworldIlluminator95.title>cave guide</CaveworldIlluminator95.title>
  <CaveworldTender26.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a cave settlement deep beneath the surface of an inhospitable region. [PAWN_pronoun] worked with the other children tending the settlement's fungus crops.</CaveworldTender26.description>
  <CaveworldTender26.title>cave tender</CaveworldTender26.title>
  <CaveworldTunneler48.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a digger in a massive underground cave network.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] knows rock so well that [PAWN_pronoun] can almost navigate caves by smell.</CaveworldTunneler48.description>
  <CaveworldTunneler48.title>cave tunneler</CaveworldTunneler48.title>
  <CharityWorker36.description>The richest old-world communities lived in comfort while nearby slums starved. [PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] life appealing for donations and supporting those in need.</CharityWorker36.description>
  <Chef52.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was the star chef at a high-class resort restaurant. [PAWN_pronoun] was famous among patrons for [PAWN_possessive] creative culinary specialties, and infamous among the kitchen staff for [PAWN_possessive] casual disdain for grunt work.</Chef52.description>
  <CombatEngineer30.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was recruited by the military as an engineer and set to work improving the army's vertibirds and armored carriers. The harsh training taught [PAWN_objective] how to build and repair military vehicles and structures.
\nOne mission left [PAWN_nameDef] with pyrophobia and a strong desire to avoid plants.</CombatEngineer30.description>
  <CountryLordling92.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a privileged Enclave family estate in Appalachia. [PAWN_possessive] early years were filled with lessons in etiquette, politics, and Whitespring traditions.
[PAWN_nameDef] and [PAWN_possessive] friends found ways to sneak out and explore the forests beyond the compound.</CountryLordling92.description>
  <CountryLordling92.title>Enclave country scion</CountryLordling92.title>
  <CountryLordling92.titleFemale>Enclave country scion</CountryLordling92.titleFemale>
  <CountryLordling92.titleShort>country scion</CountryLordling92.titleShort>
  <CountryLordling92.titleShortFemale>country scion</CountryLordling92.titleShortFemale>
  <FeyCustomChildhood.description>Growing up sheltered in a vast old-world arcology, [PAWN_nameDef] distracted [PAWN_objective]self by playing wargames and painting miniatures. While [PAWN_pronoun] was never very good at the game itself, it helped connect [PAWN_objective] with others.</FeyCustomChildhood.description>
  <GlitterworldEmpath26.description>[PAWN_nameDef] found it easy to relate to others and mediate conflict. [PAWN_pronoun] was selected for a government emotional training program. The training intensified [PAWN_possessive] natural abilities, but [PAWN_pronoun] became unable to cause others pain.</GlitterworldEmpath26.description>
  <GlitterworldEmpath26.title>trained empath</GlitterworldEmpath26.title>
  <GlitterworldOfficer60.description>Though [PAWN_nameDef]'s posting was comfortable, [PAWN_possessive] unit stayed ready for war. [PAWN_nameDef] pursued artistic hobbies in [PAWN_possessive] off hours, but [PAWN_possessive] subordinates preferred to settle disputes with their fists, so [PAWN_nameDef] got good at breaking up fights.</GlitterworldOfficer60.description>
  <GlitterworldOfficer60.title>garrison officer</GlitterworldOfficer60.title>
  <GlitterworldSurgeon15.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a surgeon in a wealthy district mostly free of disease and hardship, so [PAWN_possessive] job focused on elaborate and creative cosmetic procedures.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] understands human biology deeply, but has never had to remove a tumour or a bullet under battlefield conditions.</GlitterworldSurgeon15.description>
  <GlitterworldSurgeon15.title>cosmetic surgeon</GlitterworldSurgeon15.title>
  <IllegalShipwright76.description>There is a law that says you are not allowed to bolt heavy plasma emitters onto a cargo hauler, especially if you hide them under what looks like a communications rig for a cleaner ambush. [PAWN_nameDef] discovered that there is great profit to be made from customers who do not care about these laws.</IllegalShipwright76.description>
  <ImperialInquisitor53.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a military police officer within the Whitespring, hunting unorthodox thought and dissent.
\n[PAWN_nameDef] exposed and punished deviance to maintain order and the enclave's research priorities.</ImperialInquisitor53.description>
  <ImperialInquisitor53.title>Whitespring military police</ImperialInquisitor53.title>
  <ImperialInquisitor53.titleShort>officer</ImperialInquisitor53.titleShort>
  <ImperialInquisitor53.titleShortFemale>officer</ImperialInquisitor53.titleShortFemale>
  <ImperialPriest24.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a lawyer in the Whitespring division.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] spent half [PAWN_possessive] time studying laws and the role of the order within enclave doctrine. The other half was spent preaching discipline and loyalty.</ImperialPriest24.description>
  <ImperialPriest24.title>Whitespring lawyer</ImperialPriest24.title>
  <ImperialPriest24.titleShort>lawyer</ImperialPriest24.titleShort>
  <ImperialPriest24.titleShortFemale>lawyer</ImperialPriest24.titleShortFemale>
  <JoywireArtist8.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked in a city lab developing neural entertainment software to maximize user pleasure.
\nWhen the local government imposed harsh restrictions on the product, [PAWN_pronoun] began selling [PAWN_possessive] designs on the black market.</JoywireArtist8.description>
  <JoywireArtist8.title>neural entertainment designer</JoywireArtist8.title>
  <JoywireArtist8.titleShort>designer</JoywireArtist8.titleShort>
  <LiamCustomAdulthood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked in a comfortable research district developing hyper-realistic war simulations.</LiamCustomAdulthood.description>
  <LiamCustomChildhood.description>Born and raised in a wealthy enclave district, [PAWN_nameDef] became obsessed with simulation software. [PAWN_pronoun] spent far too much time plugged in.</LiamCustomChildhood.description>
  <MateCustomAdulthood.description>After being laid off by a giant old-world corporation, [PAWN_nameDef] spent several years disillusioned and fighting alcohol addiction.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] ended up busking aboard a battered cargo hauler, playing a beaten-up guitar and entertaining the crew with blues and folk songs from the distant past.</MateCustomAdulthood.description>
  <NavyScientist52.description>Modern wars are won by technology, so old-world naval labs hoarded the best equipment they could find. [PAWN_nameDef] worked in one of those labs, studying captured prototypes and strange relics hauled in from distant expeditions.</NavyScientist52.description>
  <Novelist7.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived in a prosperous pre-war city, penning wildly successful novels. [PAWN_pronoun] lived a carefree lifestyle, spending [PAWN_possessive] days writing and [PAWN_possessive] nights partying, and has never done a day's manual labour in [PAWN_possessive] life.</Novelist7.description>
  <OskarCustomAdulthood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed combat modifications for frontline soldiers.
\nOne night, in a nightmare, [PAWN_nameDef] was confronted by all the men and women killed by [PAWN_possessive] work. [PAWN_pronoun] decided to head into the wastes and use [PAWN_possessive] skills for good.</OskarCustomAdulthood.description>
  <OskarCustomChildhood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on the dark edge of a sprawling industrial city. After an argument, [PAWN_possessive] father sold [PAWN_objective] to a local boss as a slave artist.
\nForced to create art or be punished, [PAWN_pronoun] withdrew and became unable to form relations with others.</OskarCustomChildhood.description>
  <RoyalCook18.description>[PAWN_nameDef] made meals for Whitespring patrons.
\nOnly the finest food was acceptable, so [PAWN_nameDef] tended a small garden on the compound grounds to get the freshest herbs and vegetables. [PAWN_pronoun] fell in love with the food [PAWN_objective]self.</RoyalCook18.description>
  <RoyalCook18.title>Whitespring cook</RoyalCook18.title>
  <RoyalCook18.titleShort>cook</RoyalCook18.titleShort>
  <RoyalMasseuse43.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served wealthy Whitespring patrons as a massage artist. [PAWN_pronoun] serviced many members of the enclave and their guests.
\n[PAWN_nameDef] occasionally offered something extra, if the patron was in the mood. Advancing in this line of work meant having refined social skills.</RoyalMasseuse43.description>
  <RoyalMasseuse43.title>Whitespring masseuse</RoyalMasseuse43.title>
  <RoyalMasseuse43.titleShort>masseuse</RoyalMasseuse43.titleShort>
  <Scout44.description>Born to the administrators of a remote government outpost, [PAWN_nameDef] was enrolled in a youth program that taught military scouting skills.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] learned to survive in the wilderness, to obey, and not to ask questions.</Scout44.description>
  <Sculptor63.description>[PAWN_nameDef] started off sculpting person-sized artworks, but [PAWN_pronoun] soon began to think bigger. With the help of industrial equipment, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to carve huge monuments out of cliffsides. Soon the parks and promenades of the city where [PAWN_pronoun] lived were full of giant stone figures.</Sculptor63.description>
  <ShipboundLordling12.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s family held their power base in a grand, ancient command bunker. Born and raised inside it, [PAWN_nameDef] learned all about sealed-facility life, as well as the politics and methods of siege warfare and bunker assaults.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] learned to feel most at home with strong walls close on all sides and the gentle hiss of air scrubbers.</ShipboundLordling12.description>
  <ShipboundLordling12.title>bunker lordling</ShipboundLordling12.title>
  <ShipboundLordling12.titleFemale>bunker lady</ShipboundLordling12.titleFemale>
  <ShipboundLordling12.titleShort>bunker heir</ShipboundLordling12.titleShort>
  <ShipboundLordling12.titleShortFemale>bunker heir</ShipboundLordling12.titleShortFemale>
  <ShipBoy89.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born to low-ranked servants in an ancient command bunker. The bunker mainframe was like a third parent to [PAWN_objective], and the maintenance crew [PAWN_pronoun] worked for was like a second family.
\n[PAWN_nameDef] rarely saw plants or animals, and still finds them unnerving to touch.</ShipBoy89.description>
  <ShipBoy89.title>bunker boy</ShipBoy89.title>
  <ShipBoy89.titleFemale>bunker girl</ShipBoy89.titleFemale>
  <ShipBoy89.titleShort>bunker boy</ShipBoy89.titleShort>
  <ShipBoy89.titleShortFemale>bunker girl</ShipBoy89.titleShortFemale>
  <Shipcracker37.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s role was to blast into fortified bunkers, punch through the interior defenses, and conquer them in room-to-room combat. [PAWN_pronoun] became very good at wielding heavy breaching weapons to cut both steel and flesh.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] also developed a taste for the drugs [PAWN_pronoun] used to cope with the overwhelming stress.</Shipcracker37.description>
  <Shipcracker37.title>bunker breacher</Shipcracker37.title>
  <Shipcracker37.titleShort>breacher</Shipcracker37.titleShort>
  <SoldiersKid55.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in the ancient command bunker where [PAWN_possessive] parents were stationed. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the basics of firearm operations and maintenance from the soldiers on duty and became accustomed to a strict routine and frequent discipline.</SoldiersKid55.description>
  <SpaceMarine16.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a shock trooper in an elite army. [PAWN_possessive] job was to blast through fortified positions, gun down the defenders, and capture the place intact. And [PAWN_pronoun] was good at it.</SpaceMarine16.description>
  <SpaceMarine16.title>breach trooper</SpaceMarine16.title>
  <SpaceMarine16.titleShort>trooper</SpaceMarine16.titleShort>
  <SpaceTechnician29.description>[PAWN_nameDef] finally managed to flee [PAWN_possessive] criminal life by getting a maintenance job at a nearby relay station. [PAWN_pronoun] performed a wide range of repair and construction work, helped with basic research, and often defused co-workers' arguments. [PAWN_pronoun] never liked doing art.</SpaceTechnician29.description>
  <SpaceTechnician29.title>relay technician</SpaceTechnician29.title>
  <StarshipJanitor33.description>While other residents slept through long stretches in a sealed government bunker, [PAWN_nameDef] had to wake up at periodic intervals to perform inspections, check the life-support systems, and oil the maintenance robots.</StarshipJanitor33.description>
  <StarshipJanitor33.title>bunker janitor</StarshipJanitor33.title>
  <Taxonomist0.description>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled from region to region, studying and classifying the plant and animal life [PAWN_pronoun] found in the hope of creating a complete catalogue.</Taxonomist0.description>
  <TestSubject15.description>In the most corrupt old cities, scientists without a moral compass committed unspeakable atrocities in the name of research. [PAWN_nameDef] was kept alone in a sealed facility from birth and subjected to behavioural experiments in an attempt to turn [PAWN_objective] into a perfect super-soldier.</TestSubject15.description>
  <UrbworldDrone32.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a mindless construction hand in a massive company town. Though [PAWN_pronoun] is now free from the brutal social conditioning [PAWN_pronoun] was subjected to, [PAWN_pronoun] remains incapable of creative thought and leadership.</UrbworldDrone32.description>
  <UrbworldDrone32.title>city drone</UrbworldDrone32.title>
  <UrbworldEntrepreneur14.description>In the old corporate cities, most people suffered. But someone had to run the companies.
\n[PAWN_nameDef] learned the skills of the trade, greasing palms and balancing technical analysis with politics. [PAWN_pronoun] became a sociointellectual machine.</UrbworldEntrepreneur14.description>
  <UrbworldEntrepreneur14.title>city entrepreneur</UrbworldEntrepreneur14.title>
  <UrbworldPolitican92.description>It is no secret that the companies own much of the old cities, but someone has to take the bribes. [PAWN_nameDef] was one such figurehead.
\n[PAWN_pronoun] learned how to manipulate the hopes and dreams of the people while living comfortably in a penthouse.</UrbworldPolitican92.description>
  <UrbworldPolitican92.title>city politician</UrbworldPolitican92.title>
  <UrbworldRebel56.description>Most people around [PAWN_nameDef] lived under constant corporate surveillance and propaganda feeds. [PAWN_nameDef] joined a rebel faction that rejected modern technology entirely.</UrbworldRebel56.description>
  <UrbworldRebel56.title>city rebel</UrbworldRebel56.title>
  <UrbworldUrchin61.description>The old industrial cities were ancient, deep warrens of rust, poison, and too many people. [PAWN_nameDef] grew up in the dark, unwanted reaches of one of them and had to fight for every scrap of food.</UrbworldUrchin61.description>
  <UrbworldUrchin61.title>city urchin</UrbworldUrchin61.title>
  <VRDesigner87.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed virtual reality simulations for wealthy patrons. [PAWN_pronoun] put great effort into the details of [PAWN_possessive] virtual worlds, learning all [PAWN_pronoun] could about plant life to make [PAWN_possessive] landscapes as realistic as possible.</VRDesigner87.description>
  <WillCustomAdulthood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed elaborate entertainment mazes for wealthy patrons. Even now, [PAWN_pronoun] thinks of little else.</WillCustomAdulthood.description>
  <WillCustomChildhood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a research camp on a blasted world. [PAWN_possessive] parents were studying mysterious labyrinthine formations beneath the crust, and [PAWN_pronoun] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time wandering those tunnels and wondering what kind of thing could have created them.</WillCustomChildhood.description>
</LanguageData>
