<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.description>A coastal variant of the mirelurk that has adapted to sandy beach environments. These creatures have lighter-colored shells that blend with beach sand, making them harder to spot until they emerge from the surf. Beachlurks are slightly more aggressive than their swamp-dwelling cousins and often bury themselves in sand to ambush prey.</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.label>Beachlurk</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.description>A highly evolved mutant creature that combines features of snapping turtles and cuttlefish. Unlike mirelurks, lakelurks are much more aggressive and possess a sonic attack that can disorient prey. Their shells are extremely tough, and they're far more intelligent than other lurk variants. Found primarily in large lakes and deep waters, they're apex aquatic predators of the wasteland.</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.label>Lakelurk</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.0.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.1.label>bite</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.description>A massive male lakelurk that has grown to enormous proportions. Lakelurk kings are territorial apex predators that claim entire lakes as their domain. They possess enhanced sonic abilities that can stun multiple targets, incredibly thick shells, and devastating strength. These solitary giants are always male and highly aggressive, attacking anything that enters their territory. Extremely rare and highly 危险.</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.label>Lakelurk King</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.2.label>bite</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.description>A heavily mutated crustacean that has grown to enormous size. These creatures have thick, chitinous shells that provide excellent protection against most weapons. Mirelurks are territorial and aggressive, using their powerful claws to defend their nesting grounds. They're typically found near bodies of water and coastal areas, scavenging for food and defending their territory with surprising ferocity.</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.label>Mirelurk</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.description>Despite its name, the mirelurk king is not actually a mirelurk at all. This towering bipedal predator is believed to be a heavily mutated Jackson's chameleon, sharing no direct relation to the crustacean-like mirelurks. The name comes from their tendency to inhabit areas near mirelurk colonies. Kings stand on two legs, possess powerful clawed hands, and can emit devastating sonic screams. Their exposed flesh and lack of a protective shell is compensated by remarkable agility and deadly close-range attacks.</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.label>Mirelurk King</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.2.label>bite</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.description>A freshwater variant of the mirelurk found primarily in rivers and streams. These creatures have darker shells that help them blend into murky river bottoms. Riverlurks are somewhat more docile than their coastal relatives but still 危险 when threatened. They prefer fast-moving water and are excellent swimmers.</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.label>Riverlurk</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.2.label>
</LanguageData>
