<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Chem_Addictol.description>A powerful anti-addiction medication that purges the body of chemical dependencies. Addictol works by resetting neurological pathways and breaking the addiction cycle, though the process is uncomfortable and temporary exhaustion is common.\n\nA lifesaver for those trying to kick 危险 habits, though its high cost limits availability.</FCP_Chem_Addictol.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Addictol.label>成瘾者</FCP_Chem_Addictol.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Auto_Stimpak.description>一种自动输送系统，可在检测到受伤时分配标准针剂剂量。 The auto-injector mechanism eliminates the need for manual application, making it ideal for solo travelers.</FCP_Chem_Auto_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Auto_Stimpak.label>自动刺激剂</FCP_Chem_Auto_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Auto_Super_Stimpak.description>一种自动输送系统，装载有超级针剂配方，可实现快速紧急治疗。这种先进的注射器将军用级愈合化合物与自动输送技术相结合，使其成为荒地中最有价值的医疗物品之一。</FCP_Chem_Auto_Super_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Auto_Super_Stimpak.label>自动超级刺激剂</FCP_Chem_Auto_Super_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Berry_Mentats.description>A Mentats variant infused with berry flavoring and enhanced formula. Berry Mentats 可显着提升魅力和社交技能，使用户在谈判和社交场合中更具说服力和讨人喜欢。\n\n受到商人、外交官和任何需要留下好印象的人的青睐。</FCP_Chem_Berry_Mentats.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Berry_Mentats.label>浆果门塔斯</FCP_Chem_Berry_Mentats.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Blood_Pack.description>A sterile bag of preserved blood suitable for emergency transfusions. Blood packs provide immediate restoration of blood volume and help stabilize critically wounded patients.虽然不如现代医疗技术先进，但这些战前的医疗用品在荒原上仍然很有价值。\n\n血包是通用捐献者，适用于所有血型。</FCP_Chem_Blood_Pack.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Blood_Pack.label>血包</FCP_Chem_Blood_Pack.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Buffout.description>一种战前增强表现的类固醇。 Buffout dramatically increases strength and endurance, improving melee damage and carrying capacity.然而，长期使用会导致成瘾和潜在的器官损伤。\n\n战前深受运动员和劳工的欢迎，现在是荒地战士和拾荒者的主要产品。</FCP_Chem_Buffout.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Buffout.label>布福特</FCP_Chem_Buffout.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Cateye.description>An experimental drug that temporarily enhances night vision and low-light perception. Cateye dilates the pupils and enhances retinal sensitivity, allowing users to see clearly in near-total darkness.\n\nValued by night scouts and scavengers exploring dark 废墟s, though the light sensitivity during daytime can be problematic.</FCP_Chem_Cateye.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Cateye.label>猫眼</FCP_Chem_Cateye.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Daddy_O.description>A pre-war cognitive enhancer that boosts intelligence and perception at the cost of social skills. Daddy-O 使用户变得更聪明、更有洞察力，但在社交方面更加尴尬和孤僻。\n\n受到优先考虑心理敏锐度而非社交互动的研究人员和技术人员的青睐。</FCP_Chem_Daddy_O.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Daddy_O.label>爸爸-O</FCP_Chem_Daddy_O.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Day_Tripper.description>A pre-war recreational drug that enhances mood and social charm. Day Tripper makes the user more charismatic and likable while providing a pleasant mild high. Moderately addictive with regular use.\n\nPopular in pre-war social circles, still used by those seeking to improve their social standing.</FCP_Chem_Day_Tripper.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Day_Tripper.label>一日游</FCP_Chem_Day_Tripper.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Diluted_Stimpak.description>A watered-down stimulation delivery system that provides minor healing over time. Common among wasteland scavengers due to its lower cost and availability.</FCP_Chem_Diluted_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Diluted_Stimpak.label>稀释的针剂</FCP_Chem_Diluted_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Dixons_Jet.description>A refined and purified version of Jet created through an advanced filtration process. Dixon's Jet 比标准 Jet 提供更强烈、更持久的快感，杂质更少，但仍然很容易上瘾。\n\n这种高级变体以其创造者的名字命名，在 Jet 用户中售价很高。</FCP_Chem_Dixons_Jet.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Dixons_Jet.label>迪克森喷气式飞机</FCP_Chem_Dixons_Jet.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Doctors_Bag.description>A comprehensive medical kit containing surgical tools, antiseptics, splints, and pharmaceutical supplies.医生包可以对严重受伤和残废的肢体进行现场治疗，但正确使用需要医学知识和时间。\n\n对于任何认真的荒地医生来说都是必不可少的设备。</FCP_Chem_Doctors_Bag.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Doctors_Bag.label>医生包</FCP_Chem_Doctors_Bag.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Fixer.description>A specialized anti-addiction compound that helps break chemical dependencies.虽然不如 Addictol 强大，但 Fixer 更容易获得，并且在对抗戒断症状和减轻成瘾严重程度方面仍然有效。\n\n这是荒地医生的工具，可帮助成瘾者康复，而无需获得昂贵的战前药物。</FCP_Chem_Fixer.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Fixer.label>固定器</FCP_Chem_Fixer.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Grape_Mentats.description>A balanced Mentats variant that enhances both intelligence and charisma. Grape Mentats 使用户变得更聪明、更善于社交，非常适合技术谈判或科学演示。\n\n需要向非专家解释复杂想法的科学家的选择。</FCP_Chem_Grape_Mentats.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Grape_Mentats.label>葡萄门塔斯</FCP_Chem_Grape_Mentats.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Healing_Powder.description>A traditional wasteland medicine made from ground broc flower and xander root. While less effective than modern stimpaks, healing powder is cheaper to produce and has been used by tribal healers for generations.随着时间的推移，混合物可以逐渐愈合。</FCP_Chem_Healing_Powder.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Healing_Powder.label>愈合粉</FCP_Chem_Healing_Powder.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Hydra.description>An experimental pre-war drug designed to rapidly heal crippled limbs. Hydra uses advanced regenerative compounds to repair damaged tissue and bone, though the process is painful and can cause temporary disorientation.\n\nPopular among wasteland combatants for its ability to get wounded s老旧iers back into the fight quickly.</FCP_Chem_Hydra.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Hydra.label>九头蛇</FCP_Chem_Hydra.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Jet.description>A highly addictive meta-amphetamine created from brahmin dung fumes. Jet 可以显着提高动作速度和反应能力，但效果很严重，而且很难戒掉。\n\nJet 由一位名叫 Myron 的化学天才发明，成为战后荒原上最广泛、最具破坏性的药物。</FCP_Chem_Jet.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Jet.label>喷射</FCP_Chem_Jet.label>
  <FCP_Chem_MedX.description>战前的止痛药。 Med-X works by blocking pain receptors and reducing incoming damage through enhanced pain tolerance.该药物非常有效，但具有很大的成瘾风险。\n\nMed-X 最初作为全身麻醉剂销售，现已成为荒地中有价值的战斗药物。</FCP_Chem_MedX.description>
  <FCP_Chem_MedX.label>医学-X</FCP_Chem_MedX.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Mentats.description>A nootropic drug that enhances cognitive function. Mentats improve perception, intelligence, and mental acuity, making users sharper and more aware of their surroundings.长期使用可能会导致心理依赖。\n\n受到科学家、贸易商以及任何在谈判或技术工作中需要心理优势的人的青睐。</FCP_Chem_Mentats.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Mentats.label>门塔茨</FCP_Chem_Mentats.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Orange_Mentats.description>A specialized Mentats variant that dramatically enhances perception and awareness. Orange Mentats sharpen the senses and improve accuracy, making them invaluable for scouts, snipers, and anyone needing enhanced sensory perception.\n\nA marksman's 秘密 weapon for those critical shots.</FCP_Chem_Orange_Mentats.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Orange_Mentats.label>橙色门塔斯</FCP_Chem_Orange_Mentats.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Party_Time_Mentats.description>A recreational Mentats variant designed for social gatherings.派对时间 Mentats 可以增强魅力和心情，使社交互动更加愉快和成功，同时提供温和的欣快效果。\n\n任何废土派对的生活，但最好谨慎使用。</FCP_Chem_Party_Time_Mentats.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Party_Time_Mentats.label>派对时间 门塔斯</FCP_Chem_Party_Time_Mentats.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Psycho.description>A military combat drug that sends the user into a berserker rage. Psycho dramatically increases damage output and resistance to injury, but suppresses higher brain functions and is highly addictive.\n\nDeveloped before the war for special forces operations, Psycho turns ordinary s老旧iers into fearless killing machines.</FCP_Chem_Psycho.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Psycho.label>心理</FCP_Chem_Psycho.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Radaway.description>A pre-war intravenous chemical solution that bonds with radiation contamination in the body and flushes it out through the bloodstream.虽然可以有效地治疗有毒物质的积聚，但这个过程会让人筋疲力尽，并使患者在几个小时内变得虚弱。\n\nRad-Away 是荒地中的一种宝贵商品，那里的辐射暴露是一个持续的威胁。</FCP_Chem_Radaway.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Radaway.label>辐射远离</FCP_Chem_Radaway.label>
  <FCP_Chem_RadX.description>A pre-war anti-radiation chemical that significantly increases the body's resistance to toxic and radioactive contamination. Rad-X 的工作原理是暂时改变细胞结构以抵抗辐射吸收，尽管此过程会导致轻微的定向障碍和反射减弱。\n\n与消除现有污染的 Rad-Away 不同，Rad-X 在暴露于危险环境之前采取预防措施。</FCP_Chem_RadX.description>
  <FCP_Chem_RadX.label>辐射X</FCP_Chem_RadX.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Rebound.description>A basic anti-addiction medication that helps reduce withdrawal symptoms and cravings.虽然 Rebound 的功效不如 Addictol，但价格更便宜，并且仍然可以为那些与化学依赖作斗争的人提供显着的缓解。\n\n这是荒地诊所在预算内治疗成瘾患者的常见选择。</FCP_Chem_Rebound.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Rebound.label>反弹</FCP_Chem_Rebound.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Rocket.description>A 危险 mixture of Jet and Nuka-Cola that provides an intense burst of energy and speed. The combination of stimulants creates a powerful but unstable high that significantly boosts action speed and reflexes.\n\nPopular among couriers and raiders who need quick bursts of performance.</FCP_Chem_Rocket.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Rocket.label>火箭</FCP_Chem_Rocket.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Slasher.description>A brutal combat stimulant specifically designed to enhance melee combat effectiveness. Slasher increases melee damage output dramatically while reducing pain sensitivity, creating fearless close-combat fighters.\n\nPopular among raiders and melee specialists, though its addictive nature and side effects make it a 危险 choice.</FCP_Chem_Slasher.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Slasher.label>砍杀者</FCP_Chem_Slasher.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Steady.description>A muscle relaxant and neural stabilizer that dramatically improves shooting accuracy and reduces weapon sway. Steady 可以平息颤抖并稳定双手，这对于精确工作和狙击而言非常宝贵。\n\nSteady 是为射手和外科医生开发的，对于任何需要完美手眼协调的人来说已经成为必不可少的工具。</FCP_Chem_Steady.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Steady.label>稳定的</FCP_Chem_Steady.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Stimpak.description>用于治愈损伤的标准刺激传递系统。刺激剂是荒地中最常见的医疗物品，它结合了愈合剂和生物再生化合物来快速修复伤口。</FCP_Chem_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Stimpak.label>针剂</FCP_Chem_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Super_Stimpak.description>强大的军用级刺激包，可提供快速和广泛的治疗。 Super stimpaks use a highly concentrated formula with advanced bio-regenerative compounds, making them extremely valuable and rare.</FCP_Chem_Super_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Super_Stimpak.label>超级针剂</FCP_Chem_Super_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Turbo.description>An extremely potent inhaler that dramatically accelerates the user's perception and reflexes. Turbo makes time seem to slow down, allowing for superhuman reaction speeds.效果虽然短暂，但却非常强大。\n\nTurbo 通过先进的精炼过程创建，是荒地中最受欢迎的战斗增强器之一。</FCP_Chem_Turbo.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Turbo.label>涡轮</FCP_Chem_Turbo.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Ultra_Stimpak.description>An enhanced stimulation pack with improved healing properties and faster action. These improved stimpaks use a more concentrated formula with additional bio-regenerative compounds.</FCP_Chem_Ultra_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Ultra_Stimpak.label>超级针剂</FCP_Chem_Ultra_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Chem_Ultrajet.description>An extremely potent combination of Jet and Psycho. Ultrajet provides the speed enhancement of Jet combined with the combat fury of Psycho, creating a devastating combat stimulant. Highly addictive and 危险.\n\nA favorite among the most desperate and violent wasteland fighters.</FCP_Chem_Ultrajet.description>
  <FCP_Chem_Ultrajet.label>超喷射</FCP_Chem_Ultrajet.label>
  <FCP_Chem_X_Cell.description>An extremely rare and expensive pre-war super-drug that enhances all physical and mental capabilities simultaneously. X-Cell 提供了所有统计数据的全面增强，但生产起来极其困难且成本高昂。\n\nX-Cell 是战前制药成就的顶峰，是最终的性能增强剂。</FCP_Chem_X_Cell.description>
  <FCP_Chem_X_Cell.label>X细胞</FCP_Chem_X_Cell.label>
</LanguageData>
