<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.description>A 钢铁兄弟会 ration crate containing preserved military meals, purified water, and nutritional supplements. Designed to sustain s老旧iers during extended operations in the harsh wasteland environment.</FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.label>兄弟会食品供应箱</FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.description>A specialized 钢铁兄弟会 uniform crate containing the distinctive gear worn by Elder Lyons' reformed Brotherhood. These uniforms represent the faction's humanitarian mission and their commitment to protecting the innocent.</FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.label>里昂骄傲制服箱</FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.description>一个兄弟会被遗弃者的补给箱，里面装着纯粹派所穿的独特的红黑制服。这些制服象征着他们对原始法典的坚定奉献以及他们不惜一切代价夺回战前技术的使命。</FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.label>被遗弃的制服箱</FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.description>A sealed 钢铁兄弟会 supply crate containing essential technological components, spare parts, and advanced materials. These resources are crucial for maintaining and upgrading their sophisticated equipment and installations.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.label>兄弟会技术资源箱</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>A 钢铁兄弟会 supply crate containing standard-issue uniforms, fatigues, and protective gear worn by regular Brotherhood personnel. Each piece bears the distinctive colors and insignia of the faction.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>兄弟会标准制服箱</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>A sealed 钢铁兄弟会 weapon crate containing high-quality firearms and energy weapons used by their forces. The distinctive red and metallic finish bears the Brotherhood's emblematic cogwheel.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>钢铁兄弟会 Weapon Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>
</LanguageData>
