<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.description>A distinguished uniform issued to generals of the United States Army, symbolizing command and tradition. Its immaculate condition and ornate details reflect the prestige and authority of America's military leadership.</FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.label>US General Uniform</FCP_Apparel_US_Generals_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.description>A winterized uniform issued to generals of the United States Army, symbolizing command and tradition. Enhanced with insulated lining and weatherproof materials, it provides warmth and protection in c老旧 climates while maintaining the prestige and authority of America's military leadership.</FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.label>Winterized US General Uniform</FCP_Apparel_US_Winterized_Generals_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.description>The standard-issue US Army Combat Armor of 2077, featuring advanced composite plating and modular design. Widely deployed across conflict zones, it offers robust protection against ballistic and energy threats while maintaining mobility. Integrated with environmental seals and tactical interfaces, this armor represents the pinnacle of military technology in the United States.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.label>US Army Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_Combat_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.description>A United States Army variant of the legendary T-51 power armor. Painted in military olive drab and bearing the insignia of the US Armed Forces, this suit represents the standard issue for Army mechanized infantry units. The T-51's titanium composite shell and advanced servos provided unmatched battlefield superiority during the Resource Wars, making its wearers nearly unstoppable forces of pre-war military might.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.label>US Army T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.description>The ultimate expression of United States Army power armor technology before the Great War. This T-60 variant bears the proud colors and markings of the US military, issued only to the most elite mechanized infantry divisions. Combining superior protection with advanced environmental systems and intimidating presence, the T-60 represented the cutting edge of American military engineering and the backbone of armored operations during the final days of the 老旧 world.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.label>US Army T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Army_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.description>Heavy armor worn by United States Marine Corps personnel. Provides excellent protection against ballistic threats.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.label>US Marine Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.description>A lighter variant of the US Marine Corps armor, sacrificing some protection for improved mobility and reduced weight. Designed for rapid deployment scenarios and extended field operations where agility is paramount. Still provides substantial ballistic protection while allowing marines to operate with greater speed and endurance.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.label>US Marine Light Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Light_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.description>A specialized wetsuit worn by United States Marine Corps divers and amphibious assault teams. Made from advanced neoprene composite, it provides thermal insulation and environmental protection while maintaining flexibility for underwater operations. Designed to be worn under marine armor during amphibious missions.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.label>US Marine Wetsuit</FCP_Apparel_USA_Marine_Wetsuit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.description>An elegant formal suit worn by the President of the United States. Made from the finest materials with exquisite tailoring, it represents the dignity and authority of the highest office in the nation. The suit is both comfortable and imposing, suitable for state functions and diplomatic meetings.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.label>President's suit</FCP_Apparel_USA_Presidents_Suit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.description>Advanced tactical armor issued to elite United States 秘密 Service agents tasked with protecting the highest levels of government. Engineered from composite alloys and reinforced plating, this armor provides exceptional ballistic and energy protection without sacrificing mobility. The low-profile design allows agents to blend into formal settings while remaining combat-ready at a moment's notice.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.label>秘密 Service Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.description>A specialized tactical underarmor worn by United States 秘密 Service agents beneath their armor plating. Constructed from advanced ballistic weave and moisture-wicking fibers, it provides a baseline layer of protection and climate control. The carefully designed cut ensures full range of motion while maintaining professional appearance under formal attire when needed.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.label>秘密 Service Underarmor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Secret_Service_Underarmor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.description>The pinnacle of pre-war American power armor technology, the T-65 was developed exclusively for elite 秘密 Service operatives assigned to the most critical national security operations. Incorporating cutting-edge materials science and engineering far beyond standard military issue, this armor provides unmatched protection and strength enhancement. Its distinctive profile is instantly recognizable to those familiar with the inner workings of the United States government.</FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.label>T-65 秘密 Service Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_T65_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.description>The winterized variant of the US Army Combat Armor of 2077, featuring advanced composite plating, modular design, and enhanced insulation for extreme c老旧. Outfitted with weatherproof materials and environmental seals, it offers robust protection against ballistic and energy threats while ensuring s老旧ier mobility and warmth in harsh winter conditions.</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.label>Winterized US Army Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_USA_Winterized_Army_Combat_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
