<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Meat_Beast.description>Raw meat from wasteland beasts. The flesh is tougher and has a slightly off taste compared to domesticated animals, bearing the marks of radiation and harsh conditions. Suitable for meals, though it may contain trace amounts of wasteland contamination.</FCP_Meat_Beast.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Beast.label>beast meat</FCP_Meat_Beast.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Bug.description>Raw meat harvested from mutated wasteland insects. The flesh has an unusual texture and a faintly bitter taste. While nutritious, the high concentration of strange compounds from the insect's diet of irradiated materials makes it somewhat toxic.</FCP_Meat_Bug.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Bug.label>bug meat</FCP_Meat_Bug.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Crab.description>Firm, white meat harvested from wasteland crustaceans. The flesh is dense and flavorful, though it tends to absorb waterborne contaminants from the creature's aquatic habitat. Popular among coastal survivors despite the mild radiation.</FCP_Meat_Crab.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Crab.label>mirelurk meat</FCP_Meat_Crab.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Herptile.description>Lean meat from wasteland reptiles and amphibians. The flesh is stringy but edible, with a slightly gamey flavor. These creatures are particularly adept at storing radiation in their tissues, making the meat more contaminated than most.</FCP_Meat_Herptile.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Herptile.label>herptile meat</FCP_Meat_Herptile.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.description>Exceptionally fat and juicy meat from well-fed mutant insects. The tissue is swollen with nutritious compounds, making it more palatable than typical bug meat. Wasteland survivors prize these cuts, though they still carry moderate toxicity from the creature's irradiated diet.</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.label>plumb bug meat</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.description>Exceptionally meaty cuts from well-fed wasteland birds. The breast meat is thick and juicy, rivaling pre-war poultry in quality. Despite the radiation, this is considered a premium food source in the wasteland.</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.label>plumb irradiated poultry</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Poultry.description>Meat from mutated wasteland birds. The flesh is recognizable as poultry but has an off-color tint and unusual smell from radiation exposure. While still edible and familiar in texture, it's clearly not from any pre-war chicken.</FCP_Meat_Poultry.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Poultry.label>irradiated poultry</FCP_Meat_Poultry.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.description>Exceptionally high-quality meat from a healthy, well-fed wasteland beast. The muscle tissue is well-marbled and surprisingly clean considering its origins. Prime cuts like these are rare finds and command premium prices. Still carries minimal radiation exposure from the wasteland environment.</FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.label>prime beast meat</FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.description>Superior quality reptilian meat from a well-developed specimen. The muscle tissue is firm and properly developed, offering better texture and flavor than typical herptile meat. Even prime specimens carry moderate radiation from their wasteland diet.</FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.label>prime herptile meat</FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.description>Surprisingly good meat from a healthy wasteland varmint. The animal was well-fed and its meat is tender despite the s商场 size. These cuts are prized by survivors who know how to prepare them properly. Still moderately radioactive.</FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.label>prime varmint meat</FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.description>Delicate, flavorful meat from wasteland fish. Its texture is tender and moist, making it a rare delicacy among survivors. While highly nutritious, it may still carry trace contaminants from irradiated waters.</FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.label>succulent fish meat</FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Varmint.description>S商场 game meat from wasteland rodents and other vermin. The portions are meager and the meat quality is poor, but beggars can't be choosers. These scavengers accumulate significant radiation from eating contaminated food scraps.</FCP_Meat_Varmint.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Varmint.label>varmint meat</FCP_Meat_Varmint.label>
</LanguageData>
