<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <!--Ghoul-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="HHTools_Settler_Democratic">
    <defName>HHTools_Mutant_Ghoul</defName>
    <label>Civil Ghoul Ghosttown</label>
    <description>A democratic ghoul settlement — a ghost town community that has outlasted the civilization that built it. The residents are ghouls who have organized themselves into a functioning town, with elected leadership, trade, and shared law. Most wastelanders avoid the place on instinct, but those who stop find it considerably more organized than expected. Ghouls here have had long enough to tire of being feared, and long enough to build something worth governing.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.9</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.1</WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <factionIconPath>FIP-H&amp;HTools/HHTools_Mutant</factionIconPath>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Mutant-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="HHTools_Settler_Despotic">
    <defName>HHTools_Mutant_SuperMutant</defName>
    <label>Rough Super Mutant Stronghold</label>
    <description>An autocratic super mutant stronghold, held together by the strength and will of whoever leads it. Super mutants do not govern by consensus — authority here is established by force and maintained by the constant threat of it. What passes for order is a rough hierarchy of strength, with the most capable and aggressive at the top. Such settlements range from functional fortresses to barely-contained chaos, depending entirely on the quality of their current leader.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.1</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.9</WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <factionIconPath>FIP-H&amp;HTools/HHTools_Mutant</factionIconPath>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Army-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="HHTools_Raider">
    <defName>HHTools_Mutant_Army</defName>
    <label>Raider Mutant Army</label>
    <description>A mixed raiding force of ghouls and super mutants operating together by common interest. Neither group is particularly welcome elsewhere in the wasteland, and their combination makes them considerably more dangerous than either would be alone. They prey on settlements and trade routes, relying on numbers, toughness, and the general instinct of most wastelanders to avoid mutants whenever possible.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.5</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.5</WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <factionIconPath>FIP-H&amp;HTools/HHTools_Mutant</factionIconPath>
  </FactionDef>

</Defs>