<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AncientGravReactor.description>An ancient generator powered by a reactor core. Once capable of producing massive amounts of power, it has now fallen into disrepair. The containment shield is leaking, causing toxic fallout to blanket the whole region.

Hack or destroy the reactor to obtain the core. Be warned, it may explode if damaged.</AncientGravReactor.description>
  <AncientGravReactor.label>ancient reactor</AncientGravReactor.label>
  <FuelOptimizer.description>A control unit that synchronizes the Hellion reactor with its VTOL thrust systems. It reduces the fuel needed for Hellion flight.

One Hellion can support two fuel regulators.</FuelOptimizer.description>
  <FuelOptimizer.label>fuel regulator</FuelOptimizer.label>
  <GravAnchor.description>Prevents the local map from being destroyed during a Hellion launch.

Mooring masts stabilize the launch zone around the aircraft and keep the surrounding settlement intact during departure. They cannot be constructed on the Hellion itself, because doing so would prevent takeoff entirely.</GravAnchor.description>
  <GravAnchor.label>mooring mast</GravAnchor.label>
  <Gravcore.description>A compact pre-war reactor core recovered from prototype Hellion systems and related military hardware. It is useless by itself, but it can be integrated into advanced Hellion support equipment.</Gravcore.description>
  <Gravcore.label>reactor core</Gravcore.label>
  <GravcorePowerCell.description>A compact generator built around a salvaged reactor core, adapted to provide steady power for the Hellion's onboard systems.</GravcorePowerCell.description>
  <GravcorePowerCell.label>reactor-core power cell</GravcorePowerCell.label>
  <GravEngine.description>The pre-war reactor assembly at the heart of the Hellion. It sustains the aircraft's vertical lift envelope and powers the heavy systems needed for long-range atmospheric and orbital operations.

When launched, anything on deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map. Without a mooring mast, launching the Hellion will abandon your current map.

The Hellion was designed as an unfinished military prototype, requiring rare components, specialist fabrication, and a great deal of salvage to keep flying.</GravEngine.description>
  <GravEngine.label>Hellion reactor</GravEngine.label>
  <GravFieldExtender.description>A support assembly used to expand the Hellion's airframe. It increases the amount of deck plating the craft can carry and must be built near the Hellion reactor.

One Hellion can support up to six airframe extenders.</GravFieldExtender.description>
  <GravFieldExtender.label>airframe extender</GravFieldExtender.label>
  <GravlitePanel.description>A lightweight pre-war airframe panel used to assemble and reinforce Hellion components. It is durable, heat-resistant, and ideal for advanced aerospace construction.

Requires vacstone blocks, which can be obtained from orbital asteroids.</GravlitePanel.description>
  <GravlitePanel.label>airframe panel</GravlitePanel.label>
  <GravshipHull.description>An airtight armored hull section sized for the Hellion's frame. It seals the craft against vacuum exposure and locks directly into the underlying deck plating, so it can only be built as part of the Hellion.</GravshipHull.description>
  <GravshipHull.label>Hellion hull</GravshipHull.label>
  <GravshipShieldGenerator.description>A defensive projector that protects the Hellion by generating a short-lived repulsor screen against incoming rounds and mortar fire. Those inside the field can still shoot out.

It must be charged before use. One Hellion can support two shield projectors.</GravshipShieldGenerator.description>
  <GravshipShieldGenerator.label>Hellion shield projector</GravshipShieldGenerator.label>
  <LargeThruster.description>An advanced VTOL thruster with a heat-resistant vacstone liner. It greatly increases the Hellion's operational range. Thrusters require an unobstructed exhaust area free of large buildings and Hellion deck plating.

Requires vacstone blocks, which can be obtained from orbital asteroids.

One Hellion can support up to six heavy VTOL thrusters.</LargeThruster.description>
  <LargeThruster.label>heavy VTOL thruster</LargeThruster.label>
  <PilotConsole.description>A hardened flight console used to launch and pilot the Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</PilotConsole.description>
  <PilotConsole.label>cockpit console</PilotConsole.label>
  <PilotSubpersonaCore.description>A low-grade navigation core tuned for Hellion flight. It reduces the chance of an accident when flying the Hellion, though it cannot fully compensate for pilot error.

One Hellion can support up to two navigation cores.</PilotSubpersonaCore.description>
  <PilotSubpersonaCore.label>navigation core</PilotSubpersonaCore.label>
  <ShipChunk_Mech.description>A chunk of robot craft made of steel and salvaged airframe panels. It looks like it was torn free during re-entry or blasted off by heavy weapons.

Deconstruct it to obtain valuable resources.</ShipChunk_Mech.description>
  <SignalJammer.description>An electronic countermeasures suite that masks the Hellion's signature and helps it approach heavily defended landing sites.</SignalJammer.description>
  <SignalJammer.label>ECM suite</SignalJammer.label>
  <SmallThruster.description>A compact VTOL thruster that increases the Hellion's operational range. Thrusters require an unobstructed exhaust area free of large buildings and Hellion deck plating.

One Hellion can support up to four small VTOL thrusters.</SmallThruster.description>
  <SmallThruster.label>small VTOL thruster</SmallThruster.label>
  <VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>A small crate containing heavy uranium shells. Used by gauss artillery to reload. A crate is fed directly into adjacent Hellion artillery when it needs to be rearmed.</VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>
  <VGE_CopilotConsole.description>An auxiliary interface that allows a copilot to assist in launching and piloting a Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_CopilotConsole.description>
  <VGE_GaussGun.description>A compact electromagnetic cannon that launches dense uranium slugs at extreme velocities. Designed for local bombardment and medium-range interception, it can also target hostile orbital craft. Requires a linked targeting terminal with an operator to function. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_GaussGun.description>
  <VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.description>A massive reactor assembly that channels a salvaged reactor core into immense electrical output. Its reinforced coils can handle extreme load, making it one of the most potent power sources available for Hellion systems. Adjacent reactor-core power cells multiply the output by 15% each.</VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.description>
  <VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.label>reactor-core power coil</VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.label>
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>A heavy reactor package built for the largest Hellion frames and orbital support hulls. It sustains an enormous lift field, allowing massive aircraft to rise under their own power while operating near a planetary gravity well.

When launched, anything on Hellion deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map.

These oversized assemblies were intended for pre-war logistics craft and mobile aerospace platforms, and they demand immense fabrication capacity to keep operational.</VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>heavy Hellion reactor</VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>A compact reactor package adapted for a light Hellion. It generates the lift field needed for rapid vertical launch and short-range atmospheric insertion, but it is not suited to true interplanetary travel.

When launched, anything on Hellion deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map.

Often salvaged from scout craft, courier platforms, and other pre-war aerospace projects, these reactors are valued for their agility and relatively modest support requirements.</VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>light Hellion reactor</VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>
  <VGE_GravshipCapacitor.description>Stores large amounts of electricity for later use. Constructed in Hellion deck plating, Hellion capacitors do not obstruct movement.</VGE_GravshipCapacitor.description>
  <VGE_GravshipCapacitor.label>Hellion capacitor</VGE_GravshipCapacitor.label>
  <VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>A rapid-fire gun for point-defense use aboard the Hellion.</VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>
  <VGE_PilotBridge.description>An interface that allows launching and piloting a heavy Hellion. It draws power directly from the heavy Hellion reactor.</VGE_PilotBridge.description>
  <VGE_PilotCockpit.description>An interface that allows launching and piloting a light Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_PilotCockpit.description>
  <VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>A specialized defensive turret built exclusively for the Hellion. It intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its protective radius, but cannot engage ground targets. Interception chance scales with the target's velocity.</VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>
  <VGE_SolarPanelling.description>Produces electricity from sunlight. Does not work in darkness or under artificial light. It does not obstruct movement or provide cover, but it can only be constructed on Hellion deck plating.</VGE_SolarPanelling.description>
  <VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>A control station dedicated to operating a single Hellion artillery piece. Requires a crew member to manually aim and fire the weapon. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>
</LanguageData>