<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GravNausea.letterLabel>flight sickness</GravNausea.letterLabel>
  <GravNausea.letterText>While landing {GRAVSHIP}, {PILOT_nameDef} was forced into an emergency maneuver, resulting in an intense and prolonged deceleration. The experience has left your colonists badly motion-sick, though the effects will fade quickly.</GravNausea.letterText>
  <MinorGravshipCrash.letterLabel>rough Hellion landing</MinorGravshipCrash.letterLabel>
  <MinorGravshipCrash.letterText>While landing {GRAVSHIP}, {PILOT_nameDef} disengaged the Hellion reactor too early, causing the aircraft to drop several feet. Some structures aboard the Hellion have sustained light damage from the impact.</MinorGravshipCrash.letterText>
  <OverheatedGravEngine.letterLabel>overheated Hellion reactor</OverheatedGravEngine.letterLabel>
  <OverheatedGravEngine.letterText>While landing {GRAVSHIP}, {PILOT_nameDef} overworked the Hellion reactor, causing it to overheat. The reactor will take longer than normal to cool down. In the meantime, the Hellion cannot be launched.</OverheatedGravEngine.letterText>
  <ThrusterBreakdown.letterText>While landing {GRAVSHIP}, {PILOT_nameDef} overheated the Hellion's VTOL thrusters, frying valuable components. The thrusters will need to be repaired before they can be used again.</ThrusterBreakdown.letterText>
  <VGE_AstrofuelPipeRupture.letterText>During {GRAVSHIP}'s landing, a damaged fuel line sprayed astrofuel into the compartment. A stray spark set it ablaze in a sudden astrofire.</VGE_AstrofuelPipeRupture.letterText>
  <VGE_CriticalHeatSpike.letterText>While bringing {GRAVSHIP} down, the Hellion reactor's heat-control system malfunctioned, causing structural heat to surge far beyond safe limits.</VGE_CriticalHeatSpike.letterText>
  <VGE_GravTurbulence.letterLabel>airframe turbulence</VGE_GravTurbulence.letterLabel>
  <VGE_GravTurbulence.letterText>An unexpected lift-field vibration during {GRAVSHIP}'s descent shook every component on board, loosening bolts and wearing joints.</VGE_GravTurbulence.letterText>
  <VGE_OxygenLeak.letterText>While landing {GRAVSHIP}, a small breach opened in one of the oxygen tanks, venting the tank's entire supply. Until the leak is repaired, the oxygen tank will not work.</VGE_OxygenLeak.letterText>
  <VGE_VacBarrierFlicker.letterText>While landing {GRAVSHIP}, a power fluctuation caused one of the vac barriers to fail, depressurizing a small section of the Hellion. It will need to be repaired before it functions again.</VGE_VacBarrierFlicker.letterText>
</LanguageData>
