<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.description>The 钢铁兄弟会 operates under the strict tenets of the Codex, a sacred doctrine that demands the preservation and control of advanced technology. Under Elder Maxson, the Brotherhood has united the ideals of both the Outcasts' technological zealotry and Lyons' willingness to engage with outsiders - but on the Brotherhood's terms. Technology must be controlled, mutants and synths are abominations to be destroyed, and only through discipline and hierarchy can humanity be saved from itself. The Brotherhood is both shield and sword - protecting humanity while ensuring 危险 technology never falls into the wrong hands.</FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.description>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.label>法典至上</FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.label>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.description>Paladins are the Brotherhood's elite warriors, clad in power armor and wielding the most advanced weapons. They are the tip of the spear in any Brotherhood operation, trained to engage the most 危险 threats head-on. A Paladin's duty is to lead from the front, inspire their squadmates, and demonstrate the Brotherhood's martial superiority.</FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.description>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.label>钢铁圣骑士</FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.description>Lost Hills represents the original 钢铁兄弟会 - the purest interpretation of the Codex as written by Roger Maxson himself. Technology must be preserved at any cost, outsiders are never to be trusted, and the Brotherhood's bloodlines must remain pure. Isolation is strength. The wasteland may burn, but the Brotherhood will endure, guarding humanity's technological legacy until the world is ready to rebuild - on Brotherhood terms.</FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.label>永恒法典</FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.description>The Shield of the People represents everything the Lyons Pride stands for - warriors who protect the innocent and fight for those who cannot fight for themselves. They combine Brotherhood combat prowess with genuine compassion, serving as both s老旧iers and humanitarian workers.</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.label>人民之盾</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.description>莱昂斯长老教导说，如果技术不能为人民服务，那么技术就毫无价值。里昂骄傲队相信兄弟会不仅仅是收藏家和囤积者，他们还必须是保护者和建设者。尽管仍然受到法典技术智慧的约束，但他们拒绝其孤立主义。技术应该被保留，但也应该被用来帮助那些有需要的人。这片荒原不需要另一群技术囤积者；它需要守护者明白，拯救人类意味着真正帮助人类，而不仅仅是保护文物。</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.label>钢铁般的同情心</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.description>The Midwestern Brotherhood emerged from the wreckage of their crashed airships with a revolutionary understanding: survival demands adaptation. Unlike the isolationists at Lost Hills, the Midwest chapter actively recruits tribals, wastelanders, and even former enemies into their ranks. Technology still matters, but so does building an army capable of h老旧ing territory and protecting the people within it. The Codex is a guide, not a chain. Expansion is not corruption - it is evolution.</FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.label>钢铁先锋</FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.description>防御者是被遗弃的专家，他们将卓越的技术知识与战斗能力结合起来。他们负责从敌对势力那里获取技术，并确保先进设备不会落入不值得的人手中。他们对使命的奉献是绝对的。</FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.label>法典的捍卫者</FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.description>The Outcasts are the Brotherhood's purists - those who refused to compromise the Codex when Elder Lyons went soft. Technology is everything. It's not about helping wastelanders or building communities; it's about preserving humanity's technological legacy before fools destroy it all. The 老旧 World fell because people misused technology - the Brotherhood's sacred duty is to prevent that from happening again by controlling every piece of advanced tech in existence. Outsiders are liabilities at best, threats at worst. Only through absolute dedication to the mission can the Brotherhood fulfill its purpose.</FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.label>真正的法典</FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.label>
</LanguageData>
