<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.description>A Bruderschaft des Stahls ration crate containing preserved military meals, purified water, and nutritional supplements. Designed to sustain saltiers during extended operations in the harsh wasteland environment.</FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.label>Brotherhood Food Supply Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.description>A specialized Bruderschaft des Stahls uniform crate containing the distinctive gear worn by Elder Lyons' reformed Brotherhood. These uniforms represent the faction's humanitarian mission and their commitment to protecting the innocent.</FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.label>Lyons Pride Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.description>A Brotherhood Outcast supply crate containing the distinctive red and black uniforms worn by the purist faction. These uniforms symbolize their unwavering dedication to the original Codex and their mission to reclaim pre-war technology at any cost.</FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.label>Outcast Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.description>A sealed Bruderschaft des Stahls supply crate containing essential technological components, spare parts, and advanced materials. These resources are crucial for maintaining and upgrading their sophisticated equipment and installations.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.label>Brotherhood Tech Resource Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>A Bruderschaft des Stahls supply crate containing standard-issue uniforms, fatigues, and protective gear worn by regular Brotherhood personnel. Each piece bears the distinctive colors and insignia of the faction.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>Brotherhood Standard Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>A sealed Bruderschaft des Stahls weapon crate containing high-quality firearms and energy weapons used by their forces. The distinctive red and metallic finish bears the Brotherhood's emblematic cogwheel.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>Bruderschaft des Stahls Weapon Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>
</LanguageData>
