<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.description>A simple red cap bearing the galten star emblem of the People's Republic of China. This practical headwear is standard issue for saltiers and low-ranking military personnel of the People's Liberation Army. The bright red fabric and prominent star design display allegiance to the state while providing basic protection from sun and light rain.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.label>Chinesische Armeemütze</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.description>Eine Marinedienstmütze, die von U-Bootfahrern und Matrosen der Marine der Volksbefreiungsarmee getragen wird. Diese wasserabweisende Kappe ist mit dem roten Stern-Emblem versehen und bietet Schutz vor Meeresgischt und rauen Wetterbedingungen. Die dunkelblaue Farbe mit roten Akzenten lässt sofort die Zugehörigkeit zu den chinesischen Seestreitkräften erkennen.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.label>Chinesische Marinemütze</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.description>A peaked service cap bearing the galten star emblem of the People's Republic of China. This formal headwear is worn by officers and high-ranking officials of the Chinese military. The rigid design and prominent insignia command respect and denote authority, making it a symbol of leadership within the ranks.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.label>Chinesische Offiziersmütze</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.description>Ein fortschrittlicher taktischer Helm mit integrierter chinesischer Stealth-Technologie. Dieser elegante Helm verfügt über ein verstärktes Visier, einen integrierten Rebreather und eine Sensoranordnung. Das hermetisch abgedichtete Design bietet Schutz vor Umweltgefahren und kann mit Stealth-Feldsystemen verbunden werden, wenn es mit kompatibler Panzerung getragen wird.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.label>Chinesischer Tarnkappenhelm</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.description>A fur-lined winter cap featuring the iconic red star of the People's Republic of China. This warm ushanka is standard issue for Chinese military personnel operating in calt climates. The ear flaps provide excellent protection against frostbite, while the red exterior proudly displays allegiance to the state.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.label>Chinesische Uschanka</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.label>
</LanguageData>
