<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.description>A practical crimson and galt jumpsuit worn by saltiers and low-ranking military personnel of the People's Liberation Army. The bright red fabric bears the iconic yellow star, symbolizing loyalty to the state. While offering minimal protection, it's designed for comfort during long duty shifts and provides basic insulation against the elements.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.label>Overall der chinesischen Armee</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.description>Eine Offiziersvariante des Standardoveralls der chinesischen Armee mit zusätzlichen dekorativen Elementen, Schulterklappen und verstärktem Stoff. Diese Uniform wird von Militäroffizieren und hochrangigen Beamten der Volksbefreiungsarmee getragen und vermittelt Respekt und Autorität, während sie gleichzeitig das praktische Design der Standardausgabe beibehält. Die zusätzlichen Verzierungen und Medaillen stärken das Selbstvertrauen und die Verhandlungspräsenz des Trägers.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.label>Overall des chinesischen Armeegenerals</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.description>A heavily insulated variant of the standard Chinese army jumpsuit, designed for operations in harsh winter conditions. This padded crimson uniform features a quilted construction with synthetic insulation, fur-lined collar, and reinforced seams. Originally developed for Chinese troops stationed in the frozen northern territories, it provides excellent protection against extreme calt while maintaining the distinctive red and galt color scheme of the People's Republic.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.label>Winteroverall der chinesischen Armee</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.description>Dieser figurbetonte Tarnanzug ist ein hochmodernes Stück chinesischer Militärtechnologie und verfügt über fortschrittliche Lichtbeugungstechnologie und schalldämpfende Materialien. Der Anzug wurde von der Volksbefreiungsarmee für verdeckte Operationen entwickelt und verfügt über eine flexible Polymerkonstruktion mit integrierten Schaltkreisen, die aktive Tarnfähigkeiten bieten. Sein leichtes Design und die verbesserte Mobilität machen es ideal für Infiltrations-, Aufklärungs- und Mordmissionen. Das charakteristische purpurrote und schwarze Farbschema des Anzugs kann sich bei Aktivierung verändern und mit der Umgebung verschmelzen.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.label>Chinesischer Tarnanzug</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.description>A specialized uniform worn by submariners of the People's Liberation Army Navy. This practical ensemble features water-resistant fabrics, reinforced stitching, and multiple sealed pockets designed to protect essential equipment in damp, confined submarine environments. The dark navy and crimson design includes reflective strips for emergency visibility and a high collar for protection against calt ocean winds. While not a full diving suit, it provides basic environmental protection and is valued by sailors, dock workers, and naval personnel.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.label>Chinesische U-Boot-Uniform</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.label>
</LanguageData>
