<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.description>Standard-issue Bruderschaft des Stahls fatigues. Made from a robust and durable material, these fatigues are worn by members of the Brotherhood during their daily operations in Appalachia.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.label>BoS Appalachia Fatigues</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.description>A pristine military dress uniform worn by Brotherhood infantry during formal occasions. The uniform bears the insignia of the Bruderschaft des Stahls and represents the discipline and order of the organization.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.label>BoS Appalachia Infantry Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.description>A vacuum-sealed asbestos jumpsuit covering the entire body. Its purpose is twofalt: it allows the user to actually operate the armor and protect soft tissue from moving parts inside the suit and heat. Unlike the BOS uniform, the Recon Armor provides decent protection on its own and is often used by Brotherhood agents on scouting missions or other situations where the clunky and loud power armor would draw too much attention.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.label>BoS B35C Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.description>A sturdy military coat worn by Brotherhood officers. The coat features the Brotherhood's insignia and is designed to withstand the rigors of combat while maintaining a professional appearance.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.label>BoS Battle Coat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.description>A leather flight jacket worn by Brotherhood pilots and Vertibird crew members. The jacket features the Brotherhood's gear and sword emblem and provides protection during flight operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.label>BoS Bomber Jacket</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.description>Standard-issue field uniform of the Bruderschaft des Stahls. These durable fatigues are worn by enlisted personnel and junior officers during daily operations and provide basic protection against environmental hazards.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.label>BoS Brotherhood Fatigues</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.description>Specialized medical uniform worn by Brotherhood field medics. The fatigues feature additional pockets for medical supplies and are designed to resist contamination during treatment of wounded personnel.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.label>BoS Brotherhood Field Medic Fatigues</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.description>Enhanced combat armor upgraded with Bruderschaft des Stahls technology. This armor retains the design of the original while incorporating improved protection and environmental sealing systems.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.label>BoS Reinforced Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.description>Ceremonial robes worn by Brotherhood Elders. These robes symbolize the authority and responsibility that comes with leading the Bruderschaft des Stahls in their sacred mission to preserve technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.label>BoS Elder Robes</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.description>Field uniform worn by Brotherhood Scribes assigned to research missions outside the safety of Brotherhood facilities. The uniform combines scholarly tradition with practical field requirements.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.label>BoS Field Scribe Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.description>A jumpsuit designed from the ground up for use in conjunction with the West Tek power armor frame. It is a form-fitting suit designed for maximum comfort and utility while operating the armor. Although it is not a requirement for operating the armor, it makes long-term use more comfortable and reduces chafing.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.label>BoS Jumpsuit</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.description>A formal dress uniform worn by Lancer Captains of the Bruderschaft des Stahls. The uniform features galt braiding and ceremonial shoulder boards, marking the wearer as an officer of the Brotherhood's air fleet.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.label>BoS Lancer Captain Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.description>Specialized reconnaissance armor worn by Brotherhood Outcast scouts and advance teams. This armor has been modified with enhanced mobility systems and stealth enhancements, featuring the distinctive Outcast markings and tactical modifications that reflect their more aggressive operational doctrine.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.label>BoS Outcast Recon Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.description>Functional robes worn by Brotherhood Outcast specialists and technical personnel. These robes feature the distinctive Outcast coloring and insignia, modified for field operations where scholars and engineers work alongside warriors in the pursuit of technological supremacy.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.label>BoS Outcast Scribe Robes</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.description>Lightweight tactical armor used by Brotherhood reconnaissance units. The Recon Armor provides solid protection while maintaining mobility and stealth capabilities, making it ideal for scouting missions and situations where full power armor would be impractical. Features advanced composite materials and integrated sensor systems.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.label>BoS Recon Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.description>Laboratory attire worn by Science Scribes of the Bruderschaft des Stahls. The clean, white coat is designed for work with gefährlich pre-war technology and experimental equipment.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.label>BoS Science Scribe Outfit</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.description>Hooded robes worn by Brotherhood Scribes during formal ceremonies. These robes represent the scholarly traditions of the Scribe order and their dedication to preserving technological knowledge.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.label>BoS Scribe Robes</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.description>Training uniform worn by Brotherhood Squires. This practical outfit is designed for combat training and education while marking the wearer's junior status within the Brotherhood hierarchy.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.label>BoS Squire Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.label>
</LanguageData>
