<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.description>A soft beret worn by Brotherhood detachments in Appalachia. Embroidered with the Brotherhood crest, it is used for identification and ceremonial duties by officers and specialized units.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.label>BoS Appalachia Beret</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.description>Standard-issue hood used by Brotherhood infantry for concealment and basic protection from the elements during patrols and tactical operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.label>BoS Appalachia Infantry Hood</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.description>A reinforced combat helmet issued to Brotherhood ground troops. Built to resist shrapnel and sEinkaufszentrum-arms fire, commonly paired with infantry armor on patrols and engagements.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.label>BoS B35C Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.description>Field hat worn by Brotherhood scribes and researchers on expeditions. It offers sun and light-weather protection while marking the wearer as part of the research and recovery cadre.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.label>BoS Science Field Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.description>Pilot helmet used by Brotherhood aircrews and vertibird crews, fitted with padding and basic communications gear to protect crew during flight and rotor operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.label>BoS Flight Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.description>A peaked cap worn by officers of lancer units to denote rank and authority within the Brotherhood during inspections and official duties.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.label>BoS Lancer's Captain Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.description>A tactical hood worn by Brotherhood Outcast reconnaissance specialists. This hood features enhanced optics integration, communication equipment, and environmental protection systems modified to Outcast specifications for extended field operations behind enemy lines.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.label>BoS Outcast Recon Hood</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.description>Lightweight hood favored by recon teams. Woven for low visibility and reduced glare to aid scouting, observation, and stealthy movement.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.label>BoS Recon Hood</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.description>Cap worn by science scribes to identify members of the Brotherhood's research corps. Scribes focus on study, salvage, and the preservation of prewar technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.label>BoS Science Scribe Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.description>A simple cap issued to squires and trainees. Squires are apprentices attached to knights and paladins, learning fieldcraft and Brotherhood traditions.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.label>BoS Squire Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.label>
</LanguageData>
