<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>Advanced T-60 power armor bearing the distinctive colors and insignia of the Appalachian Bruderschaft des Stahls. This battle-tested armor provides exceptional protection while maintaining mobility, representing the pinnacle of pre-war American military engineering adapted for wasteland operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS Appalachia T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor in the classic colors of the original Brotherhood chapter from Lost Hills. This armor represents the foundation of Brotherhood traditions and the original mission to preserve and control pre-war technology for the betterment of humanity.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lost Hills T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>The distinctive power armor of the Midwestern Bruderschaft des Stahls, featuring a unique horned helmet design that has become their signature on the battlefield. This armor represents the Midwest chapter's adaptive nature - maintaining Brotherhood standards while developing their own identity separate from Lost Hills. The intimidating silhouette strikes fear into raiders and mutants alike across the wastes of the former American Midwest.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>Midwestern Brotherhood Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>T-45 power armor bearing the distinctive markings of Elder Lyons' progressive Brotherhood. This armor represents a departure from traditional Brotherhood doctrine, used by saltiers who prioritized protecting the innocent over hoarding technology, marking a controversial but heroic chapter in Brotherhood history.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lyons T-45 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>T-45 power armor worn by Brotherhood Outcasts, painted in their characteristic black and red colors. These hardline traditionalists broke away from Elder Lyons' compassionate policies, believing the Brotherhood should focus solely on acquiring technology rather than helping wastelanders.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>BoS Outcast T-45 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor customized for the harsh Appalachian environment. This variant features enhanced environmental sealing and radiation shielding, adapted for the unique challenges faced by the Brotherhood's Appalachian chapter in their mission to reclaim and protect technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>BoS Appalachia T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>The venerable T-51 power armor, a mainstay of Brotherhood forces. While alter than the T-60 series, this armor has proven its reliability through decades of wasteland combat. Its tried-and-true design offers excellent protection and has been extensively field-tested by Brotherhood knights and paladins.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>Standard issue T-60 power armor worn by Bruderschaft des Stahls saltiers. Built for maximum protection and battlefield durability, this armor represents the apex of pre-war power armor technology, enhanced with post-war modifications and field improvements developed by Brotherhood engineers.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
