<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.description>The 10mm Pistol is a semi-automatic sidearm chambered for 10mm rounds. Favored for its reliability and stopping power, it is a common sight among wastelanders and pre-war security forces alike.</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.label>10mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.description>An improved version of the classic 10mm Pistol, featuring enhanced reliability and accuracy. Favored by elite wastelanders and pre-war security forces.</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.description>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.label>10mm Pistol MkII</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_10mm_Pistol_MkII.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.description>The 10mm SMG is a compact, fully automatic submachine gun chambered for 10mm rounds. Known for its high rate of fire and ease of use, it is ideal for close-quarters combat but sacrifices accuracy at longer ranges.</FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.label>10mm SMG</FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_10mm_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.description>The 12.7mm Pistol is a heavy, semi-automatic sidearm chambered for 12.7mm rounds. Its immense stopping power and armor penetration make it a favorite among wasteland enforcers, but its weight and recoil require a strong hand.</FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.label>12.7mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_127mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.description>The 12.7mm SMG is a powerful, fully automatic submachine gun chambered for 12.7mm rounds. Known for its high damage output and rapid rate of fire, it is devastating in close-quarters combat but suffers from heavy recoil and limited accuracy at range.</FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.label>12.7mm SMG</FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_127mm_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.description>The 14mm Pistol is a powerful sidearm chambered for 14mm rounds, offering exceptional stopping power and penetration. Rare and highly sought after in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.label>14mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_14mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.description>The .223 Pistol is a unique sidearm chambered for .223 rifle rounds, offering high velocity and accuracy. Its design is favored by marksmen and collectors.</FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.label>.223 Pistol</FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_223_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.description>The .223 Rangemaster is a precision bolt-action rifle chambered for .223 rounds. Favored by marksmen for its high accuracy and range, it is a reliable choice for hunting and long-range engagements in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.description>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.label>.223 Rangemaster Rifle</FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_223_Rangemaster.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.description>The .223 Rifle is a lightweight, semi-automatic rifle chambered for .223 rounds. Known for its accuracy and low recoil, it is a popular choice for both hunting and combat in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.label>.223 Rifle</FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_223_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.description>The .32 Hunting Rifle is a pre-war bolt-action rifle chambered for .32 caliber rounds. Known for its simplicity and reliability, it is a common weapon among wastelanders, offering decent accuracy and stopping power for medium-range engagements.</FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.label>.32 Hunting Rifle</FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_32_Hunting_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.description>The .357 Revolver is a classic, six-shot sidearm chambered for .357 Magnum rounds. Renowned for its reliability and stopping power, it is a favored weapon among lawmen and gunslingers in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.description>
  <FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.label>.357 Revolver</FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.label>
  <FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_357_Revolver.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.description>The .44 Magnum Revolver is a powerful, six-shot sidearm chambered for .44 Magnum rounds. Renowned for its high stopping power and intimidating presence, it is a prized weapon among wasteland hunters and enforcers.</FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.description>
  <FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.label>.44 Magnum Revolver</FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.label>
  <FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_44Magnum_Revolver.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.description>The 5.56mm Pistol is a rare, high-powered sidearm chambered for 5.56mm rifle rounds. Its unique design offers superior penetration and range compared to typical pistols, but with increased recoil and wear.</FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.label>5.56mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_556_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.description>The 9mm Pistol is a lightweight, semi-automatic sidearm chambered for 9mm rounds. Its low recoil and plentiful ammunition make it a popular choice for both civilians and wastelanders, though it lacks the stopping power of larger calibers.</FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.label>9mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_9mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.description>The 9mm SMG is a lightweight, fully automatic submachine gun chambered for 9mm rounds. Known for its ease of use and high rate of fire, it is effective in close-quarters combat but lacks stopping power and accuracy at longer ranges.</FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.label>9mm SMG</FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_9mm_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.description>A rare, limited edition BB gun crafted for the Abilene Kid. Distinguished by its unique markings and exceptional craftsmanship, it is prized by collectors and marksmen for its nostalgic value and precision.</FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.label>Abilene Kid LE BB Gun</FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.description>The AK-112 is a robust, pre-war assault rifle chambered for 5.56mm rounds. Known for its reliability and ease of maintenance, it remains a popular choice among wasteland survivors.</FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.description>
  <FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.label>AK-112 Assault Rifle</FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_AK_112_AR.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.description>All-American is a legendary marksman carbine renowned for its exceptional accuracy, reliability, and custom craftsmanship. Featuring a unique design and advanced optics, it excels at delivering precise, rapid bursts at long range, making it a prized weapon among elite marksmen and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.description>
  <FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.label>All-American</FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.description>A compact, fully automatic carbine chambered for 5mm rounds. Designed for military use, it offers a high rate of fire and excellent handling, making it ideal for close-quarters combat and suppressive fire.</FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.label>Assault Carbine</FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Assault_Carbine.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.description>A simple air-powered BB gun. While not lethal, it can sting and is often used for training or pest control. Not recommended for serious combat.</FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.label>BB Gun</FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_BB_Gun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.description>Big Boomer is a legendary, custom double-barrel shotgun renowned for its immense stopping power and rugged craftsmanship. Its reinforced frame and oversized barrels deliver devastating close-range blasts, making it a prized weapon among wasteland hunters and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.description>
  <FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.label>Big Boomer</FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.description>The Brush Gun is a lever-action rifle chambered for .45-70 Government rounds. Favored for its high stopping power and reliability, it is a popular choice among wasteland hunters and marksmen for taking down large game and armored targets.</FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.label>Brush Gun</FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Brush_Gun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.description>A double-barreled, break-action shotgun popular with caravan guards and traders. Its simple design makes it easy to repair and maintain, but it suffers from a slow reload and limited range</FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.label>Caravan Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Caravan_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.description>A rugged and powerful assault rifle of Chinese origin. It was widely used by Chinese forces during the Sino-American War, known for its high damage output and reliability in harsh conditions.</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.label>Chinese Assault Rifle</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Assault_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.description>The Chinese Pistol is a compact, semi-automatic sidearm chambered for 9mm rounds. Manufactured before the Great War, it is lightweight and easy to conceal, but suffers from low stopping power and questionable reliability.</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.label>Chinese Pistol</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Chinese_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_ChunkyBoi.description>A massive, custom heavy weapon designed for maximum firepower and intimidation.</FCP_Gun_ChunkyBoi.description>
  <FCP_Gun_ChunkyBoi.label>Chunky Boi</FCP_Gun_ChunkyBoi.label>
  <FCP_Gun_ChunkyBoi.tools.0.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_ChunkyBoi.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Citykiller.description>The Citykiller is a high-capacity, semi-automatic shotgun designed for urban combat. Its rapid fire and large magazine make it devastating in close quarters.</FCP_Gun_Citykiller.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Citykiller.label>Citykiller Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Citykiller.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Citykiller.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Citykiller.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Citykiller.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Citykiller.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.description>The Colt 6520 is a classic pre-war sidearm, renowned for its reliability and ease of use. Chambered for .45 rounds, it remains a favorite among wasteland survivors.</FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.label>Colt 6520</FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Colt_6520_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.description>The standard combat rifle is a rugged, semi-automatic rifle chambered for .45 ACP rounds. Reliable and versatile, it is a favorite among wastelanders for its balance of firepower, accuracy, and durability.</FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.label>Combat Rifle</FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Combat_Rifle_Standard.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.description>The Combat Shotgun is a semi-automatic, magazine-fed shotgun chambered for 12 gauge shells. Designed for military and law enforcement, it offers a high rate of fire and reliability in close-quarters combat, making it a favorite among wasteland enforcers.</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.label>Combat Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.description>An advanced version of the Combat Shotgun, featuring improved reliability, accuracy, and rate of fire. Favored by elite military units and wasteland enforcers.</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.label>Combat Shotgun MkII</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Combat_Shotgun_MkII.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.description>A classic lever-action rifle chambered for .357 rounds. The Cowboy Repeater is lightweight, reliable, and favored by marksmen and wanderers alike for its fast cycling and respectable accuracy.</FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.label>Cowboy Repeater</FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Cowboy_Repeater.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Deagle.description>The Deagle is a massive, semi-automatic pistol chambered for .50 AE rounds. Its intimidating size and firepower make it a symbol of status and strength in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_Deagle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Deagle.label>Deagle</FCP_Gun_Deagle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Deagle.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Deagle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Deagle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Deagle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Deliverer.description>Deliverer is a legendary, compact 10mm pistol renowned for its exceptional rate of fire and lightweight design. Favored by covert operatives, it features a custom suppressor and ergonomic grip, making it ideal for stealth operations and rapid engagements in close quarters.</FCP_Gun_Deliverer.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Deliverer.label>Deliverer</FCP_Gun_Deliverer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.description>Dinner Bell is a unique, custom pump-action shotgun prized for its exceptional reliability and stopping power. Featuring a polished finish and precision modifications, it delivers tight shot groupings and increased damage, making it the weapon of choice for seasoned wasteland hunters seeking both performance and style.</FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.description>
  <FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.label>Dinner Bell</FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.label>
  <FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.description>The DKS-501 is a pre-war bolt-action sniper rifle chambered for .308 rounds. Known for its exceptional accuracy and stopping power, it is a favorite among marksmen for long-range engagements.</FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.label>DKS-501 Sniper Rifle</FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_DKS_501_Sniper_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_G11_AR.description>The G11 is a revolutionary German assault rifle using caseless ammunition. Its high rate of fire and advanced design make it a rare but highly sought-after weapon in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_G11_AR.description>
  <FCP_Gun_G11_AR.label>G11 Assault Rifle</FCP_Gun_G11_AR.label>
  <FCP_Gun_G11_AR.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_G11_AR.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_G11_AR.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_G11_AR.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.description>The Gobi Campaign Scout Rifle is a legendary, custom sniper rifle awarded to elite marksmen. Renowned for its lightweight frame, exceptional accuracy, and rapid handling, it stands as one of the most coveted long-range weapons in the wasteland. Its unique craftsmanship and storied history make it a prized possession among sharpshooters and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.label>Gobi Campaign Scout Rifle</FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.description>A rugged, industrial nailgun adapted for both construction and combat. Its heavy frame and rapid-fire capability make it a formidable improvised weapon, favored by those who value versatility and raw stopping power.</FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.label>HH Tools Nailgun</FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.description>The HK-10 is a modern, compact submachine gun known for its reliability and high rate of fire. Favored by security forces and elite units for urban operations.</FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.label>HK-10 SMG</FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_HK_10_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.description>The Hunting Revolver is a large, single-action revolver chambered for .45-70 Government rounds. Designed for hunting big game, it delivers devastating power and accuracy, but its heavy frame and slow rate of fire make it unwieldy in close combat.</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.label>Hunting Revolver</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Revolver.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.description>A pump-action shotgun designed for hunting game. Favored for its rugged construction, high capacity, and reliability in the harshest wasteland conditions.</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.label>Hunting Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Hunting_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.description>The Jackhammer is a fully automatic, drum-fed shotgun capable of unleashing a torrent of shells in seconds. Rare and highly prized, it is a force to be reckoned with in any firefight.</FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.label>Jackhammer Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Jackhammer.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.description>A classic lever-action shotgun, prized for its fast cycling and reliability. Popular among ranchers and lawmen, it delivers solid stopping power and can be fired rapidly in skilled hands.</FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.label>Lever-Action Shotgun</FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_LeverAction_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.description>The Light Machine Gun is a pre-war, fully automatic support weapon chambered for 5.56mm rounds. Designed for sustained suppressive fire, it features a high-capacity magazine and a high rate of fire, making it ideal for pinning down enemies and providing covering fire in open combat.</FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.label>Light Machine Gun</FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Light_Machine_Gun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.description>Lincoln's Repeater is a legendary lever-action rifle, renowned for its exceptional craftsmanship and historical significance. With its polished finish and unmatched accuracy, this weapon stands as a symbol of freedom and precision, making it a prized possession among collectors and marksmen alike.</FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.description>
  <FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.label>Lincoln's Repeater</FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Lucky.description>Lucky is a legendary .357 Magnum revolver, distinguished by its immaculate chrome finish and ornate engravings. Renowned for its flawless action and uncanny accuracy, this weapon is favored by gunslingers who trust in both skill and fortune to carry the day.</FCP_Gun_Lucky.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Lucky.label>Lucky</FCP_Gun_Lucky.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Maria.description>Maria is a beautifully engraved 9mm pistol, adorned with intricate silver inlays and a pearl grip. Once belonging to a figure of legend, it combines elegance with deadly precision, making it a prized weapon for those who value both style and performance.</FCP_Gun_Maria.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Maria.label>Maria</FCP_Gun_Maria.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.description>A lightweight, semi-automatic carbine chambered for 5.56mm rounds. Designed for precision and medium-range engagements, it was favored by NCR marksmen for its accuracy and reliability.</FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.label>Marksman Carbine</FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Marksman_Carbine.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Minigun.description>The Minigun is a multi-barrel, rotary machine gun capable of firing 5mm rounds at an extremely high rate. Its devastating firepower makes it a favorite for heavy support roles, but its weight and bulk limit mobility.</FCP_Gun_Minigun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Minigun.label>Minigun</FCP_Gun_Minigun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Minigun.tools.0.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Minigun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_MkI_Avenger.description>An early model Avenger heavy weapon, known for its high rate of fire and reliability.</FCP_Gun_MkI_Avenger.description>
  <FCP_Gun_MkI_Avenger.label>MkI Avenger</FCP_Gun_MkI_Avenger.label>
  <FCP_Gun_MkI_Avenger.tools.0.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_MkI_Avenger.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.description>The MkII Avenger is a legendary minigun chambered in 5mm, renowned for its devastating rate of fire and rugged reliability. Favored by elite operatives, its advanced design and custom modifications make it one of the most formidable automatic weapons in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.description>
  <FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.label>MkII Avenger</FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.label>
  <FCP_Gun_OlPainless.description>Ol' Painless is a legendary hunting rifle, renowned for its exceptional accuracy and lightweight design. Passed down through generations, this rifle combines reliability with precision, making it a prized weapon for any marksman.</FCP_Gun_OlPainless.description>
  <FCP_Gun_OlPainless.label>Ol' Painless</FCP_Gun_OlPainless.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.description>A crude, homemade bolt-action rifle assembled from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While slow to fire and lacking in power compared to proper rifles, it is easy to produce and maintain, making it a common weapon among wasteland survivors.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.label>Pipe Bolt-Action</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.description>A crude, homemade pistol cobbled together from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While unreliable and lacking in stopping power, it is easy to craft and maintain, making it a common sidearm among the most desperate wastelanders.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.label>Pipe Pistol</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.description>A crude, homemade revolver assembled from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While unreliable and slow to reload, it is easy to craft and maintain, making it a common sidearm among wasteland survivors.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.label>Pipe Revolver</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.description>A crude, homemade semi-automatic rifle assembled from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While unreliable and inaccurate, it offers decent firepower for its simple construction, making it popular among raiders and settlers alike.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.label>Pipe Rifle</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.description>A crude, single-shot shotgun cobbled together from pipes and scrap. Devastating at close range but slow to reload, it's a favorite among desperate wastelanders who need stopping power on a budget.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.label>Pipe Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.description>A crude, long-barreled pipe rifle fitted with a makeshift scope. While nowhere near as accurate as a proper sniper rifle, it offers improved range for wastelanders who can't afford better equipment.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.label>Pipe Sniper Rifle</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.description>The Assault Rifle is a pre-war, fully automatic rifle chambered for 5.56mm rounds. Its distinctive drum magazine and robust construction make it a favorite for sustained fire in the wasteland, though it is heavy and unwieldy compared to more modern designs requiring the use of power armor.</FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.label>Power Armor Assault Rifle</FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Power_Armor_Assault_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.description>The R-91 is a pre-war, fully automatic assault rifle chambered for 5.56mm rounds. It was the standard-issue rifle for the U.S. Armed Forces before the Great War, known for its reliability and versatility in combat.</FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.label>R-91 Assault Rifle</FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_R91_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.description>Ratslayer is a unique, silenced varmint rifle equipped with a custom scope and lightweight frame. Renowned for its exceptional accuracy and stealth, it excels at eliminating small targets from a distance without drawing attention. Its precision engineering and quiet operation make it a favorite among marksmen and hunters alike.</FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.label>Ratslayer</FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.description>Reservist's Rifle is a rare, finely-crafted sniper rifle once carried by an elite military marksman. Lightweight and exceptionally accurate, it is prized for its long-range precision and quick handling, making it a coveted weapon among sharpshooters and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.label>Reservist's Rifle</FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.description>This pre-War, semi-automatic combat shotgun was designed for law enforcement and military use. Its high rate of fire and large magazine make it devastating in close-quarters combat.</FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.label>Riot Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Riot_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.description>A double-barreled shotgun with the barrels and stock cut down for easier concealment. Extremely deadly at point-blank range, but wildly inaccurate and short-ranged.</FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.label>Sawn-Off Shotgun</FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_SawnOff_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.description>The Scoped Hunting Rifle is a pre-war bolt-action rifle chambered for .308 rounds. Equipped with a scope, it is highly accurate and effective for medium to long-range engagements, making it a reliable choice for hunters and marksmen alike.</FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.label>Scoped Hunting Rifle</FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Scoped_Hunting_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.description>The Silenced 10mm Pistol is a semi-automatic sidearm chambered for 10mm rounds and fitted with an integral suppressor. Favored by assassins and covert operatives, it offers a balance of stopping power and stealth.</FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.label>Silenced 10mm Pistol</FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Silenced_10mm_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.description>The Silenced .22 Pistol is a lightweight, semi-automatic sidearm chambered for .22 LR rounds and equipped with an integral suppressor. Extremely quiet and easy to control, it is favored for stealth operations but lacks stopping power.</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.label>Silenced .22 Pistol</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.description>A lightweight, fully automatic submachine gun chambered for .22 LR rounds and equipped with an integral suppressor. Extremely quiet and easy to control, but lacks stopping power compared to larger calibers.</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.label>Silenced .22 SMG</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Silenced_22_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.description>A simple, single-barrel break-action shotgun. Cheap to produce and easy to maintain, but slow to reload and limited to one shot at a time.</FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.label>Single Shotgun</FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Single_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.description>The Trail Carbine is a lever-action rifle chambered for .44 Magnum rounds. Renowned for its ruggedness and accuracy, it is a favorite among wasteland scouts and hunters for its fast cycling and reliable stopping power.</FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.label>Trail Carbine</FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Trail_Carbine.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.description>Vance's 9mm SMG is a legendary submachine gun, expertly customized for rapid fire and superior handling. Its polished finish and unique engravings set it apart, while its enhanced accuracy and reliability make it a prized weapon among collectors and gunslingers alike.</FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.label>Vance's 9mm SMG</FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.description>The Varmint Rifle is a lightweight, bolt-action rifle chambered for .223 rounds. Originally designed for pest control and small game hunting, it is accurate and easy to handle, but lacks the stopping power of larger rifles.</FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.label>Varmint Rifle</FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Varmint_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.description>The Victory Rifle is a legendary, custom sniper rifle renowned for its exceptional stopping power and unique knockdown capability. Its reinforced frame and precision engineering make it a prized weapon among sharpshooters, able to deliver devastating shots at extreme range while reliably staggering targets.</FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.label>Victory Rifle</FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Vindicator.description>A powerful heavy weapon, designed for maximum suppression and area denial.</FCP_Gun_Vindicator.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Vindicator.label>Vindicator</FCP_Gun_Vindicator.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Vindicator.tools.0.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Vindicator.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Wanda.description>Wanda is a unique, custom combat shotgun from the Capital Wasteland. Distinguished by its green finish and reliability, it features a faster firing rate and lighter weight compared to standard combat shotguns. Favored by those who value speed and dependability in close-quarters combat.</FCP_Gun_Wanda.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Wanda.label>Wanda</FCP_Gun_Wanda.label>
</LanguageData>