<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace" MayRequire="vanillaquestsexpanded.ancients">
    <xpath>/Defs/VEF.Storyteller.QuestChainDef[defName="VQE_TheAncientLab"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Vault-Tec blacksite</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace" MayRequire="vanillaquestsexpanded.ancients">
    <xpath>/Defs/VEF.Storyteller.QuestChainDef[defName="VQE_TheAncientLab"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>This quest chain will have you explore sealed Vault-Tec blacksites and research vaults where pre-war special projects tried to create improved humans through classified FEV and forced-adaptation programs. Recover their surviving equipment, uncover what became of the dwellers trapped inside, and decide whether those experiments should ever begin again.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace" MayRequire="vanillaquestsexpanded.ancients">
    <xpath>/Defs/QuestScriptDef[defName="VQE_AncientLabComplex"]/questNameRules/rulesStrings/li[text()="questName-&gt;Supersoldier lab"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <li>questName-&gt;Vault-Tec blacksite</li>
    </value>
  </Operation>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace" MayRequire="vanillaquestsexpanded.ancients">
    <xpath>/Defs/QuestScriptDef[defName="VQE_AncientLabComplex"]/questDescriptionRules/rulesStrings/li[contains(text(),"mysterious broadcast")]</xpath>
    <value>
      <li>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)-&gt;[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] of [asker_faction_name], has intercepted a buried emergency broadcast carrying Vault-Tec security markers and references to a restricted human-improvement program. The signal appears to originate from a forgotten installation not far from our colony. 

[asker_nameDef] believes tracing the signal will reveal the location of a hidden Vault-Tec blacksite. Scouts report a ruined surface checkpoint with an exposed vault access descending into a sealed research complex below.

Inside must be the relay responsible for the transmission. If we intercept it on-site, we may be able to trace the rest of the network. The installation is also rumored to contain intact FEV processing equipment and experimental gene hardware worth reclaiming.

The blacksite appears abandoned, but old security systems and containment failures may still be active.</li>
    </value>
  </Operation>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace" MayRequire="vanillaquestsexpanded.ancients">
    <xpath>/Defs/QuestScriptDef[defName="VQE_AncientLabComplex"]/questDescriptionRules/rulesStrings/li[contains(text(),"unstable remote broadcast")]</xpath>
    <value>
      <li>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)-&gt;We've intercepted a fragmented emergency broadcast stamped with Vault-Tec security markers and references to a restricted human-improvement program. The signal appears to originate from a buried blacksite tied to pre-war FEV trials.

The site should still contain the relay responsible for the message. Intercepting it on-site may allow us to trace the rest of the blacksite network.

We should expect a dangerous expedition. Whatever remains inside could include dormant security systems, failed subjects, and equipment valuable enough to restart the project ourselves.</li>
    </value>
  </Operation>
</Patch>