<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VPEH_Hemosage.description>Blood sage revelations burn hemogen as ritual fuel, turning blood into pain, sacrifice, and predatory miracles.</VPEH_Hemosage.description>
  <VPEH_Hemosage.label>blood sage</VPEH_Hemosage.label>
  <VPEH_Hemosage.lockedReason>Hemogenic occultists only</VPEH_Hemosage.lockedReason>
  <VPEH_Hemosage.tooltip>Blood sages are occultists who feed revelations through blood rites and curse-loaded hemogen. Their rituals leech vitality, seed terror, and leave only nightmares in their wake.</VPEH_Hemosage.tooltip>
  <VPEP_Puppeteer.description>Idol puppeteer revelations break minds, enslave wills, and turn hollowed victims into extensions of the occultist.</VPEP_Puppeteer.description>
  <VPEP_Puppeteer.label>idol puppeteer</VPEP_Puppeteer.label>
  <VPEP_Puppeteer.lockedReason>Empire-born occultists only</VPEP_Puppeteer.lockedReason>
  <VPEP_Puppeteer.tooltip>Idol puppeteers are masters of possession and psychic domination. They hollow targets out, wear puppets like masks, and cling to life by pouring themselves into disposable thralls.</VPEP_Puppeteer.tooltip>
  <VPE_Archon.description>High priest revelations enthrone a leader who binds followers, drains rivals, and rules through presence and pain.</VPE_Archon.description>
  <VPE_Archon.label>high priest</VPE_Archon.label>
  <VPE_Archotechist.description>Blacksite savant revelations channel forbidden machine-thought, insanity, and weaponized neural overload.</VPE_Archotechist.description>
  <VPE_Archotechist.label>blacksite savant</VPE_Archotechist.label>
  <VPE_Chronopath.description>Doomwatcher revelations distort age, growth, and duration by clawing at the edges of time.</VPE_Chronopath.description>
  <VPE_Chronopath.label>doomwatcher</VPE_Chronopath.label>
  <VPE_Conflagrator.description>Ashcaller revelations weaponize fire, heat, and raw destructive energy in spectacular rituals.</VPE_Conflagrator.description>
  <VPE_Conflagrator.label>ashcaller</VPE_Conflagrator.label>
  <VPE_Empath.description>Mesmerist revelations soothe minds, break panic, and flood nearby followers with unnatural calm.</VPE_Empath.description>
  <VPE_Empath.label>mesmerist</VPE_Empath.label>
  <VPE_Frostshaper.description>Rimebinder revelations shape cold, ice, and entropy into barriers, traps, and killing frost.</VPE_Frostshaper.description>
  <VPE_Frostshaper.label>rimebinder</VPE_Frostshaper.label>
  <VPE_Harmonist.description>Omenweaver revelations trade fortune for misfortune, tilting the balance of events through ritual gamble.</VPE_Harmonist.description>
  <VPE_Harmonist.label>omenweaver</VPE_Harmonist.label>
  <VPE_Necropath.description>Gravecaller revelations spread dread, exploit corpses, and drag the dead back into service.</VPE_Necropath.description>
  <VPE_Necropath.label>gravecaller</VPE_Necropath.label>
  <VPE_Nightstalker.description>Nightstalker revelations reward ambush, darkness, and silent execution under a veil of unnatural shadow.</VPE_Nightstalker.description>
  <VPE_Nightstalker.label>nightstalker</VPE_Nightstalker.label>
  <VPE_Protector.description>Wardkeeper revelations shield allies, reinforce flesh, and drag researchers out of fatal danger.</VPE_Protector.description>
  <VPE_Protector.label>wardkeeper</VPE_Protector.label>
  <VPE_Skipmaster.description>Gatewalker revelations tear short-lived holes through space, moving people and objects by occult shortcut.</VPE_Skipmaster.description>
  <VPE_Skipmaster.label>gatewalker</VPE_Skipmaster.label>
  <VPE_Staticlord.description>Stormcaller revelations command lightning, blackout machinery, and turn weather into a weapon.</VPE_Staticlord.description>
  <VPE_Staticlord.label>stormcaller</VPE_Staticlord.label>
  <VPE_Technomancer.description>Relic engineer revelations wake dead circuitry, empower scavenged technology, and stitch occult insight into hardware.</VPE_Technomancer.description>
  <VPE_Technomancer.label>relic engineer</VPE_Technomancer.label>
  <VPE_Warlord.description>Battle medium revelations are selfish war rites that sharpen reflexes, speed, and killing instinct.</VPE_Warlord.description>
  <VPE_Warlord.label>battle medium</VPE_Warlord.label>
  <VPE_Wildspeaker.description>Totem speaker revelations call on beasts, brambles, and shrine-bound wilderness spirits for survival and defense.</VPE_Wildspeaker.description>
  <VPE_Wildspeaker.label>totem speaker</VPE_Wildspeaker.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronStealthField.description>Ενεργοποιεί ένα ενσωματωμένο πεδίο διάθλασης και για λίγο καθιστά τη μονάδα σχεδόν αδύνατη.</RobCo_AssaultronStealthField.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronStealthField.label>stealth πεδίο</RobCo_AssaultronStealthField.label>
  <RobCo_HeavyFlamer.comps.2.chargeNoun>βαρύ φλόγιστρο</RobCo_HeavyFlamer.comps.2.chargeNoun>
  <RobCo_HeavyFlamer.description>Ξοδεύει το αποθηκευμένο ναπάλμ για να προβάλει μια μεγαλύτερη, θερμότερη εμπρηστική έκρηξη.</RobCo_HeavyFlamer.description>
  <RobCo_HeavyFlamer.label>βαρύ φλόγιστρο</RobCo_HeavyFlamer.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeNukeThrow.description>Εκσφενδονίζει ένα μίνι πυρήνα σε ψηλό τόξο.</RobCo_LibertyPrimeNukeThrow.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeNukeThrow.label>μίνι πυρηνική ρίψη</RobCo_LibertyPrimeNukeThrow.label>
  <RobCo_LightFlamer.comps.2.chargeNoun>φλόγιστρο</RobCo_LightFlamer.comps.2.chargeNoun>
  <RobCo_LightFlamer.description>Ξοδεύει ένα φορτίο ναπάλμ για να ψεκάσει μια εμπρηστική έκρηξη από κοντινή απόσταση.</RobCo_LightFlamer.description>
  <RobCo_LightFlamer.label>ελαφρύ φλόγιστρο</RobCo_LightFlamer.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronRocketSalvo.description>Εκτοξεύει ένα χτύπημα κορεσμού με τρεις πυραύλους.</RobCo_SecuritronRocketSalvo.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronRocketSalvo.label>σάλβο πυραύλων</RobCo_SecuritronRocketSalvo.label>
  <RobCo_ExterminatorFlamer.description>Καταναλώνει μια χρέωση για να ψεκάσει μια εμπρηστική έκρηξη μεγάλης εμβέλειας.</RobCo_ExterminatorFlamer.description>
  <RobCo_ExterminatorFlamer.label>εξολοθρευτής φλόγας</RobCo_ExterminatorFlamer.label>
  <RobCo_NapalmFlamer.description>Ξοδεύει ένα φορτίο ναπάλμ για να ψεκάσει μια εμπρηστική έκρηξη.</RobCo_NapalmFlamer.description>
  <RobCo_NapalmFlamer.label>φλόγερ ναπάλμ</RobCo_NapalmFlamer.label>
  <WestTek_NightkinInvisibility.description>Trigger a Nightkin stealth field and briefly vanish from sight.</WestTek_NightkinInvisibility.description>
  <WestTek_NightkinInvisibility.label>nightkin invisibility</WestTek_NightkinInvisibility.label>
  <VFEE_BestowAcolyte.description>Commissions the Sergeant title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 13 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Sergeant or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowAcolyte.description>
  <VFEE_BestowAcolyte.label>commission: sergeant</VFEE_BestowAcolyte.label>
  <VFEE_BestowBaron.description>Commissions the Colonel title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 45 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Colonel or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowBaron.description>
  <VFEE_BestowBaron.label>commission: colonel</VFEE_BestowBaron.label>
  <VFEE_BestowCount.description>Commissions the General title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 45 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a General or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowCount.description>
  <VFEE_BestowCount.label>commission: general</VFEE_BestowCount.label>
  <VFEE_BestowFreeholder.description>Commissions the Member title on a selected pawn. That pawn receives 1 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Member or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowFreeholder.description>
  <VFEE_BestowFreeholder.label>commission: member</VFEE_BestowFreeholder.label>
  <VFEE_BestowKnight.description>Commissions the Lieutenant title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 21 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Lieutenant or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowKnight.description>
  <VFEE_BestowKnight.label>commission: lieutenant</VFEE_BestowKnight.label>
  <VFEE_BestowPraetor.description>Commissions the Captain title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 31 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Captain or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowPraetor.description>
  <VFEE_BestowPraetor.label>commission: captain</VFEE_BestowPraetor.label>
  <VFEE_BestowYeoman.description>Commissions the Private title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 7 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Private or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowYeoman.description>
  <VFEE_BestowYeoman.label>commission: private</VFEE_BestowYeoman.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalAddress.description>is giving a presidential address from the dais. If all goes well, every ranked participant will gain a small amount of Votes, and they will gain Votes for each ranked participant. If it goes poorly, the speech will cause social strain and lose Votes for each ranked participant. The outcome depends on their social abilities. Whitespring officials currently in the area will join the address and count as ranked participants.</VFEE_RoyalAddress.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalAddress.label>presidential address</VFEE_RoyalAddress.label>
  <Speech.description>Initiate a presidential address from the presidential chair. All colonists will come and listen. If it goes well, listeners will feel inspired, and gain respect for the speaker. If it goes poorly, the address will do social damage. The outcome depends on the speaker's social abilities.</Speech.description>
  <Speech.label>presidential address</Speech.label>
</LanguageData>
