<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AdvancedGravtech.description>Build advanced Hellion upgrades and support systems.</AdvancedGravtech.description>
  <AdvancedGravtech.label>advanced Hellion systems</AdvancedGravtech.label>
  <BasicGravtech.description>Rebuild the Hellion and use it to travel the planet. Without a mooring mast, launching the Hellion will abandon your current map.</BasicGravtech.description>
  <BasicGravtech.label>Hellion airframe</BasicGravtech.label>
  <StandardGravtech.description>Build more complex Hellion components and flight systems.</StandardGravtech.description>
  <StandardGravtech.label>Hellion systems</StandardGravtech.label>
  <VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>Construct astrofuel synthesizers that automatically convert oil into astrofuel for Hellion use.</VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>
  <VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>Unlock smaller variants of workbenches designed for the Hellion. Compact enough to fit into tight quarters without sacrificing essential functions.</VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.description>Build Hellion-exclusive furniture such as bunk beds, lockers, and medbay beds to keep crew comfortable and functional during long voyages.</VGE_GravshipLiving.description>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.label>Hellion quarters</VGE_GravshipLiving.label>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.description>Construct Hellion solar panelling, reactor-core power cells, and astrofuel generators to supply energy for Hellion systems.</VGE_GravshipPower.description>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.label>Hellion power</VGE_GravshipPower.label>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>Construct Hellion artillery and point-defense turrets to fight hostile craft in orbit or provide bombardment from the sky.</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>Hellion weapon systems</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>
  <VGE_HeatDissipation.description>Harvest structural heat generated during Hellion launches and dissipate it safely. Excess heat can be converted into usable power.</VGE_HeatDissipation.description>
  <VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>Harvest and store oxygen for use on the Hellion. Unlocks construction of vacsuits and other survival gear needed to operate in vacuum.</VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>
</LanguageData>