<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>Advanced T-60 power armor bearing the distinctive colors and insignia of the Appalachian 钢铁兄弟会. This battle-tested armor provides exceptional protection while maintaining mobility, representing the pinnacle of pre-war American military engineering adapted for wasteland operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS 阿巴拉契亚 T-60 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>T-51 动力装甲采用失落山脉原始兄弟会章节的经典颜色。这件盔甲代表了兄弟会传统的基础，以及保护和控制战前技术以造福人类的最初使命。</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS 失落山丘 T-51 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>The distinctive power armor of the Midwestern 钢铁兄弟会, featuring a unique horned helmet design that has become their signature on the battlefield. This armor represents the Midwest chapter's adaptive nature - maintaining Brotherhood standards while developing their own identity separate from Lost Hills. The intimidating silhouette strikes fear into raiders and mutants alike across the wastes of the former American Midwest.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>中西部兄弟会动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>T-45 power armor bearing the distinctive markings of Elder Lyons' progressive Brotherhood. This armor represents a departure from traditional Brotherhood doctrine, used by s老旧iers who prioritized protecting the innocent over hoarding technology, marking a controversial but heroic chapter in Brotherhood history.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lyons T-45 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>兄弟会流亡者所穿着的 T-45 动力装甲，涂有他们特有的黑色和红色。这些强硬的传统主义者脱离了里昂长老的富有同情心的政策，认为兄弟会应该只专注于获取技术而不是帮助废土人。</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>BoS 流放者 T-45 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>T-51动力装甲专为恶劣的阿巴拉契亚环境而定制。该变体具有增强的环境密封和辐射屏蔽功能，适合兄弟会阿巴拉契亚分会在回收和保护技术的使命中所面临的独特挑战。</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>BoS 阿巴拉契亚 T-51 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>The venerable T-51 power armor, a mainstay of Brotherhood forces. While 老旧er than the T-60 series, this armor has proven its reliability through decades of wasteland combat. Its tried-and-true design offers excellent protection and has been extensively field-tested by Brotherhood knights and paladins.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-51 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>Standard issue T-60 power armor worn by 钢铁兄弟会 s老旧iers. Built for maximum protection and battlefield durability, this armor represents the apex of pre-war power armor technology, enhanced with post-war modifications and field improvements developed by Brotherhood engineers.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-60 动力装甲</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
