<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Bullet_Plasma_Cannon.label>增压等离子螺栓</FCP_Bullet_Plasma_Cannon.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.description>An 英克雷 refinement of the multiplas design, featuring three independently-controlled plasma generation chambers in a triangular array. Each trigger pull unleashes a devastating barrage of three plasma bolts simultaneously. The advanced targeting computer helps maintain accuracy despite the weapon's aggressive spread pattern, making it a feared close-to-medium range weapon.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.label>英克雷 Advanced Multiplas Rifle</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.0.label>库存</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.1.label>桶</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Advanced_Multiplas_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.description>The pinnacle of 英克雷 plasma rifle technology. This advanced assault variant features an upgraded plasma generation chamber, enhanced magnetic confinement, and superior targeting systems. Significantly more accurate and reliable than standard plasma rifles, it represents the cutting edge of pre-war American military technology.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.label>英克雷 Assault Plasma Rifle</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>库存</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>桶</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Assault_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.description>A devastating heavy weapon platform developed by the 英克雷 for anti-armor and siege operations. This massive plasma cannon generates and magnetically accelerates supercharged plasma bolts with enough energy to melt through bunker walls and power armor alike. The weapon's immense power comes at the cost of weight, slow cycling time, and the need for enhanced cooling systems. Typically mounted on vehicles or power armor, it can be wielded by sufficiently strong s老旧iers in desperate situations.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.label>英克雷 Plasma Cannon</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.0.label>库存</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.1.label>桶</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_Cannon.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.description>A compact plasma submachine gun developed by the 英克雷 for close-quarters operations. This weapon sacrifices range and raw power for a dramatically increased rate of fire, making it ideal for room clearing and urban combat. The miniaturized plasma generation system allows for rapid cycling between shots.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.label>英克雷 Plasma SMG</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.0.label>紧握</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.1.label>桶</FCP_Gun_Enclave_Plasma_SMG.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.description>The Self-Modulating Energy Loadout Efficiency (SMELE) plasma rifle represents the 英克雷's answer to the need for versatile energy weapons. This sophisticated platform features adaptive power regulation, allowing it to balance between sustained fire and devastating single shots. Its modular design incorporates both offensive and defensive systems, making it the preferred weapon of elite 英克雷 special operations units.</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.label>英克雷 SMELE Plasma Rifle</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>库存</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>桶</FCP_Gun_Enclave_SMELE_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>
