<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.description>一种密封的预包装餐，由碎牛排和肉汁组成，这是美国美食的另一种主食。它的馅料非常丰富，而且非常美味，即使在战后的几个世纪里，它仍然是一道受欢迎的菜肴。 BIG BOY 餐点还配有 InstaMash！</FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.description>
  <FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.label>大男孩索尔兹伯里牛排</FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.description>战前保存完好的快餐产品。这是一个长方形的盒子，里面装满了通心粉和奶酪的混合物，这是战前美国美食的主食，因此在荒地上很常见。这似乎是Extra Cheezy 的变体，为您的膳食添加稍微更多的卡路里。</FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.label>Blamco 特级芝士味</FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.description>战前保存完好的快餐产品。这是一个长方形的盒子，里面装满了通心粉和奶酪的混合物，这是战前美国美食的主食，因此在荒地上很常见。</FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.label>布拉姆科原味</FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram.description>A tin can full of processed meat. Its main ingredients are pork and ham pressed into form and h老旧 together by gelatine. It’s filled with enough preservatives to be edible over 200 years after its fabrication and is a common and popular ration for s老旧iers in the NCR due to its high calorie content.</FCP_Food_Cram.description>
  <FCP_Food_Cram.label>补习班</FCP_Food_Cram.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.description>一种高品质的包装食品，专为生存情况而制造。虽然它永远不会腐烂，但如果放在外面，它仍然会变质。非常适合旅行。</FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.description>
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.label>补习低钠</FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.label>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.description>红色纸板盒里装着蜜饯苹果，这是一种流行的战前小吃，由 Dandy Boy 公司生产。产品中添加的糖和防腐剂数量惊人，确保其即使在 200 年后仍可食用。</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.description>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.label>丹迪男孩苹果</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.label>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.description>红色纸板盒里装着蜜饯苹果，这是一种流行的战前小吃，由 Dandy Boy 公司生产。产品中添加的糖和防腐剂数量惊人，确保其即使在 200 年后仍可食用。这个变种似乎有一个美味的焦糖壳！</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.description>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.label>丹迪男孩焦糖苹果</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.label>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.description>Pre-war snack cakes packed up in a s商场 box. Bite-sized pieces of cake with icing, these snacks are nearly unperishable and still serve as a sugary, sweet treat 200 years after their making.</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.description>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.label>花式小伙子小吃蛋糕</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.label>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.description>Pre-war snack cakes packed up in a s商场 box. Bite-sized pieces of cake with icing, these snacks are nearly unperishable and still serve as a sugary, sweet treat 200 years after their making. Be sure to look out for this version as it is the limited edition Buzzbite Flavor!</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.label>花式小伙子零食蛋糕 Buzzbite 口味</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.description>A s商场 green package with logo symbolizing a radioactive hazard sign. However, its contents are relatively harmless, apart from the omnipresent background radiation. The s商场 gum drops contained within are sweet and tasty and have endured the ravages of time quite well. A sugary snack for wasteland explorers.</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.description>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.label>口香糖滴剂</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.label>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.description>A s商场 green package with logo symbolizing a radioactive hazard sign. However, its contents are relatively harmless, apart from the omnipresent background radiation. The s商场 gum drops contained within are sweet and tasty and have endured the ravages of time quite well. A sugary snack for wasteland explorers. This popular pre-war flavor features the mountain battlefields of Anchorage Alaska.</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.label>安克雷奇北极风味口香糖</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.description>一盒冻干土豆泥粉。这种方便食品在战后两个世纪后被证明可以食用，并且可以在荒地的许多地方找到。与索尔兹伯里牛排最佳搭配！</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.description>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.label>即时混搭</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.label>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.description>一盒冻干土豆泥，添加培根以增加风味和口感！这种方便食品在战后两个世纪后被证明可以食用，并且可以在荒地的许多地方找到。与索尔兹伯里牛排最佳搭配！</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.description>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.label>Insta 捣碎培根</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.label>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.description>A can of beans stewed in a tomato sauce with chunks of bacon and salt-cured pork. A product from the Greasy Prospector company, Pork n’Beans were s老旧 in a tin can with a blue and red label and remain edible to this day.</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.description>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.label>猪肉豆</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.label>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.description>一罐用番茄酱炖的豆子，配上大块培根和盐腌猪肉。 Pork n’Beans 是 Greasy Prospector 公司的产品，装在带有蓝色和红色标签的锡罐中，直到今天仍然可以食用。从包装来看，这似乎是“Hot N Spicy Flavor”。</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.label>猪肉豆麻辣味</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.description>一盒春谷薯片。这是一种标志性的战前小吃，由薄薄的土豆片腌制并在油中烘烤而成。由于它们在战前非常受欢迎，它们仍然是荒原上常见的景象。</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.description>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.label>薯片</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.description>一管春谷薯片，微咸味。这是一种标志性的战前小吃，由薄薄的土豆片腌制并在油中烘烤而成。由于它们在战前非常受欢迎，它们仍然是荒原上常见的景象。</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.description>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.label>薯片 微盐</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.label>
  <FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.description>一种高品质的包装食品，专为生存情况而制造。虽然它永远不会腐烂，但如果放在外面，它仍然会变质。非常适合旅行。</FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.description>
  <FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.label>索尔兹伯里牛排</FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.description>一盒红、白、蓝的战前早餐麦片，因其高糖含量而闻名（并且臭名昭著）。虽然如此大量的糖肯定不健康，但它也确保了它们至今仍可食用。由于其作为主要早餐麦片的地位，在荒地中几乎到处都可以找到它。</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.description>
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.label>糖弹</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.description>红蓝相间的包装，里面装有 YumYum 制作的干全芥末蛋。尽管是煮熟的鸡蛋，里面充满了由蛋黄、芥末和蛋黄酱制成的糊状物，但它们仍然可以食用，但最好还是自行斟酌。</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.description>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.label>好吃好吃芥末蛋</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.description>A yellow and g老旧 package with dried whole deviled eggs made by YumYum with a hint of sour cream added flavor. Despite being hard-boiled eggs filled with a paste made from egg yolks, mustard and mayonnaise, they’re still edible for reasons best left to discretion.</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.label>美味芥末蛋酸奶油味</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.label>
</LanguageData>
