<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_Armored_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.description>A gas mask fitted with a reinforced metal skull plate. The combination of functional protection and terrifying aesthetics makes this a favored piece of headgear among raider elites.</FCP_Apparel_Armored_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Armored_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.label>Armored Raider Skull Gas Mask</FCP_Apparel_Armored_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Battle_Helmet.description>A basic leather helmet, with a young bighorner's skull affixed to the top for decoration. The skull has a red bullseye on it, most often worn by the fiends, a particularly vicious group of raiders originating from the Mojave wasteland. It doesn’t protect well, but looks quite intimidating, which is more important to most raiders anyway.</FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Battle_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Battle_Helmet.label>Raider Fiend Battle Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Battle_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Helmet.description>A basic leather helmet, with a young bighorner's skull affixed to the top for decoration. The skull has a red bullseye on it, most often worn by the fiends, a particularly vicious group of raiders originating from the Mojave wasteland. It doesn’t protect well, but looks quite intimidating, which is more important to most raiders anyway.</FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Helmet.label>Raider Fiend Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Warrior_Helmet.description>A basic leather helmet, with a young bighorner's skull affixed to the top for decoration. The skull has a red bullseye on it, most often worn by the fiends, a particularly vicious group of raiders originating from the Mojave wasteland. It doesn’t protect well, but looks quite intimidating, which is more important to most raiders anyway.</FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Warrior_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Warrior_Helmet.label>Raider Fiend Warrior Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Fiend_Warrior_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Junkyard_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A makeshift power armor helmet assembled from salvaged parts. While not as protective as military-grade helmets, it's still far superior to conventional raider headgear.</FCP_Apparel_Junkyard_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Junkyard_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Junkyard Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Junkyard_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Mrfuzzy_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>An unusual power armor helmet that has been modified with a Mr. Fuzzy mascot theme. Despite its absurd appearance, it provides the same protection as standard raider power armor helmets.</FCP_Apparel_Mrfuzzy_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Mrfuzzy_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Mr Fuzzy Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Mrfuzzy_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Arclight_Helmet.description>A repurposed welding mask. It offers fairly good protection from the front but leaves the back of the head virtually unprotected. It encourages its wearer to storm blindly at the enemy, as retreating becomes a bad, and often fatal, idea.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Arclight_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Arclight_Helmet.label>Raider Arclight Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Arclight_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.description>Low-tech, homemade armour with a barbaric appearance. It varies in quality and appearance with most consisting of scrap metal plates melded into armor pieces reinforced by metal bars along with wires fastened together by leather straps.The heavy raider armor is usually reserved for leaders and others who bellow orders to the gang. While it protects a whole lot better than the other version, it is also bulky and heavy, severely impairing the wearers freedom of movement.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.label>Heavy Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.description>Low-tech, homemade armour with a barbaric appearance. It varies in quality and appearance with most consisting of scrap metal plates melded into armor pieces reinforced by metal bars along with wires fastened together by leather straps. The light version of the raider armor provides only basic protection but is less heavy than other variants. Not the best armor, but certainly better than nothing.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.label>Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.description>Low-tech, homemade armour with a barbaric appearance. It varies in quality and appearance with most consisting of scrap metal plates melded into armor pieces reinforced by metal bars along with wires fastened together by leather straps.This version offers slightly more protection than the lighter version, but still isn’t that great. Plus, it weighs a whole lot more</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.label>Sturdy Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.description>A piece of tattered clothing, wrapped up in some places with duct tape, a wide leather belt, and black combat boots. These clothes are often worn by raiders and provide barely any protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.label>Raider Badlands Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.description>A leather coat covered in an excessive number of rags, chains, and metal plates with pieces of rebar welded onto them. As far as raider armors go, this one protects fairly well, but in turn is quite heavy. Usually worn by raiders with (some) self-preservation instinct.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.label>Raider Blastmaster Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Helmet.description>Comprised of a firefighter's helmet worn on top of a gas mask, the blastmaster helmet does provide decent protection and is often covered with fire-retardant substances.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Helmet.label>Raider Blastmaster Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.description>A long leather duster worn by raider leaders and those who have survived long enough to earn some respect. Offers better protection than basic raider armor while maintaining an intimidating appearance.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.label>Raider Leather Coat</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.description>A crude leather outfit cobbled together from various animal hides and scraps. While offering minimal protection, it's lightweight and allows for quick movement - essential for hit-and-run raider tactics.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.label>Raider Leathers</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.description>A piece of tattered clothing, wrapped up in some places with duct tape, a wide leather belt, and black combat boots. These clothes are often worn by raiders and provide barely any protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.label>Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.description>A piece of tattered clothing, wrapped up in some places with duct tape, a wide leather belt, and black combat boots. These clothes are often worn by raiders and provide barely any protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.label>Raider Painspike Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.description>A crude suit of power armor cobbled together from scavenged parts, rusted plating, and salvaged T-45 components. While it offers decent protection for a wastelander, it lacks the refinement and reliability of proper military power armor. The makeshift construction leaves gaps in coverage, and the improvised repairs make it noticeably heavier and more cumbersome than its pre-war counterparts. Still, in the wasteland, any power armor is better than none.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.label>Raider Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A power armor helmet that has been crudely modified by raiders. The internal systems barely function, but it still provides excellent protection against most threats.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Raider Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Psycho_Tic_Helmet.description>A leather skull cap with goggles and handlebars jutting out of the sides of the head. It is not very protective, and its main use is intimidation.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Psycho_Tic_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Psycho_Tic_Helmet.label>Raider Psycho-Tic Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Psycho_Tic_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.description>This archaic armor consists of metal chaps and a leather plate of sorts worn on the left shoulder. It leaves the shoulders of its wearer bare and unprotected. Most raiders care little about that though, as its primary use is intimidation of the foe.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.label>Raider Sadist Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.description>Makeshift armor constructed from scavenged tire rubber and metal scraps. The thick rubber provides decent protection against blunt impacts while remaining surprisingly flexible. Popular among raiders who value mobility over heavy protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.label>Raider Tire Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Wastehound_Helmet.description>A helmet constructed of several pieces of heavy burlap crudely stitched together. It also includes eye protection that looks like it was torn from a gas mask and tufts of hair. Not very potent armor, but it does intimidate the foe quite well.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Wastehound_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Wastehound_Helmet.label>Raider Wastehound Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Wastehound_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Rusty_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.description>A weathered gas mask with a corroded skull plate attached. Despite its deteriorated condition, it still provides adequate protection and maintains the intimidating raider aesthetic.</FCP_Apparel_Rusty_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Rusty_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.label>Rusty Raider Skull Gas Mask</FCP_Apparel_Rusty_Raider_Skull_Gas_Mask.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Sack_Hood.description>A simple hood often worn by raiders. It provides barely any protection against bullets but is (barely) better than no helmet at all.</FCP_Apparel_Sack_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Sack_Hood.label>Sack Hood</FCP_Apparel_Sack_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.description>A more refined raider power armor variant favored by the Scabbers gang. Built from better-maintained salvage and reinforced with additional scrap plating, it offers improved protection while maintaining the characteristic ramshackle appearance. The Scabbers take pride in their armor's intimidating spikes and rust-stained panels, wearing them as badges of honor. Despite being heavier than standard raider power armor, it provides noticeably better protection against the dangers of the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.label>Scabber Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A heavily corroded power armor helmet covered in rust and decay. Despite its deteriorated appearance, the core structure remains solid and provides substantial protection.</FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Scabber Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.description>The pinnacle of raider power armor engineering, the Waster variant combines salvaged military-grade components with surprisingly competent craftsmanship. Though still crude by pre-war standards, it approaches the protection level of T-45 power armor while maintaining the brutal aesthetic raiders prefer. The heavy construction and layered plating make it a formidable sight on the battlefield. Waster bosses and elite raiders prize these suits above all other armor.</FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.label>Waster Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>A battle-worn power armor helmet showing signs of extensive use and makeshift repairs. While not pristine, it remains a formidable piece of protective gear.</FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Waster Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
</LanguageData>