<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>A RobCo Industries sentry bot armed with a tri-barrel minigun and Gatling laser, designed for sustained suppression of infantry and lightly armored targets. The sentry bot is RobCo's dedicated combat platform, built around a simple synthetic personality chip containing only combat routines. The Annihilator is the standard production variant of this line.</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>annihilator sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>A sentry bot carrying a combined full weapons suite: minigun, rocket launcher, flamethrower, and cluster grenade launchers. It is one of the most heavily armed autonomous units encountered in the wasteland. Its central processor contains a nanostructuring chip, suggesting it was used as a testbed for advanced nanotechnology programs before or after the war.</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>deathbot</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>A sentry bot variant equipped with an industrial flamethrower system and a reloadable fuel canister for extended operations. Originally designed for large-scale pest eradication and area denial, it is capable of sustained incendiary fire across a wide area. The Pestcontrol variant was marketed to agricultural and government clients before the war.</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>pestcontrol sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>A sentry bot variant configured for fortification assault and anti-armor operations. Its primary weapon system is a rack of high-yield rocket launchers suited to demolishing reinforced structures. It rides on a mecanum wheel base that allows movement across most terrain. Standard sentry bot armor and combat protocols are retained.</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>siegebreaker sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>
</LanguageData>
