<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RobCo_Collectron.description>A Protectron variant reprogrammed for resource collection and salvage. It was adopted by various post-war factions to automate the gathering of specific materials. The Collectron operates autonomously within a defined area and will defend its collection zone against interference.</RobCo_Collectron.description>
  <RobCo_Collectron.label>collectron</RobCo_Collectron.label>
  <RobCo_Constructron.description>A Protectron unit configured for construction and infrastructure work. It carries welding and assembly tool attachments in place of standard hand lasers and was deployed at pre-War building sites and industrial facilities. Standard threat response protocols remain active.</RobCo_Constructron.description>
  <RobCo_Constructron.label>constructron</RobCo_Constructron.label>
  <RobCo_Factotron.description>A Protectron variant programmed for factory and manufacturing tasks. It was designed to operate on assembly lines and production floors, performing a wide range of manufacturing sub-tasks with precision. Factotrons are among the less commonly encountered Protectron variants in the post-war wasteland.</RobCo_Factotron.description>
  <RobCo_Factotron.label>factotron</RobCo_Factotron.label>
  <RobCo_Protectron.description>A widely deployed pre-War utility and security robot manufactured by RobCo Industries. It features a large domed head with three optical sensors, dual hand-mounted laser emitters, and a head laser. Powered by a fission battery, the Protectron was used across offices, hospitals, and public facilities throughout the United States. It is slow and less capable in direct combat than dedicated military robots.</RobCo_Protectron.description>
  <RobCo_Protectron.label>Protectron</RobCo_Protectron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.description>A Protectron unit fitted with a heavy drill attachment in place of a standard hand laser, intended for mining and excavation work. It was contracted to pre-War mining operations for subterranean resource extraction. The drill arm makes it slower than a standard Protectron but gives it significant close-quarters capability.</RobCo_Utilitron.description>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.label>utilitron</RobCo_Utilitron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>drill</RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>
</LanguageData>
