<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RobCo_Assaultron.description>A bipedal combat robot manufactured by RobCo Industries for the United States military. It features an olive drab paint scheme with military markings, two claw arms for melee combat, and a head-mounted laser capable of firing a charged beam at range. Fast and aggressive, the Assaultron was designed for frontline assault roles. Some units were fitted with a stealth field generator, allowing them to cloak mid-approach.</RobCo_Assaultron.description>
  <RobCo_Assaultron.label>Assaultron</RobCo_Assaultron.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronDominator.description>A specialized Assaultron hunter-killer variant built around an integrated stealth-field emitter and a dedicated close-assault blade package. It gives up the standard head laser in exchange for faster cloaked approaches and more dangerous melee engagements.</RobCo_AssaultronDominator.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronDominator.label>Assaultron Dominator</RobCo_AssaultronDominator.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.description>A heavily modified Assaultron chassis built to resemble the legendary Sheepsquatch cryptid of Appalachian folklore. Larger than a standard Assaultron and fitted with an uprated head laser, it was likely constructed as an intimidation tool by whoever had access to a robotics workbench and a dark sense of humor.</RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.label>sheepsquatch</RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.description>An integrated Assaultron-pattern forearm blade optimized for rapid slashing and puncturing strikes at close range.</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.label>Assaultron blade</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.tools.0.label>Assaultron blade</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.description>A compact Assaultron-pattern head laser with a faster firing cycle than heavier beam projectors. This makes it more suitable for rapid engagements and close-quarters combat.</RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.label>RobCo Assaultron head laser</RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.label>
  <RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.description>A high-output head-mounted beam projector built around a long charge cycle and a large blast radius. The discharge produces significant heat and is most effective when fired from standoff range.</RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.description>
  <RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.label>RobCo sheepsquatch head laser</RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.label>
  <AncientExostriderRemains.comps.2.letterText>A crashed Vertibot lies here, its hull twisted and scorched. Pre-war technology and secrets may be hidden within the wreckage.</AncientExostriderRemains.comps.2.letterText>
  <AncientExostriderRemains.comps.3.letterText>The Vertibot wreckage has been disturbed, scattering remnants of pre-war tech and memories of its final flight.</AncientExostriderRemains.comps.3.letterText>
  <RobCo_Cyberdog.description>A military robotic canine developed by RobCo Industries for the United States Army. It combines a preserved dog brain with a mechanical body, granting it canine instincts and a sonic bark weapon for ranged combat. Cyberdogs were deployed as scouts, guard animals, and combat companions alongside military personnel.</RobCo_Cyberdog.description>
  <RobCo_Cyberdog.label>cyberdog</RobCo_Cyberdog.label>
  <RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.description>A short-range acoustic projector used by RobCo security units. It emits a concussive sonic pulse that disrupts mechanical targets without relying on direct physical damage.</RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.description>
  <RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.label>sonic bark emitter</RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.label>
  <RobCo_Eyebot.description>A small hovering surveillance and broadcast drone manufactured by RobCo Industries. It uses whip antennas and integrated loudspeakers to transmit radio signals and pre-recorded broadcasts, and is equipped with advanced facial recognition systems. The Eyebot carries a light laser weapon for self-defense. Widely deployed by the Enclave for propaganda and reconnaissance, it is fast and elusive but extremely fragile in direct combat.</RobCo_Eyebot.description>
  <RobCo_Eyebot.label>Eyebot</RobCo_Eyebot.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotCrashed.description>The remains of a Vertibot — a pre-War military VTOL drone — brought down and no longer capable of flight. Despite its condition, onboard weapon systems and automated defense protocols remain partially active. It will engage anything that enters its perimeter.</RobCo_EyebotCrashed.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotCrashed.label>crashed vertibot robot</RobCo_EyebotCrashed.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.description>An enhanced Eyebot built on the experimental Duraframe chassis. It features reinforced internal components for greater durability than a standard unit and carries a more powerful energy weapon. The most documented Duraframe unit, designated ED-E, was fitted with a Tesla cannon and carried sensitive Enclave research data across the wasteland for decades before being recovered.</RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.label>Eyebot duraframe</RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.label>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>A compact drone unit spawned and directed by the Hydra command platform. It carries a focused energy blaster and operates under slaved coordination from its parent unit. Individual Eye of Hydra units are lightly armored but attack in numbers from multiple angles simultaneously. Destroying the parent Hydra reverts them to basic autonomous attack protocols.</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>Eye of Hydra</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>A heavily modified Mister Gutsy-based platform designed to function as a drone command hub. The Hydra carries an integrated system for deploying and coordinating Eye of Hydra units, whose combat effectiveness is enhanced by a tactical aura broadcast from the central platform. Its own weapon array is substantial, and destroying it disrupts any drones it has deployed.</RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>Hydra</RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.description>A Mister Handy variant designed for childcare and domestic supervision. It is programmed with an extensive behavioral package covering infant care, hazard detection, etiquette, and disciplinary protocols. The Miss Nanny retains a laser arm for household defense and was marketed to pre-War families as a dedicated childcare solution.</RobCo_MissNanny.description>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.label>Miss Nanny</RobCo_MissNanny.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>A Mister Handy unit reconfigured for agricultural work. It is equipped with tool arms suited to planting, harvesting, and field maintenance, along with crop monitoring sensors. Sold to pre-War farming operations, the Mister Farmhand retains a laser arm for worksite defense.</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>Mister Farmhand</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>A militarized variant of the Mister Handy platform, commissioned by the United States Army. It replaces civilian tool arms with a plasma caster and flamethrower, and runs the Sergeant Major v1.0 personality package. The Mister Gutsy features heavier armor than a standard Handy and was deployed in combat zones including the Anchorage front.</RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>Mister Gutsy</RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.description>A hovering domestic servant robot produced by General Atomics International in partnership with RobCo Industries. It is equipped with three articulated arms that accept tool attachments including a buzzsaw, laser cutter, and flamethrower, along with three optical stalks. Its neural network allows near-sentient conversation, and a well-maintained unit is capable of autonomous operation for centuries.</RobCo_MisterHandy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.label>Mister Handy</RobCo_MisterHandy.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydraArray.tools.0.label>ripper</RobCo_GutsyHydraArray.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MissNannyBlaster.tools.0.label>manipulator arm</RobCo_MissNannyBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhandBlaster.tools.0.label>cattle prod</RobCo_MisterFarmhandBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsyArray.tools.0.label>ripper</RobCo_MisterGutsyArray.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandyBlaster.tools.0.label>sawblade</RobCo_MisterHandyBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <MechanoidTransponder.description>A pre-War transponder by RobCo Industries.</MechanoidTransponder.description>
  <MechanoidTransponder.label>RobCo Transponder</MechanoidTransponder.label>
  <NanostructuringChip.description>The depleted remains of a Sentry Bot fusion cell.</NanostructuringChip.description>
  <NanostructuringChip.label>depleted Sentry Bot Fusion Core</NanostructuringChip.label>
  <PowerfocusChip.description>The severed head of a broken Assaultron.</PowerfocusChip.description>
  <PowerfocusChip.label>scrap Assaultron head</PowerfocusChip.label>
  <SignalChip.description>Still functional parts of a Mister Handy unit thruster.</SignalChip.description>
  <SignalChip.label>salvaged Handy thrusters</SignalChip.label>
  <SubcoreBasic.description>civilian RobCo hardware.</SubcoreBasic.description>
  <SubcoreBasic.label>basic Circuitry</SubcoreBasic.label>
  <SubcoreRegular.description>Military-grade RobCo hardware.</SubcoreRegular.description>
  <SubcoreRegular.label>military-grade Circuitry</SubcoreRegular.label>
  <UnfinishedSubcore.description>unfinished RobCo robot parts.</UnfinishedSubcore.description>
  <UnfinishedSubcore.label>unfinished RobCo Parts</UnfinishedSubcore.label>
  <MechGestator.description>A compact RobCo pod designed for civilian automation and light fabrication.</MechGestator.description>
  <MechGestator.label>civilian RobCo pod</MechGestator.label>
  <LargeMechGestator.description>A heavy RobCo pod built for military robotics and high-throughput fabrication.</LargeMechGestator.description>
  <LargeMechGestator.label>military RobCo pod</LargeMechGestator.label>
  <BasicRecharger.description>A compact RobCo recharger for basic mech maintenance and power recovery.</BasicRecharger.description>
  <BasicRecharger.label>civilian recharger</BasicRecharger.label>
  <StandardRecharger.description>A robust RobCo recharger for sustained mech upkeep and field deployment.</StandardRecharger.description>
  <StandardRecharger.label>military recharger</StandardRecharger.label>
  <SubcoreEncoder.description>A RobCo terminal used to encode and prepare subroutine cores for machine use.</SubcoreEncoder.description>
  <SubcoreEncoder.label>RobCo subroutine terminal</SubcoreEncoder.label>
  <SubcoreSoftscanner.description>A RobCo scanner used to inspect and evaluate subroutine patterns.</SubcoreSoftscanner.description>
  <SubcoreSoftscanner.label>RobCo subroutine scanner</SubcoreSoftscanner.label>
  <SubcoreRipscanner.description>A RobCo processing station for ripscanning and extracting machine intelligence modules.</SubcoreRipscanner.description>
  <SubcoreRipscanner.label>RobCo robobrain processing</SubcoreRipscanner.label>
  <SubcoreHigh.label>Human Brain</SubcoreHigh.label>
  <SubcoreHigh.description>This is a human brain... in a jar.</SubcoreHigh.description>
  <RobCo_Liberator.description>A small quadrupedal combat robot associated with Chinese-aligned factions in the Commonwealth. It is built around a single integrated laser weapon and four mechanical legs for rapid movement over uneven terrain. The Liberator is lightly armored but fast, and is typically encountered in large groups that attack simultaneously from multiple directions.</RobCo_Liberator.description>
  <RobCo_Liberator.label>liberator</RobCo_Liberator.label>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.description>Military-grade laser rifle integrated into a Chinese Liberator combat robot.</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.description>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.label>liberator laser rifle</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.label>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.tools.0.label>servo hands</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrime.description>A massive pre-War war machine jointly developed by RobCo Industries and General Atomics International for the United States Army. It stands approximately twenty meters tall and is equipped with twin head-mounted energy cannons and a supply of tactical nuclear bombs for destroying fortified positions. Originally designed to liberate Anchorage from Chinese forces, it was never deployed before the Great War due to power supply failures.</RobCo_LibertyPrime.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrime.label>Liberty Prime</RobCo_LibertyPrime.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.description>A high-output ion beam projector based on the same long-charge head-laser architecture used by the Sheepsquatch platform. It is built for devastating standoff shots while Liberty Prime reserves its dedicated launch system for mini-nuke throws.</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.label>liberty prime ion laser</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_BallisticAuto.label>ballistic auto burst</RobCo_Bullet_BallisticAuto.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserMedium.label>medium-beam laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserMedium.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimePulse.label>liberty prime pulse</RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimePulse.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronRocket.label>securitron rocket</RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronRocket.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_WarMachinePulse.label>war machine pulse</RobCo_Bullet_WarMachinePulse.label>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.description>A platinum data storage chip recovered from a sealed RobCo management vault. It contains a pre-War RobCo operating system package and is valuable far beyond its weight in metal.</RobCo_PlatinumChip.description>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.label>platinum chip</RobCo_PlatinumChip.label>
  <RobCo_Collectron.description>A Protectron variant reprogrammed for resource collection and salvage. It was adopted by various post-war factions to automate the gathering of specific materials. The Collectron operates autonomously within a defined area and will defend its collection zone against interference.</RobCo_Collectron.description>
  <RobCo_Collectron.label>collectron</RobCo_Collectron.label>
  <RobCo_Constructron.description>A Protectron unit configured for construction and infrastructure work. It carries welding and assembly tool attachments in place of standard hand lasers and was deployed at pre-War building sites and industrial facilities. Standard threat response protocols remain active.</RobCo_Constructron.description>
  <RobCo_Constructron.label>constructron</RobCo_Constructron.label>
  <RobCo_Factotron.description>A Protectron variant programmed for factory and manufacturing tasks. It was designed to operate on assembly lines and production floors, performing a wide range of manufacturing sub-tasks with precision. Factotrons are among the less commonly encountered Protectron variants in the post-war wasteland.</RobCo_Factotron.description>
  <RobCo_Factotron.label>factotron</RobCo_Factotron.label>
  <RobCo_Protectron.description>A widely deployed pre-War utility and security robot manufactured by RobCo Industries. It features a large domed head with three optical sensors, dual hand-mounted laser emitters, and a head laser. Powered by a fission battery, the Protectron was used across offices, hospitals, and public facilities throughout the United States. It is slow and less capable in direct combat than dedicated military robots.</RobCo_Protectron.description>
  <RobCo_Protectron.label>Protectron</RobCo_Protectron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.description>A Protectron unit fitted with a heavy drill attachment in place of a standard hand laser, intended for mining and excavation work. It was contracted to pre-War mining operations for subterranean resource extraction. The drill arm makes it slower than a standard Protectron but gives it significant close-quarters capability.</RobCo_Utilitron.description>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.label>utilitron</RobCo_Utilitron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>drill</RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.description>Broken pieces of an Eyebot. A mechanic can study these parts to help unlock higher tiers of RobCo research.</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.description>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.label>broken Eyebot frame</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.label>
  <RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.description>Further boosts the performance of the comms console.</RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.description>
  <RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.label>RobCo antenna</RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.label>
  <RobCo_CommsConsole.description>Comms console with RobCo bossgroup functionality.</RobCo_CommsConsole.description>
  <RobCo_CommsConsole.label>RobCo comms console</RobCo_CommsConsole.label>
  <RobCo_MechbandDish.description>Greatly boosts the performance of the comms console.</RobCo_MechbandDish.description>
  <RobCo_MechbandDish.label>RobCo dish</RobCo_MechbandDish.label>
  <RobCo_Receiver.description>Boosts the performance of the comms console.</RobCo_Receiver.description>
  <RobCo_Receiver.label>RobCo receiver</RobCo_Receiver.label>
  <RobCo_Robobrain.description>A large tracked combat robot produced by General Atomics International for the United States Army. It houses a living primate or human brain in a biomedical gel dome, wired directly into its control systems. The Robobrain is equipped with manipulator claws, an integrated laser weapon, and a Mesmetron stun device. Its biological brain component provides exceptional tactical intelligence and the ability to handle human-standard weapons.</RobCo_Robobrain.description>
  <RobCo_Robobrain.label>robobrain</RobCo_Robobrain.label>
  <RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.description>A precision syringe gun that fires metal needles loaded with toxic compounds. It is designed to injure the target on impact and deliver poison at longer range than most sidearms.</RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.description>
  <RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.label>RobCo syringer</RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.label>
  <RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.description>A Securitron unit whose behavioral limiters have failed, leaving it in a state of indiscriminate aggression. It retains full Mark II combat capability — Gatling laser, rocket launchers, and electroshock weapons — but without faction recognition, threat assessment, or de-escalation protocols. It attacks all targets within range without distinction.</RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.description>
  <RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.label>berserk Securitron</RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkI.description>A RobCo Industries PDQ-88b security robot built on a single heavy monowheel chassis. The Mark I carries a 9mm submachine gun in its right arm and displays a pre-War police officer image on its CRT screen face. It features a titanium alloy body and integrated auto-repair systems. Mark I units run basic combat software and are less effective in complex engagements than the upgraded Mark II variant.</RobCo_SecuritronMkI.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkI.label>Securitron mark I</RobCo_SecuritronMkI.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkII.description>A PDQ-88b Securitron running the Mark II software package, which brings its full weapons loadout online: X-25 Gatling laser, M-235 rocket launchers, and G-28 grenade launchers. Its CRT screen displays a soldier rather than a police officer. The Mark II was Robert House's intended combat-ready force for the defense of New Vegas and the Mojave.</RobCo_SecuritronMkII.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkII.label>Securitron mark II</RobCo_SecuritronMkII.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.description>Upgraded laser platform integrated into a Securitron Mark II with an onboard rocket battery.</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.label>securitron police laser</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.tools.0.label>high-voltage baton</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.description>Integrated ballistic repeater mounted on a Securitron Mark I security platform.</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.label>securitron ballistic repeater</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.tools.0.label>shock baton</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>A RobCo Industries sentry bot armed with a tri-barrel minigun and Gatling laser, designed for sustained suppression of infantry and lightly armored targets. The sentry bot is RobCo's dedicated combat platform, built around a simple synthetic personality chip containing only combat routines. The Annihilator is the standard production variant of this line.</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>annihilator sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>A sentry bot carrying a combined full weapons suite: minigun, rocket launcher, flamethrower, and cluster grenade launchers. It is one of the most heavily armed autonomous units encountered in the wasteland. Its central processor contains a nanostructuring chip, suggesting it was used as a testbed for advanced nanotechnology programs before or after the war.</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>deathbot</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>A sentry bot variant equipped with an industrial flamethrower system and a reloadable fuel canister for extended operations. Originally designed for large-scale pest eradication and area denial, it is capable of sustained incendiary fire across a wide area. The Pestcontrol variant was marketed to agricultural and government clients before the war.</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>pestcontrol sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>A sentry bot variant configured for fortification assault and anti-armor operations. Its primary weapon system is a rack of high-yield rocket launchers suited to demolishing reinforced structures. It rides on a mecanum wheel base that allows movement across most terrain. Standard sentry bot armor and combat protocols are retained.</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>siegebreaker sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>
  <AncientExostriderRemains.description>The remains of a Vertibot, a pre-war military transport aircraft. Scattered with pre-war tech.</AncientExostriderRemains.description>
  <AncientExostriderRemains.label>crashed Vertibot</AncientExostriderRemains.label>
  <AncientExostriderHead.description>The cockpit of a crashed Vertibot, filled with old controls and shattered glass.</AncientExostriderHead.description>
  <AncientExostriderHead.label>Vertibot cockpit</AncientExostriderHead.label>
  <AncientExostriderLeg.description>Landing gear from a Vertibot, twisted and scorched from the crash.</AncientExostriderLeg.description>
  <AncientExostriderLeg.label>Vertibot landing gear</AncientExostriderLeg.label>
  <AncientExostriderCannon.description>A heavy autocannon salvaged from a Vertibot wreck.</AncientExostriderCannon.description>
  <AncientExostriderCannon.label>Vertibot autocannon</AncientExostriderCannon.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachine.description>A massive autonomous combat platform combining heavy sentry bot firepower with an integrated mechanoid carrier system for deploying Liberator drones. The War Machine broadcasts a tactical coordination signal that enhances the combat effectiveness of nearby Liberator units. It is armed with a multi-burst pulse battery and reinforced war gauntlets for close-range engagement.</RobCo_WarMachine.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachine.label>war machine</RobCo_WarMachine.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.description>A sustained pulse battery integrated into the War Machine's torso hardpoints.</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.label>war machine pulse battery</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>war gauntlet</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_Electroshock.label>electroshock bolt</RobCo_Bullet_Electroshock.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserAssaultron.label>RobCo Assaultron head laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserAssaultron.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserAuto.label>auto laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserAuto.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserHigh.label>high-beam laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserHigh.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserLow.label>low-beam laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserLow.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserSheepsquatch.label>RobCo overcharged Assaultron head laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserSheepsquatch.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LiberatorLaser.label>liberator laser</RobCo_Bullet_LiberatorLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimeMiniNuke.label>liberty prime mini-nuke</RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimeMiniNuke.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_ScurrybotLaser.label>scurrybot laser</RobCo_Bullet_ScurrybotLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronLaser.label>securitron laser</RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SentryRocket.label>sentry rocket</RobCo_Bullet_SentryRocket.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SonicBark.label>sonic bark</RobCo_Bullet_SonicBark.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_Syringe.label>RobCo syringe</RobCo_Bullet_Syringe.label>
</LanguageData>