<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <RobCoQuestIgnore>This is none of my concern.</RobCoQuestIgnore>
    <RobCoQuestCourierEscapedLabel>Courier escaped</RobCoQuestCourierEscapedLabel>
    <RobCoQuestCourierEscapedText>The courier slipped away before you could finish the job. The platinum chip has vanished into the wasteland.</RobCoQuestCourierEscapedText>
    <RobCoQuestCourierWindow>Courier window: {0}</RobCoQuestCourierWindow>
    <RobCoQuestChipRecoveredLabel>Platinum chip recovered</RobCoQuestChipRecoveredLabel>
    <RobCoQuestChipRecoveredText>The courier is dead. The platinum chip is yours, and {0} will not forgive the theft.</RobCoQuestChipRecoveredText>
    <RobCoQuestBuyersFallback>its buyers</RobCoQuestBuyersFallback>
    <RobCoQuestTrailLostLabel>Courier trail lost</RobCoQuestTrailLostLabel>
    <RobCoQuestTrailLostText>You traced the shipment, but the trail went cold before your scouts could pinpoint the courier's route.</RobCoQuestTrailLostText>
    <RobCoQuestCourierInterceptedLabel>Courier intercepted</RobCoQuestCourierInterceptedLabel>
    <RobCoQuestCourierInterceptedText>Your scouts have located {0}. A temporary field camp has been marked on your world map. Kill the courier within seven days and recover the platinum chip before it changes hands again.</RobCoQuestCourierInterceptedText>
    <RobCoQuestOfferLabel>Platinum chips on the market</RobCoQuestOfferLabel>
    <RobCoQuestOfferText>A recently breached RobCo management vault has spilled one of the wasteland's most dangerous secrets back onto the market. A cache of platinum chips was recovered from the vault and sold through the Mojave Express to multiple buyers.

Each lead points to a different courier and a different faction sponsor. If you move quickly, you may be able to seize one of the chips before it disappears into another power bloc.

{0}</RobCoQuestOfferText>
    <RobCoQuestOptionLabel>Courier {0} of {1} and the Platinum Chip of {2}</RobCoQuestOptionLabel>
    <RobCoQuestVaultClearedLabel>Vault site cleared</RobCoQuestVaultClearedLabel>
    <RobCoQuestVaultClearedText>You leave the RobCo vault behind with its secrets stripped bare. Whatever remained in the facility is no longer anyone else's to command.</RobCoQuestVaultClearedText>
    <RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_CEO.ChipTitle>the CEO</RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_CEO.ChipTitle>
    <RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_CEO.Stage2LetterLabel>RobCo vault location recovered</RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_CEO.Stage2LetterLabel>
    <RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_CEO.Stage2LetterText>The dead courier carried access fragments tied to a RobCo executive archive. They point to a distant vault complex still crawling with corrupted Securitrons. Somewhere inside lies the wreck of Liberty Prime.</RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_CEO.Stage2LetterText>
    <RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_PRC.ChipTitle>the People's Republic</RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_PRC.ChipTitle>
    <RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_PRC.Stage2LetterLabel>PRC cache coordinates acquired</RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_PRC.Stage2LetterLabel>
    <RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_PRC.Stage2LetterText>The courier's route logs reveal a remote RobCo cache where Chinese Liberators were stockpiled in absurd numbers. The archive also indicates that a War Machine chassis was lost there during containment failure.</RobCoQuestBranch.RobCo_PlatinumBranch_PRC.Stage2LetterText>
</LanguageData>