<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>A bizarre archotech signal flare that calls a vertibird out of nowhere. Whatever intelligence answers it is willing to provide one miraculous extraction.</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>vertibird signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.1.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.1.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.2.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.2.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.3.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.3.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.4.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.4.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.5.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.5.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.6.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.6.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.7.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.7.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.8.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.8.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.9.label>pop signal flare</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.9.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>A single-use field transponder used to request Brotherhood vertibird pickup.</Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>Brotherhood field transponder</Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.1.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.1.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.2.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.2.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.3.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.3.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.4.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.4.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.5.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.5.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.6.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.6.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.7.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.7.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.8.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.8.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.9.label>call vertibird pickup</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.9.label>
  <CashRegister_CashRegister.description>A register desk for lounge service, dining tabs, and house accounts. It does nothing on its own, but it anchors the front-of-house operation.</CashRegister_CashRegister.description>
  <CashRegister_CashRegister.label>register desk</CashRegister_CashRegister.label>
  <CashRegister_Mech.description>An automated service terminal for mechanoid attendants. From here you can direct dining and front-of-house operations.</CashRegister_Mech.description>
  <CashRegister_Mech.label>autonomous service terminal</CashRegister_Mech.label>
  <Chocolate.description>A carefully wrapped cache of pre-war chocolate. Rich, sweet, and still decadent enough to anchor desserts and syrups.</Chocolate.description>
  <Chocolate.label>preserved chocolate</Chocolate.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineBlue.description>A premium Lucky 38 slot bank built for high-limit play, polished brass, and a hungry house cut.</HC_SlotMachineBlue.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineBlue.label>Lucky 38 high roller reels</HC_SlotMachineBlue.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineGreen.description>A House-era slot bank tuned for regular patrons and reliable nightly traffic.</HC_SlotMachineGreen.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineGreen.label>Lucky 38 standard reels</HC_SlotMachineGreen.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineRed.description>A reclaimed Vault 21 slot machine with a modest stake and a forgiving house edge.</HC_SlotMachineRed.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineRed.label>Vault 21 penny slots</HC_SlotMachineRed.label>
  <Lucky38_Syrup.description>A thick preserved sweetener rendered down for Lucky 38 kitchens. It fills the same role as sugar in sauces, desserts, and mixed drinks.</Lucky38_Syrup.description>
  <Lucky38_Syrup.label>syrup</Lucky38_Syrup.label>
  <MedievalVendingMachine.description>A low-tech kiosk for patrons that needs no electricity.</MedievalVendingMachine.description>
  <MedievalVendingMachine.label>service kiosk</MedievalVendingMachine.label>
  <Museums_Sign.description>A placard used to provide context and presentation for an exhibit piece.</Museums_Sign.description>
  <Museums_Sign.label>exhibit placard</Museums_Sign.label>
  <Museums_TourGatheringSpot.description>Designates the spot where patrons gather and wait for a guided gallery tour to begin. A room must have a tour start spot to count as an exhibit gallery.</Museums_TourGatheringSpot.description>
  <Museums_TourGatheringSpot.label>gallery tour gathering spot</Museums_TourGatheringSpot.label>
  <SmallHotSpring.description>A carefully worked hot spring built over a steam geyser. Its mineral waters offer meditative relaxation, modest recovery benefits, and a premium bathhouse amenity for up to four pawns at once.</SmallHotSpring.description>
  <SmallHotSpring.label>resort hot spring</SmallHotSpring.label>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.description>A long-range IFF beacon and traffic-control mast used by Brotherhood cells and trusted allies to advertise a safe vertibird approach, coordinate landings, and broadcast refueling availability.</Spaceports_Beacon.description>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.label>Brotherhood flight beacon</Spaceports_Beacon.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>A service terminal that sells aviation fuel to Brotherhood vertibirds and other authorized aircraft. It must be placed adjacent to a vertibird pad; once payment is verified, pumps inside the pad draw fuel from tanks on the same power network.</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>vertibird refueling terminal</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>An industrial processor that refines volatile feedstock and water into aviation fuel for Brotherhood vertibirds. It runs best with water access and turns surplus chemfuel into saleable flight stock.</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>aviation fuel processor</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.description>A chilled storage tank for processed aviation fuel. Keep it powered or the stock begins to evaporate away.</Spaceports_FuelTank.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.label>aviation fuel tank</Spaceports_FuelTank.label>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>A hardened landing pad with guidance lights, fueling hookups, and an encrypted transponder for Brotherhood vertibirds. Keep it powered and clear, and visiting patrols, quartermasters, traders, and allied passengers can touch down here.</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>Brotherhood vertibird pad</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>Designates a configurable point where visiting Brotherhood personnel, traders, and allied passengers will gather after landing. If no valid point is found, they will remain near their vertibird.</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>vertibird mustering point</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>
  <Therapist.description>Help colonists and patrons work through stress, trauma, and dependency in a private counseling suite.</Therapist.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyAwful.label>pungashine (awful)</VBE_AmbrandyAwful.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyBase.description>Also known as liquid sunshine, pungashine is a refined liquor distilled from ripe punga fruit. It is rare, expensive, and prized anywhere a properly stocked bar still exists.</VBE_AmbrandyBase.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>A gilded distillery of very delicate craftsmanship meant for aging pungashine must into a drinkable form.</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>pungashine still</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyExcellent.label>pungashine (excellent)</VBE_AmbrandyExcellent.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyGood.label>pungashine (good)</VBE_AmbrandyGood.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyLegendary.label>pungashine (legendary)</VBE_AmbrandyLegendary.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMasterwork.label>pungashine (masterwork)</VBE_AmbrandyMasterwork.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>Sliced and pressed punga fruit ready to ripen toward pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>pungashine mash</VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>Fully ripened punga liquor base, ready to be distilled into pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>pungashine must</VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyNormal.label>pungashine (normal)</VBE_AmbrandyNormal.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyPoor.label>pungashine (poor)</VBE_AmbrandyPoor.label>
  <VBE_Cigarettes.description>A small, rolled paper tube stuffed loosely with coyote tobacco chew. It offers a brief euphoria, mild stimulation, and the same stale wasteland smell that keeps smokers coming back.</VBE_Cigarettes.description>
  <VBE_Cigars.description>A thick cigar rolled from coyote tobacco chew and finished for a more expensive, more deliberate smoke. It carries a rough desert bitterness under the fancy presentation.</VBE_Cigars.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.description>A sharp, fizzy bottle of guarana finished with bitterness and a radioactive aftertaste. It hits hard up front and leaves a crash waiting on the other side.</VBE_EnergyDrink.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.label>guarana</VBE_EnergyDrink.label>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.description>A fine atomic cocktail, mixed precisely from multiple ingredients.</VBE_FineCocktail.description>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.label>fine atomic cocktail</VBE_FineCocktail.label>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>A miracle of mixology where every glass, garnish, and stir has been tuned into a gourmet atomic cocktail.</VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>gourmet atomic cocktail</VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.description>A lavish atomic cocktail mixed from a wide variety of ingredients and chilled to perfection before being served.</VBE_LavishCocktail.description>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.label>lavish atomic cocktail</VBE_LavishCocktail.label>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.description>Bright carrot flowers used to freshen brewed drinks and garnish wasteland dishes.</VBE_MintLeaves.description>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.label>carrot flowers</VBE_MintLeaves.label>
  <VBE_MintPlant.description>A stand of carrot flowers used for bright herbal garnish in teas and coffee blends.</VBE_MintPlant.description>
  <VBE_MintPlant.label>carrot flower patch</VBE_MintPlant.label>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>A hardy stand of coyote tobacco suited to the Mojave and other dry wasteland climates. Once cured down, the leaves become coyote tobacco chew for smoking, rolling, or trading.</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>coyote tobacco</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.description>Vacuum-sealed tins of pre-war instant coffee. Bitter, shelf-stable, and still potent enough to anchor every Lucky 38 breakfast service.</VBE_RawCoffee.description>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.label>instant coffee</VBE_RawCoffee.label>
  <VBE_RawTea.description>Dried pre-war tea leaves stored in a Lucky 38 pantry tin. They keep well and still steep into a proper serviceable cup.</VBE_RawTea.description>
  <VBE_RawTea.label>dried tea leaves</VBE_RawTea.label>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.description>A cured pouch of coyote tobacco chew. Dry enough to smoke, roll, or pack into richer blends, with the dusty bite wasteland smokers expect.</VBE_RawTobacco.description>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.label>coyote tobacco chew</VBE_RawTobacco.label>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>A simple atomic cocktail quickly mixed from a duo of ingredients.</VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>simple atomic cocktail</VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>
  <VBE_Soda.description>A sweet, fizzy bottle of homebrew sarsaparilla. It is more refreshing than nutritious, but a chilled bottle still feels like a pre-war luxury.</VBE_Soda.description>
  <VBE_Soda.label>homebrew sarsaparilla</VBE_Soda.label>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.description>An all-in-one homebrew sarsaparilla bottling unit. Syrup is mixed, carbonated, chilled, and dispensed into sterilized bottles for service.</VBE_SodaFountain.description>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.label>homebrew sarsaparilla fountain</VBE_SodaFountain.label>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.description>A thick, intensely sweet base for homebrew sarsaparilla. It is meant to be cut, carbonated, and bottled before serving.</VBE_SodaSyrup.description>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.label>homebrew sarsaparilla syrup</VBE_SodaSyrup.label>
  <VCE_Chirashizushi.label>mirelurk bowl (simple)</VCE_Chirashizushi.label>
  <VCE_DeepFriedSushi.label>deep fried lurk</VCE_DeepFriedSushi.label>
  <VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>A rare pre-war medical suspension repackaged for the Lucky 38 kitchen. When folded into food, aqua cura floods the body with emergency repair nanites that can drag a diner back from death.</VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>
  <VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>aqua cura</VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>
  <VCE_Futomaki.label>futolurk (lavish)</VCE_Futomaki.label>
  <VCE_Gunkanmaki.label>gunkanlurk (gourmet)</VCE_Gunkanmaki.label>
  <VCE_Nigiri.label>murkiri (fine)</VCE_Nigiri.label>
  <VCE_Norimaki.label>norilurk (simple)</VCE_Norimaki.label>
  <VCE_Oshizushi.label>oshilurk (gourmet)</VCE_Oshizushi.label>
  <VCE_RawSoybean.description>Tart wasteland cranberries. They can be eaten raw, cooked into preserves, or fermented into a thick table sauce.</VCE_RawSoybean.description>
  <VCE_RawSoybean.label>cranberries</VCE_RawSoybean.label>
  <VCE_RawSpices.description>A preserved blend of pre-war kitchen spices sealed away in a Lucky 38 pantry tin. Enough survives inside each can to brighten stews, sauces, and grills.</VCE_RawSpices.description>
  <VCE_RawSugar.description>Sealed packets of pre-war sugar recovered from old kitchens and pantry caches. It keeps indefinitely and still delivers the same quick rush of sweetness.</VCE_RawSugar.description>
  <VCE_RawWasabi.label>xander root</VCE_RawWasabi.label>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>A dense, intoxicating butter churned for indulgent Lucky 38 cooking. It spreads rich, hits hard, and turns any meal into a bad idea with excellent flavor.</VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>brahmin shroom butter</VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>
  <VCE_Soybean.description>A hardy cranberry bush cultivated for sharp red berries. The fruit cooks down into a rich sauce that stands in for the old-world fermented condiment chain.</VCE_Soybean.description>
  <VCE_Soybean.label>cranberry bush</VCE_Soybean.label>
  <VCE_SoyFermenter.label>cranberry sauce vat</VCE_SoyFermenter.label>
  <VCE_SoySauce.description>A rich cranberry reduction used as a dip, glaze, and salty-sweet finishing sauce for sushi and wasteland seafood.</VCE_SoySauce.description>
  <VCE_SoySauce.label>cranberry sauce</VCE_SoySauce.label>
  <VCE_Temaki.label>temlurk (lavish)</VCE_Temaki.label>
  <VCE_Uramaki.label>uralurk (fine)</VCE_Uramaki.label>
  <VCE_Wasabi.description>A patch of xander root prized for its pungent bite. When ground into paste it makes a strong condiment for seafood and rice dishes.</VCE_Wasabi.description>
  <VCE_Wasabi.label>xander root patch</VCE_Wasabi.label>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.description>A sharp paste made from ground xander root and used as a pungent condiment for sushi and other seafood dishes.</VCE_WasabiPaste.description>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.label>xander root paste</VCE_WasabiPaste.label>
  <VCEV_CookingBook.description>A battered cookbook packed with reclaimed recipes, ingredient notes, and pre-war kitchen tricks.

Once read, it will give the reader a new favorite ingredient or meal, then fall apart from one too many hands in the kitchen.</VCEV_CookingBook.description>
  <VCEV_CookingBook.label>wasteland cookbook</VCEV_CookingBook.label>
  <VendingMachine.description>A pre-War kiosk stocked for patrons, casino traffic, and idle lounge crowds.</VendingMachine.description>
</LanguageData>