<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- VEE_IceAge -->
  <VEE_IceAge.label>nuclear winter</VEE_IceAge.label>
  <VEE_IceAge.letterLabel>Nuclear Winter</VEE_IceAge.letterLabel>
  <VEE_IceAge.letterText>High-altitude ash and radioactive soot have choked the sky, plunging the region into a nuclear winter.

Flora and fauna are suffering as biomes slide toward their colder counterparts. Food and fuel become scarce, and wasteland factions grow more desperate by the day.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</VEE_IceAge.letterText>

  <!-- VEE_GlobalWarming -->
  <VEE_GlobalWarming.label>scorched summer</VEE_GlobalWarming.label>
  <VEE_GlobalWarming.letterLabel>Scorched Summer</VEE_GlobalWarming.letterLabel>
  <VEE_GlobalWarming.letterText>Heat trapped beneath a filthy radioactive haze has driven local temperatures to punishing levels.

Flora and fauna are suffering as biomes drift toward their hotter counterparts. Water dries up, forage fails, and every faction in the wasteland feels the pressure.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</VEE_GlobalWarming.letterText>

  <!-- VEE_PsychicRain -->
  <VEE_PsychicRain.label>temporal radstorm</VEE_PsychicRain.label>
  <VEE_PsychicRain.letterLabel>Temporal Radstorm</VEE_PsychicRain.letterLabel>
  <VEE_PsychicRain.letterText>An unstable old-world weather anomaly has churned a temporal radstorm into the atmosphere.

The storm lashes the land with strange glowing rain that twists flesh and time alike. Anyone left in the open will age at a frightening pace.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</VEE_PsychicRain.letterText>

  <!-- VEE_LongNight -->
  <VEE_LongNight.label>ashen skies</VEE_LongNight.label>
  <VEE_LongNight.letterLabel>Ashen Skies</VEE_LongNight.letterLabel>
  <VEE_LongNight.letterText>Orbital debris and black ash have smothered the sun, throwing the region into a long, ruinous twilight.

With the sky darkened and visibility ruined, wasteland factions take advantage of the confusion to raid, move, and settle scores under cover of gloom.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</VEE_LongNight.letterText>

  <!-- VEE_PsychicBloom -->
  <VEE_PsychicBloom.label>mutant bloom</VEE_PsychicBloom.label>
  <VEE_PsychicBloom.letterLabel>Mutant Bloom</VEE_PsychicBloom.letterLabel>
  <VEE_PsychicBloom.letterText>A surge of unstable spores and irradiated pollen has reshaped local plant life almost overnight.

The sky glows with strange color while mutant flowers spread through fields, roads, and ruins alike. Colonists feel oddly uplifted, but the overgrowth can smother your crops if left unchecked.

It can last anywhere between a few days and a season.</VEE_PsychicBloom.letterText>

  <!-- VEE_SpaceBattle -->
  <VEE_SpaceBattle.label>vertibird dogfight</VEE_SpaceBattle.label>
  <VEE_SpaceBattle.letterLabel>Vertibird Dogfight</VEE_SpaceBattle.letterLabel>
  <VEE_SpaceBattle.letterText>Several vertibirds and old-world gunships have engaged in a running fight above the region. Missed shots and burning debris can impact the ground and start fires.</VEE_SpaceBattle.letterText>

  <!-- VEE_AnimalPodCrash -->
  <VEE_AnimalPodCrash.label>animal cargo bot crash</VEE_AnimalPodCrash.label>

  <!-- VEE_ShuttleCrash -->
  <VEE_ShuttleCrash.label>vertibird crash</VEE_ShuttleCrash.label>

  <!-- VEE_Cargopodsweapons -->
  <VEE_Cargopodsweapons.label>cargo bots (weapons)</VEE_Cargopodsweapons.label>

  <!-- VEE_Cargopodsapparel -->
  <VEE_Cargopodsapparel.label>cargo bots (apparel)</VEE_Cargopodsapparel.label>

</LanguageData>
