<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>A compact drone unit spawned and directed by the Hydra command platform. It carries a focused energy blaster and operates under slaved coordination from its parent unit. Individual Eye of Hydra units are lightly armored but attack in numbers from multiple angles simultaneously. Destroying the parent Hydra reverts them to basic autonomous attack protocols.</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>Eye of Hydra</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>A heavily modified Mister Gutsy-based platform designed to function as a drone command hub. The Hydra carries an integrated system for deploying and coordinating Eye of Hydra units, whose combat effectiveness is enhanced by a tactical aura broadcast from the central platform. Its own weapon array is substantial, and destroying it disrupts any drones it has deployed.</RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>Hydra</RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.description>A Mister Handy variant designed for childcare and domestic supervision. It is programmed with an extensive behavioral package covering infant care, hazard detection, etiquette, and disciplinary protocols. The Miss Nanny retains a laser arm for household defense and was marketed to pre-war families as a dedicated childcare solution.</RobCo_MissNanny.description>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.label>Miss Nanny</RobCo_MissNanny.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>A Mister Handy unit reconfigured for agricultural work. It is equipped with tool arms suited to planting, harvesting, and field maintenance, along with crop monitoring sensors. Sold to pre-war farming operations, the Mister Farmhand retains a laser arm for worksite defense.</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>Mister Farmhand</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>A militarized variant of the Mister Handy platform, commissioned by the United States Army. It replaces civilian tool arms with a plasma caster and flamethrower, and runs the Sergeant Major v1.0 personality package. The Mister Gutsy features heavier armor than a standard Handy and was deployed in combat zones including the Anchorage front.</RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>Mister Gutsy</RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.description>A hovering domestic servant robot produced by General Atomics International in partnership with RobCo Industries. It is equipped with three articulated arms that accept tool attachments including a buzzsaw, laser cutter, and flamethrower, along with three optical stalks. Its neural network allows near-sentient conversation, and a well-maintained unit is capable of autonomous operation for centuries.</RobCo_MisterHandy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.label>Mister Handy</RobCo_MisterHandy.label>
</LanguageData>
