<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AnimusStone.description>A resonant cryptic stone studied by Whitespring researchers. It increases cryptid meditation focus and is often used in Enclave research facilities.</AnimusStone.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>cryptic stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.description>A stump left behind after a Mothman totem has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</ChoppedStump_Anima.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.label>chopped Mothman stump</ChoppedStump_Anima.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring cryptid forces. Whitespring operatives use these to amplify cryptid focus during ritualized study.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine used by cryptid researchers to focus meditation and study. These shrines strengthen cryptid-focused meditation for Whitespring operatives.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.description>Mysterious black eggs with a red glow. Tribal peoples find that these eggs grow around the base of a Mothman totem as they meditate. It seems to reflect some kind of strengthening of the totem's cryptic power.\n\nWasteland scientists have tried to study the phenomenon, but the eggs fail to hatch when observed too closely.\n\nAnimals refuse to eat Mothman eggs. Tribal stories say this is done out of respect and fear.</Plant_GrassAnima.description>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.label>Mothman eggs</Plant_GrassAnima.label>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.description>A Mothman totem used by Appalachia cultists to focus their meditation and worship.</Plant_TreeAnima.description>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.label>Mothman totem</Plant_TreeAnima.label>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.description>The remnants of a Mothman totem destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</SmashedStump_Anima.description>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.label>smashed Mothman stump</SmashedStump_Anima.label>
</LanguageData>
