<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <!--Slanter-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>HHTools_Mutant_Slanter</defName>
    <label>Gentile Slanter Tribe</label>
    <description>A tribe of S'Lanters — FEV-mutated raccoons that gained human-level intelligence and manual dexterity through pre-war experiments at a military research facility. The escaped subjects eventually settled and multiplied, naming themselves S'Lanter, meaning "Kindred," having long since forgotten their origins as animals. Fast, secretive, and highly territorial, S'Lanter communities organize around clan and kin, with customs passed down through story and ritual.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">1</WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <factionIconPath>FIP-H&amp;HTools/HHTools_Mutant</factionIconPath>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Numen-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>HHTools_Mutant_Numen</defName>
    <label>Gentile Numen Tribe</label>
    <description>A tribe of mutated Numen who show an unusual compatibility with the living world. Numen communities are quiet and contemplative, guided by customs shaped around an awareness of nature that most ordinary people do not share. Their origins are uncertain; what is clear is that they are not fully human in the conventional sense, and do not live as humans do.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Numen MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">1</WestTek_Xenotype_Numen>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <factionIconPath>FIP-H&amp;HTools/HHTools_Mutant</factionIconPath>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Critter-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>HHTools_Mutant_Critter</defName>
    <label>Gentile Mutant Tribe</label>
    <description>A tribal community made up of both S'Lanters and Numen who have shared territory long enough that their customs have grown together. They keep to the deep wastes and margins, far from the trade routes and settlements of larger factions. Strangers are met with wariness, and those who follow too closely into their territory tend to lose the trail and not find it again.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Numen MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.5</WestTek_Xenotype_Numen>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.5</WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <factionIconPath>FIP-H&amp;HTools/HHTools_Mutant</factionIconPath>
  </FactionDef>

</Defs>