<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola.description>A standard Nuka-Cola in its iconic bottle. Provides refreshment and a mild stimulant effect from the unique blend of ingredients.</FCP_Nuka_Cola.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola.label>nuka-cola bottle</FCP_Nuka_Cola.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Can.description>Nuka-Cola in a convenient aluminum can. Same great taste and energy boost as the bottled version, but easier to stack and transport.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Can.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Can.label>nuka-cola can</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Can.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cherry.description>A cherry-flavored variant of Nuka-Cola. The added fruit flavoring provides slight health benefits along with the signature energy boost. Particularly popular before the war.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cherry.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cherry.label>nuka-cola cherry</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cherry.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Classic.description>The standard Nuka-Cola that took the world by storm before the war. This sweet, carbonated beverage provides a quick energy boost and a small amount of joy. The distinctive rocket-shaped bottle is instantly recognizable.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Classic.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Classic.label>nuka-cola</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Classic.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cranberry.description>A tart cranberry-flavored Nuka-Cola variant. The berry tang balances the sweetness, giving a pleasant, slightly acidic bite favored in holiday marketing campaigns.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cranberry.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cranberry.label>nuka-cranberry</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Cranberry.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Dark.description>A rum-flavored alcoholic Nuka-Cola variant. Combines the stimulant effects of Nuka-Cola with alcohol, resulting in unique but potentially risky effects. Popular with adventurous drinkers.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Dark.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Dark.label>nuka-dark</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Dark.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Grape.description>A grape-flavored Nuka-Cola variant with a distinctive purple hue. The grape flavoring adds a sweet taste while maintaining the energizing properties of standard Nuka-Cola.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Grape.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Grape.label>nuka-cola grape</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Grape.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Ice_Cold.description>A chilled variant of Nuka-Cola. Cold, crisp, and refreshing — a pre-war marketing hit. Said to be made by a special cold-fermentation process that gives it a sharper fizz and a brisk, invigorating kick.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Ice_Cold.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Ice_Cold.label>nuka-cola (ice cold)</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Ice_Cold.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Orange.description>An orange-flavored Nuka-Cola with hints of citrus. The vitamin content from orange flavoring provides minor immune system benefits alongside the energizing effects.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Orange.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Orange.label>nuka-cola orange</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Orange.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quantum.description>The rare and potent Nuka-Cola Quantum, featuring a blue glow from mild radioactive isotopes. Provides a massive energy boost but with potential health risks. Highly sought after for its extreme effects.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quantum.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quantum.label>nuka-cola quantum</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quantum.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quartz.description>A rare desert-region variant with a distinctive clear appearance and enhanced formula. Provides superior refreshment and energy in harsh conditions.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quartz.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quartz.label>nuka-cola quartz</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Quartz.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Rum.description>A stronger rum variant of Nuka-Cola with higher alcohol content. Less carbonation, more kick. Provides significant intoxication with mild stimulant effects.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Rum.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Rum.label>nuka-rum</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Rum.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Twist.description>A citrus-twisted variant of Nuka-Cola with bright lemon-lime notes. Popular for its zesty tang and slightly higher perceived refreshment.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Twist.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Twist.label>nuka-twist</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Twist.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Victory.description>A premium pre-war variant celebrating military victories. Enhanced with additional stimulants and a superior taste. Commands a high price for its exceptional effects.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Victory.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Victory.label>nuka-cola victory</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Victory.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Wild.description>A wild berry flavored Nuka-Cola with an aggressive marketing campaign. The exotic fruit blend provides enhanced taste and a solid energy boost.</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Wild.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Cola_Wild.label>nuka-cola wild</FCP_Nuka_Cola_Wild.label>
  <FCP_Nuka_Fridge.description>A specialized cold fermentation cabinet used by Nuka-Cola bottling teams to create the Ice Cold variant. Works like a fermenting barrel but maintains cooler temperatures for a crisper product.</FCP_Nuka_Fridge.description>
  <FCP_Nuka_Fridge.label>nuka-cola fridge</FCP_Nuka_Fridge.label>
  <FCP_Nukashine.description>A powerful homebrewed alcoholic concoction made with Nuka-Cola as a base. Extremely potent and unpredictable, it can cause memory loss and blackouts. Only the desperate or foolhardy consume this regularly.</FCP_Nukashine.description>
  <FCP_Nukashine.label>nukashine</FCP_Nukashine.label>
</LanguageData>