<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Acolyte.description>Sergeant is a non-commissioned officer rank, responsible for leading squads, maintaining discipline, and ensuring the effectiveness of Enclave operations. Sergeants are often promoted from the ranks for their leadership and technical skills.</Acolyte.description>
  <Acolyte.label>sergeant</Acolyte.label>
  <Baron.description>Colonel is a senior officer rank, commanding regiments and managing large-scale strategic operations. Colonels are responsible for the training, discipline, and combat readiness of their units within the Appalachia Division.</Baron.description>
  <Baron.label>colonel</Baron.label>
  <Consul.description>Attorney General is a top-level legal and strategic advisor, responsible for interpreting Enclave law, overseeing military justice, and advising on matters of policy and command. This rank is reserved for the most trusted officers.</Consul.description>
  <Consul.label>attorney general</Consul.label>
  <Count.description>General is a high command rank in the Enclave, overseeing multiple regiments and directing major campaigns. Generals are responsible for strategic planning and the overall success of Enclave operations in Appalachia.</Count.description>
  <Count.label>general</Count.label>
  <Duke.description>Secretary is a senior administrative rank, coordinating logistics, intelligence, and support services for the Enclave's military branches. Secretaries ensure the smooth operation of all divisions and facilitate communication with high command.</Duke.description>
  <Duke.label>secretary</Duke.label>
  <Emperor.description>President is the supreme commander of the Enclave, holding ultimate authority over all divisions, personnel, and operations. The President embodies the ideals of the prewar United States and leads the Enclave in its mission to restore order and civilization.</Emperor.description>
  <Emperor.label>president</Emperor.label>
  <Emperor.labelFemale.label>president</Emperor.labelFemale.label>
  <Freeholder.description>Member is the entry-level rank for recognized personnel in the Enclave's Appalachia Division. Most earn this status through basic service, training, or acts that demonstrate loyalty to the Enclave's mission and values.</Freeholder.description>
  <Freeholder.label>member</Freeholder.label>
  <Knight.description>Lieutenant is a junior officer rank in the Enclave, typically commanding platoons or serving as executive officers. Lieutenants are entrusted with tactical leadership and the execution of critical missions in the field.</Knight.description>
  <Knight.label>lieutenant</Knight.label>
  <Praetor.description>Captain is a commissioned officer rank, responsible for leading companies and overseeing major operations. Captains are experienced leaders who coordinate missions and ensure the Enclave's objectives are met efficiently.</Praetor.description>
  <Praetor.label>captain</Praetor.label>
  <Stellarch.description>Vice-President is a national-level executive rank, acting as deputy to the President and overseeing the coordination of all Enclave operations across multiple regions. The Vice-President ensures the Enclave's mission is carried out with unity and precision.</Stellarch.description>
  <Stellarch.label>vice-president</Stellarch.label>
  <VFEE_Archcount.description>The Whitespring rank of general is reserved for senior commanders who have built the infrastructure needed to host inspections, briefings, and high-level visitors.</VFEE_Archcount.description>
  <VFEE_Archcount.label>general</VFEE_Archcount.label>
  <VFEE_Archduke.description>The Whitespring title of senator is commissioned to secretaries whose jurisdiction requires a larger command structure to maintain order. Senators are expected to field and train their own divisions and, in peacetime, expand the Enclave's regional administrative reach.</VFEE_Archduke.description>
  <VFEE_Archduke.label>senator</VFEE_Archduke.label>
  <VFEE_Despot.description>The Whitespring title of minister maintains authority over a strategically important system. In the Whitespring Enclave, ministers ensure that resources continue to flow into Whitespring stockpiles and factories while their offices hold key administrative positions throughout the system of government.</VFEE_Despot.description>
  <VFEE_Despot.label>minister</VFEE_Despot.label>
  <VFEE_HighStellarch.description>The Whitespring title of president represents supreme executive authority within the Whitespring Enclave. The office answers to no higher power and is expected not only to maintain control, but to expand the Enclave's influence wherever possible. Very few are capable of receiving this title, and even fewer wish to take on its responsibilities.</VFEE_HighStellarch.description>
  <VFEE_HighStellarch.label>president</VFEE_HighStellarch.label>
  <VFEE_Magister.description>The Whitespring title of state secretary is the middle rank of high government. In the Whitespring Enclave, a state secretary is expected to coordinate the settlement's vast military capabilities in both peace and wartime, operating directly under the president.</VFEE_Magister.description>
  <VFEE_Magister.label>state secretary</VFEE_Magister.label>
  <VFEE_Marquess.description>The Whitespring title of attorney general is one of the highest ranks in the middle government. In the Whitespring Enclave, attorney generals oversee frontier territories and protect the edge of Whitespring space. During wartime, they can field fleets that either hold the line or support broader offensive operations.</VFEE_Marquess.description>
  <VFEE_Marquess.label>attorney general</VFEE_Marquess.label>
  <Yeoman.description>Private is the first operational rank in the Enclave's military structure, granted to those who have completed initial training and are entrusted with basic duties and responsibilities within the Appalachia Division.</Yeoman.description>
  <Yeoman.label>private</Yeoman.label>
</LanguageData>