<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFED_DivineInferno.description>The Whitespring Enclave has initiated an orbital inferno protocol on your location. May you find solace in the cleansing flames. You have 30 days before the Whitespring Enclave moves the required orbital beam satellites into position. Unless you manage to bring your visibility back down to Hidden in time, your colony will be glassed by numerous pillars of fire.</VFED_DivineInferno.description>
  <VFED_DivineInferno.label>orbital inferno</VFED_DivineInferno.label>
  <VFED_Hidden.description>You are operating in secret, and the Whitespring Enclave has no knowledge of your allegiance to the Brotherhood expeditionaries. They will not respond to your attacks on their installations, and they will generally not look for you out in the world.</VFED_Hidden.description>
  <VFED_News.description>Your actions have become public knowledge and have hit the Whitespring news stations like a storm. The Whitespring Enclave now considers you a serious threat and has placed a high priority on tracking you down. Security measures across all installations have been greatly increased. Furthermore, the Whitespring Enclave will now send more raiding parties to any settlements suspected of harboring Brotherhood expeditionaries. It will be harder to obtain prewar tech and local support as the Whitespring Enclave's propaganda campaign gains strength.</VFED_News.description>
  <VFED_PublicEnemy.description>You are now a household name, and the Whitespring Enclave considers you its number one enemy. It is using all available resources to track you down and eliminate you and your followers. The Whitespring Enclave may also employ scorched-earth tactics, bombing or shelling entire areas suspected of supporting Brotherhood expeditionaries. It is willing to sacrifice its own installations if that is what it takes to eliminate them, and it will respond to any aggression with indiscriminate Vertibot bombardment. Most smuggling operations cease, prewar tech becomes incredibly hard to obtain, and Whitespring intelligence will spread disinformation to turn other factions against you. It is a full-blown war now, and the outcome will determine both your fate and the fate of the Whitespring Enclave. Prepare for a difficult fight. Survival is the only option left.</VFED_PublicEnemy.description>
  <VFED_Rumors.description>Rumors about Brotherhood expeditionary activity are starting to circulate among lower-ranking officers and soldiers of the Whitespring Enclave. While the Whitespring Enclave does not yet have concrete evidence of your involvement, it is beginning to take the rumors seriously and has increased its security measures. Expect tighter security on Whitespring installations, along with heavy trooper reaction forces as soon as an installation is alerted to your presence. Whitespring patrols are now prominent and will inspect every caravan they come across.</VFED_Rumors.description>
  <VFED_Whispers.description>Word of your activity has started to spread within higher command, but the Whitespring Enclave still sees you as a rare, minor annoyance. You can expect patrols to be dispatched to any Whitespring installation under attack, but you should still have enough time to get in and out before they arrive. Inventory checks become part of the updated briefing, making it slightly harder to acquire prewar tech.</VFED_Whispers.description>
</LanguageData>