<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Bed_AdvBed.description>A powered high-tech bed that automatically readjusts itself to perfectly fit the contours of the sleeper, with built in white noise generation. Sleepers often report feeling refreshed and more alert the morning after.</Bed_AdvBed.description>
  <Bed_AdvBed.label>advanced bed</Bed_AdvBed.label>
  <Bed_AdvDoubleBed.description>A powered high-tech double bed that automatically readjusts itself to perfectly fit the contours of both sleepers, with built in white noise generation. Sleepers often report feeling refreshed and more alert the morning after.</Bed_AdvDoubleBed.description>
  <Bed_AdvDoubleBed.label>advanced double bed</Bed_AdvDoubleBed.label>
  <Light_SpacerLamp.description>A powerful advanced lamp for lighting up rooms effectively whilst utilising an integrated temperature regulation module to keep rooms warmer to a maximum temperature of 15C. Will not short circuit in rain.</Light_SpacerLamp.description>
  <Light_SpacerLamp.label>spacer lamp</Light_SpacerLamp.label>
  <Reinforced_WallAT.description>A reinforced impassable wall, created by layering materials over eachother. Capable of holding up a roof.</Reinforced_WallAT.description>
  <Reinforced_WallAT.label>reinforced wall</Reinforced_WallAT.label>
  <Seat_AdvChair.description>An advanced chair that automatically changes in response to the contours of the sitter, giving optimal back support at all times and vastly improving comfort. The ultimate luxury.</Seat_AdvChair.description>
  <Seat_AdvChair.label>advanced chair</Seat_AdvChair.label>
  <Shelf_RepairRack.description>A powered high-tech shelf that utilises mechanites to slowly heal any damage on any clothing, armour or weapons placed on it.</Shelf_RepairRack.description>
  <Shelf_RepairRack.label>repair shelf</Shelf_RepairRack.label>
  <Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>A self sustained lamp for outdoor use, weaker than a normal industrial lamp but does not require any power, storing energy during the day to power itself 24/7. Will not short circuit in rain.</Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>
  <Spacer_OutdoorLamp.label>outdoor solar lamp</Spacer_OutdoorLamp.label>
  <Spacer_SunLamp.description>A large sun lamp which lights a large area brightly enough to grow crops as well as providing heat for the area, whilst consuming only a moderate amount of power. Never turns off at night and will not short circuit in rain.</Spacer_SunLamp.description>
  <Spacer_SunLamp.label>biolab sun lamp</Spacer_SunLamp.label>
  <Table_IlluminatedDresser.description>An illuminated dresser, adorned with light strips. Gives a small comfort bonus to all nearby beds, whilst lighting up the room. Placing more than one dresser near the same bed has no effect.</Table_IlluminatedDresser.description>
  <Table_IlluminatedDresser.label>illuminated dresser</Table_IlluminatedDresser.label>
  <Table_IlluminatedEndTable.description>A small illuminated bedside table adorned with light strips which makes nearby beds a little bit more comfortable, whilst lighting the room. Must be placed directly adjacent to the head of the bed. Placing more than one end table near the same bed has no effect.</Table_IlluminatedEndTable.description>
  <Table_IlluminatedEndTable.label>illuminated end table</Table_IlluminatedEndTable.label>
  <Table_interactive_1x1c.description>A table for eating off of with interactive display for watching shows, playing games or taking notes on whilst eating. Fulfills recreation need when a pawn eats at this table and the table is powered.</Table_interactive_1x1c.description>
  <Table_interactive_1x1c.label>interactive table (1x1)</Table_interactive_1x1c.label>
  <Table_interactive_2x2c.description>A table for eating off of with interactive display for watching shows, playing games or taking notes on whilst eating. Fulfills recreation need when a pawn eats at this table and the table is powered.</Table_interactive_2x2c.description>
  <Table_interactive_2x2c.label>interactive table (2x2)</Table_interactive_2x2c.label>
  <UltrascreenTV.description>A huge, curved, ultra-tech television. Viewers feel as if they are part of the action themselves. Very entertaining. Capable of picking up signal from the core worlds.</UltrascreenTV.description>
  <UltrascreenTV.label>ultrascreen television</UltrascreenTV.label>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.description>A compact, high-efficiency air purifier that filters out dust, allergens, smoke, and other unwanted particulates while circulating clean, scented air. Improves room cleanliness, slightly boosts mood, and enhances the overall environment.</VFES_AirPurifier.description>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.label>air purifier</VFES_AirPurifier.label>
  <VFES_ModernArmchair.description>A sleek, spacer-era armchair. Built with memory foam, smart-fabric upholstery, and ergonomic design, it provides superior comfort and aesthetics.</VFES_ModernArmchair.description>
  <VFES_ModernArmchair.label>modern armchair</VFES_ModernArmchair.label>
  <VFES_ModernCouch.description>A sleek, double-wide spacer-era couch. Memory foam, ergonomic design and smart-fabric upholstery provide maximum comfort.</VFES_ModernCouch.description>
  <VFES_ModernCouch.label>modern couch</VFES_ModernCouch.label>
  <VFES_Table_IlluminatedWardrobe.description>A sleek, modern wardrobe with an integrated soft-glow lamp. Gives a small comfort and rest effectiveness bonus to all nearby beds. Placing more than one wardrobe near the same bed has no effect.</VFES_Table_IlluminatedWardrobe.description>
  <VFES_Table_IlluminatedWardrobe.label>illuminated wardrobe</VFES_Table_IlluminatedWardrobe.label>
  <VFES_TelevisionSpeaker.description>A high-fidelity audio system designed to enhance the viewing experience of nearby televisions. When placed near a television, it links with the screen to deliver immersive sound, increasing the recreation gain of any colonist watching.</VFES_TelevisionSpeaker.description>
  <VFES_TelevisionSpeaker.label>television speaker</VFES_TelevisionSpeaker.label>
  <VFES_WallMountedTelevision.description>A sleek, high-tech flat-screen television. Its slim profile saves floor space while delivering the same rich color and clarity as traditional flat-screen units. It doesn’t have a huge viewing space, but can be mounted on walls.</VFES_WallMountedTelevision.description>
  <VFES_WallMountedTelevision.label>wall-mounted television</VFES_WallMountedTelevision.label>
</LanguageData>