<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- Chemshine -->
  <Chemshine.description>A harsh frontier liquor with a reputation for stripping paint and dulling good judgment. Exactly the sort of bottle a wasteland bar keeps under the counter.</Chemshine.description>
  <Chemshine.label>rot gut</Chemshine.label>

  <!-- VBE_AmbrandyDistillery -->
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>A gilded distillery of very delicate craftsmanship meant for aging pungashine must into a drinkable form.</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>pungashine still</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>

  <!-- VBE_AmbrandyMush -->
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>Sliced and pressed punga fruit ready to ripen toward pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>pungashine mash</VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>

  <!-- VBE_AmbrandyMust -->
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>Fully ripened punga liquor base, ready to be distilled into pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>pungashine must</VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>

  <!-- VBE_Cigarettes -->
  <VBE_Cigarettes.description>A small, rolled paper tube stuffed loosely with coyote tobacco chew. It offers a brief euphoria, mild stimulation, and the same stale wasteland smell that keeps smokers coming back.</VBE_Cigarettes.description>

  <!-- VBE_Cigars -->
  <VBE_Cigars.description>A thick cigar rolled from coyote tobacco chew and finished for a more expensive, more deliberate smoke. It carries a rough desert bitterness under the fancy presentation.</VBE_Cigars.description>

  <!-- VBE_EnergyDrink -->
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.description>A sharp, fizzy bottle of guarana finished with bitterness and a radioactive aftertaste. It hits hard up front and leaves a crash waiting on the other side.</VBE_EnergyDrink.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.label>guarana</VBE_EnergyDrink.label>

  <!-- VBE_FineCocktail -->
  <VBE_FineCocktail.description>A fine atomic cocktail, mixed precisely from multiple ingredients.</VBE_FineCocktail.description>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.label>fine atomic cocktail</VBE_FineCocktail.label>

  <!-- VBE_GourmetCocktail -->
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>A miracle of mixology where every glass, garnish, and stir has been tuned into a gourmet atomic cocktail.</VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>gourmet atomic cocktail</VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>

  <!-- VBE_LavishCocktail -->
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.description>A lavish atomic cocktail mixed from a wide variety of ingredients and chilled to perfection before being served.</VBE_LavishCocktail.description>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.label>lavish atomic cocktail</VBE_LavishCocktail.label>

  <!-- VBE_Plant_Tobacco -->
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>A hardy stand of coyote tobacco suited to the Mojave and other dry wasteland climates. Once cured down, the leaves become coyote tobacco chew for smoking, rolling, or trading.</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>coyote tobacco</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>

  <!-- VBE_RawCoffee -->
  <VBE_RawCoffee.description>Vacuum-sealed tins of pre-war instant coffee. Bitter, shelf-stable, and still potent enough to anchor every Lucky 38 breakfast service.</VBE_RawCoffee.description>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.label>instant coffee</VBE_RawCoffee.label>

  <!-- VBE_RawTea -->
  <VBE_RawTea.description>Dried pre-war tea leaves stored in a Lucky 38 pantry tin. They keep well and still steep into a proper serviceable cup.</VBE_RawTea.description>
  <VBE_RawTea.label>dried tea leaves</VBE_RawTea.label>

  <!-- VBE_RawTobacco -->
  <VBE_RawTobacco.description>A cured pouch of coyote tobacco chew. Dry enough to smoke, roll, or pack into richer blends, with the dusty bite wasteland smokers expect.</VBE_RawTobacco.description>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.label>coyote tobacco chew</VBE_RawTobacco.label>

  <!-- VBE_SimpleCocktail -->
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>A simple atomic cocktail quickly mixed from a duo of ingredients.</VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>simple atomic cocktail</VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>

  <!-- VBE_Soda -->
  <VBE_Soda.description>A sweet, fizzy bottle of homebrew sarsaparilla. It is more refreshing than nutritious, but a chilled bottle still feels like a pre-war luxury.</VBE_Soda.description>
  <VBE_Soda.label>homebrew sarsaparilla</VBE_Soda.label>

  <!-- VBE_SodaFountain -->
  <VBE_SodaFountain.description>An all-in-one homebrew sarsaparilla bottling unit. Syrup is mixed, carbonated, chilled, and dispensed into sterilized bottles for service.</VBE_SodaFountain.description>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.label>homebrew sarsaparilla fountain</VBE_SodaFountain.label>

  <!-- VBE_SodaSyrup -->
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.description>A thick, intensely sweet base for homebrew sarsaparilla. It is meant to be cut, carbonated, and bottled before serving.</VBE_SodaSyrup.description>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.label>homebrew sarsaparilla syrup</VBE_SodaSyrup.label>
</LanguageData>
