<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VoidMonolith.label>Big MT antenna</VoidMonolith.label>
  <HarbingerTree.label>spore plant</HarbingerTree.label>
  <GoldenCube.label>toaster</GoldenCube.label>
  <Deathpall.label>FEV aerosol cloud</Deathpall.label>
  <Deathpall.description>An airborne release of aerosolized FEV — Forced Evolutionary Virus — from a ruptured Big MT containment breach. The nanoscale viral particles settle into dead tissue and begin forced reanimation, creating lobotomites from any available corpses. Wearing sealed respirators provides some protection.</Deathpall.description>
  <TwistedObelisk.label>West Tek mutagenic emitter</TwistedObelisk.label>
  <CorruptedObelisk.label>malfunctioning ZAX node</CorruptedObelisk.label>
  <WarpedObelisk.label>Big MT field projector</WarpedObelisk.label>
  <PitGate.label>service tunnel</PitGate.label>
  <VoidStructure.label>Think Tank installation</VoidStructure.label>
  <VoidNode.label>broadcast node</VoidNode.label>
  <UnnaturalCorpse.label>test subject remains</UnnaturalCorpse.label>
  <FleshmassHeart.label>FEV reactor</FleshmassHeart.label>
  <Noctolith.label>FEV containment pod</Noctolith.label>
  <BloodRain.label>FEV rain</BloodRain.label>
  <BloodRain.description>A precipitation event caused by atmospheric dispersal of diluted Forced Evolutionary Virus from a high-altitude Big MT drone. The FEV is too thin to cause full mutation but triggers extreme aggression and adrenal overdrive in anyone it contacts. Anyone exposed will enter a berserk rage.</BloodRain.description>
  <Gorehulk.label>behemoth</Gorehulk.label>
  <Revenant.label>nightkin</Revenant.label>
  <Metalhorror.label>trauma harness</Metalhorror.label>
  <Sightstealer.label>roboscorpion</Sightstealer.label>
  <Noctol.label>nightstalker</Noctol.label>
  <Devourer.label>centaur</Devourer.label>
  <Chimera.label>FEV hybrid</Chimera.label>
  <Nociosphere.label>Think Tank brain</Nociosphere.label>
  <Fleshbeasts.label>FEV beast</Fleshbeasts.label>
  <Fleshbeasts.description>Creatures produced by runaway Forced Evolutionary Virus exposure in Big MT containment vats. FEV beasts are masses of cancerous, rapidly dividing flesh organized by a distributed nervous system. Some specimens contain multiple redundant neural cores, allowing them to split into smaller beasts on death. They are directed at a high level by a ZAX unit.</Fleshbeasts.description>
  <FleshmassNucleus.label>ZAX unit</FleshmassNucleus.label>
  <Dreadmeld.label>FEV amalgam</Dreadmeld.label>
  <Shambler.label>lobotomite</Shambler.label>
  <Shambler.description>Corpses or surgically brain-absent subjects reanimated by the Big MT broadcast signal and residual FEV activity. Lobotomites are slow, relentless, and mindless. They will continue attacking until their body reaches metabolic failure. Unlike true undead, they can theoretically be captured and studied — although what's left to study is largely mechanical.</Shambler.description>
  <Ghoul.label>robobrain subject</Ghoul.label>
  <Ghoul.description>A person implanted with a Big MT neural override chip. The chip has malfunctioned and is sending constant high-frequency commands the host cannot resist, turning them into a spasmodic killing machine. They remain biologically alive. They cannot be reasoned with while the chip is active.</Ghoul.description>
</LanguageData>