<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Armorer.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as an armorer for the 英克雷, specializing in the maintenance, repair, and distribution of advanced power armor and energy weapons. With extensive knowledge of pre-war military technology, [PAWN_pronoun] was trusted to outfit elite s老旧iers with the finest equipment available. [PAWN_nameDef] took pride in [PAWN_possessive] work, ensuring every suit of armor and weapon functioned flawlessly. [PAWN_possessive] expertise and dedication made [PAWN_objective] a cornerstone of the 英克雷's military strength.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Armorer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Armorer.title>英克雷 Armorer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Armorer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Armorer.titleShort>Armorer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Armorer.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Arsenal_Specialist.description>The 英克雷’s high-tech gear needed a lot of maintenance to remain in pristine condition. [PAWN_nameDef] was an 英克雷 arsenal specialist. [PAWN_possessive] job was to repair the advanced power armour of the 英克雷’s Troopers, as well as their high-tech plasma and laser weapons. There were very few communities in the wasteland that were capable of crafting such marvels of technology and the [PAWN_nameDef] zealously guarded these 秘密s.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Arsenal_Specialist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Arsenal_Specialist.title>英克雷 Arsenal Specialist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Arsenal_Specialist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Arsenal_Specialist.titleShort>英克雷 Arsenal Specialist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Arsenal_Specialist.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Biologist.description>The 英克雷 was very concerned with the exposure of their members to the almost omnipresent radiation of the wasteland. As such, they were careful what their members consumed. [PAWN_nameDef] was tasked with growing the necessary foodstuffs for the 英克雷. While people in the wasteland couldn’t be too picky about what they ate, [PAWN_pronoun] generally preferred to grow corn and other non-mutated crops of the pre-war world, instead of their mutated successors, like tatos.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Biologist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Biologist.title>英克雷 Biologist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Biologist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Biologist.titleShort>英克雷 Biologist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Biologist.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Bureaucrat.description>While the 英克雷’s bureaucracy was considerably s商场er compared to the one of her 老旧-world pendant, it still needed numerous bureaucrats to tend to the copious amounts of paperwork that accumulated over the years. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of those faceless paper pushers and spent most of [PAWN_possessive] life in cramped offices and 蒙尘 conference rooms. While [PAWN_nameDef], was an efficient and competent clerk, [PAWN_pronoun] was rather solitary.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Bureaucrat.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Bureaucrat.title>英克雷 Bureaucrat</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Bureaucrat.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Bureaucrat.titleShort>英克雷 Bureaucrat</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Bureaucrat.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Compassionate_Child.description>Unusual for a child raised in the 英克雷, [PAWN_nameDef] showed compassion and mercy on other creatures, even those deemed lower by fellow 英克雷 members. These character traits made life within the organisation difficult for [PAWN_objective] and [PAWN_pronoun] distanced [PAWN_objective]self from most others.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Compassionate_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Compassionate_Child.title>Compassionate Child</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Compassionate_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Compassionate_Child.titleShort>Compassionate Child</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Compassionate_Child.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Conscripted_Adjutant.description>The 英克雷 never was a particularly numerous group and was, consequentially often short on staff. [PAWN_nameDef] grew up within the lower ranks of the 英克雷 and was conscripted into service at a young age. [PAWN_pronoun] worked as an adjutant for an 英克雷 officer. [PAWN_possessive] supervisor wasn’t a particularly friendly person, but [PAWN_nameDef] learned a lot about the day-to-day duties of a military officer and remembered these lessons well.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Conscripted_Adjutant.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Conscripted_Adjutant.title>Conscripted Adjutant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Conscripted_Adjutant.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Conscripted_Adjutant.titleShort>Conscripted Adjutant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Conscripted_Adjutant.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Engineer_Trainee.description>The complex machinery the 英克雷 depended upon needed near constant supervision and maintenance. This meant that skilled engineers were always needed and children with a knack for machinery, such as [PAWN_nameDef] were put into training in their early youth.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Engineer_Trainee.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Engineer_Trainee.title>Engineer Trainee</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Engineer_Trainee.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Engineer_Trainee.titleShort>Engineer Trainee</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Engineer_Trainee.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Entitled_Scion.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into the highest echelons of 英克雷 society. [PAWN_pronoun] was used to underlings taking care of [PAWN_possessive] every need and whim, while [PAWN_pronoun] trained and studied for a career in the leading positions of the 英克雷.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Entitled_Scion.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Entitled_Scion.title>Entitled Scion</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Entitled_Scion.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Entitled_Scion.titleShort>Entitled Scion</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Entitled_Scion.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Foot_Soldier.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a rank-and-file s老旧ier within the 英克雷. Of course, rank-and-file in this case meant [PAWN_pronoun] was an excellently trained fighter, equipped with some of the finest equipment of post-war America and instilled with nothing but scorn and disdain for the average wastelander and all other inhabitants of the wasteland, mutated or not.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Foot_Soldier.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Foot_Soldier.title>英克雷 Foot S老旧ier</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Foot_Soldier.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Foot_Soldier.titleShort>英克雷 Foot S老旧ier</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Foot_Soldier.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Hellfire_Trooper.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was with the 英克雷 hellfire troopers, an elite group of 英克雷 s老旧iers equipped with experimental hellfire power armour and heavy napalm throwers called incinerators. Due to [PAWN_possessive] yearlong service with the hellfire troopers [PAWN_nameDef] developed a rather… unwholesome fascination with fire, especially when it was brought in contact with living beings.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Hellfire_Trooper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Hellfire_Trooper.title>英克雷 Hellfire Trooper</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Hellfire_Trooper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Hellfire_Trooper.titleShort>英克雷 Hellfire Trooper</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Hellfire_Trooper.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Farmer.description>[PAWN_nameDef] once was a regular farmer, but [PAWN_possessive] life changed the day [PAWN_possessive] humble farmstead was visited by a man in a trench coat and his entourage of armoured brutes. It did not take much intimidation to “persuade” [PAWN_nameDef] to serve [PAWN_possessive] country and deliver the produce of the farmstead to a nearby 英克雷 outpost.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Farmer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Farmer.title>Indentured Farmer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Farmer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Farmer.titleShort>Indentured Farmer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Farmer.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Labourer.description>Once an ordinary wastelander [PAWN_nameDef], wandered around until that fateful day when [PAWN_pronoun] walked right into an 英克雷 patrol. The heavily armed s老旧iers clad in pitch-black power armour t老旧 [PAWN_objective] that the country needed [PAWN_possessive] service. [PAWN_nameDef] had no idea what that meant, but before [PAWN_pronoun] could react, [PAWN_pronoun] was knocked unconscious and dragged away, to serve as a labourer for the 英克雷, fulfilling all kinds of menial work for [PAWN_possessive] new masters.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Labourer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Labourer.title>Indentured Labourer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Labourer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Labourer.titleShort>Indentured Labourer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Labourer.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Servant.description>Many tasks were just beneath the higher-ranking members of the 英克雷. [PAWN_nameDef] was abducted by an 英克雷 patrol to handle some of these tasks. [PAWN_pronoun] was not only put to work as a custodian but was also responsible for negotiations with wastelanders in those rare cases, where the 英克雷 did not resort to violence to achieve her goals as well as supervising the indentured labourers and similar tasks the officers didn’t want to besmirch themselves with.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Servant.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Servant.title>Indentured Servant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Servant.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Servant.titleShort>Indentured Servant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Indentured_Servant.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Junior_Civil_Servant.description>After finishing basic education [PAWN_nameDef] was assigned to serve within the byzantine bureaucracy of the 英克雷, which ensured the functionality of the organisation. The institution’s focus on ruthless efficiency made [PAWN_objective] c老旧 and unkind.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Junior_Civil_Servant.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Junior_Civil_Servant.title>Junior Civil Servant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Junior_Civil_Servant.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Junior_Civil_Servant.titleShort>Junior Civil Servant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Junior_Civil_Servant.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Kidnapped_Servant.description>Every once in a while, the 英克雷 would scour the Wasteland in search of new “workers”. While the patrols preferred to abduct adults, they weren’t opposed to capturing children. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of those unfortunate kids. While [PAWN_pronoun] was generally looked down upon most other members of the 英克雷, it was possible, although unlikely for [PAWN_objective] to rise up to higher ranks within the organisation.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Kidnapped_Servant.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Kidnapped_Servant.title>Kidnapped Servant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Kidnapped_Servant.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Kidnapped_Servant.titleShort>Kidnapped Servant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Kidnapped_Servant.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Lab_Assistant.description>[PAWN_nameDef] showed great promise while being educated within the 英克雷 and was subsequently made a lab assistant. There [PAWN_pronoun] learned much about many scientific fields such as chemistry, physics, and biology from some of the brightest, albeit not very ethical minds of the Wasteland.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Lab_Assistant.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Lab_Assistant.title>Lab Assistant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Lab_Assistant.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Lab_Assistant.titleShort>Lab Assistant</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Lab_Assistant.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Levied_Recruit.description>The skills of the 英克雷’s s老旧iers was the result of years of strenuous training under the supervision of remorseless drill sergeants. Due to a shortage of able recruits, [PAWN_nameDef] was levied into service as a child and spent most of [PAWN_possessive] youth in barracks and on training fields. This made [PAWN_objective] a great warrior indeed, but left little time for anything else, since the 英克雷 did not exactly promote creative thinking within the rank and file.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Levied_Recruit.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Levied_Recruit.title>Levied Recruit</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Levied_Recruit.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Levied_Recruit.titleShort>Levied Recruit</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Levied_Recruit.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Officer.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an officer of the 英克雷 department of the army. [PAWN_pronoun] truly believed in the 英克雷’s mission to rebuild the USA and was eager to do [PAWN_possessive] part to implement this vision. While [PAWN_pronoun] was a skilled s老旧ier, [PAWN_possessive] true talent lay in motivating [PAWN_possessive] subordinates.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Officer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Officer.title>英克雷 Officer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Officer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Officer.titleShort>英克雷 Officer</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Officer.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Peacekeeper_in_Training.description>The highly stratified society of the 英克雷 demanded absolute obedience from its citizenry. As an especially loyal child [PAWN_nameDef] was accepted into the ranks of the 英克雷 Peacekeeping Force, where [PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned how to ensure peace and order, especially within the conscripted masses of forced labourers, usually by means of a cattle prod.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Peacekeeper_in_Training.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Peacekeeper_in_Training.title>Peacekeeper in Training</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Peacekeeper_in_Training.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Peacekeeper_in_Training.titleShort>Peacekeeper in Training</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Peacekeeper_in_Training.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Physician.description>The 英克雷 had a number of highly-trained physicians, whose primary task was to tend to important personnel like officers or high-ranking politicians. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of those physicians. [PAWN_pronoun] lacked the distinctive contempt most other 英克雷 members felt for the inhabitants of the wasteland, a character trait that often put [PAWN_objective] at odds with [PAWN_possessive] superiors.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Physician.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Physician.title>英克雷 Physician</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Physician.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Physician.titleShort>英克雷 Physician</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Physician.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Politician.description>As most people within the 英克雷, [PAWN_nameDef] was raised to believe that all beings that dwelt in the wasteland were mutated and genetically inferior. [PAWN_pronoun] however, took these lessons more to heart than others and so [PAWN_pronoun] became a politician in the 英克雷, to advocate for the “cleansing” of the wasteland so that, one day, the last unmutated humans could reclaim the land that is rightfully theirs and finally rebuild the nation that once was.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Politician.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Politician.title>英克雷 Politician</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Politician.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Politician.titleShort>英克雷 Politician</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Politician.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Propagandist.description>While the 英克雷 generally didn’t look favourably upon the other inhabitants of the Wasteland, they had to grudgingly accept that they were useful at times. To keep the wastelanders (mis-)informed about the 英克雷’s intents, [PAWN_nameDef] was instructed to write Propaganda material and distribute it in settlements surrounding the 英克雷’s outpost.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Propagandist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Propagandist.title>英克雷 Propagandist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Propagandist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Propagandist.titleShort>英克雷 Propagandist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Propagandist.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Quartermaster.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as a quartermaster for the 英克雷, responsible for managing and distributing uniforms, supplies, and essential equipment to s老旧iers and personnel. Known for [PAWN_possessive] meticulous record-keeping and efficient logistics, [PAWN_pronoun] ensured that every unit was properly outfitted for duty. With an eye for detail and a talent for negotiation, [PAWN_nameDef] became an invaluable asset to the 英克雷's supply chain, maintaining the organization's operational readiness even in the harshest conditions.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Quartermaster.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Quartermaster.title>英克雷 Quartermaster</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Quartermaster.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Quartermaster.titleShort>Quartermaster</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Quartermaster.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Secret_Service_Agent.description>Nominally, the 秘密 service is still tasked with the protection of the president of the United States. However, most 英克雷 presidents used them as elite troops, charged with the most pressing matters of national security. [PAWN_nameDef] was part of this elite troop. [PAWN_pronoun] was a perfectly trained killing machine, with a total lack of empathy only concerned with the fulfilment of the president’s orders. Even other 英克雷 members shuddered at [PAWN_possessive] c老旧, calculating personality.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Secret_Service_Agent.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Secret_Service_Agent.title>秘密 Service Agent</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Secret_Service_Agent.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Secret_Service_Agent.titleShort>秘密 Service Agent</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Secret_Service_Agent.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Tesla_Soldier.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a tesla s老旧ier with the 英克雷. As the name suggests, these elite troopers are known and feared for their advanced tesla power armour and their prowess with heavy plasma weaponry. Lucky for the inhabitants of the wasteland, [PAWN_nameDef] and the tesla s老旧iers [PAWN_pronoun] belonged to were a rather rare sight, deployed only against the 英克雷’s most stubborn and 危险 enemies.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Tesla_Soldier.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Tesla_Soldier.title>英克雷 Tesla S老旧ier</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Tesla_Soldier.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Tesla_Soldier.titleShort>英克雷 Tesla S老旧ier</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Tesla_Soldier.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Warden.description>While most wastelanders were more of a nuisance to the 英克雷 than an actual threat, there were some culprits that caused more trouble. [PAWN_nameDef] was a warden with the 英克雷 and [PAWN_possessive] job was to look after the unfortunate prisoners of the 英克雷, as well as to extract all important information from them, even if they weren’t in possession of such knowledge. As soon as [PAWN_possessive] superiors thought they gained all useful information from a prisoner, it was up to [PAWN_nameDef] execute them, which [PAWN_pronoun] often did in a grisly manner.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Warden.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Warden.title>英克雷 Warden</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Warden.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Warden.titleShort>英克雷 Warden</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Warden.titleShort>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Zoologist.description>The 英克雷 was always interested in the mutated wildlife that dwelled in the wasteland. However, their intentions were less based on scientific curiosity and more on the desire to weaponize the horrific beasts roaming the irradiated landscape. [PAWN_nameDef] was a zoologist with the 英克雷 and conducted cruel experiments on many different beasts to test their suitability for combat, as well as methods to control them. While [PAWN_pronoun] was a respected scientist, [PAWN_pronoun] also showed sadistic tendencies and was avoided by most other 英克雷 members.</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Zoologist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Zoologist.title>英克雷 Zoologist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Zoologist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Zoologist.titleShort>英克雷 Zoologist</FCP_Backstory_Enclave_Zoologist.titleShort>
</LanguageData>
