<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFED_BombPack_Deployed.description>A deployed bomb pack. It’s armed, and can be detonated with a press of a button.</VFED_BombPack_Deployed.description>
  <VFED_BombPack_Deployed.label>deployed bomb pack</VFED_BombPack_Deployed.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.description>A pair of antigrain warheads connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.label>remote antigrain charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>A pair of armor-piercing shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>remote armor-piercing charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.description>A pair of cluster shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.label>remote cluster charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.description>A pair of EMP shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.label>remote EMP charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.description>A pair of firefoam shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.label>remote firefoam charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.description>A pair of high-explosive shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.label>remote charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.description>A pair of incendiary shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.label>remote incendiary charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.description>A pair of shrapnel shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.label>remote shrapnel charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.description>A pair of smoke shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.label>remote smoke charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>A pair of armor-piercing shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>IED armor-piercing trap</VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.description>A pair of cluster shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.label>IED cluster trap</VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.description>A pair of shrapnel shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.label>IED shrapnel trap</VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.label>
</LanguageData>
