<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VGE_CompactDrugLab.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered drug lab designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, it’s equipped with containers, heaters, and measurement devices for producing various drugs. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactDrugLab.description>
  <VGE_CompactDrugLab.label>compact drug lab</VGE_CompactDrugLab.label>
  <VGE_CompactFabBench.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered fabrication bench designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, it’s equipped with advanced tools for producing technological marvels from simpler materials. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactFabBench.description>
  <VGE_CompactFabBench.label>compact fabrication bench</VGE_CompactFabBench.label>
  <VGE_CompactMachiningTable.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered machining table designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, it’s ideal for assembling machinery like guns and ammunition, or breaking down dead mechanoids. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactMachiningTable.description>
  <VGE_CompactMachiningTable.label>compact machining table</VGE_CompactMachiningTable.label>
  <VGE_CompactRefinery.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered biofuel refinery designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, it refines biological matter like wood or plant matter into chemfuel. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactRefinery.description>
  <VGE_CompactRefinery.label>compact biofuel refinery</VGE_CompactRefinery.label>
  <VGE_CompactSmithy.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered smithy designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, it can be used to smith non-mechanical weapons and tools, as well as extract usable metal from slag chunks. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactSmithy.description>
  <VGE_CompactSmithy.label>compact smithy</VGE_CompactSmithy.label>
  <VGE_CompactStove.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered stove designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, it contains a high-efficiency cooktop and integrated prep surface, as well as a butchering slate. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactStove.description>
  <VGE_CompactStove.label>compact stove</VGE_CompactStove.label>
  <VGE_CompactTailor.description>A space-efficient, gravship-powered tailor bench designed for use aboard gravships. Despite its smaller frame, this workbench comes with a sewing machine for rapid tailoring of clothes. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_CompactTailor.description>
  <VGE_CompactTailor.label>compact tailor bench</VGE_CompactTailor.label>
  <VGE_WallToolCabinet.description>A wall-mounted version of a tool cabinet. Increases work speed when placed near a workbench. One workbench can use up to two tool cabinets.</VGE_WallToolCabinet.description>
  <VGE_WallToolCabinet.label>wall tool cabinet</VGE_WallToolCabinet.label>
</LanguageData>
