<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VEE_Cenote.description>A deep, water filled sinkhole carved into the stone. The surface appears calm. Due to its depth, it can't be filled.</VEE_Cenote.description>
  <VEE_Cenote.label>cenote</VEE_Cenote.label>
  <VEE_Cenote_Small.description>A deep, water filled sinkhole carved into the stone. The surface appears calm. Due to its depth, it can't be filled.</VEE_Cenote_Small.description>
  <VEE_Cenote_Small.label>small cenote</VEE_Cenote_Small.label>
  <VEE_Coral.description>A colorful, calcified colony of tiny marine organisms, forming intricate reef structures teeming with life.</VEE_Coral.description>
  <VEE_Coral.label>coral</VEE_Coral.label>
  <VEE_DeadlifeVent.description>A sinister geyser that exhales eerie, ash-like dust, capable of reawakening the dead under its influence.</VEE_DeadlifeVent.description>
  <VEE_DeadlifeVent.label>deadlife geyser</VEE_DeadlifeVent.label>
  <VEE_DenseSnow.description>A heavy, compacted layer of snow that resists movement and muffles sound. Can be mined to remove it.</VEE_DenseSnow.description>
  <VEE_DenseSnow.label>solid snow</VEE_DenseSnow.label>
  <VEE_DriftwoodChunk.description>A sun-bleached fragment of wood, smoothed by waves and time, carried ashore from some distant and unknown origin.</VEE_DriftwoodChunk.description>
  <VEE_DriftwoodChunk.label>driftwood</VEE_DriftwoodChunk.label>
  <VEE_DryWheat.description>An amber cereal plant that takes almost an entire growing season to come to fruition. This wheat has been subjected to drought conditions for too long and has wilted away.</VEE_DryWheat.description>
  <VEE_DryWheat.label>dry wheat</VEE_DryWheat.label>
  <VEE_InertPitGate.description>A massive, foreboding hole that connects the surface with a dark network of underground caves. It is possible to climb down into the caverns below.</VEE_InertPitGate.description>
  <VEE_InertPitGate.label>pit gate</VEE_InertPitGate.label>
  <VEE_JadeChunk.description>A chunk of jadeite. It can be deconstructed to acquire some jade.</VEE_JadeChunk.description>
  <VEE_JadeChunk.label>jadeite chunk</VEE_JadeChunk.label>
  <VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.description>Advanced ancient electronics, compacted over time. Can be mined for useful advanced components.</VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.description>
  <VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.label>advanced compacted machinery</VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.label>
  <VEE_MineableJadeite.description>A silicate mineral in the pyroxene family that is one of the two forms of jade.</VEE_MineableJadeite.description>
  <VEE_MineableJadeite.label>jadeite</VEE_MineableJadeite.label>
  <VEE_ObsidianChunk.description>A chunk of obsidian. It can be deconstructed to acquire some obsidian.</VEE_ObsidianChunk.description>
  <VEE_ObsidianChunk.label>obsidian chunk</VEE_ObsidianChunk.label>
  <VEE_RotstinkVent.description>A foul geyser that intermittently belches clouds of corpse-born miasma, choking the air with the stench of decay.</VEE_RotstinkVent.description>
  <VEE_RotstinkVent.label>rotstink geyser</VEE_RotstinkVent.label>
  <VEE_Sinkhole.description>A sudden collapse in the ground forming a deep, unstable pit, often exposing bare rock beneath the surface.</VEE_Sinkhole.description>
  <VEE_Sinkhole.label>sinkhole</VEE_Sinkhole.label>
  <VEE_SmokeVent.description>A smoldering fissure that intermittently exhales thick, acrid smoke, reducing visibility and choking the lungs.</VEE_SmokeVent.description>
  <VEE_SmokeVent.label>smoke geyser</VEE_SmokeVent.label>
  <VEE_SmoothedJadeite.description>A silicate mineral in the pyroxene family that is one of the two forms of jade.</VEE_SmoothedJadeite.description>
  <VEE_SmoothedJadeite.label>smoothed jadeite</VEE_SmoothedJadeite.label>
  <VEE_SulfurVent.description>A naturally-occurring break in the ground from which sulfuric gases escape. The gas produced on these fissures stinks of rotten eggs.</VEE_SulfurVent.description>
  <VEE_SulfurVent.label>sulfur fissure</VEE_SulfurVent.label>
  <VEE_ToxicVent.description>A volatile fissure that periodically spews noxious green gas, poisoning the air and sickening anything that breathes it.</VEE_ToxicVent.description>
  <VEE_ToxicVent.label>toxic geyser</VEE_ToxicVent.label>
</LanguageData>
