<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VEE_Plant_DatePalm.description>A tall palm thriving along warm coasts, bearing clusters of sweet, energy-rich fruit. Its deep roots and flexible trunk help it withstand salt spray and coastal winds.</VEE_Plant_DatePalm.description>
  <VEE_Plant_DatePalm.label>date palm</VEE_Plant_DatePalm.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood.description>A hardy tree adapted to grow on volcanic ground. It is among the first plants to colonize cooled lava, helping life return to the black stone.</VEE_Plant_Firewood.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood.label>firewood tree</VEE_Plant_Firewood.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a firewood tree has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.label>chopped stump</VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a firewood tree destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.label>smashed stump</VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.description>A twisted, weathered pine shaped by wind and poor soil. Its gnarled branches and sparse needles give it a rugged, enduring appearance.</VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.description>
  <VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.label>gnarled pine tree</VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Laurel.description>An evergreen broadleaf tree with dense foliage and aromatic leaves, well adapted to mild, humid climates.</VEE_Plant_Laurel.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Laurel.label>laurel tree</VEE_Plant_Laurel.label>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a laurel tree has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.label>chopped stump</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a laurel tree destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.label>smashed stump</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.description>A hardy coastal tree with spiraled leaves and exposed roots, adapted to wind, salt, and shifting sand.</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.label>screw pine</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a screw pine has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.label>chopped stump</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a screw pine destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.label>smashed stump</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.description>A temperate-biome tree known for its thin, white, paper-like bark.</VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.label>auburn birch tree</VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.description>A common medium-sized tree, easily identifiable by its distinct three-pointed leaf.</VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.label>auburn maple tree</VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.description>A hardwood tree. Oaks take a long time to grow, but their wood is so strong that 'oak' is used as a metaphor for strength across many cultures.</VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.label>auburn oak tree</VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.description>A softwood tree that grows very fast. Unfortunately, its wood is weak and so it yields less useful material than hardwood trees.</VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.label>auburn poplar tree</VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.label>
</LanguageData>
