<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AnimusStone.description>A resonant cryptic stone studied by Whitespring researchers. It increases cryptid meditation focus and is often used in enclave research facilities.</AnimusStone.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>cryptic stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy armor used by Whitespring secret service units to break fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>A suit of heavy armor, built for maximum protection at the cost of mobility. Heavy layered plasteel-weave plates with solid ablative coatings stop all but the most well-aimed or powerful attacks. Neuro-memetic assistors prevent the suit's massive weight from immobilizing the wearer entirely, but the suit is still quite cumbersome.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with short-range thrust capabilities for quick movement in urban environments. Urban scouts prefer close-quarters engagements and quick strikes rather than static defense.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>urban scout armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor specialized for cold and arctic operations, fitted with a shoulder-mounted launcher. Arctic marines specialize in breaching cold-climate fortifications.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>arctic marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet used by Whitespring patriots, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>patriot marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of armor used by Whitespring patriots. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and ceremonial, patriot marine armor marks membership and rank. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>patriot marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A beret styled with the Whitespring insignia, worn by enclave personnel of certain ranks.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>Whitespring Beret</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A cap worn by senior Whitespring researchers, denoting a leadership role in cryptid studies.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>Whitespring Scientist Cap</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for cryptid research focus. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>cryptex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for cryptid research focus. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>cryptex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>cryptex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special cryptid-focusing materials. These enhance cryptid sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>cryptex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>cryptex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, formal longcoat used by Whitespring patriots and officers. Embroidered with the enclave sigils, it marks membership and rank.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>patriot longcoat</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.description>A stump left behind after an Mothman totem has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</ChoppedStump_Anima.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.label>chopped Mothman stump</ChoppedStump_Anima.label>
  <GrandThrone.description>An ornate grand chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential grand chair grants the occupant a sense of authority and dignity.</GrandThrone.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>presidential grand chair</GrandThrone.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword refined for Whitespring security officers. Its mono-molecular edge cuts through armor with ease, while an embedded cryptex core sharpens the wielder's cryptid insight and stabilizes the weapon's high-speed response.

The cryptex core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once that bond is established, the blade responds with extreme speed and precision and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>cryptex molecular blade</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored officer's sword wrapped in a sheath of captive plasma. Targets are sliced by the inner edge and burned by the surrounding field, giving Whitespring officers a close-range weapon that can cut and cauterize in the same strike.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the sword responds with unusual speed and control and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>plasma officer sword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A Whitespring warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. On impact it discharges a powerful pulse in addition to the physical blow, making it especially effective against power armor, robots, and other advanced hardware.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the hammer tracks the wielder's timing and strike rhythm with unusual accuracy and rejects any hand outside its assigned operator.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>pulse hammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring cryptid forces. Whitespring operatives use these to amplify cryptid focus during ritualized study.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine used by cryptid researchers to focus meditation and study. These shrines strengthen cryptid-focused meditation for Whitespring operatives.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.description>Mysterious black eggs with a red glow. Tribal peoples find that these eggs grow around the base of a Mothman totem as they meditate. It seems to reflect some kind of strengthening of the totem's cryptic power.\n\nWasteland scientists have tried to study the phenomenon, but the eggs fail to hatch when observed too closely.\n\nAnimals refuse eat Mothman eggs. Tribal stories say this is done out of respect and fear.</Plant_GrassAnima.description>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.label>Mothman eggs</Plant_GrassAnima.label>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.description>A Mothman totem used by Appalachia cultists to focus their meditation and worship.</Plant_TreeAnima.description>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.label>Mothman totem</Plant_TreeAnima.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.label>Vertibird Landing Beacon</ShipLandingBeacon.label>
  <ShuttleIncoming.label>vertibird (incoming)</ShuttleIncoming.label>
  <ShuttleLeaving.label>vertibird (leaving)</ShuttleLeaving.label>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.description>The remnants of an Mothman totem destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</SmashedStump_Anima.description>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.label>smashed Mothman stump</SmashedStump_Anima.label>
  <Throne.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential chair may be used as a focus for certain duties and ceremonies.</Throne.description>
  <Throne.label>presidential chair</Throne.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>Whitespring suite</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.description>Vertibot is a spacer-tech, unmanned aerial vehicle equipped with advanced sensors and a missile payload. Designed for autonomous long-range operations, it's commonly used by the Whitespring Enclave for reconnaissance and bombardment. Its ability to release powerful missile salvos makes it effective against various targets. This vertibot is temporarily disabled due to the recharge cycle.</VFED_Aerodrone.description>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.label>vertibot</VFED_Aerodrone.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>A large, overcharged vertibot battery. Will release a strong electromagnetic pulse when damaged, potentially disabling nearby defenses.</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>vertibot battery pack</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>A large military crate of vertibot munitions. Will explode when damaged, sending armed shells flying in random directions.</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>vertibot munitions crate</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>A multi-use personal stealthboy cloak device engineered based on experimental Whitespring technology. Allows the user to become completely invisible for a brief duration, after which the device requires a short amount of time to recharge.</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>Stealthboy</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing extremely valuable items. May contain critical intel. Due to the special restrictions, only senior Whitespring officials are capable of opening it.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary device capable of intercepting Whitespring communication. When activated, it will begin intel scraping, emitting a pulse in regular intervals. Each pulse has a chance of generating a small amount of intel, but it may also increase your visibility and even alert a Whitespring strike force. After 10 pulses, the machine burns out and triggers a fiery explosion.</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>A crashed Whitespring vertibot.</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>crashed vertibot</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.description>A dossier containing critical information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to plan high-profile assassination attempts, but it can also be exchanged into standard intel via the contraband system.</VFED_CriticalIntel.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary declassifier is a single-use, ultra-tech device consisting of a brain-scan apparatus and a long, thick needle. It is primarily used by Whitespring Brotherhood expeditionaries for data extraction. By inserting the needle into the skull of a senior official, memories can be downloaded from their brain, forming valuable Brotherhood expeditionary intel. The amount of intel received is determined by the rank of the target official. The person affected by a Brotherhood Expeditionary Declassifier dies in the process, and when used on neutral visitors, it is treated as an act of war.</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>Brotherhood declassifier</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>A spacer-tech vertibird designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>Brotherhood vertibird</VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>Brotherhood vertibird (incoming)</VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>Brotherhood vertibird (leaving)</VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>Whitespring propaganda</VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>A chunk of a Whitespring flagship. It seems to have been torn off by some kind of powerful weapon.\n\nHaving landed not long ago, it still contains useful resources which you can acquire by deconstructing it.</VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>Kovac-Muldoon debris</VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>
  <VFED_FuelTank.description>A large fuel tank used to refuel Whitespring vertibirds. Will detonate if damaged beyond a certain point, potentially triggering a chain reaction.</VFED_FuelTank.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>The governmental APC is a formidable armored transport truck, known for its impressive cargo capacity. Its armor is impenetrable, ensuring the safety of its contents throughout transit. Once in motion, the APC’s doors remain sealed until it reaches its predetermined destination. While attempting to loot its cargo is futile due to built-in self-destruct protocols, its robust exterior makes it an ideal shield on the battlefield.</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>governmental APC</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>An advanced shielding apparatus, the Whitespring mega high-shield projects a vast momentum repulsor field, allowing shots to exit but preventing any from entering. Specifically calibrated for high angles, it's adept at deflecting incoming mortar rounds, vertibot strikes and even orbital slicer beams. The unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield. Draws huge amounts of power.</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>governmental mega high-shield</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>An underground hydroponics bay used by the Whitespring Enclave to feed its personnel. Fully automated and connected to water mains, these farms require no labor to operate.</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>Whitespring underfarm</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>
  <VFED_Intel.description>A dossier containing information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to obtain prewar tech from the Brotherhood expeditionaries, or to gain access to quests and even assassination missions on Whitespring officials.</VFED_Intel.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>Decommissioned Whitespring technology since the invention of psylink neuroformers, psychic amplifier upgrades a psylink in the user's mind. It cannot form a psylink by itself, and can only be used by colonists with already present psylink. The user presses the device over the eyes, where it links to the brain directly and restructures part of it. Afterwards, the device disintegrates into worthless ash.</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>cryptid amplifier</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>
  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>A small surveillance buoy usually deployed around temporary convoy stops. Linked directly with a patrolling vertibot, once triggered, it will send down a small missile salvo on its location.</VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing valuables. May contain intel. Opening it requires bypassing several security protocols and takes a short while.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_SupplyCrate.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>A Whitespring computer interface. Linked to the surveillance console, the display bank shows live footage from all surveillance pillars in the sector.</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>
  <VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>A large pillar with a series of sensors, cameras and motion detectors. Thanks to the sophisticated face recognition system, surveillance pillar can detect the presence of Brotherhood expeditionaries in radius and will increase the visibility of whichever faction has sent them. Can be disabled via electromagnetic pulse, or by simply cutting off the power grid.</VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>A compact stack of data discs produced exclusively by the Whitespring Enclave for knowledge transcription. They are primarily designed for preserving information. When ignited, they release a dense cloud of blinding smoke and sparks, capable of engulfing a wide area in flames.</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>data disc stack</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>
  <VFED_Techprinter.description>The Data Printer is a marvel of technological innovation, designed to capture and preserve the intricate knowledge residing within a scientist’s mind. These advanced machines imprint this invaluable information directly onto data discs. Techprints provide foundational knowledge for researchers, shedding light on innovations from more advanced societies.</VFED_Techprinter.description>
  <VFED_Techprinter.label>data printer</VFED_Techprinter.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>orbital cannon capacitor bank</VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>This terminal serves as the primary interface for operating the Orbital Cannon batteries. Equipped with sophisticated controls and targeting systems, the Orbital Cannon Control Station ensures precision and coordination when deploying the formidable firepower of the Orbital Cannons. Operators need to be within its radius to control it.</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>orbital cannon control station</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.description>A non-alcoholic, pleasantly light, citrusy, and slightly bitter aperitif that owes its flavors and aromas to sweet and bitter oranges, rhubarb, and Whitespring craftsmanship. Its recipe is guarded by Whitespring hospitality offices, and few on the rim have managed to recreate it. Drinking it induces heavy but painless vomiting, completely clearing the stomach and resetting the palate.\n\nWhitespring officials prize aperitif for letting them indulge in even more of the settlement's finest cuisine.</VFEE_Aperitif.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>A high-tech helmet with a solid plasteel-weave shell and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system backed by real-time firing solutions. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>Whitespring light helmet</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>A high-tech suit of powered armor with layered plasteel-weave plates and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system that also assists the user's movement. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>Whitespring light armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>Brotherhood expeditionary armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>Brotherhood expeditionary helmet</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>Whitespring heavy armor</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>Whitespring heavy helmet</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>An exceedingly complex facemask fitted with advanced technology reserved for senior Whitespring scientists. It is designed for designated researchers so they can advance the Whitespring Enclave's needs without rest.\n\nThe inlaid techprint synchronizes with the wearer's brain while they perform research, effectively doubling research speed while restoring rest and recreation.</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>Whitespring scientist helmet</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.label>Whitespring chair</VFEE_GrandChair.label>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>A majestic rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>grand Whitespring rug</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.label>Whitespring table</VFEE_GrandTable.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>Whitespring sign</VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>A stoney bas relief of Whitespring imagery for decorating a floor.</VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>Whitespring slab</VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>An intricate rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>large Whitespring rug</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>orbital beam</VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>Whitespring mirror</VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>grand presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>large presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>small presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.label>Whitespring stool</VFEE_RoyalStool.label>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.label>presidential plaque</VFEE_SteleSmall.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential desk chair can serve as a focus for ceremonial duties and cryptid meditation.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>presidential desk chair</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>A spacer-tech Whitespring gunship designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system. Equipped with a twin-linked autocannon for ground support, these XVB02s often land in the middle of the battlefield to extract stranded troops.</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>XVB02</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>A command staff issued to Whitespring executive officers during inspections, briefings, and emergency command duty. Its cryptex head sharpens cryptid insight and helps regulate neural strain, while the embedded attunement core rejects any wielder outside the assigned chain of command.</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>cryptex command staff</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>
</LanguageData>