<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Augustus_Autumn.description>Colonel Autumn of the 英克雷 leads with military precision and overwhelming technological force. His doctrine emphasizes relentless pressure, mechanized warfare, and genetic superiority. Threats arrive in coordinated waves with minimal recovery time, forcing you to maintain constant combat readiness. Expect mechanoid incursions, genetic manipulation opportunities, and diseases that test colony resilience. This is war, and Autumn doesn't negotiate with inferior specimens.</FCP_Storyteller_Augustus_Autumn.description>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Augustus_Autumn.label>奥古斯都之秋</FCP_Storyteller_Augustus_Autumn.label>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Father_Elijah.description>A brilliant but utterly mad scientist obsessed with pre-war technology and utterly contemptuous of human life. Elijah sees people as tools - expendable pieces in his grand designs. He'll isolate you, trap you with scarcity and danger, and force you to raid 古老 废墟s for treasures. He's methodical and calculating, layering multiple threats while cutting you off from easy escape. Let go - but don't expect mercy. Finding the gravship is everything.</FCP_Storyteller_Father_Elijah.description>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Father_Elijah.label>以利亚神父</FCP_Storyteller_Father_Elijah.label>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Ranger_Rick.description>一名经验丰富的沙漠游侠，凭借技巧、勇气和纯粹的运气，在莫哈韦沙漠中幸存下来。瑞克将护林员的视角带入殖民地领导层——持续警惕、定期巡逻（威胁）以及牢固派系关系的重要性。预计稳定的压力与频繁的商队和外交机会相平衡。如果你通过特殊任务证明自己值得，他会亲自加入你的殖民地。荒地很艰难，但护林员更艰难。</FCP_Storyteller_Ranger_Rick.description>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Ranger_Rick.label>游骑兵瑞克</FCP_Storyteller_Ranger_Rick.label>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Tabitha.description>来自黑山的精神分裂症夜行领袖现在通过她破碎的意识讲述你的殖民地的命运。朗达，她想象中的巧手先生同伴，低声讲述着潜藏在感知之外的事物的黑暗真相。塔比莎的情节创造了极其不稳定的威胁模式——几天的超自然恐怖，随后是无法解释的平静，其中存在违背荒地逻辑的实体和异常现象。她的疯狂发现了其他人看不到的联系，引发了可怕的现象和扭曲的实验。永远最好的朋友！</FCP_Storyteller_Tabitha.description>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Tabitha.label>塔比莎</FCP_Storyteller_Tabitha.label>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Boy.description>Vault-Tec 公司永远存在的吉祥物，代表了避难所背后的真正目的——对人类进行控制实验。与乐观的同行不同，Vault Boy 的公司算法支持快速测试和可变条件。预计威胁之间的周期会更短，偶尔会出现意外的双重事件，同时也会出现频繁的贸易和社会发展机会。每个定居点都只是大型实验中的另一个数据点。</FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Boy.description>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Boy.label>跳马男孩</FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Boy.label>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Girl.description>她带着技术手册和乐观的微笑走出 84 号避难所，相信只要做好适当的准备，每个定居点都能蓬勃发展。她在受控避难所环境中的经验意味着她了解挑战和生存之间的平衡 - 威胁以一定的波浪形式出现，中间有喘息的空间，让你有时间强化、治疗和准备。她会用掠夺者和荒地生物来测试你，但她希望你成功。</FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Girl.description>
  <FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Girl.label>跳马女孩</FCP_Storyteller_Vault_Girl.label>
</LanguageData>
