<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.description>The largest and most dangerous deathclaws rise to dominance through combat. Alpha males are massive predators with thicker hide and more powerful attacks, while matriarch females are the mothers of the pack and lay eggs to continue the species. Both are incredibly deadly and nearly impossible to tame.</FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.label>Alpha Deathclaw</FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Alpha_Deathclaw.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.description>A coastal variant of the mirelurk that has adapted to sandy beach environments. These creatures have lighter-colored shells that blend with beach sand, making them harder to spot until they emerge from the surf. Beachlurks are slightly more aggressive than their swamp-dwelling cousins and often bury themselves in sand to ambush prey.</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.label>Beachlurk</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Beachlurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Bighorner.description>A mutated descendant of bighorn sheep. These hardy creatures are commonly used as pack animals and livestock throughout the wasteland, valued for their strength, meat, and hide. Males sport impressive curved horns and are larger and more aggressive than females.</FCP_Animal_Bighorner.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Bighorner.label>bighorner</FCP_Animal_Bighorner.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Deathclaw.description>A large, agile, and powerful creature with deadly claws, the deathclaw is the most fearsome predator of the wasteland. Created through pre-war genetic engineering, these apex predators are incredibly dangerous and nearly impossible to tame. They hunt in packs and can tear through armor with ease.</FCP_Animal_Deathclaw.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Deathclaw.label>Deathclaw</FCP_Animal_Deathclaw.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.description>A dangerous mutated gecko with the ability to breathe fire. These fearsome creatures have developed specialized glands that allow them to expel flames at their enemies. Fire geckos are highly aggressive and territorial, making them extremely dangerous to encounter in the wild. Their unique physiology makes them resistant to heat and fire, and their hide is particularly valuable. They are typically found in hot, desert regions.</FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.label>Fire Gecko</FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Gecko.description>A large mutated gecko that has grown to the size of a small dog. These reptilian creatures are common throughout the wasteland, particularly in desert regions. While not particularly aggressive, they will defend themselves when threatened. Their meat is edible and their hide makes decent leather.</FCP_Animal_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Gecko.label>Gecko</FCP_Animal_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.description>Some dogs are wild, plaguing the wastes and killing livestock, but tame versions are necessary for many struggling wastelanders. There are also rare cases of domestic breeds that act as companions towards their bipedal counterparts. Humans and super mutants are the only species known to truly tame and domesticate these canines.</FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.description>
  <FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.label>German Shepherd Dog</FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.description>A heavily mutated praying mantis grown to enormous size by prolonged radiation exposure. These aggressive predators hunt with lightning-fast reflexes and devastating raptorial forelegs capable of impaling prey in a single strike. Their chitinous exoskeleton provides considerable protection, and they're known to be territorial and highly aggressive when threatened. Found primarily in arid regions where they ambush unsuspecting victims.</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.label>giant mantis</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.0.label>left forelimb</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.1.label>right forelimb</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.2.label>mandibles</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.description>A radroach that has absorbed extreme amounts of radiation, causing it to emit an eerie green glow. These mutants are more aggressive than their common cousins and their bodies are saturated with radioactive isotopes. Exposure to them can be hazardous, but their glowing carapaces have some value to certain traders.</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.label>glowing radroach</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.0.label>mandibles</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.description>A heavily irradiated radstag that emits an eerie green glow. Prolonged exposure to radiation has made these creatures larger and more aggressive than normal radstags. Their meat is highly radioactive and dangerous to consume, but their glowing presence makes them easy to spot at night.</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.label>Glowing Radstag</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.tools.0.label>left hoof</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.tools.1.label>right hoof</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.tools.2.label>left head</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radstag.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.description>A large mutated gecko with distinctive golden scales that shimmer in the light. These creatures are prized for their valuable hide, which can be crafted into high-quality leather goods. Golden geckos are stronger and more aggressive than their common cousins, and their bite can deliver a mild poison. They are found in desert regions and rocky terrain.</FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.label>Golden Gecko</FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.description>A large mutated gecko with green scales and a more aggressive temperament than common geckos. Green geckos are tougher and more dangerous, with a stronger bite that can deliver toxins. They are commonly found in rocky areas and caves throughout the wasteland. Their hide is valuable and their meat is edible, though it must be properly prepared.</FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.label>Green Gecko</FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.description>A highly evolved mutant creature that combines features of snapping turtles and cuttlefish. Unlike mirelurks, lakelurks are much more aggressive and possess a sonic attack that can disorient prey. Their shells are extremely tough, and they're far more intelligent than other lurk variants. Found primarily in large lakes and deep waters, they're apex aquatic predators of the wasteland.</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.label>Lakelurk</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.0.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.1.label>bite</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.description>A massive male lakelurk that has grown to enormous proportions. Lakelurk kings are territorial apex predators that claim entire lakes as their domain. They possess enhanced sonic abilities that can stun multiple targets, incredibly thick shells, and devastating strength. These solitary giants are always male and highly aggressive, attacking anything that enters their territory. Extremely rare and highly dangerous.</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.label>Lakelurk King</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.2.label>bite</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Lakelurk_King.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.description>Some dogs are wild, plaguing the wastes and killing livestock, but tame versions are necessary for many struggling wastelanders. There are also rare cases of domestic breeds such as German Shepherds act as companions towards their bipedal counterparts. The Minutemen around the ruins of Boston in particular have used them as working and guard dogs for their military.</FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.label>Minutemen Guard Dog</FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.description>A heavily mutated crustacean that has grown to enormous size. These creatures have thick, chitinous shells that provide excellent protection against most weapons. Mirelurks are territorial and aggressive, using their powerful claws to defend their nesting grounds. They're typically found near bodies of water and coastal areas, scavenging for food and defending their territory with surprising ferocity.</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.label>Mirelurk</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.description>Despite its name, the mirelurk king is not actually a mirelurk at all. This towering bipedal predator is believed to be a heavily mutated Jackson's chameleon, sharing no direct relation to the crustacean-like mirelurks. The name comes from their tendency to inhabit areas near mirelurk colonies. Kings stand on two legs, possess powerful clawed hands, and can emit devastating sonic screams. Their exposed flesh and lack of a protective shell is compensated by remarkable agility and deadly close-range attacks.</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.label>Mirelurk King</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.2.label>bite</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Mirelurk_King.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Molerat.description>A grotesque mutated rodent that has grown to an unusually large size. These hairless, aggressive creatures are common throughout the wasteland, particularly in underground areas and ruins. They travel in packs and will attack anything that enters their territory. Their meat is barely edible and their hide is nearly worthless, but they breed rapidly and can overwhelm unprepared travelers.</FCP_Animal_Molerat.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Molerat.label>Mole Rat</FCP_Animal_Molerat.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Molerat.tools.0.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Molerat.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Molerat.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Molerat.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.description>A horrifying product of pre-war genetic experimentation, the nightstalker is a hybrid creature combining the DNA of coyotes and rattlesnakes. These stealthy predators hunt in packs under cover of darkness, using their venomous bite to bring down prey. They possess the pack intelligence of canines combined with the stealth and venom of serpents, making them one of the wasteland's most feared predators. Their distinctive silhouette and glowing eyes strike terror into those who encounter them.</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.label>Nightstalker</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.0.label>venomous bite</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.1.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.description>A rare albino variant of the radstag, with pale white fur and lighter build. These creatures are less affected by radiation than their common cousins, making them slightly weaker but also less dangerous to handle. They're prized for their distinctive appearance.</FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.label>Pale Radstag</FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.tools.0.label>left hoof</FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.tools.1.label>right hoof</FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.tools.2.label>left head</FCP_Animal_Pale_Radstag.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.description>A common sight on wasteland farms and ranches as well as small towns. It can grow fast and be farmed for eggs, meat and the occasional feather.</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.label>Rad Chicken</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.0.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.1.label>beak</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.description>A mutated rabbit that has adapted to the radioactive wasteland. These creatures are significantly larger than their pre-war ancestors and have developed a surprising resilience to radiation. They're skittish but breed rapidly, making them a common sight across the wasteland. Despite their exposure to radiation, their meat is relatively safe to eat and they can be easily domesticated.</FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.label>Rad Rabbit</FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.tools.0.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Rad_Rabbit.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.description>A clever and opportunistic scavenger that has thrived in the wasteland. These large black birds are known for their intelligence and adaptability, often following travelers and raiders to feed on carrion. While they prefer scavenging, rad ravens are capable predators that hunt small creatures. They can be trained to a useful degree, making them valuable companions for wasteland scouts.</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.label>Rad Raven</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.0.label>talons</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.1.label>beak</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.description>A hardy seabird that has adapted remarkably well to the irradiated coasts of the wasteland. These gregarious birds travel in large flocks, their distinctive calls echoing across contaminated shorelines. Radgulls are highly resistant to radiation and can eat almost anything, making them successful scavengers. They're commonly found along coastal areas where they dive for mutated fish and pick through debris. With intermediate intelligence, they can be trained for various tasks.</FCP_Animal_Radgull.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.label>Radgull</FCP_Animal_Radgull.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.0.label>talons</FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.1.label>beak</FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.description>A mutated cockroach, grown to enormous size by radiation exposure. Radroaches are highly adaptive pests that can survive in nearly any environment. While individually weak, they reproduce rapidly and can swarm unwary victims. Their meat is edible, though not particularly appetizing.</FCP_Animal_Radroach.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.label>radroach</FCP_Animal_Radroach.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.0.label>mandibles</FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radstag.description>A mutated two-headed deer, one of the more common creatures in the wasteland. Despite their unusual appearance, radstags are generally docile herbivores that travel in small herds. Their meat is edible and their hides make decent leather, though both carry traces of radiation.</FCP_Animal_Radstag.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Radstag.label>Radstag</FCP_Animal_Radstag.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radstag.tools.0.label>left hoof</FCP_Animal_Radstag.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radstag.tools.1.label>right hoof</FCP_Animal_Radstag.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radstag.tools.2.label>left head</FCP_Animal_Radstag.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.description>A freshwater variant of the mirelurk found primarily in rivers and streams. These creatures have darker shells that help them blend into murky river bottoms. Riverlurks are somewhat more docile than their coastal relatives but still dangerous when threatened. They prefer fast-moving water and are excellent swimmers.</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.label>Riverlurk</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Riverlurk.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.description>A mutated, aggressive turkey that survived the nuclear holocaust. These irradiated birds are larger and more dangerous than their pre-war ancestors, often attacking on sight. They've adapted well to the wasteland, thriving in various environments.</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.label>Thrasher</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.0.label>talons</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.1.label>beak</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.description>Vicious dogs are a nearly hairless and apparently, partially ghoulified species of wasteland canine. Ruthless survivors of the wastes, these starving, irradiated mutts will attack anything that moves.</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.label>Vicious Dog</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.description>Vicious dogs are a nearly hairless and apparently, partially ghoulified species of wasteland canine. Ruthless survivors of the wastes, these starving, irradiated mutts will attack anything that moves. Some dogs have been domesticated, even charged with guarding its owner and all their property this animal will do so to the best of its ability.</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.label>Vicious Dog</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.description>A terrifying mutated bear, far larger and more aggressive than its pre-war ancestors. The name "Yao Guai" comes from the Chinese word for demon, and these apex predators live up to their fearsome reputation. Their thick hide provides excellent protection, and their ferocity makes them one of the most dangerous creatures in the wasteland.</FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.label>Yao Guai</FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.tools.0.label>left claw</FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.tools.1.label>right claw</FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Yao_Guai.tools.3.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Fertilized.description>A fertilized beachlurk egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a beachlurk. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Fertilized.label>Beachlurk Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized beachlurk egg. These pale, sandy-colored eggs are found in coastal nests. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Unfertilized.label>Beachlurk Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Beachlurk_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Fertilized.description>A fertilized deathclaw egg. If properly incubated, this will hatch into one of the most dangerous predators in the wasteland. These eggs are extremely rare and highly sought after by beast masters and scientists alike. It can be eaten, but most would consider that a terrible waste.</FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Fertilized.label>Deathclaw Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized deathclaw egg. These massive eggs are incredibly rare and valuable. While they can be eaten, most would consider it a waste of such a valuable commodity.</FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Unfertilized.label>Deathclaw Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Deathclaw_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Fertilized.description>A fertilized fire gecko egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a fire gecko. These eggs are notably warm and must be kept at high temperatures to hatch. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Fertilized.label>Fire Gecko Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized fire gecko egg. These eggs are warm to the touch. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>Fire Gecko Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Fire_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Gecko_Fertilized.description>A fertilized gecko egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a gecko. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Gecko_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Gecko_Fertilized.label>Gecko Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Gecko_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized gecko egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>Gecko Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Fertilized.description>A fertilized golden gecko egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a golden gecko. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Fertilized.label>Golden Gecko Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized golden gecko egg. These eggs have a distinctive shimmer. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>Golden Gecko Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Golden_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Fertilized.description>A fertilized green gecko egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a green gecko. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Fertilized.label>Green Gecko Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized green gecko egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>Green Gecko Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Green_Gecko_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Fertilized.description>A fertilized lakelurk egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a lakelurk. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Fertilized.label>Lakelurk Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized lakelurk egg. These large, dark eggs from the apex predators of irradiated lakes are rare and valuable. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Unfertilized.label>Lakelurk Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Lakelurk_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Fertilized.description>A fertilized mirelurk egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a mirelurk. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Fertilized.label>Mirelurk Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized mirelurk egg. These large, slimy eggs are a delicacy in some wasteland settlements. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Unfertilized.label>Mirelurk Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Mirelurk_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Fertilized.description>A fertilized Rad Chicken egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a chick. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Fertilized.label>Rad Chicken egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized Rad Chicken egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much, much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Unfertilized.label>Rad Chicken egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Rad_Chicken_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Fertilized.description>A fertilized Rad Raven egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a chick. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Fertilized.label>Rad Raven Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized Rad Raven egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much, much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Unfertilized.label>Rad Raven Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Rad_Raven_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Radgull_Fertilized.description>A fertilized Radgull egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a chick. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Radgull_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Radgull_Fertilized.label>Radgull Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Radgull_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Radgull_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized Radgull egg. It can be eaten raw, but it's much, much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Radgull_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Radgull_Unfertilized.label>Radgull Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Radgull_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Radroach_Fertilized.description>A fertilized radroach egg. If incubated, it will hatch into a radroach nymph. These pests breed rapidly, and their eggs are a common sight in infested areas.</FCP_Egg_Radroach_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Radroach_Fertilized.label>radroach egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Radroach_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Radroach_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized radroach egg. Small and unappetizing, but edible in a pinch. Radroaches lay eggs in large clusters.</FCP_Egg_Radroach_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Radroach_Unfertilized.label>radroach egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Radroach_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Fertilized.description>A fertilized riverlurk egg. If all goes well, it should hatch into a riverlurk. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Fertilized.label>Riverlurk Egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized riverlurk egg. These greenish eggs are found in freshwater nests. It can be eaten raw, but it's much better cooked.</FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Unfertilized.label>Riverlurk Egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Riverlurk_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Fertilized.description>A fertilized thrasher egg. If properly incubated, it will hatch into an aggressive rad turkey. While they can be domesticated, their temperamental nature makes them dangerous livestock.</FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Fertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Fertilized.label>thrasher egg (fert.)</FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Fertilized.label>
  <FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Unfertilized.description>An unfertilized thrasher egg. Larger and more flavorful than pre-war turkey eggs, though some find the slightly irradiated taste off-putting. Still, it's a valuable food source in the wasteland.</FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Unfertilized.description>
  <FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Unfertilized.label>thrasher egg (unfert.)</FCP_Egg_Thrasher_Unfertilized.label>
  <FCP_Infestation_Burrow.description>An active mole rat burrow. If left alone, it will spawn additional mole rats and spread more burrows throughout the area. The rodents will defend their territory aggressively.</FCP_Infestation_Burrow.description>
  <FCP_Infestation_Burrow.label>mole rat burrow</FCP_Infestation_Burrow.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Beast.description>Raw meat from wasteland beasts. The flesh is tougher and has a slightly off taste compared to domesticated animals, bearing the marks of radiation and harsh conditions. Suitable for meals, though it may contain trace amounts of wasteland contamination.</FCP_Meat_Beast.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Beast.label>beast meat</FCP_Meat_Beast.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Bug.description>Raw meat harvested from mutated wasteland insects. The flesh has an unusual texture and a faintly bitter taste. While nutritious, the high concentration of strange compounds from the insect's diet of irradiated materials makes it somewhat toxic.</FCP_Meat_Bug.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Bug.label>bug meat</FCP_Meat_Bug.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Crab.description>Firm, white meat harvested from wasteland crustaceans. The flesh is dense and flavorful, though it tends to absorb waterborne contaminants from the creature's aquatic habitat. Popular among coastal survivors despite the mild radiation.</FCP_Meat_Crab.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Crab.label>mirelurk meat</FCP_Meat_Crab.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Herptile.description>Lean meat from wasteland reptiles and amphibians. The flesh is stringy but edible, with a slightly gamey flavor. These creatures are particularly adept at storing radiation in their tissues, making the meat more contaminated than most.</FCP_Meat_Herptile.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Herptile.label>herptile meat</FCP_Meat_Herptile.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.description>Exceptionally fat and juicy meat from well-fed mutant insects. The tissue is swollen with nutritious compounds, making it more palatable than typical bug meat. Wasteland survivors prize these cuts, though they still carry moderate toxicity from the creature's irradiated diet.</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.label>plumb bug meat</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Bug.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.description>Exceptionally meaty cuts from well-fed wasteland birds. The breast meat is thick and juicy, rivaling pre-war poultry in quality. Despite the radiation, this is considered a premium food source in the wasteland.</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.label>plumb irradiated poultry</FCP_Meat_Plumb_Poultry.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Poultry.description>Meat from mutated wasteland birds. The flesh is recognizable as poultry but has an off-color tint and unusual smell from radiation exposure. While still edible and familiar in texture, it's clearly not from any pre-war chicken.</FCP_Meat_Poultry.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Poultry.label>irradiated poultry</FCP_Meat_Poultry.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.description>Exceptionally high-quality meat from a healthy, well-fed wasteland beast. The muscle tissue is well-marbled and surprisingly clean considering its origins. Prime cuts like these are rare finds and command premium prices. Still carries minimal radiation exposure from the wasteland environment.</FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.label>prime beast meat</FCP_Meat_Prime_Beast.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.description>Superior quality reptilian meat from a well-developed specimen. The muscle tissue is firm and properly developed, offering better texture and flavor than typical herptile meat. Even prime specimens carry moderate radiation from their wasteland diet.</FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.label>prime herptile meat</FCP_Meat_Prime_Herptile.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.description>Surprisingly good meat from a healthy wasteland varmint. The animal was well-fed and its meat is tender despite the small size. These cuts are prized by survivors who know how to prepare them properly. Still moderately radioactive.</FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.label>prime varmint meat</FCP_Meat_Prime_Varmint.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.description>Delicate, flavorful meat from wasteland fish. Its texture is tender and moist, making it a rare delicacy among survivors. While highly nutritious, it may still carry trace contaminants from irradiated waters.</FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.label>succulent fish meat</FCP_Meat_Succulent_Fish.label>
  <FCP_Meat_Varmint.description>Small game meat from wasteland rodents and other vermin. The portions are meager and the meat quality is poor, but beggars can't be choosers. These scavengers accumulate significant radiation from eating contaminated food scraps.</FCP_Meat_Varmint.description>
  <FCP_Meat_Varmint.label>varmint meat</FCP_Meat_Varmint.label>
</LanguageData>