<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Crashlanded.description>あなたの飛行船は荒れ地の上でばらばらになり、あなた方のうち 3 名はかろうじて生きて降りてきました。難破船は物資を砂漠中に散らばったため、飛行船の墜落現場を家に変えるチャンスが 1 つだけあります。</Crashlanded.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.summary>3 人の生存者、墜落した飛行船、そして荒野への定住を目指して撃たれた 1 人。</Crashlanded.scenario.summary>
  <LostTribe.description>あなたの部族は鋼鉄の戦闘機械によって焼き尽くされ、運べる物を持って逃げたのは 5 人だけでした。今、あなたは古いやり方を長く生かし続けて、塵、骨、スクラップから新しい家を立ち上げなければなりません。

注: あなたは貧しく、空腹で、廃棄物の技術からははるかに遅れた状態で始まります。これは難しいシナリオです。</LostTribe.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.summary>滅びた部族の5人の生存者が、伝統と根性だけで再建を試みる。難しい。</LostTribe.scenario.summary>
  <NakedBrutality.description>誰かがあなたを裸にし、強盗し、裸のまま荒野に捨てて死にました。装備も食料も味方もナイフさえもありません。もしあなたがこれを生き延びるなら、それはあなたが死肉になることを拒否したからです。

警告: このシナリオは非常に不公平です。死は愚かな理由で急速に訪れることがあります。</NakedBrutality.description>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>一人の裸のウェイストランド人が何も持たずに死んだまま放置された。非常に困難で不公平です。</NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>
  <TheRichExplorer.description>あなたは金庫室の扉の向こうで、安全な場所、柔らかいベッド、そして旧世界の嘘に囲まれて生まれました。埋もれたままではなく、最高の装備を携えて、本当の荒野を探しに行きました。今、あなたのポッドはあなたを友好的な道路からはるか遠くに落とし、保管庫の物資だけを持って一人になり、誰もあなたを助けに来ません。

注: 強力な装備でもすべての弱点をカバーできるわけではありません。これは特に難しいゲーム初期のシナリオです。</TheRichExplorer.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>装備の整った Vault の住人が、物語ではなく現実の荒れ地を追いかけています。余計に難しい。</TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>
  <TheGravship.description>戦前の REPCONN 航空機である Helixen は、軌道リレーにドッキングされています。乗組員がシステムの回収を始めると、これが普通の戦前の隠し場所ではなく、ロボットのビーコンであることに気付きます。リレーがパチパチ音を立てて生命を吹き込み、遠く離れたロボット指令ハブに戦争警報を放送します。彼らは今あなたを追いかけており、あなたがどこへ行っても最終的にはあなたを見つけるでしょう。

注: これは難しいシナリオなので、新規プレイヤーにはお勧めできません。</TheGravship.description>
  <TheGravship.label>ザ・ヘリクセン</TheGravship.label>
  <TheGravship.scenario.summary>ヘリクセン号でロボットに追われる3人の乗組員。</TheGravship.scenario.summary>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>この開始は Sunset によって無効になりました。</VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>障害のある新王国</VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>
  <VFES_Bandits.description>この入植者シナリオは Sunset によって無効になりました。</VFES_Bandits.description>
  <VFES_Bandits.label>障害のある盗賊</VFES_Bandits.label>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.description>A wandering band of super mutants has broken from the chaos of the wasteland, bringing with them a cache of refined FEV doses, and just enough salvaged knowledge to attempt recreating the transformation process.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.label>Forced Evolution</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.label>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.customSummary>Start with one first-generation super mutant and two second-generation super mutants.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.customSummary>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.0.description>first-generation super mutant</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.0.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.1.description>second-generation super mutant</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.1.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.2.text>The facility burned long before you escaped it. What remained were ruined vats, sealed notes, and three living proofs that West Tek got further than anyone should have allowed.

Now the old bunker is gone, the masters are dead, and your little mutie cadre is alone in the wasteland with a little FEV and just enough knowledge to restart the work. Whether that becomes a refuge, an army, or another atrocity is up to you.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.2.text>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.summary>One first-generation super mutant, two second-generation super mutants, and some FEV.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.summary>
  <Sanguophage.description>古い物語では、あなたたちのような生き物をウェンディゴと呼びました。かつての人間よりも長生きした飢えた生き物です。たとえそれが起こったとしても、あなたは今その呪いを背負っています。狩られ、半分野生化し、決して満腹ではなかったあなたは、間違った人々があなたを押さえつける前に荒野に逃げました。

注: ウェンディゴには独特の強みと残忍な弱点があるため、これは困難なシナリオとなっています。</Sanguophage.description>
  <Sanguophage.label>ウェンディゴ</Sanguophage.label>
  <Sanguophage.scenario.summary>一人はウェンディゴを狩り、一人は人間の仲間、そして眠らない飢え。</Sanguophage.scenario.summary>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.description>Your Brotherhood expeditionary group has stumbled upon an old bunker, a potential haven. But with the valuable intel you carry, the Whitespring Enclave's visibility on you is alarmingly high. Vertibots patrol the skies, and Whitespring raiding parties are closing in. Use the intel to unlock powerful tech and Brotherhood expeditionary services, aiding your ultimate mission: to assassinate key Whitespring officials. Survive the initial onslaught and lay low; over time, the Whitespring Enclave's relentless search will wane. The choice is yours: fortify, adapt, or perish.\n\nNote: Since you start with high visibility, this is a difficult scenario.</VFED_NewSafehaven.description>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.label>Brotherhood of Steel Expedition</VFED_NewSafehaven.label>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.description>It was supposed to be another quiet night for your Whitespring splinter cell, tucked away in a secluded estate far from the main administrative halls. You do not know whether the blackout was caused by Brotherhood sabotage, a compromised security officer, or a simple systems failure, but when the perimeter defenses died at midnight your enclave cell was left blind and exposed. By the time the gates opened, there was no time to organize a proper response - only to hide and survive.
You heard your officers, researchers, and support staff being cut down as the Brotherhood expeditionary strike team swept through the compound. Whatever remained of your old command structure died with them. Now your splinter cell is shattered, your safehouse is burning, and revenge will mean nothing unless you escape this raid alive. You can wait the assault out, use permits to call for reinforcements, or try running for the hills - the choice is yours.
Note: Since you start during a raid in progress, this is a difficult scenario.</VFEE_NewFamily.description>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.label>New Splinter Cell</VFEE_NewFamily.label>
</LanguageData>
