<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFED.SurveillancePillarActivated>You have activated a Whitespring surveillance pillar. Your faction's visibility has increased by {1}. It is now {0}.</VFED.SurveillancePillarActivated>
  <VFED.IntelFromTitle>{0} has been stripped of their Whitespring rank of {1}. They have provided you with {2} Intel.</VFED.IntelFromTitle>
  <VFED.ResponseComing>Whitespring response</VFED.ResponseComing>
  <VFED.ResponseComingDesc>A Whitespring {0} is on its way to this location. It will arrive in {1}s.</VFED.ResponseComingDesc>
  <VFED.ResponseMessage>Due to triggering a Whitespring response, your visibility has increased by {0}. It is now {1}. In the future, you can avoid increasing visibility by completing the mission before the response arrives.</VFED.ResponseMessage>
  <VFED.MustHavePsylink>Must have Cryptid Insight</VFED.MustHavePsylink>
  <VFED.ExtractIntel.Desc>Extract intel from the brain of a ranked Whitespring official. They may be alive or downed, but the brain must be present. This will destroy the brain.</VFED.ExtractIntel.Desc>
  <VFED.ImperialPatrol.Desc>{0} has encountered a Whitespring patrol from {1}. They have been spotted. {0} can try to escape, but this will inevitably increase the visibility of {2}. Fighting the patrol may be dangerous, but it will keep {2} safe. The patrol consists of:\n\n{3}</VFED.ImperialPatrol.Desc>
  <VFED.ImperialPatrol.GaveUp>{0} has surrendered {1} to the Whitespring Enclave. It is unlikely you will ever see them again. Whitespring command does not take kindly to saboteurs.</VFED.ImperialPatrol.GaveUp>
  <VFED.AerodroneBombardment>Vertibot bombardment</VFED.AerodroneBombardment>
  <VFED.AerodroneBombardment.Desc>{0} has dispatched a number of Vertibots to your location. They suspect you are harboring Brotherhood expeditionaries with hostile intent toward the Whitespring Enclave.
A Vertibot is an unmanned atmospheric weapons platform designed for military suppression. Controlled from secure Whitespring installations, it is a highly effective tool for eliminating enemies of the Enclave. Equipped with advanced sensors and targeting systems, a Vertibot can detect and track targets from long distances. Once a target has been identified, it unleashes a devastating salvo of precision rockets designed to cause maximum damage and destruction.
The Whitespring Enclave has pinpointed the location of your critical infrastructure and the Vertibots will shortly begin their bombardment. Evacuation is advised.</VFED.AerodroneBombardment.Desc>
  <VFED.DivineInferno.Init>Orbital inferno initiated</VFED.DivineInferno.Init>
  <VFED.DivineInferno.Desc>The orbital beam satellites have finished arranging themselves above your colony. What follows can only be described as total destruction. The beams carve across the ground, creating a web of energy that systematically levels everything in its path. Terrain buckles and heaves as the fire slices through the earth, leaving behind deep crevices and rubble-filled craters. People, vehicles, and buildings are reduced to dust and ash in seconds. The air itself becomes superheated, creating a blast wave that can travel for miles.
There is no escape from the orbital inferno. Those caught in its path are instantly vaporized, leaving behind only charred remnants of what once stood there. Even underground shelters are no match for the destructive power of the beams.
The aftermath of the orbital inferno is a wasteland of ruin. The landscape is unrecognizable, with little more than rubble and ash as far as the eye can see. The air is thick with the smell of burnt flesh and melting metal. The once-thriving colony is now nothing more than a scorched husk.</VFED.DivineInferno.Desc>
  <VFED.GoodwillDropVisibility>Due to Whitespring disinformation, your relations with {0} have dropped by 10.</VFED.GoodwillDropVisibility>
  <VFED.VisibilityIncreases.Desc>Visibility will increase by {0}. This may lead to more and stronger Whitespring responses.</VFED.VisibilityIncreases.Desc>
  <VFED.VisibilityDecreases.Desc>Visibility will decrease by {0}. This may reduce Whitespring responses.</VFED.VisibilityDecreases.Desc>
  <VFED.BiosecuredCrateWarning>Biosecured crates can only be opened by characters with a Whitespring official backstory.</VFED.BiosecuredCrateWarning>
  <VFED.CantOpenBiosecured>requires Whitespring official backstory</VFED.CantOpenBiosecured>
  <VFED.ServiceIncreasedGoodwill>Goodwill with {0} increased by 5 due to positive rumors from Brotherhood expeditionaries.</VFED.ServiceIncreasedGoodwill>
  <VFED.NobleKilledRevenge>{0} from {1} are attempting to avenge the fallen Whitespring official {2}.</VFED.NobleKilledRevenge>
  <VFED.ContrabandArrived>Your pre-War tech shipment has arrived.</VFED.ContrabandArrived>
  <VFED.BurnoutWarning>Building a burnout intel scraper will be considered a declaration of war against the Whitespring Enclave.</VFED.BurnoutWarning>
  <VFED.ActivateScraper.Desc>Enable the intel scraper countdown, which will release a pulse every 60 seconds. This gives you a chance to obtain valuable intel, but it may also trigger a Whitespring investigation.</VFED.ActivateScraper.Desc>
  <VFED.BurnoutIntelGained>Burnout intel scraper intercepted Whitespring communication and generated {0} intel.</VFED.BurnoutIntelGained>
  <VFED.BurnoutCriticalIntelGained>Burnout intel scraper intercepted high-value Whitespring communication and generated {0} critical intel.</VFED.BurnoutCriticalIntelGained>
  <VFED.BurnoutVisibilityIncreased>Burnout intel scraper attracted Whitespring attention and increased your visibility by {0}. Current visibility is {1}.</VFED.BurnoutVisibilityIncreased>
  <VFED.BurnoutRaid>Burnout intel scraper was intercepted by a Whitespring patrol nearby. They are moving in to engage.</VFED.BurnoutRaid>
  <VFED.ContactDeserters>Contact Brotherhood Network</VFED.ContactDeserters>
  <VFED.ContrabandRecieveTimeModifier>Time to receive pre-War tech: </VFED.ContrabandRecieveTimeModifier>
  <VFED.ImperialResponseTime>Time for Presidential response: </VFED.ImperialResponseTime>
  <VFED.ImperialResponseType>Type of Presidential response: </VFED.ImperialResponseType>
  <VFED.ContrabandRecieveDesc>Items purchased through the pre-War tech network do not arrive in your colony by cargo pods. Instead, a dead drop pickup quest becomes available after some time, and it remains active only briefly. This is where you collect the purchased pre-War tech.</VFED.ContrabandRecieveDesc>
  <VFED.TimeLimitDesc>Time to receive and time to pick up depend on the amount of items you are purchasing, as well as your current visibility level. After the receive time has elapsed, a dead drop quest becomes available. It remains active only for the duration shown in 'Time to pick up'. If you fail to collect it in time, the items are gone.</VFED.TimeLimitDesc>
  <VFED.DeserterQuestDesc>This is a Brotherhood expeditionary quest. It may provide intel on the Whitespring Enclave, but it may also increase your faction's visibility.</VFED.DeserterQuestDesc>
  <VFED.QuestPurchaseDesc>You can spend intel to obtain quests from the Brotherhood network. However, you will not know what rewards a quest offers until you purchase it.</VFED.QuestPurchaseDesc>
  <VFED.Flagship>Kovac-Muldoon Platform</VFED.Flagship>
  <VFEDeserters>Brotherhood Expeditionaries</VFEDeserters>
  <VFED.VisibilityFromPillar>Visibility gain from Enclave surveillance pillar: {0}</VFED.VisibilityFromPillar>
  <VFED.ResponseTimeMultiplier>Presidential response time multiplier: {0}</VFED.ResponseTimeMultiplier>
  <VFED.EndgameText>The Whitespring Enclave, once a symbol of secrecy, privilege, and oppression, has crumbled. All over the region, Brotherhood cells and allied defectors rose in rebellion, breaking the machinery that kept the Enclave in power. Every child who now wakes to the dawn of freedom will remember the names of the people who dared to challenge the impossible:
{0}
\nHowever, this is not the end, only a transition. With the old government in ruins and the Kovac-Muldoon Platform reduced to a burning wreck in the sky, the time for healing and rebuilding has begun. Former Whitespring officials now scatter, surrender, or vanish into the wasteland. There is no denying the truth: the world has changed forever.
\nAs you stand at the threshold of that new era, you remember this chapter of defiance and sacrifice. The fall of the Whitespring Enclave will remain a testament to your resilience and to the Brotherhood's refusal to bow. You step forward into a future built on hard-won freedom, vigilance, and hope.</VFED.EndgameText>
  <VFED.EndgameWarningText>You are about to initiate the final Brotherhood operation. After the mission is complete, both the Whitespring Enclave and the Brotherhood expeditionary network will be gone. Are you sure you want to initiate the final mission?</VFED.EndgameWarningText>
  <VFEE.StartBestower.NoThrone>Unable to start because {0} does not have a dignified presidential desk chair.</VFEE.StartBestower.NoThrone>
  <VFEE.StartBestower.NoTarget>Unable to start because there is no valid cabinet room for commissioning the rank.</VFEE.StartBestower.NoTarget>
  <VFEE.StartBestower.HigherTitle>Unable to start because the target already holds a higher rank.</VFEE.StartBestower.HigherTitle>
  <VFEE.CourtRequirements>Cabinet requirements</VFEE.CourtRequirements>
  <VFEE.GrandBall.Description>An exclusive gala for ranked Whitespring officials and a few selected musicians.</VFEE.GrandBall.Description>
  <VFEE.ArtExhibit.Description>A formal exhibition for ranked Whitespring officials to view your gallery and trade political gossip.</VFEE.ArtExhibit.Description>
  <VFEE.Parade.Murder>Driven by jealousy, {0} is attempting to murder the vice president.</VFEE.Parade.Murder>
  <VFEE.Parade.Leave.Disabled>The vice president cannot leave the parade.</VFEE.Parade.Leave.Disabled>
  <VFEE.Parade.Description>A formal executive parade to send off the vice president into off-world Whitespring service.</VFEE.Parade.Description>
  <VFEE.Parade.InvalidGuard>The vice president does not trust {0} enough.</VFEE.Parade.InvalidGuard>
  <VFEE.Parade.LandingAreaUnmet>Unable to find a suitable vertibird landing beacon for the guests to use.</VFEE.Parade.LandingAreaUnmet>
  <VFEE.Parade.Reward.Label>vice president ascension</VFEE.Parade.Reward.Label>
  <VFEE.Parade.Reward.Description>Your vice president will depart off-world to progress further through the Whitespring organizational chart, serving directly under the president.</VFEE.Parade.Reward.Description>
  <VFEE.RoyaltyDead>Deserters are leaving as they have eliminated every ranked Whitespring official in the area.</VFEE.RoyaltyDead>
  <VFEE.GotDrug>{0} has sent you a Whitespring hospitality package of aperitif.</VFEE.GotDrug>
  <VFEE.TitheArrived>The contracted contribution of {0} has arrived from {1}.</VFEE.TitheArrived>
  <VFEE.HonorGainedTitle>1 Vote gained by {0} due to {1}</VFEE.HonorGainedTitle>
  <VFEE.CurrentTitle>Current rank: {0}</VFEE.CurrentTitle>
  <VFEE.CurrentHonor>Votes: {0}</VFEE.CurrentHonor>
  <VFEE.VassalPoints>Unused government contract points: {0}</VFEE.VassalPoints>
  <VFEE.ReleaseAllVassals>Cancel all contracts</VFEE.ReleaseAllVassals>
  <VFEE.ReleaseAllVassals.Confirm>Cancelling contracts will cause stored resources to be lost. Are you sure?</VFEE.ReleaseAllVassals.Confirm>
  <VFEE.VassalsOf>Government contracts of {0}, {1}</VFEE.VassalsOf>
  <VFEE.TitheDesc>Contracted contributions will be delivered via drop pods after the designated time has elapsed.</VFEE.TitheDesc>
  <VFEE.VassalDesc>You can only contract bases that are less than 100 tiles away from you or your current contract network.\nSecure more settlements to extend your reach and unlock more potential contract subjects.</VFEE.VassalDesc>
  <VFEE.NoVassalize>Can't establish contract: Too far away</VFEE.NoVassalize>
  <VFEE.Vassalize>Establish contract</VFEE.Vassalize>
  <VFEE.InviteAs>Invite as {0} (Cost: {1} Votes)</VFEE.InviteAs>
  <VFEE.Skip.Title.Previous>Skip to previous rank</VFEE.Skip.Title.Previous>
  <VFEE.Skip.Title.Next>Skip to next rank</VFEE.Skip.Title.Next>
  <VFEE.Honors.RemoveAll>Remove all commendations</VFEE.Honors.RemoveAll>
  <VFEE.Honors.Active>These commendations are active on your official. Drag them to the right to remove them from this character.</VFEE.Honors.Active>
  <VFEE.Honors.Available>These commendations are available to be assigned to your officials. Drag them to the left to activate them on the chosen official.</VFEE.Honors.Available>
  <VFEE.HonorsOf>Commendations of {0}, {1}</VFEE.HonorsOf>
  <VFEE.Honors.Reward>you will gain the commendation {0} to assign to a colonist</VFEE.Honors.Reward>
  <VFEE.Honors>Commendations</VFEE.Honors>
  <VFEE.Honor.Pending>This must be issued in a ceremony before it will become active.</VFEE.Honor.Pending>
  <VFEE.Honor.Bestow>Issue Commendation</VFEE.Honor.Bestow>
  <VFEE.Honor.BestowPlural>Issue Commendations</VFEE.Honor.BestowPlural>
  <VFEE.Honor.Bestow.Desc>Issue pending commendations for this official. Will grant the following commendations:\n{0}</VFEE.Honor.Bestow.Desc>
  <VFEE.Honor.Bestow.Success>{0} has received their pending commendations. They have gained:\n{0}</VFEE.Honor.Bestow.Success>
  <VFEE.Honor.NoHonors>Must have pending commendations to issue.</VFEE.Honor.NoHonors>
  <VFEE.ForcedFaction.Empire.CannotDisable>{FACTION} cannot be disabled as it's required by the Whitespring Enclave conversion.</VFEE.ForcedFaction.Empire.CannotDisable>
  <VFEE.ForcedFaction.Empire.FactionDiscoveryMessage>{FACTION} must be added to the game as it's required by the Whitespring Enclave conversion.</VFEE.ForcedFaction.Empire.FactionDiscoveryMessage>
  <VFEE.ForcedFaction.Deserters.CannotDisable>{FACTION} cannot be disabled as it's required by the Brotherhood expeditionary conversion.</VFEE.ForcedFaction.Deserters.CannotDisable>
  <VFEEmpire.RitualRoleTitled.NotTitled>Must be a ranked official.</VFEEmpire.RitualRoleTitled.NotTitled>
  <VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.Finished>Presidential address organized by {ORGANIZER} ended.</VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.Finished>
  <VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.OrganizerGained>{PAWN} gained {COUNT} Votes.</VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.OrganizerGained>
  <VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.OrganizerLost>{PAWN} lost {COUNT} Votes.</VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.OrganizerLost>
  <VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.TitledGained>{PAWN} can now receive the rank of {TITLE} from {FACTION}.</VFEEmpire.RoyalAddress.TitledGained>
  <VFEEmpire.BestowTitle.Finished>Commissioning ceremony organized by {ORGANIZER} ended.</VFEEmpire.BestowTitle.Finished>
  <VFEE>Whitespring Enclave</VFEE>
  <VFEE.DeserterChance>Brotherhood operation chance multiplier</VFEE.DeserterChance>
  <VFEE.NoblesPerTitle>Officials per rank: {0}</VFEE.NoblesPerTitle>
  <VFEE.NoblesPerTitleDesc>Responsible for the number of Whitespring officials in the organizational chart. By default, there is one official for each rank, not counting the very first one. Fewer officials improve performance, but also make the Whitespring hierarchy feel less active.
Does not affect the already generated organizational chart.</VFEE.NoblesPerTitleDesc>
  <LetterLabelPsylinkLevelGained>Cryptid insight gained</LetterLabelPsylinkLevelGained>
  <LetterPsylinkLevelGained_First>{USER_labelShort} has gained {USER_possessive} first level of cryptid insight! {USER_pronoun} is now an occultist.
{USER_labelShort} must build up cryptid focus through meditation. The effectiveness of this meditation is increased if the person can focus on a specific object while meditating.
Different people are able to focus on different objects. This depends on the person's backstories, traits, and ranks. For example:
- Occultists with Enclave ranks meditate on their assigned posts.
- Occultists with tribal childhoods meditate to cryptic shrines and totems.
- Ascetic occultists meditate to blank walls.
- Psychopathic occultists meditate to graves, ideally with a loved one inside.
You can see someone's meditation focus types by looking at their info card with the 'i' button.</LetterPsylinkLevelGained_First>
  <LetterPsylinkLevelGained_NotFirst>{USER_labelShort} has gained a new level of cryptid insight! {USER_pronoun} can now use cryptic revelations of that higher level, but {USER_pronoun} needs to learn them first.</LetterPsylinkLevelGained_NotFirst>
  <LetterPsylinkLevelGained_PsycastLearned>Upon gaining the new cryptid insight level, {USER_labelShort} automatically learned these revelations: {2}</LetterPsylinkLevelGained_PsycastLearned>
  <PsycastNeurotrainerLabel>cryptid essence ({0})</PsycastNeurotrainerLabel>
  <PsycastNeurotrainerUseLabel>Use cryptid essence to learn {0} revelation</PsycastNeurotrainerUseLabel>
  <PsycastNeurotrainerDescription>A one-use neural inoculation which trains a specific cryptic revelation.
The dose is administered through a specialized implant point. Once released into the brain, the mechanism forms knowledge of a specific revelation, transmuting itself into neural tissue as needed.
{PSYCAST_label}
{PSYCASTDESCRIPTION}</PsycastNeurotrainerDescription>
  <PsycastNeurotrainerNoPsylink>requires cryptid insight</PsycastNeurotrainerNoPsylink>
  <Psyfocus>Cryptid focus</Psyfocus>
  <PsyfocusLabelGizmo>Cryptid focus</PsyfocusLabelGizmo>
  <PsyfocusDesc>Cryptid focus is a special type of mental structuring required to use cryptic revelations. Cryptid focus dissipates over time and must be built by regular meditation. Losing all cryptid focus makes someone unable to use revelations.
Higher cryptid focus permits higher-level revelations, but also increases the rate of focus dissipation.</PsyfocusDesc>
  <PsyfocusLevelInfoRange>{0}-{1}%</PsyfocusLevelInfoRange>
  <PsyfocusLevelInfoPsycasts>Up to level {0} revelations.</PsyfocusLevelInfoPsycasts>
  <PsyfocusLevelInfoFallRate>Cryptid focus falls at {0} per day.</PsyfocusLevelInfoFallRate>
  <PsyfocusPerDayOfMeditation>Cryptid focus gain rate: {0}/d</PsyfocusPerDayOfMeditation>
  <BeginLinkingRitualNeedPsylink>Need {0} cryptid insight focus type</BeginLinkingRitualNeedPsylink>
  <BeginLinkingRitualMaxPsylinkLevel>Max cryptid insight level</BeginLinkingRitualMaxPsylinkLevel>
  <LetterTextLinkingRitualCompleted>{PAWN_labelShort} has completed the linking ritual with {LINKABLE_labelShort}.
{PAWN_pronoun} now has an upgraded cryptid insight, permitting the use of new revelations.</LetterTextLinkingRitualCompleted>
  <RitualTargetAnimaTreeInfo>a Mothman Totem</RitualTargetAnimaTreeInfo>
  <RitualTargetAnimaTreeNoPawnsToLink>No colonists that can link with the Mothman Totem right now.</RitualTargetAnimaTreeNoPawnsToLink>
  <RitualTargetAnimaTreeNoPawnsWithNatureFocus>No colonists with the natural meditation focus type.</RitualTargetAnimaTreeNoPawnsWithNatureFocus>
  <RitualTargetAnimaTreeNotEnoughAnimaGrass>Need at least {0} Mothman eggs.</RitualTargetAnimaTreeNotEnoughAnimaGrass>
  <RitualTargetAnimaTreeMustBeCapableOfNature>Must be a colonist with the natural meditation focus type who is below maximum cryptid insight level.</RitualTargetAnimaTreeMustBeCapableOfNature>
  <RitualTargetAnimaTreeMustBePsychicallySensitive>Must not be cryptid-insensitive.</RitualTargetAnimaTreeMustBePsychicallySensitive>
  <AnimaLinkingExplanationBase>The linking ceremony is more powerful with more participants. The more people participate, the less time the ceremony takes, and the more Mothman eggs will be restored.
With {0} additional participants, {1} Mothman eggs will be restored at the end of the ceremony.</AnimaLinkingExplanationBase>
  <AnimaTree_AboutLetterLabel>Mothman Totem</AnimaTree_AboutLetterLabel>
  <AnimaTree_AboutLetterText>The Mothman totem now has {0} eggs around it. This is enough for an enlightened person to begin their first linking ritual!\n\nThe linking ritual gives a level of cryptid insight and the ability to use cryptid powers.</AnimaTree_AboutLetterText>
  <NeedThroneAssigned>Need presidential suite</NeedThroneAssigned>
  <NeedThroneAssignedDesc>One of your people has a presidential title that requires a presidential suite, but no presidential suite is assigned.
\nEnsure the title holder is assigned a presidential chair inside an appropriate presidential suite.
\nThe presidential suite should be appropriately sized and decorated to satisfy the title's specific requirements.</NeedThroneAssignedDesc>
  <UndignifiedThroneroom>Undignified presidential suite</UndignifiedThroneroom>
  <UndignifiedThroneroomDesc>One of your people has a presidential title and a presidential chair, but the presidential suite does not satisfy the title's requirements.</UndignifiedThroneroomDesc>
  <ThroneroomInvalidConfiguration>Presidential chair not usable</ThroneroomInvalidConfiguration>
  <ThroneroomInvalidConfigurationDesc>A presidential chair is not usable because of how it is set up:</ThroneroomInvalidConfigurationDesc>
  <ThroneMustBePlacedInside>Presidential chair must be placed indoors.</ThroneMustBePlacedInside>
  <ThroneRoomImpressivenessInfo>({0} impressiveness)</ThroneRoomImpressivenessInfo>
  <ThroneMaxSatisfiedTitle>Satisfies title</ThroneMaxSatisfiedTitle>
  <AbilitySpeechDisabledNoThroneAssigned>no presidential chair assigned.</AbilitySpeechDisabledNoThroneAssigned>
  <AbilitySpeechDisabledNoThroneIsNotAccessible>presidential chair is not accessible.</AbilitySpeechDisabledNoThroneIsNotAccessible>
  <AbilitySpeechDisabledNoThroneUndignified>presidential chair not usable because it is undignified.</AbilitySpeechDisabledNoThroneUndignified>
  <AbilitySpeechTargetDescThrone>Dignified presidential chair</AbilitySpeechTargetDescThrone>
  <RoyalTitleSpeechAbilityGained>{PAWN_pronoun} can now give presidential addresses from the presidential chair. If it goes well, listeners will feel inspired. If it goes poorly, the address will do social damage. The outcome depends on {PAWN_labelShort}'s social abilities.</RoyalTitleSpeechAbilityGained>
  <UndignifiedBedroom>Undignified bedroom</UndignifiedBedroom>
  <UndignifiedBedroomDesc>One of your people has a presidential title that requires a bedroom with specific features. Either no bedroom is assigned, or the assigned bedroom doesn't satisfy the requirements.</UndignifiedBedroomDesc>
  <NeedBedroomAssigned>Title requires bedroom</NeedBedroomAssigned>
  <NeedBedroomAssignedDesc>One of your people has a presidential title that requires a personal bedroom, but no bedroom is assigned.
\nAssign them a personal bedroom. The bedroom should be appropriately sized and decorated to satisfy the title's specific requirements.</NeedBedroomAssignedDesc>
  <RoyalNoAcceptableFood>No acceptable food</RoyalNoAcceptableFood>
  <RoyalNoAcceptableFoodDesc>One of your people has a presidential title with specific food requirements. But there's no food available that satisfies these requirements.</RoyalNoAcceptableFoodDesc>
  <RoyalFavorDescription>The amount of {FACTION_royalFavorLabel} (Whitespring favor) that your negotiator will personally receive as a result of this deal.</RoyalFavorDescription>
  <QuestGivesRoyalFavor>This quest will reward {FACTION_royalFavorLabel} and thus Whitespring ranks for {PAWN_labelShort}.</QuestGivesRoyalFavor>
  <Reward_RoyalFavor>whoever accepted the quest will receive {1} {0_royalFavorLabel} from {0_name}</Reward_RoyalFavor>
  <Reward_RoyalFavor_ChoosePawn>you may choose one of the participating {2} to receive {1} {0_royalFavorLabel} from {0_name}</Reward_RoyalFavor_ChoosePawn>
  <RoyalIncapableOfSocial>{PAWN_labelShort} is incapable of social tasks. Those with Whitespring ranks have great need of social skills, so if {PAWN_labelShort} gains a rank, {PAWN_pronoun} may have a difficult time. Another colonist might be more socially-adept.</RoyalIncapableOfSocial>
  <RoyalWithConceitedTrait>Since {PAWN_labelShort} is {2}, {PAWN_pronoun} will demand that the rank's privileges be fully respected. {PAWN_labelShort} may refuse to do certain work types or eat low-class food, and will issue decrees. Another colonist would probably be more flexible.</RoyalWithConceitedTrait>
  <RoyalImplantIllegalUseWarning>According to laws of {FACTION_name}, one must have the required rank of {TITLE} to legally use a {IMPLANT}.
\n{VIOLATIONTRIGGER}, there is a chance {FACTION_name} will detect its psychic signature. This will lead to diplomatic consequences.</RoyalImplantIllegalUseWarning>
  <RoyalImplantInstallConfirmation>Install this implant anyway?</RoyalImplantInstallConfirmation>
  <RoyalImplantUpgradeConfirmation>Upgrade this implant anyway?</RoyalImplantUpgradeConfirmation>
  <RoyalWeaponEquipConfirmation>Are you sure you want to equip this item?</RoyalWeaponEquipConfirmation>
  <LetterRoyalTitlePermits>{PAWN_pronoun} has these permissions:</LetterRoyalTitlePermits>
  <LetterRoyalTitleLostPermits>{PAWN_pronoun} lost these permissions:</LetterRoyalTitleLostPermits>
  <LetterRoyalTitleDisabledWorkTag>{PAWN_pronoun} is not willing to do these work types:\n{1}</LetterRoyalTitleDisabledWorkTag>
  <LetterRoyalTitleSpeechAbilityGained>{PAWN_pronoun} can now give presidential addresses from the presidential chair. If it goes well, listeners will feel inspired. If it goes poorly, the address will do social damage. The outcome depends on {PAWN_labelShort}'s social abilities.</LetterRoyalTitleSpeechAbilityGained>
  <LetterRoyalTitleThroneroomRequirements>This rank requires a presidential suite that meets these requirements:{1}</LetterRoyalTitleThroneroomRequirements>
  <LetterRoyalTitleBedroomRequirements>This rank requires a bedroom that meets these requirements:{1}</LetterRoyalTitleBedroomRequirements>
  <LetterRoyalTitleHeir>If {PAWN_pronoun} dies, this rank will be transferred to {HEIR_nameFull} as successor.</LetterRoyalTitleHeir>
  <LetterRoyalTitleNoHeir>If {PAWN_pronoun} dies, no successor is designated for this rank.</LetterRoyalTitleNoHeir>
  <LetterRoyalTitleHeirFactionWarning>{PAWN_nameFull} is a member of {FACTION_name}.</LetterRoyalTitleHeirFactionWarning>
  <LetterRoyalTitleChangingHeir>A new successor can be chosen by contacting {FACTION_name} through a comms console.</LetterRoyalTitleChangingHeir>
  <LetterTitleHeirLostLabel>Successor lost</LetterTitleHeirLostLabel>
  <LetterTitleHeirLost>{HEIR_nameFull} has died, leaving {HOLDER_labelShort} with no designated successor for the rank received from {FACTION_name}. You can contact {FACTION_name} through a comms console to designate a new successor.</LetterTitleHeirLost>
  <LetterRoyalTitleCantBeInherited>The rank of {TITLE} cannot be inherited.</LetterRoyalTitleCantBeInherited>
  <LetterDecreeMentalBreak>{0_nameIndef}, in an attempt to release {0_possessive} stress, has issued a wild presidential decree and is now demanding that it be carried out.</LetterDecreeMentalBreak>
  <LetterRandomDecree>{0_nameIndef}, in order to affirm {0_possessive} rank of {0_bestRoyalTitleIndef}, has issued a decree and is now demanding that it be carried out.</LetterRandomDecree>
  <BestowerWaitingAlert>Whitespring envoy waiting</BestowerWaitingAlert>
  <BestowerWaitingAlertDesc>A Whitespring envoy is waiting to begin the inauguration.</BestowerWaitingAlertDesc>
  <RitualBestowingCeremony>Inauguration</RitualBestowingCeremony>
  <BestowingSpotUnavailable>No suitable location near the envoy</BestowingSpotUnavailable>
  <BeginCeremony>Start inauguration for {0_labelShort}</BeginCeremony>
  <BestowingCeremonyLabel>inauguration</BestowingCeremonyLabel>
  <BestowingOutcomeQualitySpecific>Inauguration total quality was {0}, determined by these factors</BestowingOutcomeQualitySpecific>
  <MessageBestowerWaiting>Select {BESTOWER_definite} and click 'Begin inauguration' to commence the ceremony.</MessageBestowerWaiting>
  <MessageBestowerUnreachable>Cannot reach the Whitespring envoy!</MessageBestowerUnreachable>
  <MessageBestowingTargetIsBusy>{0} is busy.</MessageBestowingTargetIsBusy>
  <MessageBestowingSpotUnreachable>The Whitespring envoy is annoyed with the interference and has decided to leave.</MessageBestowingSpotUnreachable>
  <MessageBestowingDanger>The Whitespring envoy is leaving due to life-threatening danger.</MessageBestowingDanger>
  <MessageBestowingDangerTemperature>The Whitespring envoy is leaving due to life-threatening temperature.</MessageBestowingDangerTemperature>
  <MessageBestowingDangerGas>The Whitespring envoy is leaving due to dangerous gases in the area.</MessageBestowingDangerGas>
  <MessageBestowingInterrupted>The inauguration has been interrupted.</MessageBestowingInterrupted>
  <MessageBestowingCeremonyStarted>{PAWN_definite}'s inauguration has begun.</MessageBestowingCeremonyStarted>
  <LetterLabelBestowingCeremonyExpired>Inauguration expired</LetterLabelBestowingCeremonyExpired>
  <LetterTextBestowingCeremonyExpired>{TARGET_definite} did not show up to the inauguration. The ceremony has been cancelled.</LetterTextBestowingCeremonyExpired>
  <BestowingCeremonyThroneroomRequirementsNotSatisfiedShort>{PAWN_definite}'s presidential suite does not satisfy the requirements of the rank of {TITLE}.</BestowingCeremonyThroneroomRequirementsNotSatisfiedShort>
  <BestowingCeremonyThroneroomRequirementsNotSatisfied>The envoy is offended that {PAWN_definite}'s presidential suite does not satisfy the requirements of the rank of {TITLE}. The inauguration has been cancelled.</BestowingCeremonyThroneroomRequirementsNotSatisfied>
  <CommandLeaveBestowingCeremony>Leave inauguration</CommandLeaveBestowingCeremony>
  <CommandLeaveBestowingCeremonyDesc>Stop participating in the inauguration.</CommandLeaveBestowingCeremonyDesc>
  <CommandCancelBestowingCeremony>Cancel inauguration</CommandCancelBestowingCeremony>
  <CommandCancelBestowingCeremonyDesc>End the inauguration immediately. The envoy will leave, but another opportunity to perform the inauguration will arise soon.</CommandCancelBestowingCeremonyDesc>
  <CommandCancelBestowingCeremonyConfirm>Are you sure you want to cancel the inauguration?</CommandCancelBestowingCeremonyConfirm>
  <CommandCallRoyalAid>Call Enclave aid...</CommandCallRoyalAid>
  <CommandCallRoyalAidDesc>Call for aid using a special permit.
Each type of aid may be used for free once, after which you must wait to use it for free again. You can use the aid more frequently, but it costs favor to do so.</CommandCallRoyalAidDesc>
  <CommandCallRoyalAidFavorOption>{0} days left, costs {1} {FACTION_royalFavorLabel}</CommandCallRoyalAidFavorOption>
  <ChooseRoyalPermit>Choose permit</ChooseRoyalPermit>
  <ChooseRoyalPermit_Desc>Open the permit selection screen and choose a new permit.</ChooseRoyalPermit_Desc>
  <RoyalFavorTip>You can choose one of your {0} to receive {1} {2} from {3_name}.
By receiving {2}, you gain ranks. Ranks bring psylink rewards and special permits like military aid. However, {0} with higher ranks will also need specific apparel and bedroom furnishings.</RoyalFavorTip>
  <WorkDisabledByRoyalTitle>Disabled by rank {0}</WorkDisabledByRoyalTitle>
  <RoyalTitleTooltipHasTitle>{PAWN_labelShort} currently has the rank {TITLE}, awarded by {FACTION_name}.</RoyalTitleTooltipHasTitle>
  <RoyalTitleTooltipConceited>{PAWN_labelShort} will demand that this rank's privileges be fully respected.</RoyalTitleTooltipConceited>
  <RoyalTitleTooltipNonConceited>{PAWN_labelShort} is flexible about this rank's privileges.</RoyalTitleTooltipNonConceited>
  <RoyalTitleTooltipNextTitle>Next rank</RoyalTitleTooltipNextTitle>
  <RoyalTitleTooltipNextTitleFavorCost>costs {0} {FACTION_royalFavorLabel}</RoyalTitleTooltipNextTitleFavorCost>
  <RequestChangeRoyalHeir>Change successor of {HOLDER_labelShort}'s {TITLE} rank from {HEIR_labelShort}</RequestChangeRoyalHeir>
  <RequestSetRoyalHeir>Designate successor of {HOLDER_labelShort}'s {TITLE} rank</RequestSetRoyalHeir>
  <LetterLabelLostRoyalTitle>{TITLE} rank lost: {PAWN_labelShort}</LetterLabelLostRoyalTitle>
  <LetterLabelGainedRoyalTitle>{TITLE} rank gained: {PAWN_labelShort}</LetterLabelGainedRoyalTitle>
  <LetterGainedRoyalTitle>{PAWN_labelShort} received the rank of {TITLE} from {FACTION_name}!</LetterGainedRoyalTitle>
  <LetterLostRoyalTitle>{PAWN_labelShort} no longer holds the rank of {TITLE} with {FACTION_name}.</LetterLostRoyalTitle>
  <LetterLabelRewardsForNewTitle>Rank rewards</LetterLabelRewardsForNewTitle>
  <LetterRewardsForNewTitle>To honor {PAWN_labelShort} advancing to the rank of {TITLE}, {FACTION_name} has sent {PAWN_objective} the following reward(s):</LetterRewardsForNewTitle>
  <LetterPartBestowingExtraHonor>{PAWN_labelShort} received {1} Votes as a sign of respect from {FACTION_name}, for gathering {3} spectators.</LetterPartBestowingExtraHonor>
  <LetterPartNoExtraHonor>{PAWN_labelShort} received no extra Votes since there weren't many spectators.</LetterPartNoExtraHonor>
  <LetterTextHonorAward_BanditCamp>Who should be credited with {0} Votes for defeating the bandit camp?</LetterTextHonorAward_BanditCamp>
  <LetterLabelShuttleCrashed>Vertibird crashed</LetterLabelShuttleCrashed>
  <LetterTextShuttleCrashed>A Vertibird has crashed nearby</LetterTextShuttleCrashed>
  <LetterTextLaborersArrived>The laborers from [permitFaction_name] have arrived. A vertibird will come to collect them in [laborersDurationDays] days.</LetterTextLaborersArrived>
  <LetterLabelShuttleArrived>Vertibird arrived</LetterLabelShuttleArrived>
  <LetterTextShuttleArrivedForLaborers>A vertibird has arrived to collect the laborers from [permitFaction_name].</LetterTextShuttleArrivedForLaborers>
  <InspectStringDepartShuttle>Should depart on vertibird</InspectStringDepartShuttle>
  <LetterLabelBestowingCeremonyTitleUpdated>{TARGET_definite}'s rank changed</LetterLabelBestowingCeremonyTitleUpdated>
  <LetterTextBestowingCeremonyTitleUpdated>{TARGET_definite} has gained new rank since the bestowing ceremony was scheduled. In order for bestowing to match the new rank, another ceremony will be scheduled soon.
The new bestowing ceremony will include the cryptid insight rewards for all ranks which were not yet awarded.</LetterTextBestowingCeremonyTitleUpdated>
  <LetterLabelTributeCollectorArrival>Enclave representative arrival</LetterLabelTributeCollectorArrival>
  <LetterTributeCollectorArrival>An Enclave representative from {FACTION_name} is approaching.\n\nThey will accept any prisoners and resources you offer as tribute. The one who gives over the tribute will receive {FACTION_royalFavorLabel} for supporting the Enclave.
You can expect an Enclave representative to arrive roughly twice per year as long as you are not enemies with {FACTION_name}.</LetterTributeCollectorArrival>
</LanguageData>
