<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AmbrosiaAddiction.description>A chemical addiction to punga fruit. Long-term use has caused neurological changes, making it hard to function without the fruit. Withdrawal is tough, but with time, the body can recover.</AmbrosiaAddiction.description>
  <AmbrosiaAddiction.label>punga addiction</AmbrosiaAddiction.label>
  <AmbrosiaHigh.description>Punga chemicals in the bloodstream. It lifts the mood and helps survivors forget the harshness of the wasteland.</AmbrosiaHigh.description>
  <AmbrosiaHigh.label>punga warmth</AmbrosiaHigh.label>
  <AmbrosiaTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to punga fruit. The more severe this tolerance is, the more punga it takes to get the same effect.</AmbrosiaTolerance.description>
  <AmbrosiaTolerance.label>punga tolerance</AmbrosiaTolerance.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyAsIngredient.description>This colonist drank an atomic cocktail that had pungashine as one of its ingredients.</VBE_AmbrandyAsIngredient.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyAsIngredient.label>drank pungashine-based atomic cocktail</VBE_AmbrandyAsIngredient.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyInspiration.label>pungashine inspiration</VBE_AmbrandyInspiration.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyInspiration.labelNoun>a pungashine inspiration</VBE_AmbrandyInspiration.labelNoun>
  <VBE_ConsumedCocktail.description>Consumed a nice atomic cocktail. Has a chance to provide a random inspiration.</VBE_ConsumedCocktail.description>
  <VBE_ConsumedCocktail.label>consumed atomic cocktail</VBE_ConsumedCocktail.label>
  <VBE_ConsumedCocktail.labelNoun>an atomic cocktail</VBE_ConsumedCocktail.labelNoun>
  <VBE_DrankSoda.description>A burst of sugar from a bottle of homebrew sarsaparilla provides a short-lived lift. Provides a 5% manipulation buff for 5 hours.</VBE_DrankSoda.description>
  <VBE_DrankSoda.label>drank homebrew sarsaparilla</VBE_DrankSoda.label>
  <VBE_EnergyDrinkCrash.description>An unpleasant delayed after-effect of guarana consumption.</VBE_EnergyDrinkCrash.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrinkCrash.label>guarana crash</VBE_EnergyDrinkCrash.label>
  <VBE_EnergyDrinkCrash.labelNoun>a guarana crash</VBE_EnergyDrinkCrash.labelNoun>
  <VBE_EnergyDrinkHigh.description>Guarana restores rest immediately and increases movement speed, but it always leaves a crash behind it.</VBE_EnergyDrinkHigh.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrinkHigh.label>guarana high</VBE_EnergyDrinkHigh.label>
  <VBE_EnergyDrinkHigh.labelNoun>a guarana high</VBE_EnergyDrinkHigh.labelNoun>
  <VBE_GinAsIngredient.label>drank gin-based atomic cocktail</VBE_GinAsIngredient.label>
  <VBE_RBMeadAsIngredient.label>drank mead-based atomic cocktail</VBE_RBMeadAsIngredient.label>
  <VBE_TequilaAsIngredient.label>drank tequila-based atomic cocktail</VBE_TequilaAsIngredient.label>
  <VBE_VodkaAsIngredient.label>drank vodka-based atomic cocktail</VBE_VodkaAsIngredient.label>
  <VBE_WhiskeyAsIngredient.label>drank whiskey-based atomic cocktail</VBE_WhiskeyAsIngredient.label>
  <VBE_WineAsIngredient.label>drank wine-based atomic cocktail</VBE_WineAsIngredient.label>
  <VCE_ConsumedDigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>A dose of aqua cura is active in this person's bloodstream. If they die while it remains active, the suspended repair nanites will try to rebuild them on the spot.</VCE_ConsumedDigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>
  <VCE_ConsumedDigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>consumed aqua cura (from meal)</VCE_ConsumedDigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>
  <VCE_ConsumedSoySauce.description>A tangy cranberry sauce added depth and sweetness to this meal.</VCE_ConsumedSoySauce.description>
  <VCE_ConsumedSoySauce.label>consumed cranberry sauce (from meal)</VCE_ConsumedSoySauce.label>
  <VCE_ConsumedWasabi.label>consumed xander root (from meal)</VCE_ConsumedWasabi.label>
  <GravNausea.description>Intense nausea caused by sudden acceleration or violent deceleration aboard the Hellion.</GravNausea.description>
  <GravNausea.label>flight sickness</GravNausea.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotTargetingUplink.description>Receives targeting data from a nearby Eyebot.</RobCo_EyebotTargetingUplink.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotTargetingUplink.label>eyebot targeting uplink</RobCo_EyebotTargetingUplink.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotTargetingUplink.stages.0.label>eyebot targeting uplink</RobCo_EyebotTargetingUplink.stages.0.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineLiberatorUplink.description>Receives a combat uplink from a nearby War Machine.</RobCo_WarMachineLiberatorUplink.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachineLiberatorUplink.label>war machine uplink</RobCo_WarMachineLiberatorUplink.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineLiberatorUplink.stages.0.label>war machine uplink</RobCo_WarMachineLiberatorUplink.stages.0.label>
  <Chemshined.label>rotgut</Chemshined.label>
  <Chemshined.labelNoun>rotgut intoxication</Chemshined.labelNoun>
  <DeathrestExhaustion.description>Severe exhaustion caused by prolonged Wendigo Shakes.</DeathrestExhaustion.description>
  <DeathrestExhaustion.label>wendigo shakes exhaustion</DeathrestExhaustion.label>
  <GlucosoidRush.description>Metabolic activity is temporarily increased to fight the Wendigo Shakes.</GlucosoidRush.description>
  <GlucosoidRush.label>glucosoid rush</GlucosoidRush.label>
  <HemogenAmplified.description>Blood production is temporarily boosted to counteract the effects of the Wendigo Shakes.</HemogenAmplified.description>
  <HemogenAmplified.label>hemogen boost</HemogenAmplified.label>
  <InterruptedDeathrest.description>Recovery from the Wendigo Shakes was interrupted, worsening symptoms.</InterruptedDeathrest.description>
  <InterruptedDeathrest.label>interrupted recovery</InterruptedDeathrest.label>
  <PsychofluidRush.description>Mental stability is temporarily increased to resist the Wendigo Shakes.</PsychofluidRush.description>
  <PsychofluidRush.label>psychofluid rush</PsychofluidRush.label>
  <WestTek_FEVMutationPending_1.description>An unrefined FEV dosage is tearing through this subject's body in violent, uneven waves. Their metabolism surges, tissues misfire, and the mind slips toward paranoia and collapse while the mutation struggles to take hold.</WestTek_FEVMutationPending_1.description>
  <WestTek_FEVMutationPending_1.label>unstable FEV exposure</WestTek_FEVMutationPending_1.label>
  <WestTek_FEVMutationPending_2.description>A refined FEV strain is restructuring this subject with far more control, but the process is still brutal. Violent mood swings, intrusive aggression, and bouts of instability are common until the body either stabilizes or fails.</WestTek_FEVMutationPending_2.description>
  <WestTek_FEVMutationPending_2.label>refined FEV exposure</WestTek_FEVMutationPending_2.label>
  <WestTek_FEVMutationPending_3.description>An isolated FEV culture is remaking this subject at the deepest biological level. The transformation is faster and cleaner than lesser strains, but the nervous system remains under immense pressure until the final mutation locks into place.</WestTek_FEVMutationPending_3.description>
  <WestTek_FEVMutationPending_3.label>isolated FEV exposure</WestTek_FEVMutationPending_3.label>
  <VFED_Invisibility.description>A stealthboy cloak granted by the Stealthboy device. It affects nearby observers, making their brains unable to perceive this individual even if their eyes remain unaffected.</VFED_Invisibility.description>
  <VFED_Invisibility.label>stealthboy cloak</VFED_Invisibility.label>
  <GutWorms.label>rad worms</GutWorms.label>
  <GutWorms.description>Parasitic worms found in irradiated soil and contaminated food throughout the wasteland. They consume nutrients in the gut alongside the host, causing severe malnutrition even in those who eat regularly. Common in settlements with unfiltered water or improperly preserved food.</GutWorms.description>
  <FibrousMechanites.label>cloud pustules</FibrousMechanites.label>
  <FibrousMechanites.description>A skin irritation acquired through exposure to a mysterious cloud fallout. The residue forms dense fibrous deposits throughout connective tissue and produce visible subcutaneous pustules. The infestation temporarily enhances physical capacity but causes worsening pain as the load increases.</FibrousMechanites.description>
  <SensoryMechanites.label>cloud lung</SensoryMechanites.label>
  <SensoryMechanites.description>A respiratory infestation acquired through inhaling mysterious cloud fallout. The residue lodges in the respiratory tract and nervous system, initially sharpening the senses before progressively overloading neural pathways. Worsening pain and sensory interference are the hallmarks of an advancing infection.</SensoryMechanites.description>
  <Plague.label>new plague</Plague.label>
  <Plague.description>A viral infection endemic across pre-War America. Spreads rapidly once established, overwhelming the immune system within days. Without treatment, most infected individuals die. Standard medicine can suppress the virus, while advanced medical protocols can eliminate the infection entirely.</Plague.description>
  <Malaria.label>bloatfly fever</Malaria.label>
  <Malaria.description>A parasitic infection transmitted by bloatfly bites. The parasites incubate in the bloodstream for days before symptoms appear. Bloatfly fever is rarely lethal on its own, but causes recurring fever episodes that significantly reduce the victim's capacity for work. Common in low-lying areas where bloatfly populations are dense.</Malaria.description>
  <SleepingSickness.label>bayou fungus</SleepingSickness.label>
  <SleepingSickness.description>A slow-spreading fungal infection originating in radioactive stagnant water. The spores progressively saturate neural tissue, causing deepening fatigue and diminished cognitive function. Recovery is slow. Common near stagnant water and dense organic decay.</SleepingSickness.description>
  <ScariaInfection.label>scorched plague</ScariaInfection.label>
  <ScariaInfection.labelNoun>a scorched plague infection</ScariaInfection.labelNoun>
  <ScariaInfection.description>A bacterial infection derived from the Scorched Plague pathogen. The bacteria erode self-control progressively as they reach saturation. Without treatment, the host will eventually descend into a berserk Scorched state. The infection can be halted at any stage with standard medicine.</ScariaInfection.description>
  <Abasia.label>shell shock</Abasia.label>
  <Abasia.description>Shell shock is a severe psychosomatic breakdown triggered by exposure to the unrelenting violence of modern combat. The nervous system, overwhelmed by the sensory assault of weapons fire, explosions, and close-quarters killing, shuts down voluntary motor function as a defensive response. The patient is physically unharmed but cannot walk — the commands the brain sends to the limbs no longer arrive.

Recovery occurs naturally as the mind and neural pathways slowly repair, though the process takes time. A specialized surgical procedure can restore motor function immediately by reconstructing the broken pathways.</Abasia.description>
  <Abasia.descriptionShort>A psychosomatic breakdown caused by extreme combat trauma, leaving the patient unable to walk despite no physical injury.</Abasia.descriptionShort>
</LanguageData>
