<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.description>A common sight on wasteland farms and ranches as well as sEinkaufszentrum towns. It can grow fast and be farmed for eggs, meat and the occasional feather.</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.label>Tolles Huhn</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.0.label>Krallen</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.1.label>Schnabel</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.2.label>Kopf</FCP_Animal_Rad_Chicken.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.description>A clever and opportunistic scavenger that has thrived in the wasteland. These large black birds are known for their intelligence and adaptability, often following travelers and raiders to feed on carrion. While they prefer scavenging, rad ravens are capable predators that hunt sEinkaufszentrum creatures. They can be trained to a useful degree, making them valuable companions for wasteland scouts.</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.label>Rad Rabe</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.0.label>Krallen</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.1.label>Schnabel</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.2.label>Kopf</FCP_Animal_Rad_Raven.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.description>Ein robuster Seevogel, der sich bemerkenswert gut an die verstrahlten Küsten des Ödlandes angepasst hat. Diese geselligen Vögel ziehen in großen Schwärmen umher und ihre unverwechselbaren Rufe hallen über kontaminierte Küsten wider. Radmöwen sind sehr resistent gegen Strahlung und können fast alles fressen, was sie zu erfolgreichen Aasfressern macht. Man findet sie häufig in Küstengebieten, wo sie nach mutierten Fischen tauchen und Trümmer durchsuchen. Mit mittlerer Intelligenz können sie für verschiedene Aufgaben trainiert werden.</FCP_Animal_Radgull.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.label>Radgull</FCP_Animal_Radgull.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.0.label>Krallen</FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.1.label>Schnabel</FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.2.label>Kopf</FCP_Animal_Radgull.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.description>A mutated, aggressive turkey that survived the nuclear holocaust. These irradiated birds are larger and more gefährlich than their pre-war ancestors, often attacking on sight. They've adapted well to the wasteland, thriving in various environments.</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.label>Thrasher</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.0.label>Krallen</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.1.label>Schnabel</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.2.label>Kopf</FCP_Animal_Thrasher.tools.2.label>
</LanguageData>
