<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>Advanced T-60 power armor bearing the distinctive colors and insignia of the Appalachian Bruderschaft des Stahls. This battle-tested armor provides exceptional protection while maintaining mobility, representing the pinnacle of pre-war American military engineering adapted for wasteland operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS Appalachia T-60 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>T-51-Powerrüstung in den klassischen Farben des ursprünglichen Brotherhood-Kapitels von Lost Hills. Diese Rüstung stellt das Fundament der Traditionen der Bruderschaft und die ursprüngliche Mission dar, Vorkriegstechnologie zum Wohle der Menschheit zu bewahren und zu kontrollieren.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lost Hills T-51 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>The distinctive power armor of the Midwestern Bruderschaft des Stahls, featuring a unique horned helmet design that has become their signature on the battlefield. This armor represents the Midwest chapter's adaptive nature - maintaining Brotherhood standards while developing their own identity separate from Lost Hills. The intimidating silhouette strikes fear into raiders and mutants alike across the wastes of the former American Midwest.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>Powerrüstung der Bruderschaft des Mittleren Westens</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>T-45 power armor bearing the distinctive markings of Elder Lyons' progressive Brotherhood. This armor represents a departure from traditional Brotherhood doctrine, used by saltiers who prioritized protecting the innocent over hoarding technology, marking a controversial but heroic chapter in Brotherhood history.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lyons T-45 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>T-45-Powerrüstung, die von Ausgestoßenen der Bruderschaft getragen wird und in den charakteristischen Farben Schwarz und Rot lackiert ist. Diese Hardliner-Traditionalisten lösten sich von der mitfühlenden Politik von Elder Lyons und glaubten, die Bruderschaft sollte sich ausschließlich auf den Erwerb von Technologie konzentrieren, anstatt den Ödlandbewohnern zu helfen.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>BoS Outcast T-45 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>T-51-Powerrüstung, maßgeschneidert für die raue Umgebung der Appalachen. Diese Variante verfügt über eine verbesserte Umweltabdichtung und Strahlungsabschirmung, angepasst an die einzigartigen Herausforderungen, denen sich die Appalachen-Kapitel der Bruderschaft bei ihrer Mission, Technologie zurückzugewinnen und zu schützen, gegenübersieht.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>BoS Appalachia T-51 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>The venerable T-51 power armor, a mainstay of Brotherhood forces. While alter than the T-60 series, this armor has proven its reliability through decades of wasteland combat. Its tried-and-true design offers excellent protection and has been extensively field-tested by Brotherhood knights and paladins.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-51 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>Standard issue T-60 power armor worn by Bruderschaft des Stahls saltiers. Built for maximum protection and battlefield durability, this armor represents the apex of pre-war power armor technology, enhanced with post-war modifications and field improvements developed by Brotherhood engineers.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-60 Powerrüstung</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
