<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AirConditioningUnit.description>Une machine de refroidissement qui s'installe dans un mur. Expulse de l'air frais sans forcer l'air chaud vers une autre pièce. Peut être utilisée pour refroidir les pièces en été ou pour créer un congélateur.</AirConditioningUnit.description>
  <AirConditioningUnit.label>unité de climatisation</AirConditioningUnit.label>
  <Bed_DoubleErgonomic.description>Un lit double ergonomique conçu pour soutenir la colonne vertébrale, répartir le poids du corps et améliorer la qualité du sommeil. Pour deux personnes.</Bed_DoubleErgonomic.description>
  <Bed_DoubleErgonomic.label>lit double ergonomique</Bed_DoubleErgonomic.label>
  <Bed_Ergonomic.description>Un lit ergonomique conçu pour soutenir la colonne vertébrale, répartir le poids du corps et améliorer la qualité du sommeil.</Bed_Ergonomic.description>
  <Bed_Ergonomic.label>lit ergonomique</Bed_Ergonomic.label>
  <Bed_Kingsize.description>Un lit digne d'un roi, orné de montants incrustés d'or et d'un haut appui-tête. Extrêmement confortable et beau, c'est un vrai luxe. Pour deux personnes.</Bed_Kingsize.description>
  <Bed_Kingsize.label>lit royal à baldaquin</Bed_Kingsize.label>
  <Bed_Simple.description>Un filet et un oreiller assez confortables posés sur un cadre solide.</Bed_Simple.description>
  <Bed_Simple.label>lit simple</Bed_Simple.label>
  <Bed_StoneSlab.description>Une grande dalle de pierre lisse, très inconfortable et à peine mieux que dormir sur le sol.</Bed_StoneSlab.description>
  <Bed_StoneSlab.label>lit en dalle</Bed_StoneSlab.label>
  <Bin_Large.description>Une grande poubelle pour aider à garder la zone autour d'elle propre. Élimine lentement les déchets et la saleté dans un rayon de 20 cases.</Bin_Large.description>
  <Bin_Large.label>Grande poubelle</Bin_Large.label>
  <Bin_Small.description>Une petite poubelle pour aider à garder la zone autour d'elle relativement propre. Élimine lentement les déchets et la saleté dans un rayon de 10 cases.</Bin_Small.description>
  <Bin_Small.label>Petite poubelle</Bin_Small.label>
  <Joy_Arcade.description>A tall cabinet that holds a small cathode ray display and control panel for playing a variety of pre-installed games.</Joy_Arcade.description>
  <Joy_Arcade.label>borne d'arcade</Joy_Arcade.label>
  <Joy_DartsBoard.description>A popular game among rimworlds involving throwing darts at a circular target, It's relaxing, and trains shooting skills at a higher rate than horseshoes or hoopstone.</Joy_DartsBoard.description>
  <Joy_DartsBoard.label>cible de fléchettes</Joy_DartsBoard.label>
  <Joy_InudstrialComputer.description>A desktop computer based off an old design, very inefficient and prone to crashing. Gives a minor boost to learning after use.</Joy_InudstrialComputer.description>
  <Joy_InudstrialComputer.label>vieil ordinateur</Joy_InudstrialComputer.label>
  <Joy_ModernComputer.description>A high tech computer with utilising an LCD monitor and better performance parts that are less prone to crashing. Gives a boost to learning after use.</Joy_ModernComputer.description>
  <Joy_ModernComputer.label>ordinateur moderne</Joy_ModernComputer.label>
  <Joy_Piano.description>A large playable piano for practising on, quite enjoyable and it is a great way to develop artistic talent.</Joy_Piano.description>
  <Joy_Piano.label>piano droit</Joy_Piano.label>
  <Joy_PunchingBag.description>A fabric filled punching bag to let out anger on. Can be quite calming and helps to train melee ability.</Joy_PunchingBag.description>
  <Joy_PunchingBag.label>sac de frappe</Joy_PunchingBag.label>
  <Joy_RouletteTable.description>A soft-topped bounded table with a wheel for playing roulette, a good way to train your social skills and luck.</Joy_RouletteTable.description>
  <Joy_RouletteTable.label>table de roulette</Joy_RouletteTable.label>
  <Light_ModernLamp.description>A power saving lamp that more effectively converts electricity to light, useful for lighting rooms. Will short circuit in rain.</Light_ModernLamp.description>
  <Light_ModernLamp.label>lampe moderne</Light_ModernLamp.label>
  <Light_Streetlamp.description>A tall electrical lamp that lights an area, able to be placed outside without catching fire, making it ideal for road lighting and only turns on at night.</Light_Streetlamp.description>
  <Light_Streetlamp.label>lampe d'extérieur</Light_Streetlamp.label>
  <Misc_FileCabinet.description>A piece of furniture used for organising documents and records in paper form. It will help you perform research taks faster.</Misc_FileCabinet.description>
  <Misc_FileCabinet.label>classeur</Misc_FileCabinet.label>
  <Radio_Industrial.description>An old device from a bygone era, it is able to pick up radio waves and play them back. Even on the rimworlds, there is often an old transmitter or lone radio station broadcasting something.</Radio_Industrial.description>
  <Radio_Industrial.label>radio industrielle</Radio_Industrial.label>
  <Radio_Spacer.description>A high tech radio reciever that is able to pick up very faint signals and play them back at crystal clear quality.</Radio_Spacer.description>
  <Radio_Spacer.label>radio à ondes longues</Radio_Spacer.label>
  <Seat_Bench.description>A simple long platform on which multiple people may sit at the same time, not very comfortable but much better than nothing. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</Seat_Bench.description>
  <Seat_Bench.label>banc</Seat_Bench.label>
  <Seat_Cushion.description>A simple cushion for sitting on, popular amongst the tribes. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</Seat_Cushion.description>
  <Seat_Cushion.label>coussin de sol</Seat_Cushion.label>
  <Seat_ModernChair.description>A flexible ergonomic chair designed to fit the curves of the human body, improving comfort.</Seat_ModernChair.description>
  <Seat_ModernChair.label>chaise ergonomique</Seat_ModernChair.label>
  <Seat_RoyalArmchair.description>A large, soft, luxurious seat. Fitted inside a golden frame for only the wealthiest elites. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</Seat_RoyalArmchair.description>
  <Seat_RoyalArmchair.label>fauteuil royal</Seat_RoyalArmchair.label>
  <Seat_RoyalChair.description>A comfy, padded seat with a high back plate rested inside a gold frame. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</Seat_RoyalChair.description>
  <Seat_RoyalChair.label>chaise royale</Seat_RoyalChair.label>
  <Seat_SquareChair.description>A comfortable and attractive chair not specifically used for dining. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</Seat_SquareChair.description>
  <Seat_SquareChair.label>chaise carrée</Seat_SquareChair.label>
  <Shelf_1x1c.description>A small shelf for storing miscellaneous items. Items stored in this will not deteriorate, even if outside.</Shelf_1x1c.description>
  <Shelf_1x1c.label>étagère (1x1)</Shelf_1x1c.label>
  <Shelf_WeaponRack.description>A heavy duty rack for storing weaponry. Weapons stored in this will not deteriorate, even if outside.</Shelf_WeaponRack.description>
  <Shelf_WeaponRack.label>râtelier d'armes</Shelf_WeaponRack.label>
  <Stone_Campfire.description>Cooks meals but produces less heat but more light, burns out slower than the standard campfire. As with
      all heat sources, it must be placed indoors so it has a closed space to heat. Refuelable.</Stone_Campfire.description>
  <Stone_Campfire.label>feu de camp en pierre</Stone_Campfire.label>
  <Stone_DarklightCampfire.description>A specially-treated firepit that produces a dim light over a large area. People who prefer darklight work best with this light source. Cooks meals and produces heat, but burns wood in the process. As with all heat sources, it must be placed indoors so it has a closed space to heat. Refuelable.</Stone_DarklightCampfire.description>
  <Stone_DarklightCampfire.label>foyer sombre</Stone_DarklightCampfire.label>
  <Table_1x1c.label>table (1x1)</Table_1x1c.label>
  <Table_Counter.description>A smooth, waist high surface for eating off of, commonly found in kitchens and bars.</Table_Counter.description>
  <Table_Counter.label>plan de travail</Table_Counter.label>
  <Table_LightEndTable.description>A small bedside table that has been adorned with a light, making nearby beds more comfortable. Must be placed directly adjacent to the head of the bed. Placing more than one end table near the same bed has no effect.</Table_LightEndTable.description>
  <Table_LightEndTable.label>table d'appoint avec lampe</Table_LightEndTable.label>
  <Table_Royal1x1c.label>table royale (1x1)</Table_Royal1x1c.label>
  <Table_Royal1x2c.label>table royale (1x2)</Table_Royal1x2c.label>
  <Table_Royal2x2c.label>table royale (2x2)</Table_Royal2x2c.label>
  <Table_Royal2x4c.label>table royale (2x4)</Table_Royal2x4c.label>
  <Table_Royal3x3c.label>table royale (3x3)</Table_Royal3x3c.label>
  <Table_RoyalDresser.description>A luxurious dresser, adorned with solid gold and elegant in design, making nearby beds more comfortable.Placing more than one end table near the same bed has no effect.</Table_RoyalDresser.description>
  <Table_RoyalDresser.label>coiffeuse royale</Table_RoyalDresser.label>
  <Table_RoyalEndTable.description>A small bedside table that has been adorned with luxury gold fittings, making nearby beds more comfortable. Must be placed directly adjacent to the head of the bed. Placing more than one end table near the same bed has no effect.</Table_RoyalEndTable.description>
  <Table_RoyalEndTable.label>table d'appoint royale</Table_RoyalEndTable.label>
  <Table_Wardrobe.description>A tall wardrobe for storing clothing and other items. Gives a small sleep effectiveness bonus to all nearby beds. Placing more than one wardrobe near the same bed has no effect.</Table_Wardrobe.description>
  <Table_Wardrobe.label>armoire</Table_Wardrobe.label>
  <VFE_AnimalSarcophagus.description>An ornamented burial receptacle for the honored dead animals.</VFE_AnimalSarcophagus.description>
  <VFE_AnimalSarcophagus.label>sarcophage pour animaux</VFE_AnimalSarcophagus.label>
  <VFE_Bed_SimpleDouble.description>A somewhat comfy net and pillow rested on a sturdy frame that fits two people. Due to the simple construction, quality is not a factor in this bed.</VFE_Bed_SimpleDouble.description>
  <VFE_Bed_SimpleDouble.label>lit double simple</VFE_Bed_SimpleDouble.label>
  <VFE_Bed_StoneSlabDouble.description>A simple yet beautiful stone slab used for sleeping that fits two people. It offers minimal comfort but is durable and fireproof.</VFE_Bed_StoneSlabDouble.description>
  <VFE_Bed_StoneSlabDouble.label>lit double ciselé</VFE_Bed_StoneSlabDouble.label>
  <VFE_CoffeeTable.description>A small table which makes nearby armchairs and couches a little bit more comfortable. Must be placed directly adjacent to the couch or an armchair. Placing more than one coffee table near the same couch has no effect.</VFE_CoffeeTable.description>
  <VFE_CoffeeTable.label>table basse</VFE_CoffeeTable.label>
  <VFE_DeskLamp.description>An electrical desk lamp that lights a small area. People need light to move and work at full speed.</VFE_DeskLamp.description>
  <VFE_DeskLamp.label>lampe de bureau</VFE_DeskLamp.label>
  <VFE_FloorLamp.description>A low-profile light source embedded into the floor. While not as bright as a standing lamp, it provides subtle, even lighting without obstructing movement. Does not short circuit in rain.</VFE_FloorLamp.description>
  <VFE_FloorLamp.label>lampadaire</VFE_FloorLamp.label>
  <VFE_LongPlantPot.description>Plant decorative flowers here to improve the mood of people nearby. Designed to be combined with other plant pots to form various shapes.</VFE_LongPlantPot.description>
  <VFE_LongPlantPot.label>long pot de fleurs</VFE_LongPlantPot.label>
  <VFE_Lounger.description>A reclining cushioned lounger designed for relaxation. Offers superior comfort but is not ideal for deep, restful sleep. Allows for sunbathing recreation.</VFE_Lounger.description>
  <VFE_Lounger.label>chaise longue</VFE_Lounger.label>
  <VFE_ModularCouch.description>A compact, cushioned seat designed to be combined with others to create larger couches or corner seating arrangements. Ideal for large rec rooms, lounges, or social areas.</VFE_ModularCouch.description>
  <VFE_ModularCouch.label>canapé modulaire</VFE_ModularCouch.label>
  <VFE_RoyalLamp.description>A beautifully crafted standing lamp adorned with gold trim and elegant design.</VFE_RoyalLamp.description>
  <VFE_RoyalLamp.label>lampadaire royal</VFE_RoyalLamp.label>
  <VFE_RoyalWardrobe.description>A grand, gold-trimmed wardrobe designed for nobility. Gives a small comfort bonus to all nearby beds. Placing more than one royal wardrobe near the same bed has no effect.</VFE_RoyalWardrobe.description>
  <VFE_RoyalWardrobe.label>armoire royale</VFE_RoyalWardrobe.label>
</LanguageData>