<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>Whitespring suite</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.description>A non-alcoholic, pleasantly light, citrusy, and slightly bitter aperitif that owes its flavors and aromas to sweet and bitter oranges, rhubarb, and Whitespring craftsmanship. Its recipe is guarded by Whitespring hospitality offices, and few on the rim have managed to recreate it. Drinking it induces heavy but painless vomiting, completely clearing the stomach and resetting the palate.\n\nWhitespring officials prize aperitif for letting them indulge in even more of the settlement's finest cuisine.</VFEE_Aperitif.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>A high-tech helmet with a solid plasteel-weave shell and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system backed by real-time firing solutions. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>Whitespring light helmet</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>A high-tech suit of powered armor with layered plasteel-weave plates and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system that also assists the user's movement. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>Whitespring light armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>Brotherhood expeditionary armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>Brotherhood expeditionary helmet</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>Whitespring heavy armor</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>Whitespring heavy helmet</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>An exceedingly complex facemask fitted with advanced technology reserved for senior Whitespring scientists. It is designed for designated researchers so they can advance the Whitespring Enclave's needs without rest.\n\nThe inlaid techprint synchronizes with the wearer's brain while they perform research, effectively doubling research speed while restoring rest and recreation.</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>Whitespring scientist helmet</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.label>Whitespring chair</VFEE_GrandChair.label>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>A majestic rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>grand Whitespring rug</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.label>Whitespring table</VFEE_GrandTable.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>Whitespring sign</VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>A stony bas relief of Whitespring imagery for decorating a floor.</VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>Whitespring slab</VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>An intricate rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>large Whitespring rug</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>orbital beam</VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>Whitespring mirror</VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>grand presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>large presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>small presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.label>Whitespring stool</VFEE_RoyalStool.label>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.label>presidential plaque</VFEE_SteleSmall.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential desk chair can serve as a focus for ceremonial duties and cryptid meditation.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>presidential desk chair</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>A spacer-tech Whitespring gunship designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system. Equipped with a twin-linked autocannon for ground support, these XVB02s often land in the middle of the battlefield to extract stranded troops.</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>XVB02</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.label>aperitif</VFEE_Aperitif.label>
  <VFEE_Poison.label>poison</VFEE_Poison.label>
  <VFEE_Poison.description>text_todo</VFEE_Poison.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.description>A torso-sized piece of material sculpted into an artistic form.</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.description>A person-sized piece of material sculpted into an artistic form.</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.description>A huge sculpture sized to dominate a room.</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.description>
  <VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.label>double autocannon</VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.label>
  <VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.description>A powerful, twin-linked autocannon.</VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.description>A luxurious, beautiful gold-inlaid table fit for the highborn, it is a work of art in itself. People eat off tables when chairs are placed facing them.</VFEE_GrandTable.description>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.description>A comfortable and elegant chair, it is a work of art in itself. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</VFEE_GrandChair.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.description>A decorative strip of cloth hanging from a vertical wooden frame. Appropriate for presidential rooms.</VFEE_ImperialBanner.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.description>A luxurious gold-inlaid stool fit for the nobility. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</VFEE_RoyalStool.description>
  <VFEE_Candelabra.label>candelabra</VFEE_Candelabra.label>
  <VFEE_Candelabra.description>An elaborate, artistic electrical standing lamp that lights an area. People need light to move and work at full speed.</VFEE_Candelabra.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.description>A beautiful and elegant mirror. Gives a small comfort bonus to all nearby beds. Placing more than one mirror near the same bed has no effect.</VFEE_RoyalMirror.description>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.description>A slender, modest slab with limited engravings on the sides. Steles have been used since ancient times to memorialize individuals, battles, and other important events.</VFEE_SteleSmall.description>
  <VFEE_Bomb.label>bomb</VFEE_Bomb.label>
  <VFEE_Bomb.description>A small, makeshift bomb. Can be easily defused if found on time.</VFEE_Bomb.description>
  <VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.label>unfinished organ</VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.label>
  <VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.description>An unfinished organ.</VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.description>
  <VFEE_PipeOrgan.label>organ</VFEE_PipeOrgan.label>
  <VFEE_PipeOrgan.description>An exceedingly complex stationary musical instrument crafted at a smithy. A series of tuned pipes are played from the keyboard which releases pressurized air to produce the desired pitch, which lasts as long as the key is pressed. The complex and intricate design, along with the unique sound it produces, make it an ideal apparatus for instigating concerts of the nobility as its music reaches far and wide.</VFEE_PipeOrgan.description>
  <VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>striker turret</VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>
  <VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>A redesigned cargo pod designed to bury stabilizing legs upon impact and deploy a powerful turret. Has a limited battery and ammunition pool, and will self-destruct if either run out or it is sufficiently damaged.</VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>
  <VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.label>striker gun</VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.description>A powerful turret mounted on the striker drop pod.</VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.\n\nOriginally a standard cataphract helmet, this has been modified to include a gunlink at the cost of removing the faceplate, sacrificing defense to improve offensive capabilities.</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.\n\nIncludes a plasteel-plated gas mask that offers full protection against gas-related attacks, such as toxic environments.</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.description>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.description>A glorious, long and flowing robe embroidered with intricately complex decorative designs.</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.description>A suit of heavy powered armor, built for maximum protection at the cost of mobility. Heavy layered plasteel-weave plates with solid ablative coatings stop all but the most well-aimed or powerful attacks. Neuro-memetic assistors prevent the suit's massive weight from immobilizing the wearer entirely, but the suit is still quite cumbersome.\n\nOriginally an elaborate suit of prestige armor, this has been modified to make greater use of eltex weave in order to improve the performance of psycasters. This comes at a cost of removing interfering armor plating, but enhances psychic sensitivity and neural heat dissipation.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.description>A set of pauldrons and neck guard that extends down the wearer’s chest made from layered plasteel-weave plates. While it offers high protection for those areas, it is more of a status symbol and is intended to be worn over clothing and under armor without affecting mobility.</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttleIncoming.label>armored shuttle (incoming)</VFEI_ArmoredShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttleLeaving.label>armored shuttle (leaving)</VFEI_ArmoredShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFEE_DropPodIncoming_Building.label>drop pod (incoming)</VFEE_DropPodIncoming_Building.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.label>shock officer blade</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.description>A defensive melee weapon usually assigned to Whitespring field officers of rank Private or above. While armor penetration is comparable to plasteel blades, the primary function is to dispense acidifer fluids and toxic vapors upon inflicted cuts. The effect only lasts a few seconds and is inflicted roughly half of the time due to the limited size of the weapon.</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.description>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.0.label>handle</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.1.label>point</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.1.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.2.label>edge</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.2.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.label>shock blade</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.description>A defensive melee weapon usually assigned to Whitespring field officers of rank Private or above. While armor penetration is comparable to plasteel blades, the primary function is to dispense acidifer fluids and toxic vapors upon inflicted cuts. The effect only lasts a few seconds and is inflicted roughly half of the time due to the limited size of the weapon.</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.description>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.0.label>handle</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.1.label>point</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.1.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.2.label>edge</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.2.label>
  <VEE_Gun_Fletcher.label>marksman rifle</VEE_Gun_Fletcher.label>
  <VEE_Gun_Fletcher.description>An ultra-long range sniper rifle which fires fin-stabilized flechettes with acidifier injectors. Due to their lethality and danger of falling into enemy hands, they are always biocoded and will self-destruct if their owner either dies or is disarmed. Lethal to organics and almost useless against non-organics, such as mechanoids.\n\nTargets hit by these flechettes will be inflicted with an unstable variant of acidifier fluids, designed to dissolve the target from the inside rather than destroy their equipment. The acid will rampage through the target’s body and usually results in vital organs being dissolved, however lethality isn’t guaranteed.</VEE_Gun_Fletcher.description>
  <VEE_Gun_Fletcher.tools.0.label>barrel</VEE_Gun_Fletcher.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_FletcherDart.label>acid dart</VFEE_Bullet_FletcherDart.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.label>pulse thumper</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.description>A modified charged-shot assault shotgun that incorporates mechanoid technology. Recovered thump cannons have been reversed engineered to produce a portable ranged weapon capable of firing blunt projectiles. Quite powerful but short ranged, with high performance against structures and heavily armored targets.</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.description>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.0.label>stock</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.1.label>barrel</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.1.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_ChargeThumper.label>concussion charge</VFEE_Bullet_ChargeThumper.label>
</LanguageData>