<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RB_CellWall.description>An impassable wall consisting of metal bars.</RB_CellWall.description>
  <RB_CellWall.label>cell wall</RB_CellWall.label>
  <RB_ClerestoryWall.description>An impassable half-glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof, but more fragile than a normal wall. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_ClerestoryWall.description>
  <RB_ClerestoryWall.label>clerestory wall</RB_ClerestoryWall.label>
  <RB_DoubleAutodoor.description>Divides rooms. Powered operation allows people to move through the door without slowing down.</RB_DoubleAutodoor.description>
  <RB_DoubleAutodoor.label>double autodoor</RB_DoubleAutodoor.label>
  <RB_DoubleDoor.description>Divides rooms. Simple doors must be manually opened, which slows people down. The amount of slowdown depends on what the door is made of.</RB_DoubleDoor.description>
  <RB_DoubleDoor.label>double door</RB_DoubleDoor.label>
  <RB_Fireplace.description>A stone fireplace. As with all heat sources, it must be placed indoors so it has a closed space to heat. Refuelable with wood.</RB_Fireplace.description>
  <RB_Fireplace.label>fireplace</RB_Fireplace.label>
  <RB_GlassAutodoor.description>Divides rooms. Powered operation allows people to move through the door without slowing down.</RB_GlassAutodoor.description>
  <RB_GlassAutodoor.label>glass autodoor</RB_GlassAutodoor.label>
  <RB_GlassWall.description>An impassable glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof, but far more fragile than a normal wall. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_GlassWall.description>
  <RB_GlassWall.label>glass wall</RB_GlassWall.label>
  <RB_LargeOrnateDoor.description>Divides rooms. An intricately-carved door, decorated with gold. This large, heavy door requires adjacent walls to function.</RB_LargeOrnateDoor.description>
  <RB_LargeOrnateDoor.label>large ornate door</RB_LargeOrnateDoor.label>
  <RB_OrnateWall.description>An intricate and impassable wall, decorated with gold. Capable of holding up a roof, but more fragile than a normal wall. Dignity-focused psycaster will receive a meditation bonus when meditating near them.</RB_OrnateWall.description>
  <RB_OrnateWall.label>ornate wall</RB_OrnateWall.label>
  <RB_OverwallArmor.description>A durable, reinforced armor that seamlessly integrates with existing walls. Provides enhanced protection against external threats while maintaining structural integrity. It will protect the wall under it from damage until destroyed. Must be constructed on an existing wall.</RB_OverwallArmor.description>
  <RB_OverwallArmor.label>wall armor</RB_OverwallArmor.label>
  <RB_OverwallFireplace.description>A stone fireplace build into an existing wall. As with all heat sources, it must be placed indoors so it has a closed space to heat. Refuelable with wood.</RB_OverwallFireplace.description>
  <RB_OverwallFireplace.label>wall-mounted fireplace</RB_OverwallFireplace.label>
  <RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.description>An impassable half-glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.description>
  <RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.label>reinforced clerestory wall</RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.label>
  <RB_ReinforcedGlassAutodoor.description>Divides rooms. Powered operation allows people to move through the door without slowing down.</RB_ReinforcedGlassAutodoor.description>
  <RB_ReinforcedGlassAutodoor.label>reinforced glass autodoor</RB_ReinforcedGlassAutodoor.label>
  <RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.description>An impassable reinforced glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.description>
  <RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.label>reinforced glass wall</RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.label>
  <RB_RusticWall.description>A simplistic, weak and impassable wall. Capable of holding up a roof.</RB_RusticWall.description>
  <RB_RusticWall.label>rustic wall</RB_RusticWall.label>
</LanguageData>
