<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AnimusStone.description>A resonant cryptic stone studied by Whitespring researchers. It increases cryptid meditation focus and is often used in Enclave research facilities.</AnimusStone.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>cryptic stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring cryptid forces. Whitespring operatives use these to amplify cryptid focus during ritualized study.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine used by cryptid researchers to focus meditation and study. These shrines strengthen cryptid-focused meditation for Whitespring operatives.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy armor used by Whitespring secret service units to break fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>An ornate heavy armor awarded to high-ranking Whitespring secret service operatives. Embedded cryptex threads enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.
Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.
Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with short-range thrust capabilities for quick movement in urban environments. Urban scouts prefer close-quarters engagements and quick strikes rather than static defense.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>urban scout armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor specialized for cold and arctic operations, fitted with a shoulder-mounted launcher. Arctic marines specialize in breaching cold-climate fortifications.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>arctic marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet used by Whitespring patriots, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>patriot marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of armor used by Whitespring patriots. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.
Expensive and ceremonial, patriot marine armor marks membership and rank. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>patriot marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.
Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A beret styled with the Whitespring insignia, worn by Enclave personnel of certain ranks.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>Whitespring beret</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A cap worn by senior Whitespring researchers, denoting a leadership role in cryptid studies.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>Whitespring scientist cap</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for cryptid research focus. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>cryptex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for cryptid research focus. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>cryptex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>cryptex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special cryptid-focusing materials. These enhance cryptid sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>cryptex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>cryptex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, formal longcoat used by Whitespring patriots and officers. Embroidered with the Enclave sigils, it marks membership and rank.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>patriot longcoat</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.label>vertibird landing beacon</ShipLandingBeacon.label>
  <GrandThrone.description>An ornate grand chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential grand chair grants the occupant a sense of authority and dignity.</GrandThrone.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>presidential grand chair</GrandThrone.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword refined for Whitespring security officers. Its mono-molecular edge cuts through armor with ease, while an embedded cryptex core sharpens the wielder's cryptid insight and stabilizes the weapon's high-speed response.
The cryptex core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once that bond is established, the blade responds with extreme speed and precision and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>cryptex molecular blade</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored officer's sword wrapped in a sheath of captive plasma. Targets are sliced by the inner edge and burned by the surrounding field, giving Whitespring officers a close-range weapon that can cut and cauterize in the same strike.
Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the sword responds with unusual speed and control and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>plasma officer sword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A Whitespring warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. On impact it discharges a powerful pulse in addition to the physical blow, making it especially effective against power armor, robots, and other advanced hardware.
Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the hammer tracks the wielder's timing and strike rhythm with unusual accuracy and rejects any hand outside its assigned operator.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>pulse hammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <Throne.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential chair may be used as a focus for certain duties and ceremonies.</Throne.description>
  <Throne.label>presidential chair</Throne.label>
  <ShuttleIncoming.label>vertibird (incoming)</ShuttleIncoming.label>
  <ShuttleLeaving.label>vertibird (leaving)</ShuttleLeaving.label>
</LanguageData>