<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>The remains of a Treefather, chopped down and left as a stump.</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>chopped Treefather stump</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Barkskin.description>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Dryad_Barkskin.label>
  <Dryad_Basic.description>A basic treeminder, mammal-like and loyal to its Treefather. It can morph into specialized castes as needed.</Dryad_Basic.description>
  <Dryad_Basic.label>treeminder</Dryad_Basic.label>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.description>A dryad caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Berrymaker.description>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Dryad_Berrymaker.label>
  <Dryad_Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Carrier.description>
  <Dryad_Carrier.label>portling</Dryad_Carrier.label>
  <Dryad_Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Clawer.description>
  <Dryad_Clawer.label>scratchling</Dryad_Clawer.label>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Gaumaker.description>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Dryad_Gaumaker.label>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder which specializes in pungs production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate punga fruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.\n\nIn general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Pungaling.description>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.label>pungaling treeminder</Dryad_Pungaling.label>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Woodmaker.description>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Dryad_Woodmaker.label>
  <DryadCocoon.description>A cocoon where a treeminder morphs into a new caste, guided by the Treefather's FEV-infused roots.</DryadCocoon.description>
  <DryadCocoon.label>treeminder cocoon</DryadCocoon.label>
  <DryadHealingPod.description>A pod filled with restorative Treefather sap, used to heal injured treeminders.</DryadHealingPod.description>
  <DryadHealingPod.label>healing pod</DryadHealingPod.label>
  <GaumakerCocoon.description>A cocoon where sproutlings merge to create a new Treefather pod, continuing the symbiotic cycle.</GaumakerCocoon.description>
  <GaumakerCocoon.label>sproutling cocoon</GaumakerCocoon.label>
  <GauranlenSeed.description>A seed from the Treefather, able to grow a new mutated tree and begin the symbiotic cycle.</GauranlenSeed.description>
  <GauranlenSeed.label>Treefather seed</GauranlenSeed.label>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.description>A patch of moss that grows around the Treefather, beautifying the area and aiding treeminder production.</Plant_MossGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.label>Treefather moss</Plant_MossGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.description>A pod produced by the Treefather, containing the seeds of new treeminders.</Plant_PodGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.label>Treefather pod</Plant_PodGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>A mutated tree infused with FEV, able to produce treeminders and pods. Its roots run deep, connecting it to the wasteland's secrets.</Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>Treefather</Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>The remains of a Treefather, smashed and left as a stump.</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>smashed Treefather stump</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Gaubricmaker.label>hideweaver treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Gaubricmaker.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Nectarmaker.label>sapbrewer treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Nectarmaker.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Spitter.label>spitter treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Spitter.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Stonedigger.label>stonedigger treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Stonedigger.label>
  <VIE_RelicInertApple.label>strange orb</VIE_RelicInertApple.label>
  <VIE_RelicInertCeremonialMask.label>ritual mask</VIE_RelicInertCeremonialMask.label>
  <VIE_RelicInertEngine.label>engine core</VIE_RelicInertEngine.label>
  <VIE_RelicInertEngram.label>data core</VIE_RelicInertEngram.label>
  <VIE_RelicInertIdol.label>totem</VIE_RelicInertIdol.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.description>A tall ceremonial headdress meant to mark the leader of an organized faith or wasteland cult.</VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.label>high preacher hat</VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BrimlessHat.description>A small, plain hat meant to rest gently on one's head. Those who favor it often claim it gives them the look of an old-world mystic.</VIEHAR_Apparel_BrimlessHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.description>A distinguished brimmed cap adorned with a badge of rank, meant to inspire obedience in subordinates at any cost.</VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.label>overseer cap</VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_Fez.description>A flat-topped conical hat decorated with a black tassel, often worn by desert traders, caravan bosses, and other old-road elites.</VIEHAR_Apparel_Fez.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_Rags.description>A set of worn rags meant to cover the body with minimal fuss. They offer almost no protection or warmth, but clearly signal a life of austerity and hard wasteland devotion.</VIEHAR_Apparel_Rags.description>
</LanguageData>