<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VGE_TargetingTerminalCanOnlyLinkWithGravshipArtillery>Targeting terminal can only link with Hellion artillery.</VGE_TargetingTerminalCanOnlyLinkWithGravshipArtillery>
  <VGE_LinkWithTerminalDesc>Select a targeting terminal to link with. A targeting terminal is required to operate Hellion artillery.</VGE_LinkWithTerminalDesc>
  <VGE_SetWorldTargetDesc>Set the target on the world map for Hellion artillery to fire at. Shots fired over the world map are less accurate. Can only fire at revealed locations.</VGE_SetWorldTargetDesc>
  <VGE_GravshipArtilleryNeedsVisibleMap>Hellion artillery needs to target a visible, explored map.</VGE_GravshipArtilleryNeedsVisibleMap>

  <VGE_ConfirmCrashLanding>Landing on this location will be considered a crash. Any highlighted structures underneath the Hellion will damage matching structures aboard it.\n\nThe Hellion deck plating may also be damaged and will need replacing before the next launch.\n\nSome indestructible objects underneath may completely destroy the deck plating and any objects resting on it.\n\nConsider picking a different landing zone.</VGE_ConfirmCrashLanding>
  <VGE_CrashLandingWarning>Landing on this location will be considered a crash and will damage the Hellion.</VGE_CrashLandingWarning>

  <VGE_Alert_LowOxygenExplanation>You are dangerously low on oxygen.\n\n    Oxygen in storage: {0}u³\n    Colonists and prisoners breathing oxygen: {1}\n\nWhen oxygen runs out, the Hellion will start filling with vacuum.</VGE_Alert_LowOxygenExplanation>

  <VGE_AbsorbGravheatDesc>Flush any remaining structural heat from the Hellion reactor onto this gravheat absorber, allowing for an immediate Hellion launch. The gravheat absorber will enter a long cooldown period during which it cannot absorb any more heat.</VGE_AbsorbGravheatDesc>
  <VGE_NoGravEngine>no Hellion reactor found</VGE_NoGravEngine>
  <VGE_LaunchGravAnchorCooldownInfo>However, landing in a location containing a mooring mast will completely remove the launch cooldown.</VGE_LaunchGravAnchorCooldownInfo>
  <VGE_LaunchFuelAndHeatUnitsInfo>This launch will use {0} astrofuel and generate about {0} heat units, raising the temperature across the Hellion.</VGE_LaunchFuelAndHeatUnitsInfo>

  <VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructure>Remove deck plating</VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructure>
  <VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructureDesc>Remove Hellion deck plating from the aircraft.</VGE_DesignatorRemoveSubstructureDesc>

  <VGE_MapDecisionText>Your Hellion has launched. You can now decide whether you want to keep the previous map around, or if you want to discard it.

If you keep it around, it will still be present as a colony map until you abandon it.

If you discard it, it may be replaced by an abandoned settlement, returned to its original owner, turned back into a special or quest location, or destroyed.
Please note that keeping several maps open may affect your performance.</VGE_MapDecisionText>
  <VGE_MapDecisionSettleText>Your Hellion has launched. You can now decide whether you want to settle the previous map.

If you settle it, it will still be present as a colony map until you abandon it.

If you decide not to settle it, the map will still be kept around until it is discarded automatically. It is currently kept around due to you having colonists there, a shuttle or drop pods travelling there, or some special building present on the map.
Please note that keeping several maps open may affect your performance.</VGE_MapDecisionSettleText>

  <VGE_BuildSingleGravEngineOnly>You can't build {0} if you already have another Hellion reactor.</VGE_BuildSingleGravEngineOnly>
  <VGE_BuildSingleGravEngineBuildBlueprintOnly>You can't build {0} if you already have another Hellion reactor under construction.</VGE_BuildSingleGravEngineBuildBlueprintOnly>
  <VGE_InstallSingleGravEngineOnMap>You can't install {0} if there's another Hellion reactor present nearby.</VGE_InstallSingleGravEngineOnMap>
  <VGE_InstallSingleGravEngineBuildBlueprintOnly>You can't install {0} if you already have another Hellion reactor under construction nearby.</VGE_InstallSingleGravEngineBuildBlueprintOnly>
  <VGE_InstallSingleGravEngineInstallBlueprintOnly>You can't install {0} if there's another Hellion reactor blueprint nearby.</VGE_InstallSingleGravEngineInstallBlueprintOnly>
  <VGE_GravEngineDisabled>Hellion reactor disabled:</VGE_GravEngineDisabled>
  <VGE_MultipleGravEnginesPresent>multiple Hellion reactors present</VGE_MultipleGravEnginesPresent>
  <VGE_GravshipCurrentlyActive>another Hellion is currently active</VGE_GravshipCurrentlyActive>
  <VGE_GravshipLaunchCurrentlyActive>another Hellion is currently preparing to launch</VGE_GravshipLaunchCurrentlyActive>

  <VGE_CannotLaunchGravAnomaly>Can't launch the Hellion due to a gravitational anomaly</VGE_CannotLaunchGravAnomaly>

  <VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance>Hellion maintenance low</VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance>
  <VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance_Desc>Some Hellion components have low maintenance. This can result in negative launch outcomes and eventual breakdowns. Consider assigning a colonist to maintain them. Hellion components with low maintenance:\n\n {0}</VGE_Alert_LowMaintenance_Desc>
  <VGE_SetDesiredMaintenanceDesc>Set the desired maintenance for all Hellion components on this aircraft. Colonists assigned to construction will maintain the structures if they fall below the set level.</VGE_SetDesiredMaintenanceDesc>

  <VGE_NoGravtechProjectSelected>No Hellion-systems research project selected. Launching will not yield any gravdata.</VGE_NoGravtechProjectSelected>
  <VGE_LaunchBoonOutcomeChanceLetterExtra>Based on the Hellion's launch, there was a {0_percentage} chance of a positive outcome.</VGE_LaunchBoonOutcomeChanceLetterExtra>
  <VGE_GravdataStoredInfo>Stored gravdata will automatically be applied to the selected Hellion-systems research project on next landing.</VGE_GravdataStoredInfo>

  <VGE_LaunchToOrbitDesc>Launch the Hellion directly upward and stabilize it in orbit. This is still considered a Hellion journey and the reactor will enter cooldown, potentially leaving you stranded in orbit.</VGE_LaunchToOrbitDesc>

  <VGE_RequiresSubstructureOrScaffolding>Requires Hellion deck plating or scaffold to be built on.</VGE_RequiresSubstructureOrScaffolding>
  <VGE_MustBePlacedInRangeOfGravSource>Must be placed in range of a Hellion reactor or field amplifier.</VGE_MustBePlacedInRangeOfGravSource>

  <VGE_PilotGravjumper>Launch light Hellion</VGE_PilotGravjumper>
  <VGE_PilotGravhulk>Launch heavy Hellion</VGE_PilotGravhulk>
  <VGE_GravtechNeedsGravdata>{0} needs gravdata to complete. Obtain gravdata by travelling with your Hellion.</VGE_GravtechNeedsGravdata>

  <VGE_Gravjumper>light Hellion</VGE_Gravjumper>
  <VGE_Gravship>Hellion</VGE_Gravship>
  <VGE_Gravhulk>heavy Hellion</VGE_Gravhulk>

</LanguageData>