<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)->[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] of [asker_faction_name], has contacted us with news of a long-lost starship. Generations ago, a legendary vessel belonging to a nomadic warrior fleet crashed on this planet, its crew renowned for wielding cryptoparticles in battle. The cryptoforge ship shattered upon atmospheric entry, breaking into three massive fragments scattered across the surface. To locate them, we must reactivate an alt scanning relay station. \n\n[asker_nameDef] says that initiating the scans will allow us to pinpoint the locations of the ship’s stern and bow, which may halt further clues to the whereabouts of the final, most crucial fragment. However, the relay station remains heavily secured - automated turrets still stand watch, and the surrounding grounds are riddled with a dense minefield. Worse yet, the power surge from the scan is certain to draw the attention of nearby mechanoids.\n\nComplete the scans on both relays to discover the location of the ship fragments.</VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)->We've uncovered information about a long-lost starship. Generations ago, a legendary vessel belonging to a nomadic warrior fleet crashed on this planet, its crew renowned for wielding cryptoparticles in battle. The cryptoforge ship shattered upon atmospheric entry, breaking into three massive fragments scattered across the surface. To locate them, we must reactivate an alt scanning relay station. \n\nInitiating the scans will allow us to pinpoint the locations of the ship’s stern and bow, which may halt further clues to the whereabouts of the final, most crucial fragment. However, the relay station remains heavily secured - automated turrets still stand watch, and the surrounding grounds are riddled with a dense minefield. Worse yet, the power surge from the scan is certain to draw the attention of nearby mechanoids.\n\nComplete the scans on both relays to discover the location of the ship fragments.</VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questNameRules.rulesStrings.0>questName->Scanning for the Cryptoforge</VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.questNameRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.root.nodes.0.nodes.0.name>askerIsNull</VQE_Cryptoforge_Chapter1.root.nodes.0.nodes.0.name>
</LanguageData>
