<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>A large Corvega automated field machine that combines sowing and harvesting across a designated outdoor zone. It deposits harvested goods into attached factory hoppers or drops them on the ground if hoppers are not present, and can be set to cycle automatically once most plants in the zone are fully grown.</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>agri-industrial harvester</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>A Corvega automated refinery that converts biological matter such as wood and plant stock into chemfuel.
Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>Corvega oil refinery</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>An automated Corvega deep extraction rig for pulling stone and buried metals up from the crust. Works machinery needs hoppers for intake and output, throws off serious heat, and can be overclocked at the cost of even greater draw and temperature.</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>Corvega drill platform</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>An industrial Corvega masonry saw capable of cutting stone chunks into usable blocks.
Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>automated masonry line</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>A Corvega automated smelter that extracts usable metal from slag chunks, broken-down weapons, apparel, stone chunks, and mechanoid corpses using strong electromagnets and industrial heat.
Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>A basic industrial conveyor for moving materials between work cells with minimal labor handling.</VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>industrial conveyor</VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>Stores feedstock and finished goods for automated Corvega works machinery.</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>works hopper</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>A buried intake point that lets an industrial conveyor run beneath short stretches of ground before resurfacing.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>buried conveyor intake</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>A buried discharge point that brings an underground conveyor back to the surface near the next work cell.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>buried conveyor discharge</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>
</LanguageData>
