<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VDE_Gaubricmaker.description>Đẳng cấp thợ đốn cây chuyên sản xuất những tấm da xù xì như da. Cùng với Treefather, nó có thể bị cắt liên tục để lấy vật liệu mềm, cách nhiệt, mặc dù nó hoạt động chậm và không hiệu quả khi làm việc hoặc chiến đấu.</VDE_Gaubricmaker.description>
  <VDE_Nectarmaker.description>Một đẳng cấp tò mò chuyên trồng cây chuyên sản xuất nhựa cây tiếp thêm sinh lực. Cùng với Treefather, nó có thể liên tục tạo ra loại cây kích thích này, nhưng nó hoàn toàn không có khả năng tự vệ và cần được bảo vệ cẩn thận.</VDE_Nectarmaker.description>
  <VDE_Spitter.description>Một đẳng cấp thợ chăm sóc cây chuyên bảo vệ lãnh thổ có thể phóng những viên đạn có tính ăn mòn. Mặc dù nó có thể gây ra sát thương cực lớn nhưng nó vẫn dễ bị tổn thương trong cận chiến do hàm quá khổ.</VDE_Spitter.description>
  <VDE_Stonedigger.description>Một đẳng cấp thợ chăm sóc cây cực kỳ dễ tính chuyên kéo những khối đá lên. Nó hấp thụ khoáng chất từ ​​mặt đất để làm cứng lớp da của mình trong khi để những mảnh quá khổ sang một bên.</VDE_Stonedigger.description>
  <Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies.</Barkskin.description>
  <Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Barkskin.label>
  <Berrymaker.description>A treeminder caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. It is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Berrymaker.description>
  <Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Berrymaker.label>
  <Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Carrier.description>
  <Carrier.label>portling</Carrier.label>
  <Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation.</Clawer.description>
  <Clawer.label>scratchling</Clawer.label>
  <Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process.</Gaumaker.description>
  <Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Gaumaker.label>
  <Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Medicinemaker.description>
  <Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Medicinemaker.label>
  <Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Woodmaker.description>
  <Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Woodmaker.label>
  <Pungaling.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder which specializes in punga production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate punga fruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Pungaling.description>
  <Pungaling.label>pungaling</Pungaling.label>
</LanguageData>
