<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.description>Low-tech, homemade armour with a barbaric appearance. It varies in quality and appearance with most consisting of scrap metal plates melded into armor pieces reinforced by metal bars along with wires fastened together by leather straps.The heavy raider armor is usually reserved for leaders and others who bellow orders to the gang. While it protects a whole lot better than the other version, it is also bulky and heavy, severely impairing the wearers freedom of movement.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.label>Heavy Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Heavy.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.description>Low-tech, homemade armour with a barbaric appearance. It varies in quality and appearance with most consisting of scrap metal plates melded into armor pieces reinforced by metal bars along with wires fastened together by leather straps. The light version of the raider armor provides only basic protection but is less heavy than other variants. Not the best armor, but certainly better than nothing.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.label>Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Light.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.description>Low-tech, homemade armour with a barbaric appearance. It varies in quality and appearance with most consisting of scrap metal plates melded into armor pieces reinforced by metal bars along with wires fastened together by leather straps.This version offers slightly more protection than the lighter version, but still isn’t that great. Plus, it weighs a whole lot more</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.label>Sturdy Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Armor_Medium.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.description>A piece of tattered clothing, wrapped up in some places with duct tape, a wide leather belt, and black combat boots. These clothes are often worn by raiders and provide barely any protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.label>Raider Badlands Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Badlands_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.description>A leather coat covered in an excessive number of rags, chains, and metal plates with pieces of rebar welded onto them. As far as raider armors go, this one protects fairly well, but in turn is quite heavy. Usually worn by raiders with (some) self-preservation instinct.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.label>Raider Blastmaster Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Blastmaster_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.description>A long leather duster worn by raider leaders and those who have survived long enough to earn some respect. Offers better protection than basic raider armor while maintaining an intimidating appearance.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.label>Raider Leather Coat</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leather_Coat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.description>A crude leather outfit cobbled together from various animal hides and scraps. While offering minimal protection, it's lightweight and allows for quick movement - essential for hit-and-run raider tactics.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.label>Raider Leathers</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Leathers.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.description>A piece of tattered clothing, wrapped up in some places with duct tape, a wide leather belt, and black combat boots. These clothes are often worn by raiders and provide barely any protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.label>Raider Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Long_Johns.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.description>A piece of tattered clothing, wrapped up in some places with duct tape, a wide leather belt, and black combat boots. These clothes are often worn by raiders and provide barely any protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.label>Raider Painspike Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Painspike_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.description>This archaic armor consists of metal chaps and a leather plate of sorts worn on the left shoulder. It leaves the shoulders of its wearer bare and unprotected. Most raiders care little about that though, as its primary use is intimidation of the foe.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.label>Raider Sadist Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Sadist_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.description>Makeshift armor constructed from scavenged tire rubber and metal scraps. The thick rubber provides decent protection against blunt impacts while remaining surprisingly flexible. Popular among raiders who value mobility over heavy protection.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.label>Raider Tire Armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Tire_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
