<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Baseliner.description>Wastelanders are the backbone of the post-nuclear world. Neither mutants nor vault-born, they are scavengers, traders, raiders, and settlers who made the open scars of the earth their home. Every scar tells a story, every bruise a lesson. They are the living testament that humanity can survive anything—even itself.</Baseliner.description>
  <Baseliner.label>Wastelander</Baseliner.label>
  <Sanguophage.description>Once human, now cursed by hunger and cold, the Wendigo are vampiric remnants of the old world’s darkest corners. Their bodies are gaunt, their skin pale as frost, their eyes burning with feral hunger. They feed on blood and flesh not by choice, but by the whisper of something ancient and terrible that will not let them die.</Sanguophage.description>
  <Sanguophage.label>Wendigo</Sanguophage.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_Atlantic.description>When the bombs fell, the East Coast’s dense cities became tombs of glass and steel. Those who endured the fallout adapted to life in shattered high-rises and flooded metro tunnels. The Atlantic people are resourceful, tech-savvy scavengers who learned to thrive amidst rust, rain, and radiation. They speak with the echo of a thousand pre-war voices, clinging to fragments of the old world’s ambition.</WestTek_Xenotype_Atlantic.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_Atlantic.label>Atlantic</WestTek_Xenotype_Atlantic.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_Cascadia.description>In the forests of old Cascadia, the sky froze before the earth burned. When nuclear winter blanketed the Northwest, small enclaves learned to live beneath the ash and snow. They are stoic, quiet survivalists—hunters, herbalists, and scavengers who built warmth from ruin. The cold sharpened them, and they speak in whispers like the wind through pine needles.</WestTek_Xenotype_Cascadia.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_Cascadia.label>Cascadia</WestTek_Xenotype_Cascadia.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_NatL.description>On the Colorado Plateau, nature reclaimed what mankind lost. Small, diverse groups survived in hidden canyons, ancient ruins, and red-rock sanctuaries. The Nat’L are stewards of the wilderness, descendants of hikers, rangers, and wanderers who refused to abandon the land. They hold a quiet reverence for the world that was and the world that yet survives.</WestTek_Xenotype_NatL.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_NatL.label>Nat'L</WestTek_Xenotype_NatL.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico.description>In the ashes of the Southwest, the Rio Grande became a lifeline for those who refused to die divided. Nuevo Texico rose from the union of Americans and Mexicans who shed the old borders. Their blood carries two nations, their speech blends two tongues, and their culture is a hymn to survival, sung in both sun and dust.</WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico.label>Nuevo Texico</WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_Numen.description>Numen are the green children of the wasteland—mutants born where nature refused to die. Vines lace their veins, their skin glows faintly with bioluminescent life, and their breath carries the scent of moss and decay. They are patient, serene, and unsettling, speaking softly of the forests that dream beneath the ruins.</WestTek_Xenotype_Numen.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_Numen.label>Numen</WestTek_Xenotype_Numen.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_PureHumans.description>Pure humans are rare—descendants of vault-born bloodlines, preserved genetics, or sheer luck. They see themselves as the last unbroken line of humanity, though in a world reborn through mutation, that purity can be a curse. To some, they are relics; to others, they are hope made flesh.</WestTek_Xenotype_PureHumans.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_PureHumans.label>Pure Humans</WestTek_Xenotype_PureHumans.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter.description>Slanters are the shadow-folk of the wastes—lean, fast, and pale-skinned from lives spent beneath the surface or under the ruins. Their bodies have grown agile, their eyes wide, their senses sharp. To survive, they learned to vanish: to slip between light and dark, scavenging what others leave behind. Some call them cowards; others call them ghosts.</WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter.label>S'Lanter</WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant.description>Super Mutants are the children of the wasteland’s cruel experiments. Towering, musclebound, and nearly immortal, they are the outcome of forced evolution and forgotten ambition. Though often seen as monsters, some retain fractured shards of who they were—flickers of humanity behind monstrous eyes.</WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant.label>Super Mutant</WestTek_Xenotype_SuperMutant.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_TwoCalifornia.description>California burned twice—first in the blast, then in the cold. The survivors of both sides—American and Baja—bear the scars of nuclear hellfire and the ice that followed. The Two Californias forged a bitter unity, rebuilding from the bones of cities and the ghosts of surf and sand. They remember paradise, and they remember its end.</WestTek_Xenotype_TwoCalifornia.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_TwoCalifornia.label>Two California</WestTek_Xenotype_TwoCalifornia.label>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_VaultDweller.description>Vault Dwellers grew up behind steel doors and sterile lights, sheltered from the chaos above. When the world outside decayed, they evolved within—disciplined, educated, but naive to the raw savagery of the surface. Some see them as saviors. Others, as pampered relics playing hero in a world that forgot their comfort.</WestTek_Xenotype_VaultDweller.description>
  <WestTek_Xenotype_VaultDweller.label>Vault Dweller</WestTek_Xenotype_VaultDweller.label>
</LanguageData>