<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- FCP_Animal_Radroach -->
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.label>radroach</FCP_Animal_Radroach.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.description>A mutated cockroach, grown to enormous size by radiation exposure. Radroaches are highly adaptive pests that can survive in nearly any environment. While individually weak, they reproduce rapidly and can swarm unwary victims. Their meat is edible, though not particularly appetizing.</FCP_Animal_Radroach.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.0.label>mandibles</FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Radroach.tools.1.label>

  <!-- FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach -->
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.label>glowing radroach</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.description>A radroach that has absorbed extreme amounts of radiation, causing it to emit an eerie green glow. These mutants are more aggressive than their common cousins and their bodies are saturated with radioactive isotopes. Exposure to them can be hazardous, but their glowing carapaces have some value to certain traders.</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.0.label>mandibles</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Glowing_Radroach.tools.1.label>

  <!-- FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis -->
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.label>giant mantis</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.description>A heavily mutated praying mantis grown to enormous size by prolonged radiation exposure. These aggressive predators hunt with lightning-fast reflexes and devastating raptorial forelegs capable of impaling prey in a single strike. Their chitinous exoskeleton provides considerable protection, and they're known to be territorial and highly aggressive when threatened. Found primarily in arid regions where they ambush unsuspecting victims.</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.0.label>left forelimb</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.1.label>right forelimb</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.2.label>mandibles</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.2.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.3.label>head</FCP_Animal_Giant_Mantis.tools.3.label>
</LanguageData>
