<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor -->
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.label>Blamco Original Flavor</FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.description>A surprisingly well-preserved fast-food product from before the war. It’s a rectangular box filled with a mix of macaroni and cheese, a staple of pre-war American cuisine and as such is a common sight in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor -->
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.label>Blamco Extra Cheezy Flavor</FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.description>A surprisingly well-preserved fast-food product from before the war. It’s a rectangular box filled with a mix of macaroni and cheese, a staple of pre-war American cuisine and as such is a common sight in the wasteland. This seems to be the Extra Cheezy variation, adding slightly more calories to your meal.</FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Cram -->
  <FCP_Food_Cram.label>Cram</FCP_Food_Cram.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram.description>A tin can full of processed meat. Its main ingredients are pork and ham pressed into form and hold together by gelatine. It’s filled with enough preservatives to be edible over 200 years after its fabrication and is a common and popular ration for soldiers in the NCR due to its high calorie content.</FCP_Food_Cram.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium -->
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.label>Cram Low Sodium</FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.description>A high-quality packaged meal, manufactured for use in survival situations. While it never rots, it can still deteriorate if left outside. Great for traveling.</FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Cram_Family_Size -->
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Family_Size.label>Cram family size</FCP_Food_Cram_Family_Size.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Family_Size.description>A large, family-sized can of Cram. This bulk packaging was marketed to pre-war families as an economical option for feeding multiple people. Contains significantly more of the processed meat product than standard cans, making it a valuable find in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Cram_Family_Size.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples -->
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.label>Dandy Boy Apples</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.label>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.description>Candied apples contained in a red cardboard box, a popular pre-war snack, made by the Dandy Boy company. The staggering amount of sugar and preservatives added to the product ensures its edibility even 200 years later.</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples -->
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.label>Dandy Boy Caramel Apples</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.label>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.description>Candied apples contained in a red cardboard box, a popular pre-war snack, made by the Dandy Boy company. The staggering amount of sugar and preservatives added to the product ensures its edibility even 200 years later. This variation seems to have a delicious caramel shell!</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes -->
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.label>Fancy Lad Snack Cakes</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.label>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.description>Pre-war snack cakes packed up in a small box. Bite-sized pieces of cake with icing, these snacks are nearly unperishable and still serve as a sugary, sweet treat 200 years after their making.</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor -->
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.label>Fancy Lad Snack Cakes Buzzbite Flavor</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.description>Pre-war snack cakes packed up in a small box. Bite-sized pieces of cake with icing, these snacks are nearly unperishable and still serve as a sugary, sweet treat 200 years after their making. Be sure to look out for this version as it is the limited edition Buzzbite Flavor!</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Gum_Drops -->
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.label>Gum Drops</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.label>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.description>A small green package with logo symbolizing a radioactive hazard sign. However, its contents are relatively harmless, apart from the omnipresent background radiation. The small gum drops contained within are sweet and tasty and have endured the ravages of time quite well. A sugary snack for wasteland explorers.</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor -->
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.label>Gum Drops Anchorage Arctic Flavor</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.description>A small green package with logo symbolizing a radioactive hazard sign. However, its contents are relatively harmless, apart from the omnipresent background radiation. The small gum drops contained within are sweet and tasty and have endured the ravages of time quite well. A sugary snack for wasteland explorers. This popular pre-war flavor features the mountain battlefields of Anchorage Alaska.</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Insta_Mash -->
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.label>Insta Mash</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.label>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.description>A box of freeze-dried powdered mashed potatoes. This convenience food product proved to be edible two centuries after the war and can be found in many locations in the wasteland. Best paired with Salisbury Steak!</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon -->
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.label>Insta Mash And Bacon</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.label>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.description>A box of freeze-dried powdered mashed potatoes with bacon added for extra flavor and texture! This convenience food product proved to be edible two centuries after the war and can be found in many locations in the wasteland. Best paired with Salisbury Steak!</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Packaged_Iguana_Bits -->
  <FCP_Food_Packaged_Iguana_Bits.label>packaged iguana bits</FCP_Food_Packaged_Iguana_Bits.label>
  <FCP_Food_Packaged_Iguana_Bits.description>Pre-packaged chunks of iguana meat, processed and preserved for long-term storage. A common protein source in the pre-war wasteland regions, this meat was hunted, processed, and sold as an exotic alternative to traditional meats. The heavy irradiation and chemical preservatives keep it edible centuries later.</FCP_Food_Packaged_Iguana_Bits.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Crispy_Squirrel_Bits -->
  <FCP_Food_Crispy_Squirrel_Bits.label>crispy squirrel bits</FCP_Food_Crispy_Squirrel_Bits.label>
  <FCP_Food_Crispy_Squirrel_Bits.description>Fried and seasoned chunks of pre-war squirrel meat, packaged for convenient consumption. This low-cost protein option was marketed to budget-conscious consumers in rural areas before the war. The deep-frying process and heavy salting have preserved the meat surprisingly well, though the texture has become quite tough over the centuries.</FCP_Food_Crispy_Squirrel_Bits.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans -->
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.label>Pork N Beans</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.label>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.description>A can of beans stewed in a tomato sauce with chunks of bacon and salt-cured pork. A product from the Greasy Prospector company, Pork n’Beans were sold in a tin can with a blue and red label and remain edible to this day.</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor -->
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.label>Pork N Beans Hot N Spicy Flavor</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.description>A can of beans stewed in a tomato sauce with chunks of bacon and salt-cured pork. A product from the Greasy Prospector company, Pork n’Beans were sold in a tin can with a blue and red label and remain edible to this day. Based on the packaging this seems to be the &quot;Hot N Spicy Flavor&quot;.</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps -->
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.label>Potato Crisps</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.description>A box of Spring Valley potato chips. An iconic pre-war snack composed of thin potato slices salted and baked in oil. Due to their immense popularity before the war they’re still a common sight in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted -->
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.label>Potato Crisps Lightly Salted</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.description>A tube of Spring Valley potato chips in lightly salted flavor. An iconic pre-war snack composed of thin potato slices salted and baked in oil. Due to their immense popularity before the war they're still a common sight in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak -->
  <FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.label>Salisbury Steak</FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.description>A high-quality packaged meal, manufactured for use in survival situations. While it never rots, it can still deteriorate if left outside. Great for traveling.</FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak -->
  <FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.label>BIG BOY Salisbury Steak</FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.description>A sealed pre-packaged meal consisting of ground beef steak with gravy, another staple of American cuisine. It’s very filling and quite tasty, making it a popular dish even centuries after the war. The BIG BOY meal comes with a side of InstaMash!</FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs -->
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.label>Sugar Bombs</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.description>A red, white and blue box of pre-war breakfast cereals, famous (and notorious) for their high sugar content. While such an amount of sugar surely is unhealthy, it also ensured that they’re edible to this day. Due to its status as the dominant breakfast cereal, it can still be found nearly everywhere in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs_Fun_Size -->
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs_Fun_Size.label>Sugar Bombs fun size</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs_Fun_Size.label>
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs_Fun_Size.description>A smaller, snack-sized package of Sugar Bombs cereal. These fun-sized portions were marketed as a convenient on-the-go breakfast option for busy pre-war Americans. Despite the reduced portion size, they still pack the same sugar-fueled punch.</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs_Fun_Size.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Bubblegum -->
  <FCP_Food_Bubblegum.label>bubblegum</FCP_Food_Bubblegum.label>
  <FCP_Food_Bubblegum.description>A small package of pre-war bubblegum. While not particularly nutritious, this sweet treat was a beloved confection before the war. The synthetic ingredients and heavy preservatives mean it's still chewable centuries later, though the flavor has become somewhat artificial.</FCP_Food_Bubblegum.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Canned_Dog_Food -->
  <FCP_Food_Canned_Dog_Food.label>canned dog food</FCP_Food_Canned_Dog_Food.label>
  <FCP_Food_Canned_Dog_Food.description>A tin can of pre-war dog food. While formulated for canine consumption, desperate wasteland survivors have found it to be technically edible. The meat by-products and fillers provide basic nutrition, though the taste leaves much to be desired.</FCP_Food_Canned_Dog_Food.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Cotton_Candy_Bites -->
  <FCP_Food_Cotton_Candy_Bites.label>cotton candy bites</FCP_Food_Cotton_Candy_Bites.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cotton_Candy_Bites.description>Bite-sized nuggets of compressed cotton candy preserved in a sealed package. These carnival treats were a popular indulgence at pre-war fairs and amusement parks. The sheer amount of sugar and artificial coloring has kept them remarkably well-preserved, though they dissolve almost instantly when eaten.</FCP_Food_Cotton_Candy_Bites.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Perfectly_Preserved_Pie -->
  <FCP_Food_Perfectly_Preserved_Pie.label>perfectly preserved pie</FCP_Food_Perfectly_Preserved_Pie.label>
  <FCP_Food_Perfectly_Preserved_Pie.description>A remarkably well-preserved pre-war pie sealed in advanced packaging. The combination of preservatives, vacuum-sealing, and irradiation has kept this dessert in near-perfect condition for over two centuries. A rare and valuable find that provides both nutrition and a taste of pre-war luxury.</FCP_Food_Perfectly_Preserved_Pie.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Potted_Meat -->
  <FCP_Food_Potted_Meat.label>potted meat</FCP_Food_Potted_Meat.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potted_Meat.description>A small tin of potted meat product, a pre-war food staple made from mechanically separated meat scraps and spices pressed into a paste. While the ingredients were questionable even before the war, the heavy processing and preservatives ensure it remains edible. Not appetizing, but filling.</FCP_Food_Potted_Meat.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Slocums_Joe_Canned_Coffee -->
  <FCP_Food_Slocums_Joe_Canned_Coffee.label>Slocum's Joe canned coffee</FCP_Food_Slocums_Joe_Canned_Coffee.label>
  <FCP_Food_Slocums_Joe_Canned_Coffee.description>A pre-war canned coffee drink from the popular Slocum's Joe chain. This ready-to-drink coffee was a staple for busy pre-war workers. The high caffeine content and preservatives mean it still provides a significant energy boost centuries after production, though the flavor has become somewhat metallic.</FCP_Food_Slocums_Joe_Canned_Coffee.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs -->
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.label>Yum Yum Deviled Eggs</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.description>A red and blue package with dried whole deviled eggs made by YumYum. Despite being hard-boiled eggs filled with a paste made from egg yolks, mustard and mayonnaise, they’re still edible for reasons best left to discretion.</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor -->
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.label>Yum Yum Deviled Eggs Sour Cream Flavor</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.description>A yellow and gold package with dried whole deviled eggs made by YumYum with a hint of sour cream added flavor. Despite being hard-boiled eggs filled with a paste made from egg yolks, mustard and mayonnaise, they’re still edible for reasons best left to discretion.</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.description>

  <!-- FCP_Food_Slocums_BuzzBites_Donut -->
  <FCP_Food_Slocums_BuzzBites_Donut.label>Slocum's BuzzBites donut</FCP_Food_Slocums_BuzzBites_Donut.label>
  <FCP_Food_Slocums_BuzzBites_Donut.description>A pre-war fried dough confection from Slocum's BuzzBites. These ring-shaped treats are glazed with sugar and packed with enough preservatives to remain edible centuries after production. A sweet taste of pre-war indulgence that provides a quick burst of energy.</FCP_Food_Slocums_BuzzBites_Donut.description>

  <!-- FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Box -->
  <FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Box.label>Slocum's BuzzBites box</FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Box.label>
  <FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Box.description>A sealed box of Slocum's BuzzBites donuts. These pre-war packages were a staple of American breakfast culture, found in every convenience store and coffee shop. The hermetically sealed packaging has kept the contents remarkably fresh. Opening it will reveal an assortment of classic donuts.</FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Box.description>

  <!-- FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Party_Box -->
  <FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Party_Box.label>Slocum's BuzzBites party box</FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Party_Box.label>
  <FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Party_Box.description>A large party-sized box of Slocum's BuzzBites donuts. These bulk packages were marketed for office meetings, birthday parties, and other social gatherings in pre-war America. The extra-large hermetically sealed packaging contains a generous assortment of premium donuts. A rare find that promises a significant haul of sweet treats.</FCP_Slocums_BuzzBites_Party_Box.description>
</LanguageData>
