<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- FCP_Gun_Lucky -->
  <FCP_Gun_Lucky.label>Lucky</FCP_Gun_Lucky.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Lucky.description>Lucky is a legendary .357 Magnum revolver, distinguished by its immaculate chrome finish and ornate engravings. Renowned for its flawless action and uncanny accuracy, this weapon is favored by gunslingers who trust in both skill and fortune to carry the day.</FCP_Gun_Lucky.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_Maria -->
  <FCP_Gun_Maria.label>Maria</FCP_Gun_Maria.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Maria.description>Maria is a beautifully engraved 9mm pistol, adorned with intricate silver inlays and a pearl grip. Once belonging to a figure of legend, it combines elegance with deadly precision, making it a prized weapon for those who value both style and performance.</FCP_Gun_Maria.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun -->
  <FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.label>Abilene Kid LE BB Gun</FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.description>A rare, limited edition BB gun crafted for the Abilene Kid. Distinguished by its unique markings and exceptional craftsmanship, it is prized by collectors and marksmen for its nostalgic value and precision.</FCP_Gun_AbileneKidLEBBGun.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_AllAmerican -->
  <FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.label>All-American</FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.label>
  <FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.description>All-American is a legendary marksman carbine renowned for its exceptional accuracy, reliability, and custom craftsmanship. Featuring a unique design and advanced optics, it excels at delivering precise, rapid bursts at long range, making it a prized weapon among elite marksmen and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_AllAmerican.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_BigBoomer -->
  <FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.label>Big Boomer</FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.description>Big Boomer is a legendary, custom double-barrel shotgun renowned for its immense stopping power and rugged craftsmanship. Its reinforced frame and oversized barrels deliver devastating close-range blasts, making it a prized weapon among wasteland hunters and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_BigBoomer.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_Deliverer -->
  <FCP_Gun_Deliverer.label>Deliverer</FCP_Gun_Deliverer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Deliverer.description>Deliverer is a legendary, compact 10mm pistol renowned for its exceptional rate of fire and lightweight design. Favored by covert operatives, it features a custom suppressor and ergonomic grip, making it ideal for stealth operations and rapid engagements in close quarters.</FCP_Gun_Deliverer.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun -->
  <FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.label>HH Tools Nailgun</FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.description>A rugged, industrial nailgun adapted for both construction and combat. Its heavy frame and rapid-fire capability make it a formidable improvised weapon, favored by those who value versatility and raw stopping power.</FCP_Gun_HHToolsNailgun.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater -->
  <FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.label>Lincoln's Repeater</FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.label>
  <FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.description>Lincoln's Repeater is a legendary lever-action rifle, renowned for its exceptional craftsmanship and historical significance. With its polished finish and unmatched accuracy, this weapon stands as a symbol of freedom and precision, making it a prized possession among collectors and marksmen alike.</FCP_Gun_LincolnsRepeater.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger -->
  <FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.label>MkII Avenger</FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.label>
  <FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.description>The MkII Avenger is a legendary minigun chambered in 5mm, renowned for its devastating rate of fire and rugged reliability. Favored by elite operatives, its advanced design and custom modifications make it one of the most formidable automatic weapons in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_MkIIAvenger.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG -->
  <FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.label>Vance's 9mm SMG</FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.description>Vance's 9mm SMG is a legendary submachine gun, expertly customized for rapid fire and superior handling. Its polished finish and unique engravings set it apart, while its enhanced accuracy and reliability make it a prized weapon among collectors and gunslingers alike.</FCP_Gun_Vances9mmSMG.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle -->
  <FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.label>Gobi Campaign Scout Rifle</FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.description>The Gobi Campaign Scout Rifle is a legendary, custom sniper rifle awarded to elite marksmen. Renowned for its lightweight frame, exceptional accuracy, and rapid handling, it stands as one of the most coveted long-range weapons in the wasteland. Its unique craftsmanship and storied history make it a prized possession among sharpshooters and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_GobiCampaignScoutRifle.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_DinnerBell -->
  <FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.label>Dinner Bell</FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.label>
  <FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.description>Dinner Bell is a unique, custom pump-action shotgun prized for its exceptional reliability and stopping power. Featuring a polished finish and precision modifications, it delivers tight shot groupings and increased damage, making it the weapon of choice for seasoned wasteland hunters seeking both performance and style.</FCP_Gun_DinnerBell.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_Ratslayer -->
  <FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.label>Ratslayer</FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.description>Ratslayer is a unique, silenced varmint rifle equipped with a custom scope and lightweight frame. Renowned for its exceptional accuracy and stealth, it excels at eliminating small targets from a distance without drawing attention. Its precision engineering and quiet operation make it a favorite among marksmen and hunters alike.</FCP_Gun_Ratslayer.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_Wanda -->
  <FCP_Gun_Wanda.label>Wanda</FCP_Gun_Wanda.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Wanda.description>Wanda is a unique, custom combat shotgun from the Capital Wasteland. Distinguished by its green finish and reliability, it features a faster firing rate and lighter weight compared to standard combat shotguns. Favored by those who value speed and dependability in close-quarters combat.</FCP_Gun_Wanda.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_OlPainless -->
  <FCP_Gun_OlPainless.label>Ol' Painless</FCP_Gun_OlPainless.label>
  <FCP_Gun_OlPainless.description>Ol' Painless is a legendary hunting rifle, renowned for its exceptional accuracy and lightweight design. Passed down through generations, this rifle combines reliability with precision, making it a prized weapon for any marksman.</FCP_Gun_OlPainless.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle -->
  <FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.label>Victory Rifle</FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.description>The Victory Rifle is a legendary, custom sniper rifle renowned for its exceptional stopping power and unique knockdown capability. Its reinforced frame and precision engineering make it a prized weapon among sharpshooters, able to deliver devastating shots at extreme range while reliably staggering targets.</FCP_Gun_VictoryRifle.description>

  <!-- FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle -->
  <FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.label>Reservist's Rifle</FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.description>Reservist's Rifle is a rare, finely-crafted sniper rifle once carried by an elite military marksman. Lightweight and exceptionally accurate, it is prized for its long-range precision and quick handling, making it a coveted weapon among sharpshooters and collectors alike.</FCP_Gun_ReservistsRifle.description>
</LanguageData>
