<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog -->
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.label>Vicious Dog</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.description>Vicious dogs are a nearly hairless and apparently, partially ghoulified species of wasteland canine. Ruthless survivors of the wastes, these starving, irradiated mutts will attack anything that moves.</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Dog.description>

  <!-- FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog -->
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.label>Vicious Dog</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.description>Vicious dogs are a nearly hairless and apparently, partially ghoulified species of wasteland canine. Ruthless survivors of the wastes, these starving, irradiated mutts will attack anything that moves. Some dogs have been domesticated, even charged with guarding its owner and all their property this animal will do so to the best of its ability.</FCP_Animal_Vicious_Guard_Dog.description>

  <!-- FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog -->
  <FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.label>German Shepherd Dog</FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.description>Some dogs are wild, plaguing the wastes and killing livestock, but tame versions are necessary for many struggling wastelanders. There are also rare cases of domestic breeds that act as companions towards their bipedal counterparts. Humans and super mutants are the only species known to truly tame and domesticate these canines.</FCP_Animal_German_Shepherd_Dog.description>

  <!-- FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog -->
  <FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.label>Minutemen Guard Dog</FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.description>Some dogs are wild, plaguing the wastes and killing livestock, but tame versions are necessary for many struggling wastelanders. There are also rare cases of domestic breeds such as German Shepherds act as companions towards their bipedal counterparts. The Minutemen around the ruins of Boston in particular have used them as working and guard dogs for their military.</FCP_Animal_Minutemen_Guard_Dog.description>

  <!-- FCP_Animal_Nightstalker -->
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.label>Nightstalker</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.description>A horrifying product of pre-war genetic experimentation, the nightstalker is a hybrid creature combining the DNA of coyotes and rattlesnakes. These stealthy predators hunt in packs under cover of darkness, using their venomous bite to bring down prey. They possess the pack intelligence of canines combined with the stealth and venom of serpents, making them one of the wasteland's most feared predators. Their distinctive silhouette and glowing eyes strike terror into those who encounter them.</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.0.label>venomous bite</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.1.label>claws</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.2.label>head</FCP_Animal_Nightstalker.tools.2.label>
</LanguageData>
