<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VHGE_GasCooler.description>An air-cooling machine that releases cooled air around itself. Can be used to create a walk-in freezer. Cannot be adjusted and will automatically lower temperature slightly below zero.</VHGE_GasCooler.description>
  <VHGE_GasCooler.label>gas cooler</VHGE_GasCooler.label>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>A gas-powered tall floodlight that lights a massive area. People need light to move and work at full speed. It doesn’t shine bright enough to grow crops. Needs to be connected to the helixien gas network. Can be safely placed outdoors.</VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>gas floodlight</VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>
  <VHGE_GasGeyser.description>A natural source of high-pressure gas. Helixien pumps can be built on top to extract the gas.</VHGE_GasGeyser.description>
  <VHGE_GasGeyser.label>gas geyser</VHGE_GasGeyser.label>
  <VHGE_GasHeater.description>A device that converts helixien gas into radiated heat. It can automatically turn itself on or off to reach a specific target temperature.</VHGE_GasHeater.description>
  <VHGE_GasHeater.label>gas heater</VHGE_GasHeater.label>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.description>A gas-powered standing lamp that lights an area. People need light to move and work at full speed. Needs to be connected to the helixien gas network. Can be safely placed outdoors.</VHGE_GasLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.label>gas lamp</VHGE_GasLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasOperatedPodLauncher.description>A fueling port for launching one transport pod. Pod launchers can launch as a group - but the launchers must be placed adjacent to each other. Requires connection to a helixien gas system.</VHGE_GasOperatedPodLauncher.description>
  <VHGE_GasOperatedPodLauncher.label>gas-operated pod launcher</VHGE_GasOperatedPodLauncher.label>
  <VHGE_GasPipeValve.description>Switches gas flow on/off.</VHGE_GasPipeValve.description>
  <VHGE_GasPipeValve.label>gas valve</VHGE_GasPipeValve.label>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredCrematorium.description>A huge stone crematorium which vaporizes corpses with extremely high temperatures. Operates on helixien gas.</VHGE_GasPoweredCrematorium.description>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredCrematorium.label>gas-powered crematorium</VHGE_GasPoweredCrematorium.label>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredRefinery.description>Refines biological matter like wood or plant matter into chemfuel. Needs to be connected to the helixien gas network.</VHGE_GasPoweredRefinery.description>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredRefinery.label>gas-powered refinery</VHGE_GasPoweredRefinery.label>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredSmelter.description>Extracts usable metal from slag chunks and other mixed metal items. Operates on helixien gas.</VHGE_GasPoweredSmelter.description>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredSmelter.label>gas-powered smelter</VHGE_GasPoweredSmelter.label>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredSmithy.description>A gas-powered station for smithing non-mechanical weapons and tools.</VHGE_GasPoweredSmithy.description>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredSmithy.label>gas-powered smithy</VHGE_GasPoweredSmithy.label>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredStove.description>A gas-powered stove with an attached countertop for preparing meals.</VHGE_GasPoweredStove.description>
  <VHGE_GasPoweredStove.label>gas-powered stove</VHGE_GasPoweredStove.label>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>An industrial lamp which lights an area brightly enough to grow crops, but consumes a medium amount of helixien gas. Automatically turns itself off at night.</VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>gas sun lamp</VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasTank.description>A large steel tank for gas storage. Will explode if damaged.</VHGE_GasTank.description>
  <VHGE_GasTank.label>gas tank</VHGE_GasTank.label>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>A gas-powered wall light that lights an area. People need light to move and work at full speed. Needs to be connected to the helixien gas network. Can be safely placed outdoors.</VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>gas wall lamp</VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>
  <VHGE_Helixien.description>Helixien gas.</VHGE_Helixien.description>
  <VHGE_Helixien.label>helixien</VHGE_Helixien.label>
  <VHGE_HelixienGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming helixien gas. Must be connected to a gas pipe network.</VHGE_HelixienGenerator.description>
  <VHGE_HelixienGenerator.label>gas powered generator</VHGE_HelixienGenerator.label>
  <VHGE_HelixienPipe.description>A pipe that transmits helixien gas.</VHGE_HelixienPipe.description>
  <VHGE_HelixienPipe.label>gas pipe</VHGE_HelixienPipe.label>
  <VHGE_HelixienPump.description>An extractor machine mounted on a pocket of helixien gas. This machine pumps out valuable gas and needs to be connected to other gas-based utilities using the pipe network.</VHGE_HelixienPump.description>
  <VHGE_HelixienPump.label>helixien pump</VHGE_HelixienPump.label>
  <VHGE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.description>Produces a large amount of power by consuming helixien gas. Must be connected to a gas pipe network.</VHGE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.description>
  <VHGE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.label>industrial gas powered generator</VHGE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.label>
  <VHGE_SubterraneanHelixienPipe.description>A pipe that transmits helixien gas. This pipe is hidden from view and is protected from gas explosions. Much more expensive to build than regular pipes.</VHGE_SubterraneanHelixienPipe.description>
  <VHGE_SubterraneanHelixienPipe.label>subterranean gas pipe</VHGE_SubterraneanHelixienPipe.label>
</LanguageData>