<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.description>A simple red cap bearing the golden star emblem of the People's Republic of China. This practical headwear is standard issue for soldiers and low-ranking military personnel of the People's Liberation Army. The bright red fabric and prominent star design display allegiance to the state while providing basic protection from sun and light rain.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.label>Chinese army cap</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Army_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.description>A practical crimson and gold jumpsuit worn by soldiers and low-ranking military personnel of the People's Liberation Army. The bright red fabric bears the iconic yellow star, symbolizing loyalty to the state. While offering minimal protection, it's designed for comfort during long duty shifts and provides basic insulation against the elements.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.label>Chinese army jumpsuit</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.description>An officer's variant of the standard Chinese army jumpsuit, featuring additional decorative elements, shoulder boards, and reinforced fabric. Worn by military officers and high-ranking officials of the People's Liberation Army, this uniform commands respect and authority while maintaining the practical design of the standard issue. The added ornamentation and medals boost the wearer's confidence and negotiating presence.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.label>Chinese army general's jumpsuit</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_General.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.description>A heavily insulated variant of the standard Chinese army jumpsuit, designed for operations in harsh winter conditions. This padded crimson uniform features a quilted construction with synthetic insulation, fur-lined collar, and reinforced seams. Originally developed for Chinese troops stationed in the frozen northern territories, it provides excellent protection against extreme cold while maintaining the distinctive red and gold color scheme of the People's Republic.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.label>Chinese army winter jumpsuit</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Jumpsuit_Winter.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.description>A naval service cap worn by submariners and sailors of the People's Liberation Army Navy. This water-resistant cap features the red star emblem and provides protection against ocean spray and harsh weather conditions. The dark navy blue color with red accents is instantly recognizable as belonging to China's naval forces.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.label>Chinese naval cap</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Naval_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.description>A peaked service cap bearing the golden star emblem of the People's Republic of China. This formal headwear is worn by officers and high-ranking officials of the Chinese military. The rigid design and prominent insignia command respect and denote authority, making it a symbol of leadership within the ranks.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.label>Chinese officer cap</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Officer_Cap.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.description>An advanced tactical helmet integrated with Chinese stealth technology. This sleek helmet features a reinforced visor, built-in rebreather, and sensor array. The hermetically sealed design provides protection against environmental hazards and can interface with stealth field systems when worn with compatible armor.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.label>Chinese stealth helmet</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.description>A cutting-edge piece of Chinese military technology, this form-fitting stealth suit incorporates advanced light-bending technology and sound-dampening materials. Developed by the People's Liberation Army for covert operations, the suit features a flexible polymer construction with integrated circuitry that provides active camouflage capabilities. Its lightweight design and mobility enhancements make it ideal for infiltration, reconnaissance, and assassination missions. The suit's signature crimson and black color scheme can shift to blend with surroundings when activated.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.label>Chinese stealth suit</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Stealth_Suit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.description>A specialized uniform worn by submariners of the People's Liberation Army Navy. This practical ensemble features water-resistant fabrics, reinforced stitching, and multiple sealed pockets designed to protect essential equipment in damp, confined submarine environments. The dark navy and crimson design includes reflective strips for emergency visibility and a high collar for protection against cold ocean winds. While not a full diving suit, it provides basic environmental protection and is valued by sailors, dock workers, and naval personnel.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.label>Chinese submariner uniform</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Submariner.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.description>A fur-lined winter cap featuring the iconic red star of the People's Republic of China. This warm ushanka is standard issue for Chinese military personnel operating in cold climates. The ear flaps provide excellent protection against frostbite, while the red exterior proudly displays allegiance to the state.</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.label>Chinese ushanka</FCP_Apparel_PRC_Ushanka.label>
  <FCP_Currency_PRC_Yuan.description>Pre-war Chinese currency, issued by the People's Republic of China. These crisp red banknotes feature the portrait of Chairman Mao and various symbols of communist pride. Despite the passage of centuries since the Great War, yuan notes remain a recognized medium of exchange in regions influenced by Chinese culture and among traders who deal with remnants of the former People's Republic.</FCP_Currency_PRC_Yuan.description>
  <FCP_Currency_PRC_Yuan.label>Chinese Yuan</FCP_Currency_PRC_Yuan.label>
</LanguageData>