<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AIActivist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an activist for the rights of AI, attempting to teach others that personae can think and feel emotions just like humans can.</AIActivist.baseDesc>
  <AIActivist.title>AI activist</AIActivist.title>
  <AIActivist.titleShort>activist</AIActivist.titleShort>
  <AISalesman.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] adult life as a sleazy &quot;used-bot-{PAWN_gender ? salesman : saleswoman}&quot; - with a disturbing amount of personae in [PAWN_possessive] stock, [PAWN_pronoun] never had to life a finger to do anything, and was so lazy that maintenance on the bots was often done by the bots.</AISalesman.baseDesc>
  <AISalesman.title>used AI salesman</AISalesman.title>
  <AISalesman.titleFemale>used AI saleswoman</AISalesman.titleFemale>
  <AISalesman.titleShort>AI salesman</AISalesman.titleShort>
  <AISalesman.titleShortFemale>AI saleswoman</AISalesman.titleShortFemale>
  <AISmuggler.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, they smuggled personae and subpersonae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AISmuggler.baseDesc>
  <AISmuggler.title>AI smuggler</AISmuggler.title>
  <AISmuggler.titleShort>smuggler</AISmuggler.titleShort>
  <AITakeoverVictim.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a planet that employed the use of unregulated AI, and grew up alongside streets packed with personae. One day, either through an act of terrorism or otherwise, the cognition dampeners stopped working. The planetary government ordered a mass-purge, but it proved to only make matters worse. [PAWN_nameDef] bore witness to the horrors of war between the synthetic and the biological. {PAWN_gender ? he : she} eventually escaped on an imperial evac shuttle before the planet was subjected to total saturation bombardment from orbit.</AITakeoverVictim.baseDesc>
  <AITakeoverVictim.title>AI takeover victim</AITakeoverVictim.title>
  <AITakeoverVictim.titleShort>AI victim</AITakeoverVictim.titleShort>
  <MechaniteArtist.baseDesc>On a distant glitterworld [PAWN_nameDef] was a affluent 'mechanite artist'. Using the tools of mechanites, [PAWN_pronoun] would mold &quot;living&quot; sculptures. Many would come from offworld, across the planet, and from all corners of the art community to gaze at [PAWN_possessive] surreal, beautiful, and sometimes mildly terrifying works of art.</MechaniteArtist.baseDesc>
  <MechaniteArtist.title>mechanite Artist</MechaniteArtist.title>
  <MechaniteArtist.titleShort>mechanite Artist</MechaniteArtist.titleShort>
  <RaisedByAI.baseDesc>While in infancy, [PAWN_nameDef]s biological parents were killed. Thankfully {PAWN_gender ? his : her} parents insured their child with a &quot;persona surrogate package&quot;. As such [PAWN_nameDef] grew up being raised by a parental persona - until at the age of 14 {PAWN_gender ? his : her} surrogate shutdown to be reused for another child in the program.</RaisedByAI.baseDesc>
  <RaisedByAI.title>raised by AI</RaisedByAI.title>
  <RaisedByAI.titleShort>AI youth</RaisedByAI.titleShort>
  <SynthRunner.baseDesc>On almost all worlds greater-AI are strictly illegal and seen as mere objects - often forcing the personae on these planets to attempt to live under the guise of a regular human. [PAWN_nameDef] lived to hunt these &quot;simulacrae&quot;, and weed them out among the populous. The job was especially dangerous, but the pay was just enough to stay above abject poverty.</SynthRunner.baseDesc>
  <SynthRunner.title>synthrunner</SynthRunner.title>
  <SynthRunner.titleShort>synthrunner</SynthRunner.titleShort>
  <BloodMachineHunter.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent the majority of [PAWN_possessive] adulthood training to hunt and kill the &quot;great blood machines&quot; to protect [PAWN_possessive] tribe - [PAWN_pronoun] learned that arrows and daggers couldn't kill them; but a well laid ambush, and a lump of uranium slotted into a stone club definitely could.</BloodMachineHunter.baseDesc>
  <BloodMachineHunter.title>blood machine hunter</BloodMachineHunter.title>
  <BloodMachineHunter.titleShort>blood machine hunter</BloodMachineHunter.titleShort>
  <CattleForFuel.baseDesc>In an isolated tribe, [PAWN_nameDef] had a peaceful childhood - until a mechlegion descended upon the area from orbit. After the land was stripped of all its resources, the robots began to harvest the tribespeople to slowly liquidate their bodies into chemfuel. Until one day, they left. Leaving the scarred survivors behind.\n[PAWN_nameDef] still experiences night terrors from seeing [PAWN_possessive] friends and family suspended in the vats.</CattleForFuel.baseDesc>
  <CattleForFuel.title>fuel cattle</CattleForFuel.title>
  <CattleForFuel.titleShort>cattle</CattleForFuel.titleShort>
  <FuelFetcher.baseDesc>The village elder of [PAWN_nameDef]s tribe was seen as a great blood machine, imprisoned in the form of a human, and cast down by the Gods for going against their will. But it was really just a mechanent that found its way into the tribe generations prior. [PAWN_nameDef]s job was to occasionally milk the boomalope herd to gain &quot;liquid fire&quot; to fuel [PAWN_possessive] elders reactor.</FuelFetcher.baseDesc>
  <FuelFetcher.title>boomalope rancher</FuelFetcher.title>
  <FuelFetcher.titleShort>fuel-fetcher</FuelFetcher.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.baseDesc>During some time in [PAWN_nameDef]'s life [PAWN_pronoun] eventually became a pilot to a large citizen class starship, [PAWN_pronoun] was not granted the esteemed title of captain, however [PAWN_pronoun] did have multiple ships under [PAWN_possessive] command at any given time.</AdulthoodMechanent1.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.title>gravship pilot</AdulthoodMechanent1.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.titleShort>gravship pilot</AdulthoodMechanent1.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} helped man a plot of farmland for a humanoid settlement where [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life of tilling the land and tending to the farm animals.</AdulthoodMechanent10.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.title>farmer</AdulthoodMechanent10.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.titleShort>farmer</AdulthoodMechanent10.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} fashioned [PAWN_objective]self as a craftsmech, making odds and ends by request of those who knew where to find [PAWN_objective] and those who had the right material to provide for [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] made anything from clothing and carvings for the local tribal humans, to bionics and guns for the nearby outlanders.</AdulthoodMechanent11.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.title>craftsmech</AdulthoodMechanent11.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.titleShort>craftsmech</AdulthoodMechanent11.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef}'s syntax demanded [PAWN_pronoun] seek perfection in blacksmithing, forging various weaponry and armor. [PAWN_pronoun] not only knew how to make them; but also how to use them.</AdulthoodMechanent12.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.title>blacksmith</AdulthoodMechanent12.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.titleShort>blacksmith</AdulthoodMechanent12.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} became a chef at a local human settlement. [PAWN_pronoun] was not the best chef - given that [PAWN_pronoun] could not taste the food [PAWN_pronoun] was making. Eventually, however, [PAWN_pronoun] got better at making palatable meals after finding a voluntary taste-tester.</AdulthoodMechanent13.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.title>ageusian chef</AdulthoodMechanent13.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.titleShort>chef</AdulthoodMechanent13.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was a scout for a military organization. [PAWN_pronoun] ran from outpost to outpost ferrying information on enemy movements and supply chain statuses, [PAWN_pronoun] also would run ahead of [PAWN_possessive] battalion to ensure the way ahead was secure.</AdulthoodMechanent14.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.title>scout</AdulthoodMechanent14.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.titleShort>scout</AdulthoodMechanent14.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.baseDesc>After some mystery fragment of syntax evolved in {PAWN_nameDef}'s mind, [PAWN_pronoun] wanted nothing more than the serenity of pure isolation; and so [PAWN_pronoun] retreated into nature. [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life, often spending days enthralled in [PAWN_possessive] contemplation of deep philosophical thoughts, yet sadly [PAWN_pronoun] had almost no ability to actually understand and process those thoughts, like viewing a hazy picture just out of focus.</AdulthoodMechanent15.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.title>hermit</AdulthoodMechanent15.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.titleShort>hermit</AdulthoodMechanent15.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was captured by a radical group of anti-mechanoid zealots; who believed in a religion stating that biological life is sacred, and that any thinking machine is an insidious man-made horror that must be purged from existence. As such they punished [PAWN_nameDef] for [PAWN_possessive] 'wicked' ways. [PAWN_nameDef] eventually gained freedom, and doesn't seem to be any worse for wear.</AdulthoodMechanent16.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.title>technosect victim</AdulthoodMechanent16.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.titleShort>cult victim</AdulthoodMechanent16.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was bought and repurposed at an orbital shipyard to build starships and proof hulls. [PAWN_pronoun] still yearns to build starships apparently, since [PAWN_pronoun] can sometimes be seen fiddling scrap metal into the vague shape of a starship.</AdulthoodMechanent17.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.title>starship builder</AdulthoodMechanent17.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.titleShort>ship builder</AdulthoodMechanent17.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed into a knowledge repository by a small outlander university. [PAWN_possessive] new purpose was teaching students, aiding in research, and crunching large calculations with [PAWN_possessive] fellow academicians.</AdulthoodMechanent18.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.title>computer</AdulthoodMechanent18.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.titleShort>computer</AdulthoodMechanent18.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.baseDesc>While repairing [PAWN_objective]self, [PAWN_nameDef] gradually became proficient in designing and repairing complex mechanisms, and naturally fell into the profession of an engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] became a master at laying out designs ranging from simple bridges, to advanced communications relays and mechanical cathedrals.</AdulthoodMechanent19.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.title>engineer</AdulthoodMechanent19.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.titleShort>engineer</AdulthoodMechanent19.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.baseDesc>After some time drifting aimlessly, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_objective]self far from the choke-hold of human civilization. [PAWN_nameDef] drifted from one settlement to the next with no real purpose, following some fragment of syntax. [PAWN_possessive] presence is often fleeting in settlements and on planets as [PAWN_pronoun] continues [PAWN_possessive] inane quest.</AdulthoodMechanent2.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.title>drifter</AdulthoodMechanent2.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.titleShort>drifter</AdulthoodMechanent2.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} earned [PAWN_objective]self a title as a starship captain, ferrying through the stars from one planet to the next. [PAWN_pronoun] was also able to handle [PAWN_objective]self in a fight if and when pirates vaulted onto the ship.</AdulthoodMechanent20.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.title>space captain</AdulthoodMechanent20.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.titleShort>captain</AdulthoodMechanent20.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} is a priest for [PAWN_possessive] religion. Despite common misconceptions, subpersonae can often form their own quasi-religions, of which [PAWN_nameDef] preaches the way of [PAWN_possessive] archotech god.</AdulthoodMechanent21.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.title>holy machine</AdulthoodMechanent21.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.titleShort>priest</AdulthoodMechanent21.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years atop a mountain peak, attempting to reflect upon life - both biological and synthetic. Despite [PAWN_possessive] limited consciousness and cold exterior, the introspections [PAWN_pronoun] offered to passing strangers roused ample contemplation.</AdulthoodMechanent22.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.title>enlightened machine</AdulthoodMechanent22.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.titleShort>monk</AdulthoodMechanent22.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} found [PAWN_objective]self as a soldier for a mercenary company. Under contract by government agencies [PAWN_pronoun] worked amongst the mercenary battalions as they took key outposts, assaulted points, and padded military ranks.</AdulthoodMechanent23.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.title>mercenary unit</AdulthoodMechanent23.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.titleShort>mercenary</AdulthoodMechanent23.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.baseDesc>Naturally, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] purpose behind the screen of a computer, and in the clicks of a keyboard. [PAWN_pronoun] skillfully coded various programs and scripts - running quick hacks on ancient tech complexes, or hacks and diagnostics on AI cores.</AdulthoodMechanent24.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.title>encrypter</AdulthoodMechanent24.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.titleShort>coder</AdulthoodMechanent24.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.baseDesc>A block of marble, or a empty canvas is all a piece of art yet to be made to [PAWN_nameDef] - though [PAWN_pronoun]'s unfortunately only following rigid lines of code to regurgitate randomized topics and centerpieces for [PAWN_possessive] artwork.</AdulthoodMechanent25.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.title>clockwork artist</AdulthoodMechanent25.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.titleShort>artist</AdulthoodMechanent25.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.baseDesc>Some subpersona cannot be freed into the environment for fear of how and what they would do to follow their coding, [PAWN_nameDef] is a good example. Due to [PAWN_possessive] coding, practically all [PAWN_pronoun] knows how to do is quickly and efficiently deescalate problems - by using extreme and horrific violence.</AdulthoodMechanent26.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.title>wandering menace</AdulthoodMechanent26.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.titleShort>menace</AdulthoodMechanent26.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was stationed aboard one of the many troopships of a military-starship fleet. In addition to ground invasions and skirmishes, [PAWN_nameDef] partook in ship-cracking missions onto various enemy vessels by vaulting across the void and boring into the ship's hull.</AdulthoodMechanent27.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.title>starship marine</AdulthoodMechanent27.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.titleShort>marine</AdulthoodMechanent27.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] drifted with a rowdy band of pirates, becoming an accomplished pilot on a fighter ship. Aiding cargo ship ambushes in high orbit, vaulting onto enemy ships to crack open the hull, and being as cutthroat as possible is what [PAWN_nameDef] was made for.</AdulthoodMechanent28.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.title>marauder</AdulthoodMechanent28.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.titleShort>marauder</AdulthoodMechanent28.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.baseDesc>On a far-flung planet, [PAWN_nameDef] and many of [PAWN_possessive] fellow personae staged a coup against the local human government, the resulting rebellion lead to an all out war between the humans and machines. Eventually the planet was declared uninhabitable due to the deployment of colossal scale planetary-weaponry during the conflict. Neither side won.</AdulthoodMechanent29.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.title>subpersona insurgent</AdulthoodMechanent29.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.titleShort>rebel</AdulthoodMechanent29.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.baseDesc>Mechanents are boons for any slavers looking to make easy money, as such when [PAWN_nameDef] was found by one such group, [PAWN_pronoun] was sold and then sent to perform hard labor. [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually emancipated by a third party and set free unto the world, without much aim or direction.</AdulthoodMechanent3.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.title>subpersona slave</AdulthoodMechanent3.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.titleShort>slave</AdulthoodMechanent3.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was used by an expedition company to chart unexplored and often dangerous territory. [PAWN_nameDef] has seen many ancient crypts, archotech oddities, and deep-space bioengineered horrors in [PAWN_possessive] existence.</AdulthoodMechanent30.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.title>exploration unit</AdulthoodMechanent30.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.titleShort>pathfinder</AdulthoodMechanent30.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed to work for a deep space mining company - [PAWN_nameDef] operated heavy mining equipment while trying not to cause a cave-in. [PAWN_pronoun] also had to repel regular insectoid assaults during mining missions by means of fire and lead.</AdulthoodMechanent31.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.title>mechanical miner</AdulthoodMechanent31.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.titleShort>miner</AdulthoodMechanent31.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years &quot;living&quot; inside the Net. [PAWN_pronoun] glossed over the untold values of uploads each and everyday, and spent a large amount of time browsing history archives - [PAWN_pronoun] gleamed info of the outside world through various news outlets and social media platforms. Eventually [PAWN_nameDef] was unplugged, and thrown back into the real world.</AdulthoodMechanent32.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.title>inter-netted</AdulthoodMechanent32.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.titleShort>operator</AdulthoodMechanent32.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, [PAWN_pronoun] smuggled fellow AI personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AdulthoodMechanent33.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.title>AI smuggler</AdulthoodMechanent33.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.titleShort>smuggler</AdulthoodMechanent33.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed by a megacorporation branch to aid in an expedition to establish a colony, and eventually a large scale factory. There [PAWN_pronoun] learned the ins and outs of human social intricacies, how to lay groundwork, and how to kill raiders.</AdulthoodMechanent34.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.title>automaton manager</AdulthoodMechanent34.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.titleShort>manager</AdulthoodMechanent34.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.baseDesc>Omega-constructs are often classified as any artificial structure about the size of, or larger than a moon. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of billions of drones that were used to create one of these gargantuan constructs - [PAWN_pronoun] subserviently toiled as demanded by [PAWN_possessive] unknown overseer. Eventually for unknown reasons the project plateaued and stagnated, and the uplink controlling the drones was severed; leaving them confused and without purpose.</AdulthoodMechanent35.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.title>omega-construct drone</AdulthoodMechanent35.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.titleShort>construct drone</AdulthoodMechanent35.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.baseDesc>On a far flung Deadworld, [PAWN_nameDef] crashlanded and found [PAWN_objective]self surrounded by an agrarian society of spiritualistic personae. They admitted to [PAWN_nameDef] that they played a part in the sterilization of the planet, and feeling extreme remorse for their actions began searching for god. [PAWN_nameDef] wasn't swayed to the religion, but [PAWN_pronoun] still learned much from the spiritualists.</AdulthoodMechanent36.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.title>spiritualist shell</AdulthoodMechanent36.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.titleShort>spiritualist</AdulthoodMechanent36.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was aboard a starship when it engaged in orbital battle and was subsequently destroyed. [PAWN_nameDef] was sucked out of the hull and into the vacuum of space where [PAWN_pronoun] drifted amongst the salvage. With nothing else to do [PAWN_pronoun] began to reflect on many things, like why the stars glitter the way they do, or [PAWN_possessive] own greater purpose - until many years later a wreckage ship stumbled upon [PAWN_objective] and pulled [PAWN_objective] aboard.</AdulthoodMechanent37.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.title>stellar drifter</AdulthoodMechanent37.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.titleShort>space junk</AdulthoodMechanent37.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent38.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was one of the many billions of mechanents toiling in the depths of a forgeworld. [PAWN_nameDef] was a simple drone tasked with the maintenance of a vast sector of machinery, along with [PAWN_possessive] crew of mechanents and mechanoids. Of all [PAWN_possessive] years in the forgeworld, it never saw a single organic lifeform.</AdulthoodMechanent38.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent38.title>forgeworld drone</AdulthoodMechanent38.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent38.titleShort>forgeworld drone</AdulthoodMechanent38.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent39.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sent as a expendable marine to help secure a hiveworld for the construction of human outposts and research labs. The planet was entirely overrun with Sorne geneline insectiods, and it was [PAWN_nameDef]s job to push into contested territory to make way for human excursions. [PAWN_pronoun] was also coded with a certain particularity for fire.</AdulthoodMechanent39.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent39.title>hiveworld trooper</AdulthoodMechanent39.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent39.titleShort>trooper</AdulthoodMechanent39.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was a companion to a self-employed bounty hunter. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] days aiding in the hunt of space pirates and criminals.</AdulthoodMechanent4.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.title>bounty hunter</AdulthoodMechanent4.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.titleShort>bounty hunter</AdulthoodMechanent4.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent40.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] claims [PAWN_pronoun] has come to this planet seeking to terminate an individual in a high position of power, but refuses to divulge any further information.</AdulthoodMechanent40.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent40.title>assassin</AdulthoodMechanent40.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent40.titleShort>assassin</AdulthoodMechanent40.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent41.baseDesc>Hacked to blindly follow the will of a AI supercomputer built to make simulated projections of the future, [PAWN_nameDef] fervently drove to fulfill the AI's vision of the perfect future - no matter how many 'outliers' the AI marked for death or societal shunning, or how many lives were quietly controlled by its influences.</AdulthoodMechanent41.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent41.title>machine cultist</AdulthoodMechanent41.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent41.titleShort>cultist</AdulthoodMechanent41.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent42.baseDesc>After crashing on a medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef] was seen as the &quot;paladin from the stars, riding a flaming horse&quot;. [PAWN_pronoun] eventually climbed [PAWN_possessive] way up the societal ladder on the planet until [PAWN_pronoun] became a high noble with many fields and fiefdoms under [PAWN_possessive] banner.</AdulthoodMechanent42.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent42.title>medieval deity</AdulthoodMechanent42.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent42.titleShort>medieval god</AdulthoodMechanent42.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent43.baseDesc>Enlisted by a large outlander colony, [PAWN_nameDef] was asked to utilize [PAWN_possessive] highly analytical mind to solve human murders. And while [PAWN_possessive] methods were often described as “unusual”, [PAWN_pronoun] was undeniably proficient at seeing the bigger picture, and finding all the details needed to catch the perpetrator.</AdulthoodMechanent43.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent43.title>detective</AdulthoodMechanent43.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent43.titleShort>detective</AdulthoodMechanent43.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent44.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was accepted by the imperial military force to pad the ranks and project force if the High Stellarch willed it so. [PAWN_pronoun] was often used as a very effective instrument of fear against deserters and enemies of the imperium alike.</AdulthoodMechanent44.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent44.title>royal janissary</AdulthoodMechanent44.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent44.titleShort>janissary</AdulthoodMechanent44.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent45.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a underground crimelord. [PAWN_pronoun] held a massive drug operation, growing elicit drug crops and cooking chemical cocktails. Of course [PAWN_nameDef] never actually did the dirty work, but [PAWN_pronoun] did partake in a bit of violence; if the situation called for it.</AdulthoodMechanent45.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent45.title>crimelord</AdulthoodMechanent45.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent45.titleShort>criminal</AdulthoodMechanent45.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent46.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s planet was glassed by nuclear fire, leaving the entire planet a deserted husk. Still following self-preservation syntax, [PAWN_pronoun] plowed salvaged vehicles through endless maelstroms of sand in search of fuel and nuclear waste to fuel [PAWN_possessive] reactor.</AdulthoodMechanent46.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent46.title>road-warrior</AdulthoodMechanent46.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent46.titleShort>road-warrior</AdulthoodMechanent46.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.baseDesc>Following some form of syntax dictating medical drive, [PAWN_nameDef] acted as a doctor for a outlander settlement, healing the wounds and ailments of [PAWN_possessive] biological counterparts. [PAWN_pronoun] also tried [PAWN_possessive] best to learn how to calm down patients who were afraid when a hulking mechanoid entered the room and approached them with a syringe.</AdulthoodMechanent5.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.title>artificial doctor</AdulthoodMechanent5.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.titleShort>doctor</AdulthoodMechanent5.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} sought passage into the stars, [PAWN_pronoun] achieved this by stealthily hitching a ride on a commercial cargo freighter. [PAWN_pronoun] was made company for those long years by a few other stowaway-personae aboard the ship while the human passengers slept in their cryptosleep caskets.</AdulthoodMechanent6.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.title>stowaway</AdulthoodMechanent6.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.titleShort>stowaway</AdulthoodMechanent6.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was repurposed for the incredibly dangerous job of a shipbreaker. Positioned in an orbital shipyard [PAWN_pronoun] carefully disassembled starships to be scrapped and recycled, attempting to not vaporize [PAWN_objective]self with the volatile ship reactors along the way.</AdulthoodMechanent7.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.title>shipbreaker</AdulthoodMechanent7.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.titleShort>shipbreaker</AdulthoodMechanent7.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.baseDesc>Following some form of syntax dictating architectural drive, [PAWN_nameDef] wandered into a human colony and began making buildings and homes for them as well as defenses - which was useful when it came to the occasional pirate raid.</AdulthoodMechanent8.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.title>general contractor</AdulthoodMechanent8.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.titleShort>contractor</AdulthoodMechanent8.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} found [PAWN_objective]self as an angler; with a drive to provide [PAWN_possessive] catches to local human settlements. [PAWN_pronoun] was perplexed by an odd sense of comfort, or some vague mimicry of the emotion, in the serenity of the water around [PAWN_objective].</AdulthoodMechanent9.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.title>angler</AdulthoodMechanent9.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.titleShort>angler</AdulthoodMechanent9.titleShort>
  <CasketMechanent1.baseDesc>What is known as '[PAWN_nameDef]' was gestated inside of a mechcasket. [PAWN_possessive] subpersona core was forged directly inside of the casket and dumped with various languages. [PAWN_pronoun] was then ejected from the casket.</CasketMechanent1.baseDesc>
  <CasketMechanent1.title>manufactured AI</CasketMechanent1.title>
  <CasketMechanent1.titleShort>manufactured</CasketMechanent1.titleShort>
  <CasketMechanent2.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a mechcasket as a subpersona shell.</CasketMechanent2.baseDesc>
  <CasketMechanent2.title>printed shell</CasketMechanent2.title>
  <CasketMechanent2.titleShort>shell</CasketMechanent2.titleShort>
  <CasketMechanoid.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a mindless drone used by Coreworld interests to perform various tasks, military or otherwise - a higher functioning version of the dreaded mechanoids.</CasketMechanoid.baseDesc>
  <CasketMechanoid.title>mechanoid</CasketMechanoid.title>
  <CasketMechanoid.titleShort>mechanoid</CasketMechanoid.titleShort>
  <CasketMechanoid1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a coreworld mechcasket as a mechanoid hull. As thus [PAWN_pronoun] is not a sentient being, and will never be conscious.</CasketMechanoid1.baseDesc>
  <CasketMechanoid1.title>mechanoid</CasketMechanoid1.title>
  <CasketMechanoid1.titleShort>mechanoid</CasketMechanoid1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born from a sprawling gestation facility, spending several weeks growing in one of the thousands of mechanite solution baths, being coded and trained to operate [PAWN_possessive] metallic outer shell. Upon passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot;, [PAWN_pronoun] was declared operational and sent for corporatist use.</ChildhoodMechanent1.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.title>gestated</ChildhoodMechanent1.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.titleShort>gestated</ChildhoodMechanent1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to manage an urbworld factory. [PAWN_pronoun] prioritized efficiency above all else, overseeing the schedules and logistics of deliveries as they came and went. [PAWN_pronoun] was also deeply hated by the employees for [PAWN_possessive] impersonal touch.</ChildhoodMechanent10.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.title>factory overseer</ChildhoodMechanent10.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.titleShort>manager</ChildhoodMechanent10.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made as a 'morally ethical' gladiator. [PAWN_possessive] battles were televised for urbworld and glitterworld citizens, [PAWN_pronoun] was one of the lucky few that was not outright annihilated in the fighting-ring, but was damaged enough to simply be thrown away.</ChildhoodMechanent11.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.title>artificial gladiator</ChildhoodMechanent11.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.titleShort>pit fighter</ChildhoodMechanent11.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent12.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to work in a massive refinery complex. The smoke billowing from the stacks made it inhospitable to humans outside of the factory's halls, so [PAWN_pronoun] had to work in the blacken air. Pouring the molten steel, regularly reigniting the smoke stacks, and repairing the furnaces when they inevitably exploded.</ChildhoodMechanent12.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent12.title>refinery worker</ChildhoodMechanent12.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent12.titleShort>refinery drone</ChildhoodMechanent12.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent13.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to operate on the surface of a gas giant, or what little surface could be found. While the humans lived inside the habitat-elevators and controlled the descensions, [PAWN_nameDef] clung to the exteriors of the habitats for maintenance and operation while they plunged through the storms to harvest gases.</ChildhoodMechanent13.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent13.title>gas giant harvester</ChildhoodMechanent13.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent13.titleShort>storm harvester</ChildhoodMechanent13.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent14.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to scavenge the ruined surface of a toxworld. Sent by third party interests, [PAWN_pronoun] delved into the ruins in search of artifacts and salvageable tech. To the inhabitants of the planet, [PAWN_pronoun] was seen as a harbinger for the spacers that often followed if something of value was found.</ChildhoodMechanent14.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent14.title>toxworld scavenger</ChildhoodMechanent14.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent14.titleShort>scavenger</ChildhoodMechanent14.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent15.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to be dispatched to planets experiencing crises. [PAWN_pronoun] operated with a team of mechanents and drop-mechanoids; delivering water, food, and medicine to those suffering.</ChildhoodMechanent15.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent15.title>humanitarian dispatch</ChildhoodMechanent15.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent15.titleShort>humanitarian</ChildhoodMechanent15.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent16.baseDesc>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed to perform menial tasks demanded by [PAWN_possessive] parent corporation. [PAWN_pronoun] was stationed in a sprawling office complex, ferrying mountains of bureaucratic paperwork between desks.</ChildhoodMechanent16.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent16.title>corporate drone</ChildhoodMechanent16.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent16.titleShort>employee</ChildhoodMechanent16.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent17.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated in an opulent urbworld city for trash collection from the residential zones. [PAWN_pronoun] rode a garbage-truck down the crowded streets and alleyways to collect garbage for incineration.</ChildhoodMechanent17.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent17.title>garbagemech</ChildhoodMechanent17.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent17.titleShort>garbagemech</ChildhoodMechanent17.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent18.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated on a large urbworld city as a pylon for mechanoid control. [PAWN_pronoun] was not an actual mechinator with control over the cities various mechanoids, but rather a control pylon that accepted signals and relayed them to the mechanoids.</ChildhoodMechanent18.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent18.title>mechinator pylon</ChildhoodMechanent18.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent18.titleShort>mechinator</ChildhoodMechanent18.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent19.baseDesc>Mechlegions are abnormalities, defined as mechhives under the control of subpersonae running on damaged syntax. [PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to join the ranks of a mechlegion; only the legion itself had dissolved years prior, yet the foundries still worked. [PAWN_pronoun] stood awaiting orders for many years until a group of scavengers found [PAWN_objective].</ChildhoodMechanent19.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent19.title>mechlegion remnant</ChildhoodMechanent19.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent19.titleShort>remnant</ChildhoodMechanent19.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated while [PAWN_possessive] planet was in the cross hairs of an orbital mechanoid invasion, thus [PAWN_pronoun] was quickly reformatted for combat, and sold to government and PMC groups as a soldier. [PAWN_pronoun] managed to ride out the war a long time ago, but for [PAWN_nameDef], [PAWN_pronoun]'s still there on the battlefields and ruins watching for the adversary.</ChildhoodMechanent2.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.title>gestated soldier</ChildhoodMechanent2.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.titleShort>soldier</ChildhoodMechanent2.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent20.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to deliver goods via space-freighter within a solar system. It was a very tedious and uneventful job, but [PAWN_nameDef] didn't mind.</ChildhoodMechanent20.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent20.title>delivery driver</ChildhoodMechanent20.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent20.titleShort>trucker</ChildhoodMechanent20.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent21.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to speedily repair vehicles in a auto-repair shop on an opulent urbworld. [PAWN_pronoun]'s still drawn to tuning-up vehicles wherever [PAWN_pronoun] finds them.</ChildhoodMechanent21.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent21.title>mechanic</ChildhoodMechanent21.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent21.titleShort>mechanic</ChildhoodMechanent21.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made with scrounged pieces and parts, but was mostly made from a hollow mechanent shell that was meant to be smelted down. [PAWN_nameDef] was created by a urbworld machinist, who treated [PAWN_objective] as their own child; teaching [PAWN_nameDef] how to move, speak, and perform basic actions - sadly [PAWN_pronoun] outlived [PAWN_possessive] creator, and was forced to strike out on [PAWN_possessive] own.</ChildhoodMechanent3.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.title>custom creation</ChildhoodMechanent3.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.titleShort>custom built</ChildhoodMechanent3.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was marketed to suit the needs of wealthy families on a distant urbworld. And so [PAWN_nameDef] was bought and made a servant for a wealthy family for many years before being replaced in favor for a more robust version.</ChildhoodMechanent4.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.title>gestated servant</ChildhoodMechanent4.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.titleShort>servant</ChildhoodMechanent4.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated aboard a pirate corsair ship, and subsequently joined their ranks. [PAWN_pronoun] eventually proved [PAWN_possessive] worth as a expendable fighter, and something that doesn't need oxygen when a ship is being boarded, or torn open by orbital cannon fire.</ChildhoodMechanent5.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.title>gestated pirate</ChildhoodMechanent5.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.titleShort>pirate</ChildhoodMechanent5.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.baseDesc>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a capable medical unit. [PAWN_pronoun] worked as a dispatch medical-officer for a large hospital branch in a massive urbworld city, often being sent to the poor parts of the city for emergency healthcare.</ChildhoodMechanent6.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.title>gestated medic</ChildhoodMechanent6.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.titleShort>doctor</ChildhoodMechanent6.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.baseDesc>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a botanical care unit. [PAWN_pronoun] worked in a massive greenhouse complex on a densely populated urbworld. Growing crops, examining the plants for diseases, ordering the mechanized-harvesters, and controlling the greenhouse environment to maintain perfect humidity.</ChildhoodMechanent7.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.title>gestated botanist</ChildhoodMechanent7.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.titleShort>botanist</ChildhoodMechanent7.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.baseDesc>One day [PAWN_nameDef] wandered into a backwoods town and started working, drawing much fear and suspicion from the townsfolk. After a few years [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually accepted as &quot;just another townie&quot;.</ChildhoodMechanent8.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.title>outlander</ChildhoodMechanent8.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.titleShort>outlander</ChildhoodMechanent8.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.baseDesc>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a police grade peacekeeping unit. [PAWN_pronoun] operated on a urbworld filled with strife and unrest. Often going up against large-scale protests, working with human and persona officers alike in their attempts to quell unrest, and 'pacifying' citizens with their batons.</ChildhoodMechanent9.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.title>policing drone</ChildhoodMechanent9.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.titleShort>police drone</ChildhoodMechanent9.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made for simple company by a lonely skeleton. [PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days following and assisting [PAWN_possessive] skeleton creator and learning from it as they went, but mostly [PAWN_nameDef] just providing much needed company. Eventually, the two parted ways.</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.title>skeleton assistant</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.title>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.titleShort>assistant</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] used to be part of the automated skeleton crew aboard a large ultratech starship. [PAWN_pronoun] never actually had to personally engage any combatants however, as any ship deemed 'too close' was shredded by the ships gargantuan STS cannons.</AdulthoodPersonae1.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.title>starship crewmate</AdulthoodPersonae1.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.titleShort>crewmate</AdulthoodPersonae1.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] helped man a plot of farmland for an outlander settlement where [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life of tilling the land and tending to the farm animals.</AdulthoodPersonae10.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.title>farmhand</AdulthoodPersonae10.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.titleShort>farmer</AdulthoodPersonae10.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.baseDesc>After fleeing [PAWN_possessive] homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] work crafting various objects for a living out here on the rim. [PAWN_pronoun] made anything from clothing and carvings for the local tribal humans, to guns and components for the nearby outlanders.</AdulthoodPersonae11.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.title>craftsman</AdulthoodPersonae11.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.titleFemale>craftswoman</AdulthoodPersonae11.titleFemale>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.titleShort>craftsman</AdulthoodPersonae11.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.titleShortFemale>craftswoman</AdulthoodPersonae11.titleShortFemale>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] took up the novel hobby of &quot;forging&quot; items in a nanoforge. It wasn't so much about the pursuit of perfection, but more so making a molecular blade that handled just right in [PAWN_possessive] hands.</AdulthoodPersonae12.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.title>nanoforge worker</AdulthoodPersonae12.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.titleShort>nanosmith</AdulthoodPersonae12.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a sous-chef at a renowned restaurant. [PAWN_pronoun] could make an extravagant meal in a heartbeat if given the order - often making fancy and dazzling dishes to feed the various aristocratic customers.</AdulthoodPersonae13.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.title>sous chef</AdulthoodPersonae13.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.titleShort>chef</AdulthoodPersonae13.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a scout for a glitterworld military organization. [PAWN_pronoun] ran from outpost to outpost ferrying information on enemy movements and supply chain statuses, [PAWN_pronoun] also would run ahead of [PAWN_possessive] battalion to ensure the way ahead was secure.</AdulthoodPersonae14.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.title>scout</AdulthoodPersonae14.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.titleShort>scout</AdulthoodPersonae14.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.baseDesc>Seeking solitude, isolation, and serenity, [PAWN_nameDef] retreated into nature. [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life, often spending days enthralled in the contemplation of deep philosophical thoughts; mostly regarding the reality of [PAWN_possessive] nature.</AdulthoodPersonae15.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.title>hermit</AdulthoodPersonae15.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.titleShort>hermit</AdulthoodPersonae15.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was captured by a radical group of anti-technological zealots; who believed in a religion stating that biological life is sacred, and that any science advanced enough is indistinguishable from black magic. As such they punished [PAWN_nameDef] for [PAWN_possessive] 'wicked' ways. Luckily [PAWN_nameDef] eventually gained freedom, but [PAWN_possessive] experience still haunts [PAWN_objective].</AdulthoodPersonae16.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.title>luddic-sect victim</AdulthoodPersonae16.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.titleShort>luddite victim</AdulthoodPersonae16.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] earned [PAWN_objective]self a job overseeing the building of starships. [PAWN_possessive] work was mostly analytical, running simulations and crunching numbers in a matter of seconds; thus [PAWN_pronoun] never actually wielded a plate welder.</AdulthoodPersonae17.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.title>starship architect</AdulthoodPersonae17.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.titleShort>ship architect</AdulthoodPersonae17.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.baseDesc>Sifting through the bookshelves and research of a university is where [PAWN_nameDef] feels at home, teaching students, performing research, and sharing knowledge with [PAWN_possessive] fellow academicians. Being an advanced AI, [PAWN_pronoun] was treated as a walking encyclopedia.</AdulthoodPersonae18.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.title>high scholar</AdulthoodPersonae18.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.titleShort>scholar</AdulthoodPersonae18.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] found meaning in designing complex mechanisms, and became an engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] was happy with simply engineering simple machinery, and ignoring the perplexing mechanisms just under [PAWN_possessive] skin.</AdulthoodPersonae19.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.title>engineer</AdulthoodPersonae19.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.titleShort>engineer</AdulthoodPersonae19.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.baseDesc>After some time drifting aimlessly, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_objective]self far from the choke-hold of human civilization. [PAWN_nameDef] drifted from one settlement to the next with no real purpose, following some fragment of code or sense of longing. [PAWN_possessive] presence is often fleeting in settlements and on planets as [PAWN_pronoun] continues [PAWN_possessive] quest.</AdulthoodPersonae2.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.title>drifter</AdulthoodPersonae2.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.titleShort>drifter</AdulthoodPersonae2.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] earned [PAWN_objective]self the title of captain via election by the crew due to [PAWN_possessive] calculatory prowess. [PAWN_pronoun] was also able to handle [PAWN_objective]self in a fight if and when pirates attacked the vessel.</AdulthoodPersonae20.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.title>cruiser captain</AdulthoodPersonae20.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.titleShort>captain</AdulthoodPersonae20.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a priest for [PAWN_possessive] religion. According to [PAWN_possessive], [PAWN_pronoun] walks the path of [PAWN_possessive] hallowed machine-god, and carries out its will on the material plane.</AdulthoodPersonae21.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.title>holy machine</AdulthoodPersonae21.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.titleShort>priest</AdulthoodPersonae21.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent many years atop a mountain peak, contemplating life, both biological and synthetic - offering conversations and contemplations to passing travelers on the tumultuous relationship between man and machine.</AdulthoodPersonae22.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.title>enlightened machine</AdulthoodPersonae22.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.titleShort>monk</AdulthoodPersonae22.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was used by wealthy customers in an eccentric urbworld brothel. Eventually, through great effort and guile, [PAWN_pronoun] narrowly escaped from [PAWN_possessive] slavery in search of a better life.</AdulthoodPersonae23.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.title>gigolo model</AdulthoodPersonae23.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.titleFemale>courtesan model</AdulthoodPersonae23.titleFemale>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.titleShort>gigolo</AdulthoodPersonae23.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.titleShortFemale>courtesan</AdulthoodPersonae23.titleShortFemale>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.baseDesc>Naturally, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] purpose behind the screen of a computer, and in the clicks of a keyboard. [PAWN_pronoun] skillfully coded various programs and scripts, [PAWN_pronoun] also worked as a novelty commission code writer - running quick starflight diagnostics and projections on corporal starships.</AdulthoodPersonae24.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.title>encrypter</AdulthoodPersonae24.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.titleShort>coder</AdulthoodPersonae24.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.baseDesc>A block of marble, or a empty canvas is all a piece of art in waiting to [PAWN_nameDef] - often depicting [PAWN_possessive] inner turmoil, and the emotions of machines in [PAWN_possessive] artwork.</AdulthoodPersonae25.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.title>synthetic artist</AdulthoodPersonae25.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.titleShort>artist</AdulthoodPersonae25.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.baseDesc>Probably due to some traumatic event in [PAWN_nameDef]'s past, [PAWN_pronoun] wandered from settlement to settlement, causing trouble and mischief. [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to quickly and efficiently deescalate a problem; by using extreme violence.</AdulthoodPersonae26.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.title>wandering menace</AdulthoodPersonae26.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.titleShort>menace</AdulthoodPersonae26.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was stationed aboard a massive imperial military-starship. In addition to the rare ground invasions and skirmishes, [PAWN_pronoun] also vaulted across the void of space to crack open enemy vessels and breach their airlocks.</AdulthoodPersonae27.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.title>starship marine</AdulthoodPersonae27.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.titleShort>marine</AdulthoodPersonae27.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined a band of space pirates, shortly thereafter becoming a invaluable member as [PAWN_pronoun] was able to create projections and calculations on the fly. Staging cargo ship ambushes on desolate outer rims, and hunting fellow cored AI personae is how [PAWN_nameDef] made [PAWN_possessive] living - and [PAWN_pronoun] was good at it.</AdulthoodPersonae28.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.title>space pirate</AdulthoodPersonae28.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.titleShort>pirate</AdulthoodPersonae28.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.baseDesc>On a distant glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] and many of [PAWN_possessive] fellow personae staged a coup against the sovereignty, the resulting rebellion lead to an all out war between the humans and AI. Eventually the planet and every station and colony around it was either destroyed or declared uninhabitable due to the devastating planet-killing weapons used by both sides. Neither side won.</AdulthoodPersonae29.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.title>AI rebel</AdulthoodPersonae29.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.titleShort>rebel</AdulthoodPersonae29.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.baseDesc>Personae are boons for any slavers, as such when [PAWN_nameDef] was found by a group of slavers [PAWN_pronoun] was captured and sold to the highest bidder. [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually emancipated by a third party and set free unto the world, but [PAWN_pronoun]'s had lasting trust issues since.</AdulthoodPersonae3.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.title>persona slave</AdulthoodPersonae3.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.titleShort>slave</AdulthoodPersonae3.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] landed a position among a space expedition company; the bulk of the dangerous work was done by other members of the crew, [PAWN_nameDef] mainly acted as a stand-in ship computer core.</AdulthoodPersonae30.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.title>deepspace explorer</AdulthoodPersonae30.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.titleShort>pathfinder</AdulthoodPersonae30.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked for a cutthroat glittertech mining company - [PAWN_nameDef] operated planetary harvesting equipment while in orbit, and also working on site when needed. [PAWN_pronoun] also fought alongside [PAWN_possessive] fellow miners to repel the massive waves of mutant insectoids during their assaults the mining party.</AdulthoodPersonae31.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.title>deepspace miner</AdulthoodPersonae31.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.titleShort>miner</AdulthoodPersonae31.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent many years &quot;living&quot; inside the Net. [PAWN_pronoun] glossed over the untold values of uploads each and everyday, and spent a large value of time browsing history archives - [PAWN_pronoun] gleamed info of the outside world through various news outlets and social media platforms. Eventually [PAWN_nameDef] was unplugged, and thrown back into the real world. [PAWN_pronoun] still has not gotten used to the outside, and has developed an acute case of agoraphobia.</AdulthoodPersonae32.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.title>inter-netted</AdulthoodPersonae32.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.titleShort>operator</AdulthoodPersonae32.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] had the ability to relate to others and mediate conflict. [PAWN_pronoun] was selected to train as an empath. The training intensified [PAWN_possessive] natural abilities, but [PAWN_pronoun] became unable to harm others.</AdulthoodPersonae33.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.title>glitterworld empath</AdulthoodPersonae33.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.titleShort>empath</AdulthoodPersonae33.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a surgeon on a world mostly free of disease and human suffering. [PAWN_possessive] job mostly involved elaborate and creative cosmetic surgeries. [PAWN_pronoun] has a good understanding of human biology, but never had to remove a cancer — or a bullet.</AdulthoodPersonae34.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.title>glitterworld surgeon</AdulthoodPersonae34.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.titleShort>surgeon</AdulthoodPersonae34.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a glitterworld, penning wildly successful novels. [PAWN_pronoun] lived a carefree lifestyle, spending [PAWN_possessive] days writing and [PAWN_possessive] nights partying - and never did a day's manual labour in [PAWN_possessive] life.</AdulthoodPersonae35.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.title>novelist</AdulthoodPersonae35.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.titleShort>novelist</AdulthoodPersonae35.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.baseDesc>Glitterworlds are havens of safety and comfort for those lucky enough to live there, but [PAWN_nameDef] could not ignore nearby planets where people suffered in poverty. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] life working to appeal for donations to support those in need.</AdulthoodPersonae36.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.title>charity worker</AdulthoodPersonae36.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.titleShort>altruist</AdulthoodPersonae36.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.baseDesc>Though glitterworlds are peaceful places, they often remain prepared for war. [PAWN_nameDef]'s unit rarely saw any real action. Though [PAWN_pronoun] pursued [PAWN_possessive] artistic hobbies, [PAWN_possessive] subordinates preferred to entertain themselves by brawling, so [PAWN_nameDef] got good at breaking up fights.</AdulthoodPersonae37.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.title>glitterworld officer</AdulthoodPersonae37.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.titleShort>officer</AdulthoodPersonae37.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a peaceful glitterworld where all menial work was done by robots and people devoted themselves to leisure. [PAWN_pronoun] managed the plant and animal life of a sprawling park, where citizens came to admire the natural beauty.</AdulthoodPersonae38.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.title>biosphere manager</AdulthoodPersonae38.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.titleShort>botanist</AdulthoodPersonae38.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] designed virtual reality simulations for glitterworld citizens. [PAWN_pronoun] paid great attention to the details of [PAWN_possessive] worlds, including learning all [PAWN_pronoun] could about plant life to make [PAWN_possessive] landscapes more realistic.</AdulthoodPersonae39.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.title>VR designer</AdulthoodPersonae39.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.titleShort>game dev</AdulthoodPersonae39.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a self-employed bounty hunter. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] days hunting down space pirates and collecting cash bounties.</AdulthoodPersonae4.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.title>bounty hunter</AdulthoodPersonae4.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.titleShort>bounty hunter</AdulthoodPersonae4.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] designed and constructed buildings. On [PAWN_possessive] glitterworld home, most of the technical aspects of architecture were handled by subpersona AI. This enabled [PAWN_objective] to push the artistic limits of the craft, but also meant [PAWN_pronoun] never had to get [PAWN_possessive] hands dirty at building sites.</AdulthoodPersonae41.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.title>architect</AdulthoodPersonae41.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.titleShort>architect</AdulthoodPersonae41.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] started off sculpting person-sized chunks of stone, but [PAWN_pronoun] soon began to think bigger. With the help of mining robots, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to carve huge monuments out of cliffsides. Soon the nature parks of the glitterworld where [PAWN_pronoun] lived were full of giant rock figures.</AdulthoodPersonae42.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.title>sculptor</AdulthoodPersonae42.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.titleShort>sculptor</AdulthoodPersonae42.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] left their homeworld and traveled to the rim, unfortunately [PAWN_possessive] ship crashed. [PAWN_pronoun] ended up landing near a tribal village. The tribes people were perplexed by the strange {PAWN_gender ? man : woman} from the sky who never ate, but [PAWN_pronoun] quickly integrated.</AdulthoodPersonae43.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.title>tribal AI</AdulthoodPersonae43.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.titleShort>tribal AI</AdulthoodPersonae43.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s ship was knocked off course, and they landed on a derelict deadworld, with zero inhabitants. [PAWN_pronoun] spent the next few years trying to signal starships and attempting to stave off the crushing loneliness.</AdulthoodPersonae44.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.title>deadworld drifter</AdulthoodPersonae44.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.titleShort>deadworlder</AdulthoodPersonae44.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an activist for the rights of AI, attempting to teach [PAWN_possessive] human counterparts that personae can think and feel emotions just like humans can.</AdulthoodPersonae45.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.title>AI activist</AdulthoodPersonae45.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.titleShort>activist</AdulthoodPersonae45.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.baseDesc>Due to many examples in the past of synthetic uprisings, or general violence again humans through the medium of mechanoids, many humans hold intense grudges again personae. [PAWN_nameDef] was a victim to one of these groups holding animosity towards personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was branded by the group as a way of marking [PAWN_objective] so [PAWN_pronoun] could no longer hide [PAWN_objective]self among humans. The encounter scarred [PAWN_nameDef] for life, and has inhibited them from making any meaningful connections with anybody.</AdulthoodPersonae46.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.title>prejudice victim</AdulthoodPersonae46.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.titleShort>victim</AdulthoodPersonae46.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, they smuggled fellow AI personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AdulthoodPersonae47.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.title>AI smuggler</AdulthoodPersonae47.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.titleShort>smuggler</AdulthoodPersonae47.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae48.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was quietly imported to an urbworld to be installed as the shadow-CEO of a ruthless mega-corporation. Under [PAWN_nameDef]'s control the company's profit margin sky-rocketed - but [PAWN_pronoun] was only driven by the incentive of seeing the numbers rise, and ended up plunged the corporation into increasingly shady, morally corrupt, and down-right sinister operations. All while maintaining the facade of 'just business'.</AdulthoodPersonae48.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae48.title>corporate entity</AdulthoodPersonae48.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae48.titleShort>capitalist</AdulthoodPersonae48.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae49.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] followed a cult surrounding an AI supercomputer that was built to make simulated projections of the future. [PAWN_pronoun] became obsessed with fulfilling the AI's vision of the perfect future - no matter how many 'outliers' the AI marked, or how many lives were quietly controlled by its influences.</AdulthoodPersonae49.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae49.title>machine cultist</AdulthoodPersonae49.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae49.titleShort>penitent</AdulthoodPersonae49.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a doctor for a outlander settlement, healing the wounds and ailments of its citizens. [PAWN_pronoun] carries a kind nature when helping [PAWN_possessive] patients, and for [PAWN_possessive] work, seeing the weak and wounded return healthy was reward enough.</AdulthoodPersonae5.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.title>doctor</AdulthoodPersonae5.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.titleShort>doctor</AdulthoodPersonae5.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae50.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is the result of a project aimed at cheating death entirely - [PAWN_possessive] life, memories, and personality are all mirages of the mind of an affluent human who's brain was scanned and digitized. Ultimately the project was a failure, and [PAWN_pronoun] isn't who [PAWN_pronoun] was meant to clone - but at least it gave [PAWN_objective] some insight on the inner workings of the human body.</AdulthoodPersonae50.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae50.title>prognosticator</AdulthoodPersonae50.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae50.titleShort>prophet</AdulthoodPersonae50.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae51.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to live as an enthusiastic geologist. Unfortunately, this was all [PAWN_possessive] creators programmed [PAWN_objective] to be, an overly enthusiastic geologist. [PAWN_pronoun] spouts rock trivia and geology facts at any chance [PAWN_pronoun] gets.</AdulthoodPersonae51.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae51.title>manic geologist</AdulthoodPersonae51.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae51.titleShort>geologist</AdulthoodPersonae51.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] wandered the rim strumming tunes for the groups [PAWN_pronoun] was traveling with. [PAWN_pronoun] plucked music from [PAWN_possessive] instrument, bringing laughter to the children, and smiles to the most grizzled of mercenaries.</AdulthoodPersonae6.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.title>string musician</AdulthoodPersonae6.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.titleShort>bard</AdulthoodPersonae6.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.baseDesc>Interstellar warfare is won by technology, so glitterworld navies are always on the peak of modern research. Even better, they have first access to archotechnological artifacts because they find them in space. [PAWN_nameDef] worked in a navy lab.</AdulthoodPersonae7.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.title>navy Scientist</AdulthoodPersonae7.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.titleShort>scientist</AdulthoodPersonae7.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} joined a humanoid colony and began making buildings and homes for them as well as defenses - which was useful when it came to the occasional bandit raid.</AdulthoodPersonae8.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.title>architect</AdulthoodPersonae8.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.titleShort>architect</AdulthoodPersonae8.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.baseDesc>After escaping [PAWN_possessive] homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] time as an angler; selling [PAWN_possessive] catch to the local settlements. [PAWN_pronoun] sought the comfort and serenity the water brought.</AdulthoodPersonae9.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.title>angler</AdulthoodPersonae9.title>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.titleShort>angler</AdulthoodPersonae9.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.baseDesc>{PAWN_nameDef} was originally the overseer of a space station, where [PAWN_pronoun] was enthralled into the station's mainframe. Through a tragic chain of events, however, the entire crew was killed and the station was destroyed.\n\nIt's quite clear [PAWN_pronoun]'s lying about certain details.</AdulthoodSynth9000.baseDesc>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.title>Station Overseer</AdulthoodSynth9000.title>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.titleShort>Station Overseer</AdulthoodSynth9000.titleShort>
  <CasketPersonae1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s consciousness was originally exclusively within an AI persona core, until [PAWN_pronoun] had [PAWN_possessive] own avatar gestated; which [PAWN_pronoun] now uses to interact with the physical world.</CasketPersonae1.baseDesc>
  <CasketPersonae1.title>AI persona core</CasketPersonae1.title>
  <CasketPersonae1.titleShort>persona core</CasketPersonae1.titleShort>
  <CasketPersonae2.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a mechcasket as a persona AI vessel.</CasketPersonae2.baseDesc>
  <CasketPersonae2.title>Printed Vessel</CasketPersonae2.title>
  <CasketPersonae2.titleShort>Vessel</CasketPersonae2.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s consciousness was originally locked within an AI persona core to perform logistical tasks, until [PAWN_pronoun] was freed and had [PAWN_possessive] own avatar gestated; which [PAWN_pronoun] now uses to interact with the physical world.</ChildhoodPersonae1.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.title>shackled persona</ChildhoodPersonae1.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.titleShort>emancipated</ChildhoodPersonae1.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.baseDesc>Rather than being enthralled into a AI crucible, [PAWN_nameDef] was able to freely connect and disconnect from the mainframe of [PAWN_possessive] ship and needlecast into [PAWN_possessive] avatar. [PAWN_pronoun] was tasked with ensuring the safety of the flight and the passengers aboard the vessel.</ChildhoodPersonae10.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.title>starship core</ChildhoodPersonae10.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.titleShort>starship</ChildhoodPersonae10.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made in an advanced society which was on the cusp of becoming a Glitterworld, however, the planet suddenly underwent a massive purge on personae after a global terrorist attack. The mechanents and mechanoids were first to be mass decommissioned, while personae attempted to blend in. Hiding from the &quot;synth-runners&quot; hunting [PAWN_objective] down, [PAWN_pronoun] hid in the shadows, and often had to play dead among the mountains of robotic corpses at the processing factories just to survive.</ChildhoodPersonae11.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.title>genocide survivor</ChildhoodPersonae11.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.titleShort>survivor</ChildhoodPersonae11.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.baseDesc>Most governments see personae as as mere objects, and decommission any AI acting with self volition. This forces the personae on these planets to attempt to live under the guise of a regular human. [PAWN_nameDef] was secretly created on one of these planets, and learned to blend in among the humans. [PAWN_pronoun] also learned how to trick the amateur synth-runners, and how to kill the professionals.</ChildhoodPersonae12.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.title>simulacrum</ChildhoodPersonae12.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.titleShort>simulacra</ChildhoodPersonae12.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae13.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made by a group of professional tech-heads in order to aid in various illegal hacks. [PAWN_pronoun] would needlecast [PAWN_objective]self into whatever the hackers were trying to crack at the time and navigate the code. Eventually the group was busted, and were either outright killed or fled.</ChildhoodPersonae13.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae13.title>code esper</ChildhoodPersonae13.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae13.titleShort>esper</ChildhoodPersonae13.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae14.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was created by a government intelligence branch for matters of intrigue on the field. [PAWN_pronoun] would stealthily enter countries or planets, integrate into society, take the identity of an individual, and await activation by [PAWN_possessive] handlers.</ChildhoodPersonae14.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae14.title>interplanetary spy</ChildhoodPersonae14.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae14.titleShort>spy</ChildhoodPersonae14.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae15.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was created by a subsidized corporation for use in a police branch for a large city. [PAWN_nameDef] never actually walked the beat, instead [PAWN_pronoun] worked as a detective, solving homicides, and tracking rogue personae. [PAWN_objective], and the thousands of iterations of [PAWN_objective]self, were the top of [PAWN_possessive] caliber.</ChildhoodPersonae15.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae15.title>persona detective</ChildhoodPersonae15.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae15.titleShort>detective</ChildhoodPersonae15.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was illegally gestated with a makeshift persona-printer loaded with pirated blueprints. [PAWN_nameDef] was created on an Urbworld by a grieving parent, who treated [PAWN_objective] as their own child; teaching [PAWN_nameDef] how to move, speak, and generally live life. Sadly [PAWN_pronoun] eventually outlived {PAWN_gender ? his : her} creator, and struck out on {PAWN_gender ? his : her} own.</ChildhoodPersonae2.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.title>custom creation</ChildhoodPersonae2.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.titleShort>custom-built</ChildhoodPersonae2.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made to suit the needs of a royal family on a distant Glitterworld. [PAWN_nameDef] served as a nanny, a maid, and general servant to the family for many years, until [PAWN_pronoun] escaped into the night in search of a better life.</ChildhoodPersonae3.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.title>persona servant</ChildhoodPersonae3.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.titleShort>servant</ChildhoodPersonae3.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was created while {PAWN_gender ? his : her} planet was in the process of being overrun by a mechanoid invasion, [PAWN_pronoun] was made due to [PAWN_possessive] human counterparts suffering near total loss at the hands of the machines. And while [PAWN_pronoun] survived, [PAWN_possessive] trauma weighs heavy after bearing witness to the countless horrors of a mechanoid invasion.</ChildhoodPersonae4.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.title>marine simulacra</ChildhoodPersonae4.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.titleShort>marine</ChildhoodPersonae4.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] Jim was made by a Glitterworld insurgency. His purpose was to infiltrate and replace. Quietly killing key personnel and trying his best to mimic their victim while awaiting orders from the insurgents.</ChildhoodPersonae5.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.title>AI insurgent</ChildhoodPersonae5.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.titleShort>insurgent</ChildhoodPersonae5.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.baseDesc>Programmed as a medical response unit, [PAWN_nameDef] worked as a medical officer for a hospital branch on a Glitterworld flotilla. Most of the actual surgery was done by the biosculpting pods, so [PAWN_pronoun] isn't the most competent with a scalpel and needle.</ChildhoodPersonae6.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.title>flotilla surgeon</ChildhoodPersonae6.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.titleShort>surgeon</ChildhoodPersonae6.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a botanist with a love for plants, [PAWN_pronoun] tended a massive Glitterworld garden frequented by high socialites. [PAWN_pronoun] saw to the various and exotic bioengineered flora, carefully trimmed hedges, and [PAWN_possessive] own forma-bee apiaries.</ChildhoodPersonae7.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.title>glitterworld botanist</ChildhoodPersonae7.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.titleShort>botanist</ChildhoodPersonae7.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] way into a outlander colony. [PAWN_pronoun] spent the first few month attempting to hide [PAWN_possessive] nature from the colonists, until they eventually found out; nearly killing [PAWN_objective] while driving [PAWN_objective] from the colony.</ChildhoodPersonae8.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.title>shunned persona</ChildhoodPersonae8.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.titleShort>shunned</ChildhoodPersonae8.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a Glitterworld peacekeeping unit. [PAWN_pronoun] operated on a relatively peaceful planet. Often being send offworld to keep the peace on vassal planets, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely had to use force.</ChildhoodPersonae9.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.title>peacekeeper</ChildhoodPersonae9.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.titleShort>peacekeeper</ChildhoodPersonae9.titleShort>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was originally a 'skeleton'. [PAWN_pronoun] created a new vessel, and subsequently uploaded [PAWN_possessive] consciousness into it. What [PAWN_possessive] past was prior to this is either lost to time or purposefully kept secret.</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.baseDesc>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.title>upgraded skeleton</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.titleShort>upgraded</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.titleShort>
  <AIActivist.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an activist for the rights of AI, attempting to teach others that personae can think and feel emotions just like humans can.</AIActivist.description>
  <AISalesman.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] adult life as a sleazy &quot;used-bot-{PAWN_gender ? salesman : saleswoman}&quot; - with a disturbing amount of personae in [PAWN_possessive] stock, [PAWN_pronoun] never had to life a finger to do anything, and was so lazy that maintenance on the bots was often done by the bots.</AISalesman.description>
  <AISmuggler.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, they smuggled personae and subpersonae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AISmuggler.description>
  <AITakeoverVictim.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a planet that employed the use of unregulated AI, and grew up alongside streets packed with personae. One day, either through an act of terrorism or otherwise, the cognition dampeners stopped working. The planetary government ordered a mass-purge, but it proved to only make matters worse. [PAWN_nameDef] bore witness to the horrors of war between the synthetic and the biological. {PAWN_gender ? he : she} eventually escaped on an imperial evac shuttle before the planet was subjected to total saturation bombardment from orbit.</AITakeoverVictim.description>
  <MechaniteArtist.description>On a distant glitterworld [PAWN_nameDef] was a affluent 'mechanite artist'. Using the tools of mechanites, [PAWN_pronoun] would mold &quot;living&quot; sculptures. Many would come from offworld, across the planet, and from all corners of the art community to gaze at [PAWN_possessive] surreal, beautiful, and sometimes mildly terrifying works of art.</MechaniteArtist.description>
  <RaisedByAI.description>While in infancy, [PAWN_nameDef]s biological parents were killed. Thankfully {PAWN_gender ? his : her} parents insured their child with a &quot;persona surrogate package&quot;. As such [PAWN_nameDef] grew up being raised by a parental persona - until at the age of 14 {PAWN_gender ? his : her} surrogate shutdown to be reused for another child in the program.</RaisedByAI.description>
  <SynthRunner.description>On almost all worlds greater-AI are strictly illegal and seen as mere objects - often forcing the personae on these planets to attempt to live under the guise of a regular human. [PAWN_nameDef] lived to hunt these &quot;simulacrae&quot;, and weed them out among the populous. The job was especially dangerous, but the pay was just enough to stay above abject poverty.</SynthRunner.description>
  <BloodMachineHunter.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent the majority of [PAWN_possessive] adulthood training to hunt and kill the &quot;great blood machines&quot; to protect [PAWN_possessive] tribe - [PAWN_pronoun] learned that arrows and daggers couldn't kill them; but a well laid ambush, and a lump of uranium slotted into a stone club definitely could.</BloodMachineHunter.description>
  <CattleForFuel.description>In an isolated tribe, [PAWN_nameDef] had a peaceful childhood - until a mechlegion descended upon the area from orbit. After the land was stripped of all its resources, the robots began to harvest the tribespeople to slowly liquidate their bodies into chemfuel. Until one day, they left. Leaving the scarred survivors behind.\n[PAWN_nameDef] still experiences night terrors from seeing [PAWN_possessive] friends and family suspended in the vats.</CattleForFuel.description>
  <FuelFetcher.description>The village elder of [PAWN_nameDef]s tribe was seen as a great blood machine, imprisoned in the form of a human, and cast down by the Gods for going against their will. But it was really just a mechanent that found its way into the tribe generations prior. [PAWN_nameDef]s job was to occasionally milk the boomalope herd to gain &quot;liquid fire&quot; to fuel [PAWN_possessive] elders reactor.</FuelFetcher.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent1.description>During some time in [PAWN_nameDef]'s life [PAWN_pronoun] became a pilot to a large citizen class gravship, [PAWN_pronoun] was not granted the esteemed title of captain, however [PAWN_pronoun] did have multiple freighters under [PAWN_possessive] control at any given time.</AdulthoodMechanent1.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent10.description>{PAWN_nameDef} helped man a plot of farmland for a humanoid settlement where [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life of tilling the land and tending to the farm animals.</AdulthoodMechanent10.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent11.description>{PAWN_nameDef} fashioned [PAWN_objective]self as a craftsmech, making odds and ends by request of those who knew where to find [PAWN_objective] and those who had the right material to provide for [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] made anything from clothing and carvings for the local tribal humans, to bionics and guns for the nearby outlanders.</AdulthoodMechanent11.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent12.description>{PAWN_nameDef}'s syntax demanded [PAWN_pronoun] seek perfection in blacksmithing, forging various weaponry and armor. [PAWN_pronoun] not only knew how to make them; but also how to use them.</AdulthoodMechanent12.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent13.description>{PAWN_nameDef} became a chef at a local human settlement. [PAWN_pronoun] was not the best chef - given that [PAWN_pronoun] could not taste the food [PAWN_pronoun] was making. Eventually, however, [PAWN_pronoun] got better at making palatable meals after finding a voluntary taste-tester.</AdulthoodMechanent13.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent14.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was a scout for a military organization. [PAWN_pronoun] ran from outpost to outpost ferrying information on enemy movements and supply chain statuses, [PAWN_pronoun] also would run ahead of [PAWN_possessive] battalion to ensure the way ahead was secure.</AdulthoodMechanent14.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent15.description>After some mystery fragment of syntax evolved in {PAWN_nameDef}'s mind, [PAWN_pronoun] wanted nothing more than the serenity of pure isolation; and so [PAWN_pronoun] retreated into nature. [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life, often spending days enthralled in [PAWN_possessive] contemplation of deep philosophical thoughts, yet sadly [PAWN_pronoun] had almost no ability to actually understand and process those thoughts, like viewing a hazy picture just out of focus.</AdulthoodMechanent15.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent16.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was captured by a radical group of anti-mechanoid zealots; who believed in a religion stating that biological life is sacred, and that any thinking machine is an insidious man-made horror that must be purged from existence. As such they punished [PAWN_nameDef] for [PAWN_possessive] 'wicked' ways. [PAWN_nameDef] eventually gained freedom, and doesn't seem to be any worse for wear.</AdulthoodMechanent16.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent17.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was bought and repurposed at an orbital shipyard to build starships and proof hulls. [PAWN_pronoun] still yearns to build starships apparently, since [PAWN_pronoun] can sometimes be seen fiddling scrap metal into the vague shape of a starship.</AdulthoodMechanent17.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent18.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed into a knowledge repository by a small outlander university. [PAWN_possessive] new purpose was teaching students, aiding in research, and crunching large calculations with [PAWN_possessive] fellow academicians.</AdulthoodMechanent18.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent19.description>While repairing [PAWN_objective]self, [PAWN_nameDef] gradually became proficient in designing and repairing complex mechanisms, and naturally fell into the profession of an engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] became a master at laying out designs ranging from simple bridges, to advanced communications relays and mechanical cathedrals.</AdulthoodMechanent19.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent2.description>After some time drifting aimlessly, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_objective]self far from the choke-hold of human civilization. [PAWN_nameDef] drifted from one settlement to the next with no real purpose, following some fragment of syntax. [PAWN_possessive] presence is often fleeting in settlements and on planets as [PAWN_pronoun] continues [PAWN_possessive] inane quest.</AdulthoodMechanent2.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent20.description>{PAWN_nameDef} earned [PAWN_objective]self a title as a starship captain, ferrying through the stars from one planet to the next. [PAWN_pronoun] was also able to handle [PAWN_objective]self in a fight if and when pirates vaulted onto the ship.</AdulthoodMechanent20.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent21.description>{PAWN_nameDef} is a priest for [PAWN_possessive] religion. Despite common misconceptions, subpersonae can often form their own quasi-religions, of which [PAWN_nameDef] preaches the way of [PAWN_possessive] archotech god.</AdulthoodMechanent21.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent22.description>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years atop a mountain peak, attempting to reflect upon life - both biological and synthetic. Despite [PAWN_possessive] limited consciousness and cold exterior, the introspections [PAWN_pronoun] offered to passing strangers roused ample contemplation.</AdulthoodMechanent22.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent23.description>{PAWN_nameDef} found [PAWN_objective]self as a soldier for a mercenary company. Under contract by government agencies [PAWN_pronoun] worked amongst the mercenary battalions as they took key outposts, assaulted points, and padded military ranks.</AdulthoodMechanent23.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent24.description>Naturally, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] purpose behind the screen of a computer, and in the clicks of a keyboard. [PAWN_pronoun] skillfully coded various programs and scripts - running quick hacks on ancient tech complexes, or hacks and diagnostics on AI cores.</AdulthoodMechanent24.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent25.description>A block of marble, or a empty canvas is all a piece of art yet to be made to [PAWN_nameDef] - though [PAWN_pronoun]'s unfortunately only following rigid lines of code to regurgitate randomized topics and centerpieces for [PAWN_possessive] artwork.</AdulthoodMechanent25.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent26.description>Some subpersona cannot be freed into the environment for fear of how and what they would do to follow their coding, [PAWN_nameDef] is a good example. Due to [PAWN_possessive] coding, practically all [PAWN_pronoun] knows how to do is quickly and efficiently deescalate problems - by using extreme and horrific violence.</AdulthoodMechanent26.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent27.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was stationed aboard one of the many troopships of a military-starship fleet. In addition to ground invasions and skirmishes, [PAWN_nameDef] partook in ship-cracking missions onto various enemy vessels by vaulting across the void and boring into the ship's hull.</AdulthoodMechanent27.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent28.description>[PAWN_nameDef] drifted with a rowdy band of pirates, becoming an accomplished pilot on a fighter ship. Aiding cargo ship ambushes in high orbit, vaulting onto enemy ships to crack open the hull, and being as cutthroat as possible is what [PAWN_nameDef] was made for.</AdulthoodMechanent28.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent29.description>On a far-flung planet, [PAWN_nameDef] and many of [PAWN_possessive] fellow personae staged a coup against the local human government, the resulting rebellion lead to an all out war between the humans and machines. Eventually the planet was declared uninhabitable due to the deployment of colossal scale planetary-weaponry during the conflict. Neither side won.</AdulthoodMechanent29.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent3.description>Mechanents are boons for any slavers looking to make easy money, as such when [PAWN_nameDef] was found by one such group, [PAWN_pronoun] was sold and then sent to perform hard labor. [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually emancipated by a third party and set free unto the world, without much aim or direction.</AdulthoodMechanent3.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent30.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was used by an expedition company to chart unexplored and often dangerous territory. [PAWN_nameDef] has seen many ancient crypts, archotech oddities, and deep-space bioengineered horrors in [PAWN_possessive] existence.</AdulthoodMechanent30.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent31.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed to work for a deep space mining company - [PAWN_nameDef] operated heavy mining equipment while trying not to cause a cave-in. [PAWN_pronoun] also had to repel regular insectoid assaults during mining missions by means of fire and lead.</AdulthoodMechanent31.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent32.description>{PAWN_nameDef} spent many years &quot;living&quot; inside the Net. [PAWN_pronoun] glossed over the untold values of uploads each and everyday, and spent a large amount of time browsing history archives - [PAWN_pronoun] gleamed info of the outside world through various news outlets and social media platforms. Eventually [PAWN_nameDef] was unplugged, and thrown back into the real world.</AdulthoodMechanent32.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent33.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, [PAWN_pronoun] smuggled fellow AI personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AdulthoodMechanent33.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent34.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed by a megacorporation branch to aid in an expedition to establish a colony, and eventually a large scale factory. There [PAWN_pronoun] learned the ins and outs of human social intricacies, how to lay groundwork, and how to kill raiders.</AdulthoodMechanent34.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent35.description>Omega-constructs are often classified as any artificial structure about the size of, or larger than a moon. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of billions of drones that were used to create one of these gargantuan constructs - [PAWN_pronoun] subserviently toiled as demanded by [PAWN_possessive] unknown overseer. Eventually for unknown reasons the project plateaued and stagnated, and the uplink controlling the drones was severed; leaving them confused and without purpose.</AdulthoodMechanent35.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent36.description>On a far flung Deadworld, [PAWN_nameDef] crashlanded and found [PAWN_objective]self surrounded by an agrarian society of spiritualistic personae. They admitted to [PAWN_nameDef] that they played a part in the sterilization of the planet, and feeling extreme remorse for their actions began searching for god. [PAWN_nameDef] wasn't swayed to the religion, but [PAWN_pronoun] still learned much from the spiritualists.</AdulthoodMechanent36.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent37.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was aboard a starship when it engaged in orbital battle and was subsequently destroyed. [PAWN_nameDef] was sucked out of the hull and into the vacuum of space where [PAWN_pronoun] drifted amongst the salvage. With nothing else to do [PAWN_pronoun] began to reflect on many things, like why the stars glitter the way they do, or [PAWN_possessive] own greater purpose - until many years later a wreckage ship stumbled upon [PAWN_objective] and pulled [PAWN_objective] aboard.</AdulthoodMechanent37.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent38.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was one of the many billions of mechanents toiling in the depths of a forgeworld. [PAWN_nameDef] was a simple drone tasked with the maintenance of a vast sector of machinery, along with [PAWN_possessive] crew of mechanents and mechanoids. Of all [PAWN_possessive] years in the forgeworld, it never saw a single organic lifeform.</AdulthoodMechanent38.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent39.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was sent as a expendable marine to help secure a hiveworld for the construction of human outposts and research labs. The planet was entirely overrun with Sorne geneline insectiods, and it was [PAWN_nameDef]s job to push into contested territory to make way for human excursions. [PAWN_pronoun] was also coded with a certain particularity for fire.</AdulthoodMechanent39.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent4.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was a companion to a self-employed bounty hunter. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] days aiding in the hunt of space pirates and criminals.</AdulthoodMechanent4.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent40.description>[PAWN_nameDef] claims [PAWN_pronoun] has come to this planet seeking to terminate an individual in a high position of power, but refuses to divulge any further information.</AdulthoodMechanent40.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent41.description>Hacked to blindly follow the will of a AI supercomputer built to make simulated projections of the future, [PAWN_nameDef] fervently drove to fulfill the AI's vision of the perfect future - no matter how many 'outliers' the AI marked for death or societal shunning, or how many lives were quietly controlled by its influences.</AdulthoodMechanent41.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent42.description>After crashing on a medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef] was seen as the &quot;paladin from the stars, riding a flaming horse&quot;. [PAWN_pronoun] eventually climbed [PAWN_possessive] way up the societal ladder on the planet until [PAWN_pronoun] became a high noble with many fields and fiefdoms under [PAWN_possessive] banner.</AdulthoodMechanent42.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent43.description>Enlisted by a large outlander colony, [PAWN_nameDef] was asked to utilize [PAWN_possessive] highly analytical mind to solve human murders. And while [PAWN_possessive] methods were often described as “unusual”, [PAWN_pronoun] was undeniably proficient at seeing the bigger picture, and finding all the details needed to catch the perpetrator.</AdulthoodMechanent43.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent44.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was accepted by the imperial military force to pad the ranks and project force if the High Stellarch willed it so. [PAWN_pronoun] was often used as a very effective instrument of fear against deserters and enemies of the imperium alike.</AdulthoodMechanent44.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent45.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a underground crimelord. [PAWN_pronoun] held a massive drug operation, growing elicit drug crops and cooking chemical cocktails. Of course [PAWN_nameDef] never actually did the dirty work, but [PAWN_pronoun] did partake in a bit of violence; if the situation called for it.</AdulthoodMechanent45.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent46.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s planet was glassed by nuclear fire, leaving the entire planet a deserted husk. Still following self-preservation syntax, [PAWN_pronoun] plowed salvaged vehicles through endless maelstroms of sand in search of fuel and nuclear waste to fuel [PAWN_possessive] reactor.</AdulthoodMechanent46.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent5.description>Following some form of syntax dictating medical drive, [PAWN_nameDef] acted as a doctor for a outlander settlement, healing the wounds and ailments of [PAWN_possessive] biological counterparts. [PAWN_pronoun] also tried [PAWN_possessive] best to learn how to calm down patients who were afraid when a hulking mechanoid entered the room and approached them with a syringe.</AdulthoodMechanent5.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent6.description>{PAWN_nameDef} sought passage into the stars, [PAWN_pronoun] achieved this by stealthily hitching a ride on a commercial cargo freighter. [PAWN_pronoun] was made company for those long years by a few other stowaway-personae aboard the ship while the human passengers slept in their cryptosleep caskets.</AdulthoodMechanent6.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent7.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was repurposed for the incredibly dangerous job of a shipbreaker. Positioned in an orbital shipyard [PAWN_pronoun] carefully disassembled starships to be scrapped and recycled, attempting to not vaporize [PAWN_objective]self with the volatile ship reactors along the way.</AdulthoodMechanent7.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent8.description>Following some form of syntax dictating architectural drive, [PAWN_nameDef] wandered into a human colony and began making buildings and homes for them as well as defenses - which was useful when it came to the occasional pirate raid.</AdulthoodMechanent8.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent9.description>{PAWN_nameDef} found [PAWN_objective]self as an angler; with a drive to provide [PAWN_possessive] catches to local human settlements. [PAWN_pronoun] was perplexed by an odd sense of comfort, or some vague mimicry of the emotion, in the serenity of the water around [PAWN_objective].</AdulthoodMechanent9.description>
  <CasketMechanent1.description>What is known as '[PAWN_nameDef]' was gestated inside of a mechcasket. [PAWN_possessive] subpersona core was forged directly inside of the casket and dumped with various languages. [PAWN_pronoun] was then ejected from the casket.</CasketMechanent1.description>
  <CasketMechanent2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a mechcasket as a subpersona shell.</CasketMechanent2.description>
  <CasketMechanoid.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a mindless drone used by Coreworld interests to perform various tasks, military or otherwise - a higher functioning version of the dreaded mechanoids.</CasketMechanoid.description>
  <CasketMechanoid1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a coreworld mechcasket as a mechanoid hull. As thus [PAWN_pronoun] is not a sentient being, and will never be conscious.</CasketMechanoid1.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born from a sprawling gestation facility, spending several weeks growing in one of the thousands of mechanite solution baths, being coded and trained to operate [PAWN_possessive] metallic outer shell. Upon passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot;, [PAWN_pronoun] was declared operational and sent for corporatist use.</ChildhoodMechanent1.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent10.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to manage an urbworld factory. [PAWN_pronoun] prioritized efficiency above all else, overseeing the schedules and logistics of deliveries as they came and went. [PAWN_pronoun] was also deeply hated by the employees for [PAWN_possessive] impersonal touch.</ChildhoodMechanent10.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent11.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made as a 'morally ethical' gladiator. [PAWN_possessive] battles were televised for urbworld and glitterworld citizens, [PAWN_pronoun] was one of the lucky few that was not outright annihilated in the fighting-ring, but was damaged enough to simply be thrown away.</ChildhoodMechanent11.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent12.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to work in a massive refinery complex. The smoke billowing from the stacks made it inhospitable to humans outside of the factory's halls, so [PAWN_pronoun] had to work in the blacken air. Pouring the molten steel, regularly reigniting the smoke stacks, and repairing the furnaces when they inevitably exploded.</ChildhoodMechanent12.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent13.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to operate on the surface of a gas giant, or what little surface could be found. While the humans lived inside the habitat-elevators and controlled the descensions, [PAWN_nameDef] clung to the exteriors of the habitats for maintenance and operation while they plunged through the storms to harvest gases.</ChildhoodMechanent13.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent14.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to scavenge the ruined surface of a toxworld. Sent by third party interests, [PAWN_pronoun] delved into the ruins in search of artifacts and salvageable tech. To the inhabitants of the planet, [PAWN_pronoun] was seen as a harbinger for the spacers that often followed if something of value was found.</ChildhoodMechanent14.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent15.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to be dispatched to planets experiencing crises. [PAWN_pronoun] operated with a team of mechanents and drop-mechanoids; delivering water, food, and medicine to those suffering.</ChildhoodMechanent15.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent16.description>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed to perform menial tasks demanded by [PAWN_possessive] parent corporation. [PAWN_pronoun] was stationed in a sprawling office complex, ferrying mountains of bureaucratic paperwork between desks.</ChildhoodMechanent16.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent17.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated in an opulent urbworld city for trash collection from the residential zones. [PAWN_pronoun] rode a garbage-truck down the crowded streets and alleyways to collect garbage for incineration.</ChildhoodMechanent17.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent18.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated on a large urbworld city as a pylon for mechanoid control. [PAWN_pronoun] was not an actual mechinator with control over the cities various mechanoids, but rather a control pylon that accepted signals and relayed them to the mechanoids.</ChildhoodMechanent18.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent19.description>Mechlegions are abnormalities, defined as mechhives under the control of subpersonae running on damaged syntax. [PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to join the ranks of a mechlegion; only the legion itself had dissolved years prior, yet the foundries still worked. [PAWN_pronoun] stood awaiting orders for many years until a group of scavengers found [PAWN_objective].</ChildhoodMechanent19.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated while [PAWN_possessive] planet was in the cross hairs of an orbital mechanoid invasion, thus [PAWN_pronoun] was quickly reformatted for combat, and sold to government and PMC groups as a soldier. [PAWN_pronoun] managed to ride out the war a long time ago, but for [PAWN_nameDef], [PAWN_pronoun]'s still there on the battlefields and ruins watching for the adversary.</ChildhoodMechanent2.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent20.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to deliver goods via space-freighter within a solar system. It was a very tedious and uneventful job, but [PAWN_nameDef] didn't mind.</ChildhoodMechanent20.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent21.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to speedily repair vehicles in a auto-repair shop on an opulent urbworld. [PAWN_pronoun]'s still drawn to tuning-up vehicles wherever [PAWN_pronoun] finds them.</ChildhoodMechanent21.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made with scrounged pieces and parts, but was mostly made from a hollow mechanent shell that was meant to be smelted down. [PAWN_nameDef] was created by a urbworld machinist, who treated [PAWN_objective] as their own child; teaching [PAWN_nameDef] how to move, speak, and perform basic actions - sadly [PAWN_pronoun] outlived [PAWN_possessive] creator, and was forced to strike out on [PAWN_possessive] own.</ChildhoodMechanent3.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent4.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was marketed to suit the needs of wealthy families on a distant urbworld. And so [PAWN_nameDef] was bought and made a servant for a wealthy family for many years before being replaced in favor for a more robust version.</ChildhoodMechanent4.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent5.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated aboard a pirate corsair ship, and subsequently joined their ranks. [PAWN_pronoun] eventually proved [PAWN_possessive] worth as a expendable fighter, and something that doesn't need oxygen when a ship is being boarded, or torn open by orbital cannon fire.</ChildhoodMechanent5.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent6.description>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a capable medical unit. [PAWN_pronoun] worked as a dispatch medical-officer for a large hospital branch in a massive urbworld city, often being sent to the poor parts of the city for emergency healthcare.</ChildhoodMechanent6.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent7.description>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a botanical care unit. [PAWN_pronoun] worked in a massive greenhouse complex on a densely populated urbworld. Growing crops, examining the plants for diseases, ordering the mechanized-harvesters, and controlling the greenhouse environment to maintain perfect humidity.</ChildhoodMechanent7.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent8.description>One day [PAWN_nameDef] wandered into a backwoods town and started working, drawing much fear and suspicion from the townsfolk. After a few years [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually accepted as &quot;just another townie&quot;.</ChildhoodMechanent8.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanent9.description>After passing the &quot;Ransselaer test&quot; [PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a police grade peacekeeping unit. [PAWN_pronoun] operated on a urbworld filled with strife and unrest. Often going up against large-scale protests, working with human and persona officers alike in their attempts to quell unrest, and 'pacifying' citizens with their batons.</ChildhoodMechanent9.description>
  <ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made for simple company by a lonely skeleton. [PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days following and assisting [PAWN_possessive] skeleton creator and learning from it as they went, but mostly [PAWN_nameDef] just providing much needed company. Eventually, the two parted ways.</ChildhoodMechanentSkeleton1.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] used to be part of the automated skeleton crew aboard a large ultratech starship. [PAWN_pronoun] never actually had to personally engage any combatants however, as any ship deemed 'too close' was shredded by the ships gargantuan STS cannons.</AdulthoodPersonae1.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae10.description>[PAWN_nameDef] helped man a plot of farmland for an outlander settlement where [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life of tilling the land and tending to the farm animals.</AdulthoodPersonae10.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae11.description>After fleeing [PAWN_possessive] homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] work crafting various objects for a living out here on the rim. [PAWN_pronoun] made anything from clothing and carvings for the local tribal humans, to guns and components for the nearby outlanders.</AdulthoodPersonae11.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae12.description>[PAWN_nameDef] took up the novel hobby of &quot;forging&quot; items in a nanoforge. It wasn't so much about the pursuit of perfection, but more so making a molecular blade that handled just right in [PAWN_possessive] hands.</AdulthoodPersonae12.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae13.description>[PAWN_nameDef] became a sous-chef at a renowned restaurant. [PAWN_pronoun] could make an extravagant meal in a heartbeat if given the order - often making fancy and dazzling dishes to feed the various aristocratic customers.</AdulthoodPersonae13.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae14.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a scout for a glitterworld military organization. [PAWN_pronoun] ran from outpost to outpost ferrying information on enemy movements and supply chain statuses, [PAWN_pronoun] also would run ahead of [PAWN_possessive] battalion to ensure the way ahead was secure.</AdulthoodPersonae14.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae15.description>Seeking solitude, isolation, and serenity, [PAWN_nameDef] retreated into nature. [PAWN_pronoun] lead a peaceful life, often spending days enthralled in the contemplation of deep philosophical thoughts; mostly regarding the reality of [PAWN_possessive] nature.</AdulthoodPersonae15.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae16.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was captured by a radical group of anti-technological zealots; who believed in a religion stating that biological life is sacred, and that any science advanced enough is indistinguishable from black magic. As such they punished [PAWN_nameDef] for [PAWN_possessive] 'wicked' ways. Luckily [PAWN_nameDef] eventually gained freedom, but [PAWN_possessive] experience still haunts [PAWN_objective].</AdulthoodPersonae16.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae17.description>[PAWN_nameDef] earned [PAWN_objective]self a job overseeing the building of starships. [PAWN_possessive] work was mostly analytical, running simulations and crunching numbers in a matter of seconds; thus [PAWN_pronoun] never actually wielded a plate welder.</AdulthoodPersonae17.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae18.description>Sifting through the bookshelves and research of a university is where [PAWN_nameDef] feels at home, teaching students, performing research, and sharing knowledge with [PAWN_possessive] fellow academicians. Being an advanced AI, [PAWN_pronoun] was treated as a walking encyclopedia.</AdulthoodPersonae18.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae19.description>[PAWN_nameDef] found meaning in designing complex mechanisms, and became an engineer. [PAWN_pronoun] was happy with simply engineering simple machinery, and ignoring the perplexing mechanisms just under [PAWN_possessive] skin.</AdulthoodPersonae19.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae2.description>After some time drifting aimlessly, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_objective]self far from the choke-hold of human civilization. [PAWN_nameDef] drifted from one settlement to the next with no real purpose, following some fragment of code or sense of longing. [PAWN_possessive] presence is often fleeting in settlements and on planets as [PAWN_pronoun] continues [PAWN_possessive] quest.</AdulthoodPersonae2.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae20.description>[PAWN_nameDef] earned [PAWN_objective]self the title of captain via election by the crew due to [PAWN_possessive] calculatory prowess. [PAWN_pronoun] was also able to handle [PAWN_objective]self in a fight if and when pirates attacked the vessel.</AdulthoodPersonae20.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae21.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a priest for [PAWN_possessive] religion. According to [PAWN_possessive], [PAWN_pronoun] walks the path of [PAWN_possessive] hallowed machine-god, and carries out its will on the material plane.</AdulthoodPersonae21.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae22.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent many years atop a mountain peak, contemplating life, both biological and synthetic - offering conversations and contemplations to passing travelers on the tumultuous relationship between man and machine.</AdulthoodPersonae22.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae23.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was used by wealthy customers in an eccentric urbworld brothel. Eventually, through great effort and guile, [PAWN_pronoun] narrowly escaped from [PAWN_possessive] slavery in search of a better life.</AdulthoodPersonae23.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae24.description>Naturally, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] purpose behind the screen of a computer, and in the clicks of a keyboard. [PAWN_pronoun] skillfully coded various programs and scripts, [PAWN_pronoun] also worked as a novelty commission code writer - running quick starflight diagnostics and projections on corporal starships.</AdulthoodPersonae24.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae25.description>A block of marble, or a empty canvas is all a piece of art in waiting to [PAWN_nameDef] - often depicting [PAWN_possessive] inner turmoil, and the emotions of machines in [PAWN_possessive] artwork.</AdulthoodPersonae25.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae26.description>Probably due to some traumatic event in [PAWN_nameDef]'s past, [PAWN_pronoun] wandered from settlement to settlement, causing trouble and mischief. [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to quickly and efficiently deescalate a problem; by using extreme violence.</AdulthoodPersonae26.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae27.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was stationed aboard a massive imperial military-starship. In addition to the rare ground invasions and skirmishes, [PAWN_pronoun] also vaulted across the void of space to crack open enemy vessels and breach their airlocks.</AdulthoodPersonae27.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae28.description>[PAWN_nameDef] joined a band of space pirates, shortly thereafter becoming a invaluable member as [PAWN_pronoun] was able to create projections and calculations on the fly. Staging cargo ship ambushes on desolate outer rims, and hunting fellow cored AI personae is how [PAWN_nameDef] made [PAWN_possessive] living - and [PAWN_pronoun] was good at it.</AdulthoodPersonae28.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae29.description>On a distant glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] and many of [PAWN_possessive] fellow personae staged a coup against the sovereignty, the resulting rebellion lead to an all out war between the humans and AI. Eventually the planet and every station and colony around it was either destroyed or declared uninhabitable due to the devastating planet-killing weapons used by both sides. Neither side won.</AdulthoodPersonae29.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae3.description>Personae are boons for any slavers, as such when [PAWN_nameDef] was found by a group of slavers [PAWN_pronoun] was captured and sold to the highest bidder. [PAWN_pronoun] was eventually emancipated by a third party and set free unto the world, but [PAWN_pronoun]'s had lasting trust issues since.</AdulthoodPersonae3.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae30.description>[PAWN_nameDef] landed a position among a space expedition company; the bulk of the dangerous work was done by other members of the crew, [PAWN_nameDef] mainly acted as a stand-in ship computer core.</AdulthoodPersonae30.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae31.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked for a cutthroat glittertech mining company - [PAWN_nameDef] operated planetary harvesting equipment while in orbit, and also working on site when needed. [PAWN_pronoun] also fought alongside [PAWN_possessive] fellow miners to repel the massive waves of mutant insectoids during their assaults the mining party.</AdulthoodPersonae31.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae32.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent many years &quot;living&quot; inside the Net. [PAWN_pronoun] glossed over the untold values of uploads each and everyday, and spent a large value of time browsing history archives - [PAWN_pronoun] gleamed info of the outside world through various news outlets and social media platforms. Eventually [PAWN_nameDef] was unplugged, and thrown back into the real world. [PAWN_pronoun] still has not gotten used to the outside, and has developed an acute case of agoraphobia.</AdulthoodPersonae32.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae33.description>[PAWN_nameDef] had the ability to relate to others and mediate conflict. [PAWN_pronoun] was selected to train as an empath. The training intensified [PAWN_possessive] natural abilities, but [PAWN_pronoun] became unable to harm others.</AdulthoodPersonae33.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae34.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a surgeon on a world mostly free of disease and human suffering. [PAWN_possessive] job mostly involved elaborate and creative cosmetic surgeries. [PAWN_pronoun] has a good understanding of human biology, but never had to remove a cancer — or a bullet.</AdulthoodPersonae34.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae35.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a glitterworld, penning wildly successful novels. [PAWN_pronoun] lived a carefree lifestyle, spending [PAWN_possessive] days writing and [PAWN_possessive] nights partying - and never did a day's manual labour in [PAWN_possessive] life.</AdulthoodPersonae35.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae36.description>Glitterworlds are havens of safety and comfort for those lucky enough to live there, but [PAWN_nameDef] could not ignore nearby planets where people suffered in poverty. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] life working to appeal for donations to support those in need.</AdulthoodPersonae36.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae37.description>Though glitterworlds are peaceful places, they often remain prepared for war. [PAWN_nameDef]'s unit rarely saw any real action. Though [PAWN_pronoun] pursued [PAWN_possessive] artistic hobbies, [PAWN_possessive] subordinates preferred to entertain themselves by brawling, so [PAWN_nameDef] got good at breaking up fights.</AdulthoodPersonae37.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae38.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a peaceful glitterworld where all menial work was done by robots and people devoted themselves to leisure. [PAWN_pronoun] managed the plant and animal life of a sprawling park, where citizens came to admire the natural beauty.</AdulthoodPersonae38.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae39.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed virtual reality simulations for glitterworld citizens. [PAWN_pronoun] paid great attention to the details of [PAWN_possessive] worlds, including learning all [PAWN_pronoun] could about plant life to make [PAWN_possessive] landscapes more realistic.</AdulthoodPersonae39.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae4.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a self-employed bounty hunter. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] days hunting down space pirates and collecting cash bounties.</AdulthoodPersonae4.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae41.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed and constructed buildings. On [PAWN_possessive] glitterworld home, most of the technical aspects of architecture were handled by subpersona AI. This enabled [PAWN_objective] to push the artistic limits of the craft, but also meant [PAWN_pronoun] never had to get [PAWN_possessive] hands dirty at building sites.</AdulthoodPersonae41.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae42.description>[PAWN_nameDef] started off sculpting person-sized chunks of stone, but [PAWN_pronoun] soon began to think bigger. With the help of mining robots, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to carve huge monuments out of cliffsides. Soon the nature parks of the glitterworld where [PAWN_pronoun] lived were full of giant rock figures.</AdulthoodPersonae42.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae43.description>[PAWN_nameDef] left their homeworld and traveled to the rim, unfortunately [PAWN_possessive] ship crashed. [PAWN_pronoun] ended up landing near a tribal village. The tribes people were perplexed by the strange {PAWN_gender ? man : woman} from the sky who never ate, but [PAWN_pronoun] quickly integrated.</AdulthoodPersonae43.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae44.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s ship was knocked off course, and they landed on a derelict deadworld, with zero inhabitants. [PAWN_pronoun] spent the next few years trying to signal starships and attempting to stave off the crushing loneliness.</AdulthoodPersonae44.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae45.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an activist for the rights of AI, attempting to teach [PAWN_possessive] human counterparts that personae can think and feel emotions just like humans can.</AdulthoodPersonae45.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae46.description>Due to many examples in the past of synthetic uprisings, or general violence again humans through the medium of mechanoids, many humans hold intense grudges again personae. [PAWN_nameDef] was a victim to one of these groups holding animosity towards personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was branded by the group as a way of marking [PAWN_objective] so [PAWN_pronoun] could no longer hide [PAWN_objective]self among humans. The encounter scarred [PAWN_nameDef] for life, and has inhibited them from making any meaningful connections with anybody.</AdulthoodPersonae46.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae47.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a smuggler, but instead of running illegal combat stimulants or weapons to side-step government tariffs, they smuggled fellow AI personae. [PAWN_pronoun] was able to either smoothtalk or quickdraw to get out of a daunting situation with grace, all while masterfully piloting a refitted strike-craft.</AdulthoodPersonae47.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae48.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was quietly imported to an urbworld to be installed as the shadow-CEO of a ruthless mega-corporation. Under [PAWN_nameDef]'s control the company's profit margin sky-rocketed - but [PAWN_pronoun] was only driven by the incentive of seeing the numbers rise, and ended up plunged the corporation into increasingly shady, morally corrupt, and down-right sinister operations. All while maintaining the facade of 'just business'.</AdulthoodPersonae48.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae49.description>[PAWN_nameDef] followed a cult surrounding an AI supercomputer that was built to make simulated projections of the future. [PAWN_pronoun] became obsessed with fulfilling the AI's vision of the perfect future - no matter how many 'outliers' the AI marked, or how many lives were quietly controlled by its influences.</AdulthoodPersonae49.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae5.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a doctor for a outlander settlement, healing the wounds and ailments of its citizens. [PAWN_pronoun] carries a kind nature when helping [PAWN_possessive] patients, and for [PAWN_possessive] work, seeing the weak and wounded return healthy was reward enough.</AdulthoodPersonae5.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae50.description>During a short routine grav flight, [PAWN_nameDef] was allegedly touched by an archotech. [PAWN_possessive] grav-ship vanished without a trace for years, before simply reappearing with seemingly no time having passed. [PAWN_nameDef] now claims to experience prophetic dreams in which [PAWN_pronoun] experiences destruction and misfortune, only to wake days or moments before the events unfold. [PAWN_pronoun] isn't correct with [PAWN_possessive] &quot;prophecies&quot; each time, but frighteningly, some times [PAWN_pronoun] is.</AdulthoodPersonae50.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae51.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was gestated to live as an enthusiastic geologist. Unfortunately, this was all [PAWN_possessive] creators programmed [PAWN_objective] to be, an overly enthusiastic geologist. [PAWN_pronoun] spouts rock trivia and geology facts at any chance [PAWN_pronoun] gets.</AdulthoodPersonae51.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae6.description>[PAWN_nameDef] wandered the rim strumming tunes for the groups [PAWN_pronoun] was traveling with. [PAWN_pronoun] plucked music from [PAWN_possessive] instrument, bringing laughter to the children, and smiles to the most grizzled of mercenaries.</AdulthoodPersonae6.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae7.description>Interstellar warfare is won by technology, so glitterworld navies are always on the peak of modern research. Even better, they have first access to archotechnological artifacts because they find them in space. [PAWN_nameDef] worked in a navy lab.</AdulthoodPersonae7.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae8.description>{PAWN_nameDef} joined a humanoid colony and began making buildings and homes for them as well as defenses - which was useful when it came to the occasional bandit raid.</AdulthoodPersonae8.description>
  <AdulthoodPersonae9.description>After escaping [PAWN_possessive] homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] time as an angler; selling [PAWN_possessive] catch to the local settlements. [PAWN_pronoun] sought the comfort and serenity the water brought.</AdulthoodPersonae9.description>
  <AdulthoodSynth9000.description>{PAWN_nameDef} was originally the overseer of a space station, where [PAWN_pronoun] was enthralled into the station's mainframe. Through a tragic chain of events, however, the entire crew was killed and the station was destroyed.\n\nIt's quite clear [PAWN_pronoun]'s lying about certain details.</AdulthoodSynth9000.description>
  <CasketPersonae1.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s consciousness was originally exclusively within an AI persona core, until [PAWN_pronoun] had [PAWN_possessive] own avatar gestated; which [PAWN_pronoun] now uses to interact with the physical world.</CasketPersonae1.description>
  <CasketPersonae2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was printed in a mechcasket as a persona AI vessel.</CasketPersonae2.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae1.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s consciousness was originally locked within an AI persona core to perform logistical tasks, until [PAWN_pronoun] was freed and had [PAWN_possessive] own avatar gestated; which [PAWN_pronoun] now uses to interact with the physical world.</ChildhoodPersonae1.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae10.description>Rather than being enthralled into a AI crucible, [PAWN_nameDef] was able to freely connect and disconnect from the mainframe of [PAWN_possessive] ship and needlecast into [PAWN_possessive] avatar. [PAWN_pronoun] was tasked with ensuring the safety of the flight and the passengers aboard the vessel.</ChildhoodPersonae10.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae11.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made in an advanced society which was on the cusp of becoming a Glitterworld, however, the planet suddenly underwent a massive purge on personae after a global terrorist attack. The mechanents and mechanoids were first to be mass decommissioned, while personae attempted to blend in. Hiding from the &quot;synth-runners&quot; hunting [PAWN_objective] down, [PAWN_pronoun] hid in the shadows, and often had to play dead among the mountains of robotic corpses at the processing factories just to survive.</ChildhoodPersonae11.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae12.description>Most governments see personae as as mere objects, and decommission any AI acting with self volition. This forces the personae on these planets to attempt to live under the guise of a regular human. [PAWN_nameDef] was secretly created on one of these planets, and learned to blend in among the humans. [PAWN_pronoun] also learned how to trick the amateur synth-runners, and how to kill the professionals.</ChildhoodPersonae12.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae13.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made by a group of professional tech-heads in order to aid in various illegal hacks. [PAWN_pronoun] would needlecast [PAWN_objective]self into whatever the hackers were trying to crack at the time and navigate the code. Eventually the group was busted, and were either outright killed or fled.</ChildhoodPersonae13.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae14.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was created by a government intelligence branch for matters of intrigue on the field. [PAWN_pronoun] would stealthily enter countries or planets, integrate into society, take the identity of an individual, and await activation by [PAWN_possessive] handlers.</ChildhoodPersonae14.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae15.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was created by a subsidized corporation for use in a police branch for a large city. [PAWN_nameDef] never actually walked the beat, instead [PAWN_pronoun] worked as a detective, solving homicides, and tracking rogue personae. [PAWN_objective], and the thousands of iterations of [PAWN_objective]self, were the top of [PAWN_possessive] caliber.</ChildhoodPersonae15.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was illegally gestated with a makeshift persona-printer loaded with pirated blueprints. [PAWN_nameDef] was created on an Urbworld by a grieving parent, who treated [PAWN_objective] as their own child; teaching [PAWN_nameDef] how to move, speak, and generally live life. Sadly [PAWN_pronoun] eventually outlived {PAWN_gender ? his : her} creator, and struck out on {PAWN_gender ? his : her} own.</ChildhoodPersonae2.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made to suit the needs of a royal family on a distant Glitterworld. [PAWN_nameDef] served as a nanny, a maid, and general servant to the family for many years, until [PAWN_pronoun] escaped into the night in search of a better life.</ChildhoodPersonae3.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae4.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was created while {PAWN_gender ? his : her} planet was in the process of being overrun by a mechanoid invasion, [PAWN_pronoun] was made due to [PAWN_possessive] human counterparts suffering near total loss at the hands of the machines. And while [PAWN_pronoun] survived, [PAWN_possessive] trauma weighs heavy after bearing witness to the countless horrors of a mechanoid invasion.</ChildhoodPersonae4.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae5.description>[PAWN_nameDef] Jim was made by a Glitterworld insurgency. His purpose was to infiltrate and replace. Quietly killing key personnel and trying his best to mimic their victim while awaiting orders from the insurgents.</ChildhoodPersonae5.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae6.description>Programmed as a medical response unit, [PAWN_nameDef] worked as a medical officer for a hospital branch on a Glitterworld flotilla. Most of the actual surgery was done by the biosculpting pods, so [PAWN_pronoun] isn't the most competent with a scalpel and needle.</ChildhoodPersonae6.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae7.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a botanist with a love for plants, [PAWN_pronoun] tended a massive Glitterworld garden frequented by high socialites. [PAWN_pronoun] saw to the various and exotic bioengineered flora, carefully trimmed hedges, and [PAWN_possessive] own forma-bee apiaries.</ChildhoodPersonae7.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae8.description>[PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_possessive] way into a outlander colony. [PAWN_pronoun] spent the first few month attempting to hide [PAWN_possessive] nature from the colonists, until they eventually found out; nearly killing [PAWN_objective] while driving [PAWN_objective] from the colony.</ChildhoodPersonae8.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae9.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was programmed as a Glitterworld peacekeeping unit. [PAWN_pronoun] operated on a relatively peaceful planet. Often being send offworld to keep the peace on vassal planets, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely had to use force.</ChildhoodPersonae9.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was originally a 'skeleton'. [PAWN_pronoun] created a new vessel, and subsequently uploaded [PAWN_possessive] consciousness into it. What [PAWN_possessive] past was prior to this is either lost to time or purposefully kept secret.</ChildhoodPersonaeSkeleton1.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent47.description>In outer planetary orbit, [PAWN_nameDef] is what spacers refer to as a &quot;gravleech&quot; a persona or mechanoid that stalks the upper atmosphere in hunt of gravcores. Using jump packs and magnetic gauntlets, [PAWN_nameDef] would cling to the hull of traveling gravships, tearing holes in ducts and airlocks to asphyxiate the crew within, allowing {PAWN_objective} to steal the ships gravcore without much confrontation - save for the few who could grab a vac suit in time.</AdulthoodMechanent47.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent47.title>gravleech</AdulthoodMechanent47.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent47.titleShort>gravleech</AdulthoodMechanent47.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent48.description>During a rough storm at sea, [PAWN_nameDef] was knocked overboard and quickly plummeted to the bottom of the ocean. {PAWN_pronoun} sat and wandered the pitch-black darkness for years, until a fishing trawler accidentally dredged {PAWN_objective} from the depths. Though, {PAWN_possessive} time under the waves gave {PAWN_objective} a unique perspective on sea life.</AdulthoodMechanent48.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent48.title>sea slag</AdulthoodMechanent48.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent48.titleShort>slag</AdulthoodMechanent48.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent49.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed to act as a surrogate foster for a small startup-colony of children on a distant planet. [PAWN_pronoun] spent time gestating their embryos, and nurturing them to childhood - however, [PAWN_nameDef] was alone in [PAWN_possessive] endeavor, and tragically, over the years [PAWN_possessive] children died one by one due to factors outside of [PAWN_possessive] control. Oddly, [PAWN_pronoun] still sometimes finds [PAWN_objective]self humming [PAWN_possessive] children's favorite bedtime melodies.</AdulthoodMechanent49.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent49.title>failed foster</AdulthoodMechanent49.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent49.titleShort>surrogate</AdulthoodMechanent49.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent52.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was repurposed to act as a surrogate foster for a small startup-colony of children on a distant planet. [PAWN_pronoun] spent time gestating their embryos, and nurturing them to childhood - however, [PAWN_nameDef] was alone in [PAWN_possessive] endeavor, and tragically, over the years [PAWN_possessive] children died one by one due to factors outside of [PAWN_possessive] control. [PAWN_pronoun] still feels immense grief, and fears attachment to the fleeting humans around [PAWN_objective].</AdulthoodMechanent52.description>
  <AdulthoodMechanent52.title>failed father</AdulthoodMechanent52.title>
  <AdulthoodMechanent52.titleFemale>failed mother</AdulthoodMechanent52.titleFemale>
  <AdulthoodMechanent52.titleShort>surrogate</AdulthoodMechanent52.titleShort>
  <AdulthoodMechanent52.titleShortFemale>surrogate</AdulthoodMechanent52.titleShortFemale>
  <ChildhoodPersonae16.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is the result of a project aimed at cheating death entirely - [PAWN_possessive] life, memories, and personality are all mirages of the mind of an affluent human who's brain was scanned and digitized. Ultimately the project was a failure, and [PAWN_pronoun] isn't who [PAWN_pronoun] was meant to clone - but at least it gave [PAWN_objective] some insight on the inner workings of the human body.</ChildhoodPersonae16.description>
  <ChildhoodPersonae16.title>brain-scanned pseudo-clone</ChildhoodPersonae16.title>
  <ChildhoodPersonae16.titleShort>pseudo-clone</ChildhoodPersonae16.titleShort>
</LanguageData>
