<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Elder.description>The Elder is the supreme commander of a Brotherhood chapter, responsible for all strategic decisions, diplomatic relations, and the chapter's overall direction. They have devoted their lives to the Brotherhood's cause and earned the respect of all members through wisdom, skill, and unwavering dedication to preserving technology and protecting humanity.</FCP_Title_BoS_Elder.description>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Elder.label>elder</FCP_Title_BoS_Elder.label>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Initiate.description>The lowest rank in the Brotherhood of Steel. Initiates are in training, learning the Brotherhood's ways and proving their worth. They perform basic duties and assist full members while earning the right to become a true Brother or Sister of Steel.</FCP_Title_BoS_Initiate.description>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Initiate.label>initiate</FCP_Title_BoS_Initiate.label>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Knight.description>Knights are the Brotherhood's front-line warriors, fully trained in combat operations and the maintenance of power armor. They lead patrols, engage hostile forces, and recover pre-War technology from dangerous locations. Knights are the backbone of Brotherhood military strength.</FCP_Title_BoS_Knight.description>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Knight.label>knight</FCP_Title_BoS_Knight.label>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Paladin.description>Paladins are the Brotherhood's elite warriors and field commanders. They lead major operations, command Knights in battle, and make critical tactical decisions. Clad in the finest power armor and wielding the most advanced weapons, Paladins embody the Brotherhood's military might and tactical expertise.</FCP_Title_BoS_Paladin.description>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Paladin.label>paladin</FCP_Title_BoS_Paladin.label>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Scribe.description>Scribes are the Brotherhood's scholars and technicians, dedicated to preserving and understanding pre-War technology. They maintain archives, research artifacts, and ensure that knowledge is not lost. While not primarily combatants, Scribes are crucial to the Brotherhood's mission.</FCP_Title_BoS_Scribe.description>
  <FCP_Title_BoS_Scribe.label>scribe</FCP_Title_BoS_Scribe.label>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Champion.description>The leader of Lyons' Pride remnants, carrying on Elder Lyons' legacy through action rather than doctrine. They have chosen compassion over dogma, humanity over tradition, and remain the last true believers in Elder Lyons' dream of a Brotherhood that serves rather than rules.</FCP_Title_Lyons_Champion.description>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Champion.label>Lyons' champion</FCP_Title_Lyons_Champion.label>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Member.description>Full members of Lyons' Pride who have proven themselves worthy of Elder Lyons' trust. They fight to protect the innocent and represent the best of what the Brotherhood can be when it serves humanity.</FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Member.description>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Member.label>pride member</FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Member.label>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Recruit.description>New members of Lyons' Pride who have sworn to fight for Elder Lyons' vision of a protected Capital Wasteland. Recruits are proving their dedication to defending humanity, not just hoarding technology.</FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Recruit.description>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Recruit.label>recruit</FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Recruit.label>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Shield.description>Elite warriors who embody Elder Lyons' vision completely. They are the shield between wasteland communities and the dangers that threaten them, fighting not for glory or technology, but for the survival of humanity itself.</FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Shield.description>
  <FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Shield.label>shield of the people</FCP_Title_Lyons_Pride_Shield.label>
  <FCP_Title_Outcast_Defender.description>Defenders are the Outcasts' combat specialists, focused on securing technology and defending Outcast installations. They reject the Brotherhood's shift toward humanitarianism, maintaining strict focus on their original mission.</FCP_Title_Outcast_Defender.description>
  <FCP_Title_Outcast_Defender.label>defender</FCP_Title_Outcast_Defender.label>
  <FCP_Title_Outcast_Protector.description>The Protector leads the Outcasts, maintaining iron discipline and unwavering commitment to technology preservation. They represent the purest form of the Brotherhood's original mission, refusing any compromise or deviation from the founder's vision.</FCP_Title_Outcast_Protector.description>
  <FCP_Title_Outcast_Protector.label>protector</FCP_Title_Outcast_Protector.label>
  <FCP_Title_Outcast_Specialist.description>The entry rank for Outcasts. Specialists have proven their commitment to the original Brotherhood mission of technology recovery above all else. They serve the Outcasts' pragmatic, no-nonsense approach to preserving pre-War knowledge.</FCP_Title_Outcast_Specialist.description>
  <FCP_Title_Outcast_Specialist.label>specialist</FCP_Title_Outcast_Specialist.label>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Captain.description>Senior field officers who command company-sized units. Captains are proven leaders with extensive combat experience. They handle complex operations and serve as the Enclave's primary tactical commanders.</FCP_Title_Enclave_Captain.description>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Captain.label>captain</FCP_Title_Enclave_Captain.label>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Colonel.description>High-ranking officers who oversee strategic operations and base management. Colonels answer directly to the Enclave leadership and are responsible for executing the organization's broader objectives. They command respect and absolute authority.</FCP_Title_Enclave_Colonel.description>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Colonel.label>colonel</FCP_Title_Enclave_Colonel.label>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Lieutenant.description>Junior officers responsible for platoon-level operations. Lieutenants coordinate multiple squads and make tactical decisions in the field. They are expected to demonstrate both combat prowess and leadership ability.</FCP_Title_Enclave_Lieutenant.description>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Lieutenant.label>lieutenant</FCP_Title_Enclave_Lieutenant.label>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Private.description>The lowest rank in the Enclave military structure. Privates are frontline soldiers, trained in the use of advanced weaponry and power armor. They carry out orders without question and serve as the backbone of Enclave forces.</FCP_Title_Enclave_Private.description>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Private.label>private</FCP_Title_Enclave_Private.label>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Sergeant.description>Non-commissioned officers who lead small squads in the field. Sergeants are experienced soldiers who maintain discipline and coordinate tactical operations. They bridge the gap between officers and enlisted personnel.</FCP_Title_Enclave_Sergeant.description>
  <FCP_Title_Enclave_Sergeant.label>sergeant</FCP_Title_Enclave_Sergeant.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_COL.description>The highest rank that achievable in the New California Republic without a political ally. This is one of the highest command positions with the ability to call in reinforcements at the company level and higher including special forces.</FCP_Title_NCR_COL.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_COL.label>NCR army colonel</FCP_Title_NCR_COL.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_LT.description>The first rank within the New California Republic's commissioned officer corps. This is the lowest command position with the ability to call in reinforcements and supplies much faster and with greater quality and quantity.</FCP_Title_NCR_LT.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_LT.label>NCR army lieutenant</FCP_Title_NCR_LT.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_PVT.description>The lowest rank within the New California Republic's military. There isn't a lot of repect in this role, nor is the pay well.</FCP_Title_NCR_PVT.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_PVT.label>NCR army private</FCP_Title_NCR_PVT.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Patrolman.description>.</FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Patrolman.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Patrolman.label>NCR ranger patrolman</FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Patrolman.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Veteran.description>.</FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Veteran.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Veteran.label>NCR ranger veteran</FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Veteran.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Volunteer.description>.</FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Volunteer.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Volunteer.label>NCR ranger volunteer</FCP_Title_NCR_Ranger_Volunteer.label>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_SGT.description>The first rank within the New California Republic's non commissioned officer corps. This is the first step in a professional military carrer with reaL power and responsibilities.</FCP_Title_NCR_SGT.description>
  <FCP_Title_NCR_SGT.label>NCR army sergeant</FCP_Title_NCR_SGT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.description>The highest rank that achievable in the United States Army without a political ally. This is one of the highest command positions with the ability to call in reinforcements at the company level and higher including special forces.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.label>US army colonel</FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.description>The first rank within the United States Army's commissioned officer corps. This is the lowest command position with the ability to call in reinforcements and supplies much faster and with greater quality and quantity.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.label>US army lieutenant</FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.description>The lowest rank within the United States Army. There isn't a lot of respect in this role, nor is the pay well.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.label>US army private</FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.description>The first rank within the United States' non commissioned officer corps. This is the first step in a professional military carrer with reaL power and responsibilities.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.label>US army sergeant</FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.description>.</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.label>US marine colonel</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.description>The lowest rank within the United States Marine Corps. There isn't a lot of respect in this role, nor is the pay well.</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.label>US marine private</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.description>The first rank within the United States Marine Corps' non commissioned officer corps. This is the first step in a professional military career with real power and responsibilities.</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.label>US marine sergeant</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.label>
</LanguageData>
