<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Plant_Banana_Yucca.description>A hardy desert plant found throughout the Mojave, banana yucca produces sweet, starchy fruit that is a staple for survival. Its thick leaves and resilience make it a reliable source of nutrition for wasteland wanderers.</FCP_Plant_Banana_Yucca.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Banana_Yucca.label>Banana Yucca</FCP_Plant_Banana_Yucca.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Barrel_Cactus.description>This round, spiny cactus stores water in its thick stem and can be found scattered across arid landscapes. Barrel cactus fruit is edible and provides a modest but vital source of hydration and nutrition in the harsh wasteland.</FCP_Plant_Barrel_Cactus.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Barrel_Cactus.label>Barrel Cactus</FCP_Plant_Barrel_Cactus.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Broc_Flower.description>A rare desert flower prized for its medicinal properties. Broc flower is a key ingredient in healing powders and is sought after by wasteland survivors for its restorative effects.</FCP_Plant_Broc_Flower.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Broc_Flower.label>Broc Flower</FCP_Plant_Broc_Flower.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Buffalo_Gourd.description>A tough, wild gourd found in arid regions. While not especially tasty, its seeds and flesh can be eaten in a pinch, and it is sometimes used in traditional recipes by wastelanders.</FCP_Plant_Buffalo_Gourd.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Buffalo_Gourd.label>Buffalo Gourd</FCP_Plant_Buffalo_Gourd.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Carrot.description>A nutritious root vegetable cultivated by survivors for its sweet flavor and versatility. Carrots are a staple crop in many wasteland settlements.</FCP_Plant_Carrot.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Carrot.label>Carrot</FCP_Plant_Carrot.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Carrot_Flower.description>The delicate flower of the carrot plant, sometimes found growing wild. Its seeds are used for propagation and can be a rare treat for foragers.</FCP_Plant_Carrot_Flower.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Carrot_Flower.label>Carrot Flower</FCP_Plant_Carrot_Flower.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Cranberry.description>A tart, red berry cultivated in wasteland farms for its nutritional value and use in preserves. Cranberries are a resilient crop, thriving in moist soil.</FCP_Plant_Cranberry.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Cranberry.label>Cranberry</FCP_Plant_Cranberry.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Glowing_Mushroom.description>A mutated fungus that emits a faint, eerie glow. Glowing mushrooms are found in irradiated caves and are sometimes used in wasteland remedies, though they may be mildly radioactive.</FCP_Plant_Glowing_Mushroom.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Glowing_Mushroom.label>Glowing Mushroom</FCP_Plant_Glowing_Mushroom.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Gourd.description>A versatile vegetable grown for its edible flesh and use as a container. Gourds are a common sight in wasteland gardens and provide a reliable food source.</FCP_Plant_Gourd.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Gourd.label>Gourd</FCP_Plant_Gourd.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Honey_Mesquite.description>A hardy desert shrub with sweet pods. Honey mesquite is used by wastelanders for food, fuel, and even medicine, making it a valuable resource in arid regions.</FCP_Plant_Honey_Mesquite.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Honey_Mesquite.label>Honey Mesquite</FCP_Plant_Honey_Mesquite.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Jalapeno.description>A spicy pepper grown in wasteland gardens, jalapenos add heat and flavor to many survivor recipes. Hardy and productive, they are a favorite among cultivators.</FCP_Plant_Jalapeno.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Jalapeno.label>Jalapeno</FCP_Plant_Jalapeno.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Maize.description>A staple crop in the wasteland, maize is grown for its hearty ears and versatility. It is a key ingredient in many survivor meals and can be stored for long periods.</FCP_Plant_Maize.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Maize.label>Maize</FCP_Plant_Maize.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Melon.description>A sweet, juicy fruit grown in wasteland gardens. Melons are prized for their refreshing taste and high water content, making them a valuable crop in arid regions.</FCP_Plant_Melon.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Melon.label>Melon</FCP_Plant_Melon.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Mutated_Fern.description>A strange, mutated fern found in irradiated areas. Its fronds are tough and sometimes used in makeshift remedies, though caution is advised due to possible contamination.</FCP_Plant_Mutated_Fern.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Mutated_Fern.label>Mutated Fern</FCP_Plant_Mutated_Fern.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Mutfruit.description>A genetically modified fruit, mutfruit is a staple crop in the Fallout universe. Its sweet, tangy flavor and high yield make it a favorite among wasteland farmers.</FCP_Plant_Mutfruit.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Mutfruit.label>Mutfruit</FCP_Plant_Mutfruit.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Nevada_Agave.description>A resilient desert succulent, Nevada agave is harvested for its sweet sap and fibrous leaves. Wastelanders use it for food, drink, and crafting.</FCP_Plant_Nevada_Agave.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Nevada_Agave.label>Nevada Agave</FCP_Plant_Nevada_Agave.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Prickly_Pear_Cactus.description>A spiny cactus found in the Mojave, prized for its edible pads and sweet fruit. Prickly pear is a vital source of hydration and nutrition for desert dwellers.</FCP_Plant_Prickly_Pear_Cactus.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Prickly_Pear_Cactus.label>Prickly Pear Cactus</FCP_Plant_Prickly_Pear_Cactus.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Razorgrain.description>A hardy, mutated grain crop grown for its tough stalks and nutritious seeds. Razorgrain is a staple in many wasteland settlements, used for bread and porridge.</FCP_Plant_Razorgrain.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Razorgrain.label>Razorgrain</FCP_Plant_Razorgrain.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Siltbean.description>A protein-rich bean crop, siltbeans are grown in the wasteland for their nutritional value and ability to thrive in poor soil. They are a key ingredient in many survivor meals.</FCP_Plant_Siltbean.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Siltbean.label>Siltbean</FCP_Plant_Siltbean.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Tarberry.description>A mutated berry found in marshy areas, tarberries are prized for their sweet flavor and mild radioactivity. Used in unique wasteland recipes and sometimes for trade.</FCP_Plant_Tarberry.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Tarberry.label>Tarberry</FCP_Plant_Tarberry.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Tato.description>A hybrid of tomato and potato, the tato is a staple crop in the Fallout universe. Its hearty tubers and tangy fruit are a reliable food source for survivors.</FCP_Plant_Tato.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Tato.label>Tato</FCP_Plant_Tato.label>
  <FCP_Plant_Xander_Root.description>A gnarled desert root with potent medicinal properties. Xander root is a key ingredient in healing powders and is highly valued by wasteland healers.</FCP_Plant_Xander_Root.description>
  <FCP_Plant_Xander_Root.label>Xander Root</FCP_Plant_Xander_Root.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Broc_Flower.description>Medicinal flower harvested from broc flower plants. Used in healing powders.</FCP_Raw_Broc_Flower.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Broc_Flower.label>broc flower</FCP_Raw_Broc_Flower.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Buffalo_Gourd.description>Seeds and flesh harvested from buffalo gourd plants. Edible in a pinch.</FCP_Raw_Buffalo_Gourd.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Buffalo_Gourd.label>buffalo gourd</FCP_Raw_Buffalo_Gourd.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Carrot.description>A sweet, nutritious root vegetable harvested from carrot plants. A staple food in the wasteland.</FCP_Raw_Carrot.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Carrot.label>carrot</FCP_Raw_Carrot.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Carrot_Flower.description>Delicate flower harvested from wild carrot plants. Used for propagation and as a rare treat.</FCP_Raw_Carrot_Flower.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Carrot_Flower.label>carrot flower</FCP_Raw_Carrot_Flower.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Cranberry.description>A tart, red berry harvested from cranberry plants. Used in preserves and survivor meals.</FCP_Raw_Cranberry.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Cranberry.label>cranberry</FCP_Raw_Cranberry.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Food_Banana_Yucca.description>Sweet, starchy fruit harvested from banana yucca plants. A staple for survival.</FCP_Raw_Food_Banana_Yucca.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Food_Banana_Yucca.label>banana yucca fruit</FCP_Raw_Food_Banana_Yucca.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Food_Barrel_Cactus.description>Edible fruit harvested from barrel cactus. Provides hydration and nutrition.</FCP_Raw_Food_Barrel_Cactus.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Food_Barrel_Cactus.label>barrel cactus fruit</FCP_Raw_Food_Barrel_Cactus.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Glowing_Mushroom.description>Mutated fungus harvested from glowing mushroom plants. Emits a faint glow and may be mildly radioactive.</FCP_Raw_Glowing_Mushroom.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Glowing_Mushroom.label>glowing mushroom</FCP_Raw_Glowing_Mushroom.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Gourd.description>A versatile vegetable harvested from gourd plants. Edible and useful as a container.</FCP_Raw_Gourd.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Gourd.label>gourd</FCP_Raw_Gourd.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Honey_Mesquite.description>Sweet pods harvested from honey mesquite shrubs. Used for food, fuel, and medicine.</FCP_Raw_Honey_Mesquite.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Honey_Mesquite.label>honey mesquite pod</FCP_Raw_Honey_Mesquite.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Jalapeno.description>A spicy pepper harvested from jalapeno plants. Adds heat to wasteland recipes.</FCP_Raw_Jalapeno.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Jalapeno.label>jalapeno</FCP_Raw_Jalapeno.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Maize.description>Hearty ears of maize harvested from maize plants. A key ingredient in survivor meals.</FCP_Raw_Maize.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Maize.label>maize</FCP_Raw_Maize.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Melon.description>A sweet, juicy fruit harvested from melon plants. Prized for its refreshing taste.</FCP_Raw_Melon.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Melon.label>melon</FCP_Raw_Melon.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Mutated_Fern.description>Tough fronds harvested from mutated fern plants. Sometimes used in makeshift remedies.</FCP_Raw_Mutated_Fern.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Mutated_Fern.label>mutated fern frond</FCP_Raw_Mutated_Fern.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Mutfruit.description>A genetically modified fruit harvested from mutfruit trees. Sweet and tangy.</FCP_Raw_Mutfruit.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Mutfruit.label>mutfruit</FCP_Raw_Mutfruit.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Nevada_Agave.description>Sweet sap and fibrous leaves harvested from Nevada agave. Used for food, drink, and crafting.</FCP_Raw_Nevada_Agave.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Nevada_Agave.label>nevada agave</FCP_Raw_Nevada_Agave.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Prickly_Pear.description>Edible pads and sweet fruit harvested from prickly pear cactus. Vital for desert dwellers.</FCP_Raw_Prickly_Pear.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Prickly_Pear.label>prickly pear</FCP_Raw_Prickly_Pear.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Razorgrain.description>Tough stalks and nutritious seeds harvested from razorgrain plants. Used for bread and porridge.</FCP_Raw_Razorgrain.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Razorgrain.label>razorgrain</FCP_Raw_Razorgrain.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Siltbean.description>Protein-rich beans harvested from siltbean plants. Thrives in poor soil.</FCP_Raw_Siltbean.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Siltbean.label>siltbean</FCP_Raw_Siltbean.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Tarberry.description>Mutated berry harvested from tarberry plants. Sweet and mildly radioactive.</FCP_Raw_Tarberry.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Tarberry.label>tarberry</FCP_Raw_Tarberry.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Tato.description>A hybrid tuber harvested from tato plants. Hearty and tangy.</FCP_Raw_Tato.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Tato.label>tato</FCP_Raw_Tato.label>
  <FCP_Raw_Xander_Root.description>Gnarled root harvested from xander root plants. Highly valued for its medicinal properties.</FCP_Raw_Xander_Root.description>
  <FCP_Raw_Xander_Root.label>xander root</FCP_Raw_Xander_Root.label>
</LanguageData>