<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.description>A sealed pre-packaged meal consisting of ground beef steak with gravy, another staple of American cuisine. It’s very filling and quite tasty, making it a popular dish even centuries after the war. The BIG BOY meal comes with a side of InstaMash!</FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.description>
  <FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.label>BIG BOY Salisbury Steak</FCP_Food_BIG_BOY_Salisbury_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.description>A surprisingly well-preserved fast-food product from before the war. It’s a rectangular box filled with a mix of macaroni and cheese, a staple of pre-war American cuisine and as such is a common sight in the wasteland. This seems to be the Extra Cheezy variation, adding slightly more calories to your meal.</FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.label>Blamco Extra Cheezy Flavor</FCP_Food_Blamco_Extra_Cheezy_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.description>A surprisingly well-preserved fast-food product from before the war. It’s a rectangular box filled with a mix of macaroni and cheese, a staple of pre-war American cuisine and as such is a common sight in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.label>Blamco Original Flavor</FCP_Food_Blamco_Original_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram.description>A tin can full of processed meat. Its main ingredients are pork and ham pressed into form and hold together by gelatine. It’s filled with enough preservatives to be edible over 200 years after its fabrication and is a common and popular ration for soldiers in the NCR due to its high calorie content.</FCP_Food_Cram.description>
  <FCP_Food_Cram.label>Cram</FCP_Food_Cram.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.description>A high-quality packaged meal, manufactured for use in survival situations. While it never rots, it can still deteriorate if left outside. Great for traveling.</FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.description>
  <FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.label>Cram Low Sodium</FCP_Food_Cram_Low_Sodium.label>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.description>Candied apples contained in a red cardboard box, a popular pre-war snack, made by the Dandy Boy company. The staggering amount of sugar and preservatives added to the product ensures its edibility even 200 years later.</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.description>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.label>Dandy Boy Apples</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Apples.label>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.description>Candied apples contained in a red cardboard box, a popular pre-war snack, made by the Dandy Boy company. The staggering amount of sugar and preservatives added to the product ensures its edibility even 200 years later. This variation seems to have a delicious caramel shell!</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.description>
  <FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.label>Dandy Boy Caramel Apples</FCP_Food_Dandy_Boy_Caramel_Apples.label>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.description>Pre-war snack cakes packed up in a small box. Bite-sized pieces of cake with icing, these snacks are nearly unperishable and still serve as a sugary, sweet treat 200 years after their making.</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.description>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.label>Fancy Lad Snack Cakes</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes.label>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.description>Pre-war snack cakes packed up in a small box. Bite-sized pieces of cake with icing, these snacks are nearly unperishable and still serve as a sugary, sweet treat 200 years after their making. Be sure to look out for this version as it is the limited edition Buzzbite Flavor!</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.label>Fancy Lad Snack Cakes Buzzbite Flavor</FCP_Food_Fancy_Lad_Snack_Cakes_Buzzbite_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.description>A small green package with logo symbolizing a radioactive hazard sign. However, its contents are relatively harmless, apart from the omnipresent background radiation. The small gum drops contained within are sweet and tasty and have endured the ravages of time quite well. A sugary snack for wasteland explorers.</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.description>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.label>Gum Drops</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops.label>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.description>A small green package with logo symbolizing a radioactive hazard sign. However, its contents are relatively harmless, apart from the omnipresent background radiation. The small gum drops contained within are sweet and tasty and have endured the ravages of time quite well. A sugary snack for wasteland explorers. This popular pre-war flavor features the mountain battlefields of Anchorage Alaska.</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.label>Gum Drops Anchorage Arctic Flavor</FCP_Food_Gum_Drops_Anchorage_Arctic_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.description>A box of freeze-dried powdered mashed potatoes. This convenience food product proved to be edible two centuries after the war and can be found in many locations in the wasteland. Best paired with Salisbury Steak!</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.description>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.label>Insta Mash</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash.label>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.description>A box of freeze-dried powdered mashed potatoes with bacon added for extra flavor and texture! This convenience food product proved to be edible two centuries after the war and can be found in many locations in the wasteland. Best paired with Salisbury Steak!</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.description>
  <FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.label>Insta Mash And Bacon</FCP_Food_Insta_Mash_And_Bacon.label>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.description>A can of beans stewed in a tomato sauce with chunks of bacon and salt-cured pork. A product from the Greasy Prospector company, Pork n’Beans were sold in a tin can with a blue and red label and remain edible to this day.</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.description>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.label>Pork N Beans</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans.label>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.description>A can of beans stewed in a tomato sauce with chunks of bacon and salt-cured pork. A product from the Greasy Prospector company, Pork n’Beans were sold in a tin can with a blue and red label and remain edible to this day. Based on the packaging this seems to be the "Hot N Spicy Flavor".</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.label>Pork N Beans Hot N Spicy Flavor</FCP_Food_Pork_N_Beans_Hot_N_Spicy_Flavor.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.description>A box of Spring Valley potato chips. An iconic pre-war snack composed of thin potato slices salted and baked in oil. Due to their immense popularity before the war they’re still a common sight in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.description>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.label>Potato Crisps</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps.label>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.description>A tube of Spring Valley potato chips in lightly salted falvor. An iconic pre-war snack composed of thin potato slices salted and baked in oil. Due to their immense popularity before the war they’re still a common sight in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.description>
  <FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.label>Potato Crisps Lightly Salted</FCP_Food_Potato_Crisps_Lightly_Salted.label>
  <FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.description>A high-quality packaged meal, manufactured for use in survival situations. While it never rots, it can still deteriorate if left outside. Great for traveling.</FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.description>
  <FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.label>Salisbury Steak</FCP_Food_Salisbury_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.description>A red, white and blue box of pre-war breakfast cereals, famous (and notorious) for their high sugar content. While such an amount of sugar surely is unhealthy, it also ensured that they’re edible to this day. Due to its status as the dominant breakfast cereal, it can still be found nearly everywhere in the wasteland.</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.description>
  <FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.label>Sugar Bombs</FCP_Food_Sugar_Bombs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.description>A red and blue package with dried whole deviled eggs made by YumYum. Despite being hard-boiled eggs filled with a paste made from egg yolks, mustard and mayonnaise, they’re still edible for reasons best left to discretion.</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.description>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.label>Yum Yum Deviled Eggs</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.description>A yellow and gold package with dried whole deviled eggs made by YumYum with a hint of sour cream added flavor. Despite being hard-boiled eggs filled with a paste made from egg yolks, mustard and mayonnaise, they’re still edible for reasons best left to discretion.</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.description>
  <FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.label>Yum Yum Deviled Eggs Sour Cream Flavor</FCP_Food_Yum_Yum_Deviled_Eggs_Sour_Cream_Flavor.label>
</LanguageData>