<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Speech.description>Initiate a presidential address from the presidential chair. All colonists will come and listen. If it goes well, listeners will feel inspired, and gain respect for the speaker. If it goes poorly, the address will do social damage. The outcome depends on the speaker's social abilities.</Speech.description>
  <Speech.label>presidential address</Speech.label>
  <VFEE_BestowAcolyte.description>Commissions the Sergeant title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 13 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Sergeant or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowAcolyte.description>
  <VFEE_BestowAcolyte.label>commission: sergeant</VFEE_BestowAcolyte.label>
  <VFEE_BestowBaron.description>Commissions the Colonel title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 45 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Colonel or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowBaron.description>
  <VFEE_BestowBaron.label>commission: colonel</VFEE_BestowBaron.label>
  <VFEE_BestowCount.description>Commissions the General title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 45 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a General or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowCount.description>
  <VFEE_BestowCount.label>commission: general</VFEE_BestowCount.label>
  <VFEE_BestowFreeholder.description>Commissions the Member title on a selected pawn. That pawn receives 1 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Member or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowFreeholder.description>
  <VFEE_BestowFreeholder.label>commission: member</VFEE_BestowFreeholder.label>
  <VFEE_BestowKnight.description>Commissions the Lieutenant title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 21 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Lieutenant or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowKnight.description>
  <VFEE_BestowKnight.label>commission: lieutenant</VFEE_BestowKnight.label>
  <VFEE_BestowPraetor.description>Commissions the Captain title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 31 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Captain or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowPraetor.description>
  <VFEE_BestowPraetor.label>commission: captain</VFEE_BestowPraetor.label>
  <VFEE_BestowYeoman.description>Commissions the Private title on a selected pawn. That pawn now has 7 Votes. Can’t be cast on a pawn that’s already a Private or higher. Has a 3 day cooldown.</VFEE_BestowYeoman.description>
  <VFEE_BestowYeoman.label>commission: private</VFEE_BestowYeoman.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalAddress.description>is giving a presidential address from the dais. If all goes well, every ranked participant will gain a small amount of Votes, and they will gain Votes for each ranked participant. If it goes poorly, the speech will cause social strain and lose Votes for each ranked participant. The outcome depends on their social abilities. Whitespring officials currently in the area will join the address and count as ranked participants.</VFEE_RoyalAddress.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalAddress.label>presidential address</VFEE_RoyalAddress.label>
</LanguageData>