<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Flake.description>A crumbly dehydrated preparation of brahmin shrooms, dried and pressed into brittle chips. Highly addictive, producing a brief but intense euphoric rush. A common street chem among wasteland settlements.</Flake.description>
  <GoJuice.description>A concentrated distillate extracted from brahmin shrooms under heat and pressure. The resulting compound dramatically sharpens reflexes and dulls pain, making the user temporarily lethal in combat. Highly addictive with severe withdrawal effects.</GoJuice.description>
  <Luciferium.description>A mysterious pre-war compound recovered from sealed medical bunkers. Steadily enhances all physical and mental capabilities over time. The body becomes permanently dependent — missing a dose triggers a violent and ultimately fatal withdrawal. Nobody knows who made it or why.</Luciferium.description>
  <Neutroamine.description>Industrial antiseptic compounds stockpiled from pre-war medical and military supplies. Required as a base ingredient for synthesizing most wasteland drugs and medicines. Too concentrated to apply directly.</Neutroamine.description>
  <Penoxycyline.description>Pre-war antibiotics recovered from military medical kits and hospital stockpiles. Prevents common wasteland infections — bloatfly fever, bayou fungus, and the new plague — before they take hold. Must be taken every five days to remain effective.\n\nThis only prevents new infections. It does not treat existing ones, even those not yet symptomatic.</Penoxycyline.description>
  <Plant_Psychoid.description>A psychoactive mushroom variety that grows readily in brahmin waste. Mildly hallucinogenic when eaten raw, but primarily cultivated as the base ingredient for a range of stronger preparations.</Plant_Psychoid.description>
  <PsychiteTea.description>A lightly fermented kombucha brewed from brahmin shrooms and water. The fermentation process mellows the psychoactive content, producing a mildly mood-lifting drink with low addiction potential. Widely consumed across settlements as a social beverage.</PsychiteTea.description>
  <PsychoidLeaves.description>Freshly harvested brahmin shrooms, still moist and pungent. Mildly psychoactive when eaten raw. Primarily used as the base ingredient for kombucha, dried chips, and more refined chem preparations.</PsychoidLeaves.description>
  <WakeUp.description>A stimulant preparation brewed from herbs, pre-war compounds, and local ingredients following old traditions. Eliminates the need for sleep and sharpens focus for hours. Prolonged use degrades health and creates dependency.</WakeUp.description>
  <Flake.label>dried brahmin shrooms</Flake.label>
  <GoJuice.label>distilled brahmin shrooms</GoJuice.label>
  <Luciferium.label>smooch</Luciferium.label>
  <Neutroamine.label>antiseptics</Neutroamine.label>
  <Penoxycyline.label>antibiotics</Penoxycyline.label>
  <Plant_Psychoid.label>brahmin shrooms</Plant_Psychoid.label>
  <PsychiteTea.label>brahmin shroom kombucha</PsychiteTea.label>
  <PsychoidLeaves.label>brahmin shrooms</PsychoidLeaves.label>
  <WakeUp.label>voodoo</WakeUp.label>
  <Yayo.label>fermented brahmin shrooms</Yayo.label>
  <Yayo.description>Powdered fermented brahmin shroom preparation, typically snorted for a rapid and intense euphoric effect. Highly addictive and damaging with prolonged use. A potent form of the brahmin shroom product line.</Yayo.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>The remains of a Treefather, chopped down and left as a stump.</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>chopped Treefather stump</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Basic.description>A basic treeminder, mammal-like and loyal to its Treefather. It can morph into specialized castes as needed.</Dryad_Basic.description>
  <Dryad_Basic.label>treeminder</Dryad_Basic.label>
  <DryadCocoon.description>A cocoon where a treeminder morphs into a new caste, guided by the Treefather's FEV-infused roots.</DryadCocoon.description>
  <DryadCocoon.label>treeminder cocoon</DryadCocoon.label>
  <DryadHealingPod.description>A pod filled with restorative Treefather sap, used to heal injured treeminders.</DryadHealingPod.description>
  <DryadHealingPod.label>healing pod</DryadHealingPod.label>
  <GaumakerCocoon.description>A cocoon where sproutlings merge to create a new Treefather pod, continuing the symbiotic cycle.</GaumakerCocoon.description>
  <GaumakerCocoon.label>sproutling cocoon</GaumakerCocoon.label>
  <GauranlenSeed.description>A seed from the Treefather, able to grow a new mutated tree and begin the symbiotic cycle.</GauranlenSeed.description>
  <GauranlenSeed.label>Treefather seed</GauranlenSeed.label>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.description>A patch of moss that grows around the Treefather, beautifying the area and aiding treeminder production.</Plant_MossGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.label>Treefather moss</Plant_MossGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.description>A pod produced by the Treefather, containing the seeds of new treeminders.</Plant_PodGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.label>Treefather pod</Plant_PodGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>A mutated tree infused with FEV, able to produce treeminders and pods. Its roots run deep, connecting it to the wasteland's secrets.</Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>Treefather</Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>The remains of a Treefather, smashed and left as a stump.</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>smashed Treefather stump</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Barkskin.description>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Dryad_Barkskin.label>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.description>A dryad caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Berrymaker.description>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Dryad_Berrymaker.label>
  <Dryad_Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Carrier.description>
  <Dryad_Carrier.label>portling</Dryad_Carrier.label>
  <Dryad_Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Clawer.description>
  <Dryad_Clawer.label>scratchling</Dryad_Clawer.label>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Gaumaker.description>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Dryad_Gaumaker.label>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Woodmaker.description>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Dryad_Woodmaker.label>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder which specializes in punga production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate punga fruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.\n\nIn general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Pungaling.description>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.label>pungaling treeminder</Dryad_Pungaling.label>
</LanguageData>