<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- Dryad_Barkskin -->
  <!-- Dryad_Berrymaker -->
  <!-- Dryad_Carrier -->
  <!-- Dryad_Clawer -->
  <!-- Dryad_Gaumaker -->
  <!-- Dryad_Medicinemaker -->
  <!-- Dryad_Woodmaker -->

  <Dryad_Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Barkskin.description>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Dryad_Barkskin.label>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.description>A dryad caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Berrymaker.description>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Dryad_Berrymaker.label>
  <Dryad_Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Carrier.description>
  <Dryad_Carrier.label>portling</Dryad_Carrier.label>
  <Dryad_Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Clawer.description>
  <Dryad_Clawer.label>scratchling</Dryad_Clawer.label>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Gaumaker.description>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Dryad_Gaumaker.label>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat. In general, treeminders are mammal-like creatures that have a symbiotic relationship with the treefather. They reproduce together with their tree, which contains FEV samples. Treeminders can morph into various specialized castes.</Dryad_Woodmaker.description>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Dryad_Woodmaker.label>
</LanguageData>
