<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationSequence">
    <operations>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Crashlanded"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
          <description>Your airship broke apart over the wasteland and three of you barely escaped in scavenged pods. The wreck scattered supplies across the desert, and now you have one chance to turn a crash site into a home.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Crashlanded"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
          <summary>Three crash survivors, a pile of salvaged gear, and one shot at settling the wasteland.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Crashlanded"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]</xpath>
        <value>
          <li Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog">
            <def>GameStartDialog</def>
            <text>Warning sirens howl as your airship tears itself apart over the wasteland. Three of you make it into the escape pods before the hull breaks open.

When the smoke clears, you are alive, armed, and stranded among the wreckage of the old world. If you cannot raise shelter from scrap, the wasteland will finish what the crash started.</text>
            <closeSound>GameStartSting</closeSound>
          </li>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="LostTribe"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
          <description>Your pueblo was burned out by steel war machines and only five of you escaped with what you could carry. Now you must keep the old ways alive long enough to raise a new home from dust, bone, and scrap.

Note: You begin poor, hungry, and far behind the technology of the wastes. This is a difficult scenario.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="LostTribe"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
          <summary>Five survivors from a ruined pueblo try to rebuild with little more than tradition and grit. Difficult.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="LostTribe"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
        <value>
          <text>The old stories were right. The metal devils came in the night with fire, blades, and screaming engines. Your pueblo fell before dawn.

Five of you survived the slaughter. Hungry, grieving, and alone, you now stand in a harsh land that offers nothing freely. Build again, and make sure your people do not vanish here.</text>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="TheRichExplorer"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
          <description>You left a life of safety, money, and sealed doors because the wasteland felt more honest than comfort. Now your pod has dropped you far from any civilized road with fine equipment, a restless ambition, and no one coming to save you.

Note: Strong gear cannot cover every weakness. This is an especially difficult early game scenario.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="TheRichExplorer"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
          <summary>One well-equipped explorer chasing the real wasteland instead of stories. Extra difficult.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="TheRichExplorer"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
        <value>
          <text>The lounges, vault comforts, and polished lies never satisfied you. You wanted dust in your lungs, bad roads under your boots, and a life that could not be bought.

Now the pod door opens onto an unforgiving stretch of wasteland. You brought fine weapons and better medicine, but none of it matters if you cannot survive alone.</text>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="NakedBrutality"]/description</xpath>
        <value>
          <description>One moment you were under anesthesia. The next, you woke inside a failing pod dropping into the wasteland with nothing but your own skin. No gear, no allies, no plan.

Warning: This scenario is brutally unfair. Death can come fast and for stupid reasons.</description>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="NakedBrutality"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
        <value>
          <summary>Naked, alone, and dumped into the wasteland without a scrap of help. Extremely difficult and unfair.</summary>
        </value>
      </li>
      <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
        <xpath>/Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="NakedBrutality"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
        <value>
          <text>It was supposed to be a routine procedure. Instead you woke to alarms, heat, and a pod shell screaming through the sky.

Now you lie naked in the dirt with no supplies, no tools, and no explanation. The wasteland does not care what happened to you. Survive anyway.</text>
        </value>
      </li>
    </operations>
  </Operation>
</Patch>