<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Megascarab.description>A massive ant swollen to enormous size by generations of radiation exposure. Its powerful mandibles can shear through bone, and it will fight to the death for its colony.</Megascarab.description>
  <Megascarab.label>kiến thợ khổng lồ</Megascarab.label>
  <Megaspider.description>Loài kiến ​​khổng lồ hung hãn nhất. Những sinh vật này bảo vệ tổ của chúng với sự hung dữ không ngừng và bộ hàm mạnh mẽ.</Megaspider.description>
  <Megaspider.label>kiến lính khổng lồ</Megaspider.label>
  <Spelopede.description>Một con kiến ​​khổng lồ thích nghi với cuộc sống dưới lòng đất. Bộ xương ngoài cứng cáp và khả năng đào bới khiến nó trở thành cư dân đường hầm đáng gờm.</Spelopede.description>
  <Spelopede.label>kiến khổng lồ</Spelopede.label>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.description>Một cái kén ứ chứa kiến ​​lửa.</Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.description>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.label>Kén kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.label>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.description>Một cái kén ứ chứa kiến ​​lính lửa.</Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.description>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.label>Kén kiến ​​lính cứu hỏa</Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.label>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.description>Một cái kén ứ chứa kiến ​​thợ lửa.</Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.description>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.label>Kén kiến ​​công nhân cứu hỏa</Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.description>Một loài kiến ​​lửa thích nghi với cuộc sống dưới lòng đất. Móng vuốt đào và khả năng phối hợp tổ ong của nó khiến nó trở thành cư dân đường hầm đáng gờm.</Arktos_FireAnt.description>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.label>kiến lửa</Arktos_FireAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.tools.0.label>móng vuốt đầu</Arktos_FireAnt.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAnt.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.description>Một loài kiến ​​lửa có cánh được lai tạo để giao phối và trinh sát. Bản thân nó rất mong manh, nhưng những đàn máy bay không người lái vẫn rất nguy hiểm.</Arktos_FireAntDrone.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.label>máy bay kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntDrone.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.0.label>hàm dưới</Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntHive.description>Một tổ kiến ​​lửa khổng lồ. Nếu được kích hoạt, nó sẽ sinh ra thêm kiến ​​lửa và tổ ong theo thời gian, cũng như thạch côn trùng có giá trị.</Arktos_FireAntHive.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntHive.label>tổ kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntHive.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.description>Giai đoạn non của kiến ​​lửa. Ấu trùng kiến ​​lửa được kiến ​​thợ nuôi dưỡng và trưởng thành thành giai cấp tiếp theo của tổ.</Arktos_FireAntLarva.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.label>ấu trùng kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntLarva.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.0.label>hàm dưới</Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.description>Nữ hoàng của loài kiến ​​lửa khổng lồ. Cô neo giữ thuộc địa, đẻ thế hệ tiếp theo và biến bất kỳ tổ nào cô sống sót thành mối đe dọa lớn hơn.</Arktos_FireAntQueen.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.label>nữ hoàng kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntQueen.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.0.label>móng vuốt đầu</Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.description>Là loài kiến ​​lửa hung hãn nhất. Những sinh vật này bảo vệ tổ của mình bằng sự hung dữ không ngừng, chất kitin dày và bộ hàm mạnh mẽ.</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.description>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.label>kiến lính lửa</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.0.label>móng vuốt đầu</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.description>Một con kiến ​​lửa khổng lồ được thiết kế để có sức mạnh và khả năng phục hồi. Kiến thợ cứu hỏa có tính lãnh thổ quyết liệt và duy trì tổ của chúng với lòng trung thành tuyệt đối.</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.description>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.label>kiến thợ cứu hỏa</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.0.label>hàm dưới</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.1.label>
  <Fish_Salmon.description>Là loài cá di cư có vảy sẫm màu và nhiều thịt, phổ biến ở những nơi sông lạnh gặp biển.</Fish_Salmon.description>
  <Fish_Salmon.label>cá hồi khói</Fish_Salmon.label>
  <Fish_Bass.description>Là loài săn mồi nước ngọt phổ biến được biết đến với khả năng tấn công bất ngờ và thịt có vị nhẹ.</Fish_Bass.description>
  <Fish_Bass.label>cuốc dây chuyền</Fish_Bass.label>
  <Fish_Tilapia.description>Một loài cá nước ngọt khỏe mạnh được tìm thấy ở các sông và ao ấm áp, thường phát triển mạnh ở những nơi mà các loài sạch hơn không thể.</Fish_Tilapia.description>
  <Fish_Tilapia.label>mắt khô héo</Fish_Tilapia.label>
  <Fish_Cod.description>Là loài cá ven biển nước lạnh có vảy dày và sống lưng cứng, có giá trị nhờ thịt trắng săn chắc.</Fish_Cod.description>
  <Fish_Cod.label>cá gai bọc thép</Fish_Cod.label>
  <Fish_Bluefish.description>Một thợ săn ven biển nhanh nhẹn săn mồi trong thời tiết khắc nghiệt và lướt sóng rộng rãi.</Fish_Bluefish.description>
  <Fish_Bluefish.label>vận động viên bơi lội trong bão</Fish_Bluefish.label>
  <Fish_Guppy.description>Một loài nước ngọt nhỏ được đánh giá cao nhờ mang có nếp gấp khác thường; ăn được, nhưng quá nhỏ để cung cấp nhiều thịt.</Fish_Guppy.description>
  <Fish_Guppy.label>kỳ nhông nước</Fish_Guppy.label>
  <Fish_Frostfish.description>Là loài cá nước lạnh lớn có thịt nhạt và thân hình nặng nề, thường được tìm thấy ở các con sông sâu được nuôi dưỡng bởi sông băng.</Fish_Frostfish.description>
  <Fish_Frostfish.label>bụng phệ</Fish_Frostfish.label>
  <Fish_Catfish.description>Một con tàu ăn đáy có râu lớn rình mò các kênh bùn lầy và làm ngập các tàn tích sau khi trời tối.</Fish_Catfish.description>
  <Fish_Catfish.label>râu máu</Fish_Catfish.label>
  <Fish_Piranha.description>Là loài cá nước ngọt nhỏ nhưng hung dữ với hàm răng sắc nhọn và bộ hàm khỏe, thường bị bắt làm chiến lợi phẩm.</Fish_Piranha.description>
  <Fish_Piranha.label>cá piranha Kanawha</Fish_Piranha.label>
  <Fish_Dogfish.description>Một loài cá ven biển nhỏ giống cá mập với làn da thô ráp và hàm răng sắc nhọn, thường sống dọc theo bờ biển nhiều đá.</Fish_Dogfish.description>
  <Fish_Dogfish.label>mang cưa</Fish_Dogfish.label>
  <Fish_Marlin.description>Một thợ săn khổng lồ ở vùng nước mở với chiếc mõm giống ngọn giáo, được đánh giá cao như một chiến lợi phẩm nguy hiểm.</Fish_Marlin.description>
  <Fish_Marlin.label>hàm tử thần</Fish_Marlin.label>
  <Fish_Tuna.description>Là loài cá di cư lớn từ vùng biển ấm áp, nổi tiếng với thịt nhiều dầu và khả năng chạy bền bỉ.</Fish_Tuna.description>
  <Fish_Tuna.label>máy bắn cá ngừ vây xanh</Fish_Tuna.label>
  <Fish_Flounder.description>Một loài cá ven biển bằng phẳng vùi mình trong phù sa và phục kích con mồi dọc theo đáy biển.</Fish_Flounder.description>
  <Fish_Flounder.label>kẻ phục kích ashen</Fish_Flounder.label>
  <Fish_Toxfish.description>Một loài cá đột biến do nước bị ô nhiễm. Ăn sống không an toàn nhưng vẫn có thể sử dụng trong các bữa ăn nấu chín có giá trị dinh dưỡng thấp.</Fish_Toxfish.description>
  <Fish_Toxfish.label>ngụm phát sáng</Fish_Toxfish.label>
  <Plant_TreeDrago.description>Một loại yucca sa mạc cứng cáp với các chi xoắn và lá dao găm. Ở Mojave cũ, những cây này đánh dấu đường đi, nước và rắc rối cách xa hàng dặm.</Plant_TreeDrago.description>
  <Plant_TreeDrago.label>cây joshua</Plant_TreeDrago.label>
  <Plant_TreeSnagroot.description>A blackened, near-dead tree that survived a nearby atomic blast. When harvested, it yields a meager amount of wood.</Plant_TreeSnagroot.description>
  <Plant_TreeSnagroot.label>cây cháy</Plant_TreeSnagroot.label>
  <Ambrosia.description>A mutated fruit with thick, fibrous leaves and an unusually sweet pulp. Its natural compounds cause mild euphoria, and prolonged consumption leads to dependence. Still, it remains one of the more bearable vices the wasteland has to offer.</Ambrosia.description>
  <Ambrosia.label>quả punga</Ambrosia.label>
  <VCEF_RawAnchovy.description>A small silvery bait fish that travels in dense schools through estuaries and coastal shallows.</VCEF_RawAnchovy.description>
  <VCEF_RawAnchovy.label>brook silverside</VCEF_RawAnchovy.label>
  <VCEF_RawAngelfish.description>A bright reef fish with tall fins and sharp territorial behavior despite its ornamental look.</VCEF_RawAngelfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawAngelfish.label>sunscream</VCEF_RawAngelfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawAnglerfish.description>A deepwater ambush predator that waits motionless in dark pools until prey comes within reach.</VCEF_RawAnglerfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawAnglerfish.label>bog lurker</VCEF_RawAnglerfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawClownfish.description>A banded saltwater fish once common in pre-war aquariums, now found around warm reef waters.</VCEF_RawClownfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawClownfish.label>brahfin</VCEF_RawClownfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawEel.description>A long, slick fish that slips through reeds, drainage pipes, and tidal pools with ease.</VCEF_RawEel.description>
  <VCEF_RawEel.label>purple radpole</VCEF_RawEel.label>
  <VCEF_RawGoldfish.description>A plump ornamental pond fish with bright scales, descended from escaped pre-war stock.</VCEF_RawGoldfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawGoldfish.label>blisterfish</VCEF_RawGoldfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawHaddock.description>A heavy coldwater fish with a rigid back ridge and faintly luminous scales in low light.</VCEF_RawHaddock.description>
  <VCEF_RawHaddock.label>glowing spinefish</VCEF_RawHaddock.label>
  <VCEF_RawHalibut.description>A huge broad flatfish from deep coastal waters, valued for thick cuts of meat.</VCEF_RawHalibut.description>
  <VCEF_RawHalibut.label>leatherback</VCEF_RawHalibut.label>
  <VCEF_RawHerring.description>A narrow-bodied shoal fish that runs in fast coldwater schools through inlets and coves.</VCEF_RawHerring.description>
  <VCEF_RawHerring.label>timber sawgill</VCEF_RawHerring.label>
  <VCEF_RawKoi.description>A glossy freshwater pond fish, likely descended from ornamental carp strains.</VCEF_RawKoi.description>
  <VCEF_RawKoi.label>bavarian creekfin</VCEF_RawKoi.label>
  <VCEF_RawLobster.description>A small armored crustacean with little meat, usually boiled in batches for stews.</VCEF_RawLobster.description>
  <VCEF_RawLobster.label>mirelurk hatchling</VCEF_RawLobster.label>
  <VCEF_RawMackerel.description>A fast coastal fish that travels in dense shoals along piers, reefs, and cold surf lines.</VCEF_RawMackerel.description>
  <VCEF_RawMackerel.label>bavarian tidefin</VCEF_RawMackerel.label>
  <VCEF_RawMinnow.description>A tiny river fish with a red belly, commonly found schooling in clear creeks.</VCEF_RawMinnow.description>
  <VCEF_RawMinnow.label>redbelly</VCEF_RawMinnow.label>
  <VCEF_RawPerch.description>A lean freshwater hunter with yellow eyes, common in cool lakes and slow rivers.</VCEF_RawPerch.description>
  <VCEF_RawPerch.label>walleye</VCEF_RawPerch.label>
  <VCEF_RawPufferfish.description>A round-bodied fish that inflates when threatened; edible, but not highly prized for taste.</VCEF_RawPufferfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawPufferfish.label>gulpy</VCEF_RawPufferfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawSprat.description>A tiny oily bait fish found in dense cold shoals, commonly netted during seasonal coastal runs.</VCEF_RawSprat.description>
  <VCEF_RawSprat.label>alpine sawgill</VCEF_RawSprat.label>
  <VCEF_RawSwordfish.description>A fast open-water predator with a long stabbing snout and a powerful strike.</VCEF_RawSwordfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawSwordfish.label>spikesnapper</VCEF_RawSwordfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawTrout.description>A coldwater game fish commonly caught in upland rivers and snowmelt lakes.</VCEF_RawTrout.description>
  <VCEF_RawTrout.label>ridge trout</VCEF_RawTrout.label>
  <MedicineUltratech.label>Thuốc Vault-Tec</MedicineUltratech.label>
  <VQED_MilitaryCrateOfDeadlifeShells.description>Một chiếc thùng quân sự rỉ sét chứa đầy đạn chết người. Những viên đạn pháo này chứa đầy một hợp chất giống như bụi bám trên xác người và động vật gần đó sau khi phát nổ và biến chúng thành ma cà rồng hoang dã và ma cà rồng. Nhiều vỏ đã mất tác dụng, nhưng một số vẫn có thể hoạt động.</VQED_MilitaryCrateOfDeadlifeShells.description>
  <VQE_AncientARCPart.description>Một mảnh cũ rỉ sét của lò phản ứng nguyên mẫu. Nó có thể đã bị bỏ hoang khi chương trình xây dựng của Moldaver bị tạm dừng. Vẫn có thể tháo rời nó và thu hồi các thành phần nhiệt hạch có giá trị.</VQE_AncientARCPart.description>
  <VQE_AncientARCPart.label>phần lò phản ứng cổ</VQE_AncientARCPart.label>
  <VQE_Genetron_Basic.description>Một lõi nhiệt hạch nguyên mẫu có khả năng tạo ra lượng điện lớn từ nền tảng địa nhiệt. Sau này nó có thể được nâng cấp thành các biến thể lò phản ứng tiên tiến hơn sau khi các ghi chú nghiên cứu và phần cứng chính xác đã được khôi phục. Phải được đặt trên một mạch nước phun hơi nước.</VQE_Genetron_Basic.description>
  <VQE_Genetron_Basic.label>lõi nhiệt hạch nguyên mẫu</VQE_Genetron_Basic.label>
  <VQE_GenetronJunk.description>Một khối nhà lò phản ứng xoắn từ một trong những dự án bị bỏ hoang của Moldaver. Những bộ phận có giá trị đã biến mất và mọi thứ khác đều biến thành phế liệu.</VQE_GenetronJunk.description>
  <VQE_GenetronJunk.label>rác thải lò phản ứng</VQE_GenetronJunk.label>
  <Flake.label>dried brahmin shrooms</Flake.label>
  <Flake.description>A crumbly dehydrated preparation of brahmin shrooms, dried and pressed into brittle chips. Highly addictive, producing a brief but intense euphoric rush. A common street chem among wasteland settlements.</Flake.description>
  <GoJuice.label>destilled brahmin shrooms</GoJuice.label>
  <GoJuice.description>A concentrated distillate extracted from brahmin shrooms under heat and pressure. The resulting compound dramatically sharpens reflexes and dulls pain, making the user temporarily lethal in combat. Highly addictive with severe withdrawal effects.</GoJuice.description>
  <Luciferium.label>smooch</Luciferium.label>
  <Luciferium.description>A mysterious pre-war compound recovered from sealed medical bunkers. Steadily enhances all physical and mental capabilities over time. The body becomes permanently dependent — missing a dose triggers a violent and ultimately fatal withdrawal. Nobody knows who made it or why.</Luciferium.description>
  <Neutroamine.label>antiseptics</Neutroamine.label>
  <Neutroamine.description>Industrial antiseptic compounds stockpiled from pre-war medical and military supplies. Required as a base ingredient for synthesizing most wasteland drugs and medicines. Too concentrated to apply directly.</Neutroamine.description>
  <Penoxycyline.label>antibiotics</Penoxycyline.label>
  <Penoxycyline.description>Pre-war antibiotics recovered from military medical kits and hospital stockpiles. Prevents common wasteland infections — bloatfly fever, bayou fungus, and the new plague — before they take hold. Must be taken every five days to remain effective.\n\nThis only prevents new infections. It does not treat existing ones, even those not yet symptomatic.</Penoxycyline.description>
  <Plant_Psychoid.label>brahmin shrooms</Plant_Psychoid.label>
  <Plant_Psychoid.description>A psychoactive mushroom variety that grows readily in brahmin waste. Mildly hallucinogenic when eaten raw, but primarily cultivated as the base ingredient for a range of stronger preparations.</Plant_Psychoid.description>
  <PsychiteTea.label>brahmin shroom kombucha</PsychiteTea.label>
  <PsychiteTea.description>A lightly fermented kombucha brewed from brahmin shrooms and water. The fermentation process mellows the psychoactive content, producing a mildly mood-lifting drink with low addiction potential. Widely consumed across settlements as a social beverage.</PsychiteTea.description>
  <PsychoidLeaves.label>brahmin shrooms</PsychoidLeaves.label>
  <PsychoidLeaves.description>Freshly harvested brahmin shrooms, still moist and pungent. Mildly psychoactive when eaten raw. Primarily used as the base ingredient for kombucha, dried chips, and more refined chem preparations.</PsychoidLeaves.description>
  <WakeUp.label>voodoo</WakeUp.label>
  <WakeUp.description>A stimulant preparation brewed from herbs, pre-war compounds, and local ingredients following old traditions. Eliminates the need for sleep and sharpens focus for hours. Prolonged use degrades health and creates dependency.</WakeUp.description>
  <Yayo.label>fermented brahmin shrooms</Yayo.label>
  <Yayo.description>Powdered fermented brahmin shroom preparation, typically snorted for a rapid and intense euphoric effect. Highly addictive and damaging with prolonged use. A potent form of the brahmin shroom product line.</Yayo.description>
  <VDE_Dryad_Gaubricmaker.label>người làm nghề dệt da</VDE_Dryad_Gaubricmaker.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Nectarmaker.label>người chăm sóc cây sapbrewer</VDE_Dryad_Nectarmaker.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Spitter.label>người nhổ cây</VDE_Dryad_Spitter.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Stonedigger.label>người đào đá</VDE_Dryad_Stonedigger.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.description>Một chiếc mũ đội đầu nghi lễ cao nhằm đánh dấu người lãnh đạo của một tín ngưỡng có tổ chức hoặc giáo phái ở vùng đất hoang.</VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.label>mũ thuyết giáo cao</VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BrimlessHat.description>Một chiếc mũ nhỏ đơn giản dùng để đội nhẹ nhàng trên đầu. Những người ủng hộ nó thường cho rằng nó mang lại cho họ vẻ ngoài thần bí của thế giới cũ.</VIEHAR_Apparel_BrimlessHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.description>Một chiếc mũ lưỡi trai có vành nổi bật được trang trí bằng huy hiệu cấp bậc, nhằm mục đích truyền cảm hứng cho cấp dưới tuân theo bằng bất cứ giá nào.</VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.label>mũ giám sát</VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_Fez.description>Một chiếc mũ hình nón đỉnh phẳng được trang trí bằng tua rua màu đen, thường được đội bởi những người buôn bán sa mạc, ông chủ đoàn lữ hành và những người thuộc giới thượng lưu đường cũ khác.</VIEHAR_Apparel_Fez.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_Rags.description>Một bộ giẻ rách dùng để che phủ cơ thể một cách tối giản nhất. Họ hầu như không mang lại sự bảo vệ hay sự ấm áp nào, nhưng báo hiệu rõ ràng một cuộc sống khắc khổ và tận tụy với vùng đất hoang khắc nghiệt.</VIEHAR_Apparel_Rags.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>Phần còn lại của Treefather, bị chặt xuống và để lại như một gốc cây.</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>gốc cây cha cây bị chặt</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Basic.description>Một người chăm sóc cây cơ bản, giống động vật có vú và trung thành với Cha Cây của nó. Nó có thể biến thành các diễn viên chuyên biệt khi cần thiết.</Dryad_Basic.description>
  <Dryad_Basic.label>người dọn cây</Dryad_Basic.label>
  <DryadCocoon.description>Một cái kén nơi người chăm sóc cây biến thành một đẳng cấp mới, được hướng dẫn bởi rễ cây được truyền FEV của Treefather.</DryadCocoon.description>
  <DryadCocoon.label>kén người trồng cây</DryadCocoon.label>
  <DryadHealingPod.description>Một cái vỏ chứa đầy nhựa cây của Cha cây có tác dụng phục hồi, dùng để chữa lành những người chăm sóc cây bị thương.</DryadHealingPod.description>
  <DryadHealingPod.label>vỏ chữa bệnh</DryadHealingPod.label>
  <GaumakerCocoon.description>Một cái kén nơi các mầm non kết hợp với nhau để tạo ra một nhóm Treefather mới, tiếp tục chu trình cộng sinh.</GaumakerCocoon.description>
  <GaumakerCocoon.label>kén nảy mầm</GaumakerCocoon.label>
  <GauranlenSeed.description>Một hạt giống từ Treefather, có thể phát triển thành một cây đột biến mới và bắt đầu chu kỳ cộng sinh.</GauranlenSeed.description>
  <GauranlenSeed.label>Hạt giống bố cây</GauranlenSeed.label>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.description>Một mảng rêu mọc xung quanh Treefather, làm đẹp khu vực này và hỗ trợ việc sản xuất người chăm sóc cây.</Plant_MossGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.label>Rêu cha cây</Plant_MossGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.description>Một loại quả được tạo ra bởi Treefather, chứa hạt giống của những người chăm sóc cây mới.</Plant_PodGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.label>Vỏ cây cha</Plant_PodGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>Một cây đột biến được truyền FEV, có thể tạo ra thân cây và quả. Rễ của nó ăn sâu, kết nối nó với những bí mật của vùng đất hoang.</Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>Bố Cây</Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>Phần còn lại của Treefather, bị đập nát và để lại như một gốc cây.</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>gốc cây Treefather bị đập nát</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies.</Dryad_Barkskin.description>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Dryad_Barkskin.label>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.description>A treeminder caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. It is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Berrymaker.description>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Dryad_Berrymaker.label>
  <Dryad_Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Carrier.description>
  <Dryad_Carrier.label>portling</Dryad_Carrier.label>
  <Dryad_Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation.</Dryad_Clawer.description>
  <Dryad_Clawer.label>scratchling</Dryad_Clawer.label>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process.</Dryad_Gaumaker.description>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Dryad_Gaumaker.label>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Woodmaker.description>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Dryad_Woodmaker.label>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.description>Một đẳng cấp chậm chạp, vụng về của người trồng cây chuyên sản xuất cá punga. Cùng với cây Gauranlen, cây thần này có thể liên tục tạo ra quả punga. Tuy nhiên, nó chậm và không hiệu quả trong công việc hoặc chiến đấu.\n\nNói chung, người trồng cây là những sinh vật giống động vật có vú có mối quan hệ cộng sinh với cha cây. Chúng sinh sản cùng với cây của chúng, trong đó có chứa các mẫu FEV. Treeminders có thể biến thành nhiều đẳng cấp chuyên biệt khác nhau.</Dryad_Pungaling.description>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.label>người nhổ cây</Dryad_Pungaling.label>
  <ShuttleCrashing.label>vertibird (crashing)</ShuttleCrashing.label>
  <TransportPod.description>Automated cargo bots used to deliver people and supplies across the planet.</TransportPod.description>
  <TransportPod.label>cargo bot</TransportPod.label>
  <AnimusStone.description>A resonant cryptic stone studied by Whitespring researchers. It increases cryptid meditation focus and is often used in enclave research facilities.</AnimusStone.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>cryptic stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.description>A stump left behind after an Mothman totem has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</ChoppedStump_Anima.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.label>chopped Mothman stump</ChoppedStump_Anima.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring cryptid forces. Whitespring operatives use these to amplify cryptid focus during ritualized study.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine used by cryptid researchers to focus meditation and study. These shrines strengthen cryptid-focused meditation for Whitespring operatives.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.description>Mysterious black eggs with a red glow. Tribal peoples find that these eggs grow around the base of a Mothman totem as they meditate. It seems to reflect some kind of strengthening of the totem's cryptic power.\n\nWasteland scientists have tried to study the phenomenon, but the eggs fail to hatch when observed too closely.\n\nAnimals refuse eat Mothman eggs. Tribal stories say this is done out of respect and fear.</Plant_GrassAnima.description>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.label>Mothman eggs</Plant_GrassAnima.label>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.description>A Mothman totem used by Appalachia cultists to focus their meditation and worship.</Plant_TreeAnima.description>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.label>Mothman totem</Plant_TreeAnima.label>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.description>The remnants of an Mothman totem destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</SmashedStump_Anima.description>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.label>smashed Mothman stump</SmashedStump_Anima.label>
  <Chemshine.description>A harsh, flammable wasteland liquor distilled from chemfuel. Rot gut dulls pain and misery for a while, but it leaves the drinker soaked in volatile fumes and can turn a bad death into a fireball.</Chemshine.description>
  <Chemshine.label>rot gut</Chemshine.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>Một nhà máy chưng cất mạ vàng với tay nghề rất tinh tế nhằm mục đích ủ rượu pungashine phải ở dạng có thể uống được.</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>pungashine vẫn còn</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>Quả punga cắt lát và ép sẵn để chín thành pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>nghiền pungashine</VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>Cơ sở rượu punga đã chín hoàn toàn, sẵn sàng để chưng cất thành pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>pungashine phải</VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>
  <VBE_Cigarettes.description>Một ống giấy cuộn nhỏ được nhồi lỏng lẻo bằng thuốc lá nhai. Nó mang lại cảm giác hưng phấn ngắn ngủi, sự kích thích nhẹ nhàng và mùi đất hoang cũ kỹ khiến người hút thuốc quay trở lại.</VBE_Cigarettes.description>
  <VBE_Cigars.description>Một điếu xì gà dày cuộn từ thuốc lá coyote nhai và kết thúc để tạo ra làn khói đắt tiền hơn, có chủ ý hơn. Nó mang một vị đắng sa mạc thô ráp dưới cách trình bày cầu kỳ.</VBE_Cigars.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.description>Một chai guarana sắc bén, sủi bọt kết thúc với vị đắng và dư vị phóng xạ. Nó va mạnh vào phía trước và để lại tiếng va chạm chờ sẵn ở phía bên kia.</VBE_EnergyDrink.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.label>guarana</VBE_EnergyDrink.label>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.description>Một loại cocktail nguyên tử hảo hạng, được pha trộn chính xác từ nhiều thành phần.</VBE_FineCocktail.description>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.label>cocktail nguyên tử tốt</VBE_FineCocktail.label>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>Một điều kỳ diệu của công nghệ pha chế, trong đó mỗi ly, cách trang trí và cách khuấy đều được điều chỉnh thành một loại cocktail nguyên tử dành cho người sành ăn.</VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>cocktail nguyên tử dành cho người sành ăn</VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.description>Một loại cocktail nguyên tử xa hoa được pha trộn từ nhiều loại nguyên liệu khác nhau và được làm lạnh đến mức hoàn hảo trước khi được phục vụ.</VBE_LavishCocktail.description>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.label>cocktail nguyên tử xa hoa</VBE_LavishCocktail.label>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>Một loại thuốc lá chó sói cứng phù hợp với khí hậu Mojave và các vùng đất hoang khô cằn khác. Sau khi khỏi bệnh, những chiếc lá trở thành thuốc lá nhai để hút, lăn hoặc buôn bán.</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>thuốc lá chó sói</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.description>Hộp cà phê hòa tan trước chiến tranh được hút chân không. Đắng, ổn định và vẫn đủ mạnh để neo giữ mọi dịch vụ bữa sáng Lucky 38.</VBE_RawCoffee.description>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.label>cà phê hòa tan</VBE_RawCoffee.label>
  <VBE_RawTea.description>Lá trà khô trước chiến tranh được bảo quản trong hộp đựng thức ăn Lucky 38. Chúng giữ tốt và vẫn rót vào một chiếc cốc có thể sử dụng được.</VBE_RawTea.description>
  <VBE_RawTea.label>lá trà khô</VBE_RawTea.label>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.description>Một túi nhai thuốc lá chó sói đã được chữa khỏi. Đủ khô để hút, cuộn hoặc đóng gói thành các hỗn hợp đậm đà hơn, phù hợp với những gì mà người hút thuốc ở vùng đất hoang bụi bặm mong đợi.</VBE_RawTobacco.description>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.label>chó sói nhai thuốc lá</VBE_RawTobacco.label>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>Một loại cocktail nguyên tử đơn giản được pha trộn nhanh chóng từ bộ đôi nguyên liệu.</VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>cocktail nguyên tử đơn giản</VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>
  <VBE_Soda.description>Một chai sarsaparilla homebrew có ga ngọt ngào. Nó sảng khoái hơn là bổ dưỡng, nhưng một chai ướp lạnh vẫn có cảm giác như một thứ xa xỉ trước Chiến tranh.</VBE_Soda.description>
  <VBE_Soda.label>sarsaparilla homebrew</VBE_Soda.label>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.description>Một đơn vị đóng chai sarsaparilla homebrew tất cả trong một. Xi-rô được trộn, có ga, làm lạnh và phân phối vào chai khử trùng để sử dụng.</VBE_SodaFountain.description>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.label>đài phun nước sarsaparilla homebrew</VBE_SodaFountain.label>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.description>Lớp đế dày, cực kỳ ngọt ngào dành cho món sarsaparilla homebrew. Nó có nghĩa là phải được cắt nhỏ, có ga và đóng chai trước khi phục vụ.</VBE_SodaSyrup.description>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.label>xi-rô sarsaparilla homebrew</VBE_SodaSyrup.label>
  <CashRegister_CashRegister.description>Bàn đăng ký dịch vụ phòng chờ, tab ăn uống và tài khoản nhà. Nó không tự mình làm gì cả, nhưng nó giữ vững hoạt động trước nhà.</CashRegister_CashRegister.description>
  <CashRegister_CashRegister.label>bàn đăng ký</CashRegister_CashRegister.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineBlue.description>Một ngân hàng máy đánh bạc Lucky 38 cao cấp được xây dựng để chơi với giới hạn cao, đồng thau bóng loáng và một nhà cái khao khát.</HC_SlotMachineBlue.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineBlue.label>may mắn 38 cuộn lăn cao</HC_SlotMachineBlue.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineGreen.description>Một ngân hàng đánh bạc thời House được điều chỉnh cho khách quen thường xuyên và lưu lượng truy cập hàng đêm đáng tin cậy.</HC_SlotMachineGreen.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineGreen.label>may mắn 38 cuộn tiêu chuẩn</HC_SlotMachineGreen.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineRed.description>Một máy đánh bạc Vault 21 đã được thu hồi lại với số tiền đặt cược khiêm tốn và tỷ lệ lợi nhuận nhà cái dễ chấp nhận.</HC_SlotMachineRed.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineRed.label>vault 21 khe xu</HC_SlotMachineRed.label>
  <VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.description>A polished Lucky 38 Luxobrew coffee pot rebuilt for high-volume service. It handles espresso pulls, reheating chilled coffee, and tea blends from a single compact station.</VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.description>
  <VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.label>luxobrew coffee pot</VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.label>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.description>Bright carrot flowers used to freshen brewed drinks and garnish wasteland dishes.</VBE_MintLeaves.description>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.label>carrot flowers</VBE_MintLeaves.label>
  <VBE_MintPlant.description>A stand of carrot flowers used for bright herbal garnish in teas and coffee blends.</VBE_MintPlant.description>
  <VBE_MintPlant.label>carrot flower patch</VBE_MintPlant.label>
  <Chocolate.description>Một hộp sô-cô-la trước chiến tranh được gói cẩn thận. Đậm đà, ngọt ngào và vẫn đủ đậm đà để kết hợp các món tráng miệng và xi-rô.</Chocolate.description>
  <Chocolate.label>sô cô la bảo quản</Chocolate.label>
  <VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>Một hệ thống treo y tế hiếm có trước Chiến tranh được đóng gói lại cho nhà bếp Lucky 38. Khi được gấp thành thức ăn, aqua cura tràn vào cơ thể các nanite sửa chữa khẩn cấp có thể kéo thực khách thoát chết.</VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>
  <VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>nước chữa bệnh</VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>
  <VCE_RawSpices.description>Hỗn hợp gia vị nhà bếp trước chiến tranh được bảo quản trong hộp đựng thức ăn Lucky 38. Đủ lượng tồn tại trong mỗi hộp để làm sáng các món hầm, nước sốt và đồ nướng.</VCE_RawSpices.description>
  <VCE_RawSugar.description>Những gói đường được niêm phong trước Chiến tranh được thu hồi từ những căn bếp cũ và những kho đựng thức ăn. Nó giữ được vô thời hạn và vẫn mang lại cảm giác ngọt ngào nhanh chóng như nhau.</VCE_RawSugar.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>Loại bơ đậm đặc, say mê được khuấy để tạo cảm giác thích thú cho món ăn Lucky 38. Nó lan tỏa đậm đà, đánh mạnh và biến bất kỳ bữa ăn nào thành một ý tưởng tồi với hương vị tuyệt vời.</VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>bơ shroom Bà la môn</VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>
  <VCEV_CookingBook.description>Một cuốn sách dạy nấu ăn cũ nát chứa đầy các công thức nấu ăn đã được sử dụng lại, ghi chú về nguyên liệu và các thủ thuật nhà bếp trước Chiến tranh.

Sau khi đọc, nó sẽ cung cấp cho người đọc một nguyên liệu hoặc bữa ăn yêu thích mới, sau đó sẽ thất bại nếu có quá nhiều bàn tay vào bếp.</VCEV_CookingBook.description>
  <VCEV_CookingBook.label>sách dạy nấu ăn vùng đất hoang</VCEV_CookingBook.label>
  <Gastronomy_Waiting.description>Nhận đơn đặt hàng và phục vụ bữa ăn cho khách hàng tại sảnh khách và phòng ăn của bạn.</Gastronomy_Waiting.description>
  <CashRegister_Mech.description>Một thiết bị đầu cuối dịch vụ tự động dành cho người phục vụ cơ khí. Từ đây bạn có thể chỉ đạo việc ăn uống và vận hành trước nhà.</CashRegister_Mech.description>
  <CashRegister_Mech.label>thiết bị đầu cuối dịch vụ tự trị</CashRegister_Mech.label>
  <SmallHotSpring.description>Một suối nước nóng được làm việc cẩn thận được xây dựng trên một mạch nước phun hơi nước. Nước khoáng của nó mang lại sự thư giãn thiền định, lợi ích phục hồi khiêm tốn và tiện nghi nhà tắm cao cấp cho tối đa bốn con tốt cùng một lúc.</SmallHotSpring.description>
  <SmallHotSpring.label>khu nghỉ dưỡng suối nước nóng</SmallHotSpring.label>
  <HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.label>thu phí nhà tắm</HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.label>
  <HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.verb>thu phí nhà tắm</HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.verb>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>Một ngọn lửa tín hiệu công nghệ cao kỳ quái gọi một con vertibird bất ngờ xuất hiện. Dù trí thông minh trả lời thế nào thì nó cũng sẵn sàng cung cấp một sự chiết xuất kỳ diệu.</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>pháo hiệu vertibird</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>bùng phát tín hiệu pop</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>Bộ phát đáp hiện trường sử dụng một lần được sử dụng để yêu cầu đón vertibird của Brotherhood.</Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>Bộ phát đáp trường tình anh em</Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>gọi đón vertibird</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.description>Đèn hiệu IFF tầm xa và cột điều khiển giao thông được sử dụng bởi các tổ chức Brotherhood và các đồng minh đáng tin cậy để quảng cáo cách tiếp cận an toàn của loài chim vertibird, điều phối các cuộc đổ bộ và phát sóng tình trạng sẵn sàng tiếp nhiên liệu.</Spaceports_Beacon.description>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.label>Đèn hiệu chuyến bay tình anh em</Spaceports_Beacon.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>Một nhà ga dịch vụ bán nhiên liệu hàng không cho các hãng vertibirds của Brotherhood và các máy bay được ủy quyền khác. Nó phải được đặt liền kề với một tấm đệm vertibird; Sau khi thanh toán được xác minh, máy bơm bên trong tấm đệm sẽ hút nhiên liệu từ các bồn chứa trên cùng một mạng điện.</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>trạm tiếp nhiên liệu vertibird</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>Một bộ xử lý công nghiệp có chức năng tinh chế nguyên liệu dễ bay hơi và nước thành nhiên liệu hàng không cho loài chim vertibird Brotherhood. Nó hoạt động tốt nhất khi có nước và biến nhiên liệu hóa học dư thừa thành kho chuyến bay có thể bán được.</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>bộ xử lý nhiên liệu hàng không</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.description>Một bể chứa lạnh để xử lý nhiên liệu hàng không. Giữ nó hoạt động hoặc cổ phiếu bắt đầu bay hơi.</Spaceports_FuelTank.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.label>bình nhiên liệu hàng không</Spaceports_FuelTank.label>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>Một bãi đáp cứng cáp có đèn dẫn đường, hệ thống tiếp nhiên liệu và bộ phát đáp được mã hóa cho các loài chim vertibird của Brotherhood. Giữ cho nó luôn hoạt động và thông suốt, đồng thời các chuyến thăm tuần tra, quản lý khu vực, thương nhân và hành khách đồng minh có thể chạm xuống đây.</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>Tình anh em vertibird pad</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>Chỉ định một điểm có thể định cấu hình nơi các nhân viên, thương nhân và hành khách đồng minh của Brotherhood sẽ tập trung sau khi hạ cánh. Nếu không tìm thấy điểm hợp lệ, chúng sẽ ở gần loài vertibird của chúng.</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>điểm tập trung của vertibird</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>
  <VCE_Chirashizushi.label>bát mirelurk (đơn giản)</VCE_Chirashizushi.label>
  <VCE_DeepFriedSushi.label>luống chiên giòn</VCE_DeepFriedSushi.label>
  <VCE_Futomaki.label>futolurk (xa hoa)</VCE_Futomaki.label>
  <VCE_Gunkanmaki.label>gunkanlurk (người sành ăn)</VCE_Gunkanmaki.label>
  <VCE_Nigiri.label>murkiri (tốt)</VCE_Nigiri.label>
  <VCE_Norimaki.label>norilurk (đơn giản)</VCE_Norimaki.label>
  <VCE_Oshizushi.label>oshilurk (người sành ăn)</VCE_Oshizushi.label>
  <VCE_RawSoybean.description>Tart quả nam việt quất đất hoang. Chúng có thể được ăn sống, nấu chín để bảo quản hoặc lên men thành nước sốt đặc.</VCE_RawSoybean.description>
  <VCE_RawSoybean.label>quả nam việt quất</VCE_RawSoybean.label>
  <VCE_RawWasabi.label>gốc xander</VCE_RawWasabi.label>
  <VCE_Soybean.description>Một bụi nam việt quất cứng được trồng để cho quả mọng màu đỏ sắc nét. Trái cây nấu thành một loại nước sốt đậm đà tượng trưng cho chuỗi gia vị lên men của thế giới cũ.</VCE_Soybean.description>
  <VCE_Soybean.label>bụi nam việt quất</VCE_Soybean.label>
  <VCE_SoyFermenter.label>thùng nước sốt nam việt quất</VCE_SoyFermenter.label>
  <VCE_SoySauce.description>Một loại nước ép nam việt quất đậm đà được sử dụng làm nước chấm, tráng men và nước sốt hoàn thiện có vị mặn ngọt cho món sushi và hải sản vùng đất hoang.</VCE_SoySauce.description>
  <VCE_SoySauce.label>nước sốt nam việt quất</VCE_SoySauce.label>
  <VCE_Temaki.label>temlurk (xa hoa)</VCE_Temaki.label>
  <VCE_Uramaki.label>uralurk (tốt)</VCE_Uramaki.label>
  <VCE_Wasabi.description>Một miếng rễ xander được đánh giá cao vì vị cay nồng của nó. Khi nghiền thành bột nhão, nó tạo thành một loại gia vị đậm đà cho các món hải sản và cơm.</VCE_Wasabi.description>
  <VCE_Wasabi.label>bản vá gốc xander</VCE_Wasabi.label>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.description>Một loại bột nhão được làm từ rễ xander xay và được dùng làm gia vị cay nồng cho món sushi và các món hải sản khác.</VCE_WasabiPaste.description>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.label>dán gốc xander</VCE_WasabiPaste.label>
  <Therapist.description>Giúp những người thực dân và những người bảo trợ vượt qua căng thẳng, chấn thương và sự phụ thuộc trong phòng tư vấn riêng.</Therapist.description>
  <Therapist.gerundLabel>tư vấn</Therapist.gerundLabel>
  <Therapist.labelShort>Luật sư</Therapist.labelShort>
  <MedievalVendingMachine.description>Một ki-ốt công nghệ thấp dành cho những khách hàng không cần dùng điện.</MedievalVendingMachine.description>
  <MedievalVendingMachine.label>ki-ốt dịch vụ</MedievalVendingMachine.label>
  <VendingMachine.description>Một ki-ốt trước Chiến tranh có đầy đủ đồ cho khách quen, khách đến sòng bạc và những đám đông nhàn rỗi trong phòng chờ.</VendingMachine.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.description>A Poseidon home reactor powered by scavenged dark archotechnology. It burns bioferrite to agitate atmospheric gases, raising the outdoor temperature while flooding the area with waste heat.</AtmosphericHeater.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.label>Poseidon home reactor</AtmosphericHeater.label>
  <BioferriteGenerator.description>An experimental generator that works by pressurizing and igniting bioferrite, then harvesting energy from the resulting heat. The fuel remains bioferrite, but the chassis and control layout read like a harsh Poseidon prototype.</BioferriteGenerator.description>
  <BioferriteShaper.description>A specialized shaping bench that uses heat and electromagnetic stimulation to temporarily coax bioferrite into a pliable state. The material remains bioferrite, but the surrounding hardware fits cleanly into a Fallout-style industrial workshop.</BioferriteShaper.description>
  <SerumCentrifuge.description>A Med-Tek serum lab that uses scavenged archotechnology to create single-use injectable serums. Clean, expensive, and morally questionable in exactly the right pre-War way.</SerumCentrifuge.description>
  <SerumCentrifuge.label>Med-Tek serum lab</SerumCentrifuge.label>
  <RB_FloorLamp.description>A floor-mounted Wattz lamp that lights an area using electricity. It is less powerful than a standing lamp, but it looks right at home in a retro-futurist sitting room.</RB_FloorLamp.description>
  <Chemfuel.description>A refined liquid fuel suitable for generators, burners, and industrial feed systems. In a saner age Poseidon would have sold it through a smiling subsidiary with a patriotic slogan.</Chemfuel.description>
  <Chemfuel.label>oil</Chemfuel.label>
  <PS_ChemfuelTank.description>An industrial storage tank meant for oil delivered through the pipe network. Tanks can be siphoned for usable fuel as needed, but even light damage can turn leaking vapors into a violent fireball.</PS_ChemfuelTank.description>
  <PS_ChemfuelTank.label>oil tank</PS_ChemfuelTank.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.description>A basin meant to feed stored oil into the network and fill connected tanks.</VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.label>oil drain</VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.description>Steel pipes designed to move usable oil from deepchem refineries to oil tanks for storage or to oil-fed structures for automatic refilling.</VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.label>oil pipe</VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelTap.description>A basin meant to hold dispensed oil from storage tanks for later use.</VCHE_ChemfuelTap.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelTap.label>oil tap</VCHE_ChemfuelTap.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelValve.description>Switches oil flow on or off.</VCHE_ChemfuelValve.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelValve.label>oil valve</VCHE_ChemfuelValve.label>
  <VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.description>Buried steel pipes designed to move usable oil from deepchem refineries to oil tanks for storage or to oil-fed structures for automatic refilling.</VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.description>
  <VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.label>subterranean oil pipe</VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.label>
  <Battery.description>A Poseidon reserve battery for holding excess electricity. Charged units remain dangerous when exposed to rain or fire, regardless of what the brochure claims.</Battery.description>
  <BiofuelRefinery.description>A Poseidon refinery that converts biological matter into oil for generators, burners, and industrial storage systems.</BiofuelRefinery.description>
  <BiofuelRefinery.label>oil refinery</BiofuelRefinery.label>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming oil. It must be periodically refueled by hand unless your settlement has the industrial habits of an actual Poseidon facility.</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>oil generator</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>
  <CommsConsole.description>A Wattz communications console for contacting other factions and orbital traders. Big, expensive, and full of humming pre-War electronics.</CommsConsole.description>
  <Cooler.description>An Appalachia Freeze cooling unit that pushes cold air to one side and hot exhaust to the other. It can preserve food or simply make summer tolerable if the rest of the grid holds.</Cooler.description>
  <DeepDrill.description>A Corvega deep-crust drilling rig for extracting minerals from far below the surface. Use a ground-penetrating scanner to detect the best seams.</DeepDrill.description>
  <DrugLab.description>A powered industrial chem lab with containers, heaters, and measurement devices for efficient batch processing of drugs and compounds.</DrugLab.description>
  <ElectricCrematorium.description>A heavy industrial crematorium that vaporizes corpses at extreme temperatures. It is efficient, impersonal, and unmistakably pre-War in temperament.</ElectricCrematorium.description>
  <ElectricSmelter.description>A Corvega reclamation smelter that extracts usable metal from slag and mixed scrap. It consumes a lot of power and throws off serious industrial heat.</ElectricSmelter.description>
  <ElectricSmelter.label>Corvega reclamation smelter</ElectricSmelter.label>
  <FabricationBench.description>A Corvega fabrication bench equipped with advanced tools for producing sophisticated machines and components from simpler materials.</FabricationBench.description>
  <FirefoamPopper.description>A Wattz safety device that sprays fire-retardant foam when it detects a blaze. Exactly the kind of sensible utility hardware that survives long after the corporation that sold it is gone.</FirefoamPopper.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>A Radiation King flatscreen television with crystal-clear image and rich color. Trust the king for all your TV and radio needs.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <GeothermalGenerator.description>A Poseidon geothermal plant that taps deep heat for steady, high-output power. It is exactly the kind of hulking civic infrastructure Poseidon loved to dominate a skyline with.</GeothermalGenerator.description>
  <GeothermalGenerator.label>geothermal plant</GeothermalGenerator.label>
  <Heater.description>A Wattz Electronics heating unit that converts electricity into controlled room heat. It automatically cycles to reach a target temperature.</Heater.description>
  <HiTechResearchBench.description>A Wattz high-tech research bench with computers and electronic measurement equipment. It enables rapid research and more advanced technical projects.</HiTechResearchBench.description>
  <HospitalBed.description>A Med-Tek hospital bed specially designed for clinical care. Adjustable support geometry and integrated instruments improve patient outcomes over ordinary beds.</HospitalBed.description>
  <MegascreenTelevision.description>A huge Radiation King television for settlements that want their entertainment loud, bright, and impossible to ignore.</MegascreenTelevision.description>
  <NutrientPasteDispenser.description>An industrial dispenser that synthesizes edible nutrient paste from feedstocks placed in adjacent hoppers. Efficient, joyless, and exactly the sort of machine a large contractor would call progress.</NutrientPasteDispenser.description>
  <OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>A Wattz orbital trade beacon used to mark goods for exchange with orbital merchants. Dependable, compact, and built for practical frontier commerce.</OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>
  <PowerConduit.description>A bundle of utility cables for moving power around a settlement. It can be placed under walls and other structures as part of a proper pre-War grid.</PowerConduit.description>
  <SolarGenerator.description>A Poseidon Civilian Helios Two solar panel array for settlement-scale power generation. It delivers its best output under full daylight and clear skies.</SolarGenerator.description>
  <SolarGenerator.label>civilian Helios Two</SolarGenerator.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>A Radiation King tube television built around bulky old display hardware and a distinctly pre-War sense of domestic prestige.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <VanometricPowerCell.description>A compact power cell that generates free energy forever without conventional fuel. Even by pre-War standards it feels less like engineering and more like a secret Poseidon program nobody was meant to understand.</VanometricPowerCell.description>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>A Med-Tek patient telemetry unit that improves tend quality, surgery success, and recovery when mounted directly beside a hospital bed.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>A Poseidon hydro unit designed to draw steady power from moving water. Crowded placements create turbulence and reduce output.</WatermillGenerator.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.label>hydro turbine</WatermillGenerator.label>
  <WindTurbine.description>A utility-grade wind turbine for civilian settlements. It needs a broad, clear approach to keep airflow stable.</WindTurbine.description>
  <WindTurbine.label>civilian wind turbine</WindTurbine.label>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>A large Corvega automated field machine that combines sowing and harvesting across a designated outdoor zone. It deposits harvested goods into attached factory hoppers or drops them on the ground if hoppers are not present, and can be set to cycle automatically once most plants in the zone are fully grown.</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>agri-industrial harvester</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>A Corvega automated refinery that converts biological matter such as wood and plant stock into chemfuel.

Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>Corvega oil refinery</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>An automated Corvega deep extraction rig for pulling stone and buried metals up from the crust. Works machinery needs hoppers for intake and output, throws off serious heat, and can be overclocked at the cost of even greater draw and temperature.</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>Corvega drill platform</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>An industrial Corvega masonry saw capable of cutting stone chunks into usable blocks.

Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>automated masonry line</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>A Corvega automated smelter that extracts usable metal from slag chunks, broken-down weapons, apparel, stone chunks, and mechanoid corpses using strong electromagnets and industrial heat.

Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>A basic industrial conveyor for moving materials between work cells with minimal labor handling.</VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>industrial conveyor</VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>Stores feedstock and finished goods for automated Corvega works machinery.</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>works hopper</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>A buried intake point that lets an industrial conveyor run beneath short stretches of ground before resurfacing.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>buried conveyor intake</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>A buried discharge point that brings an underground conveyor back to the surface near the next work cell.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>buried conveyor discharge</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>A tall propane floodlight that illuminates a massive area. It is not bright enough for crop growth, but it provides dependable yard lighting when connected to the propane network.</VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>propane floodlight</VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.description>A propane-fed standing lamp for utility lighting. It must be connected to the propane network and can be placed safely outdoors.</VHGE_GasLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.label>propane lamp</VHGE_GasLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>An industrial lamp bright enough for crop growth, but it burns a steady supply of propane. It shuts itself off at night.</VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>propane sun lamp</VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>A propane-fed wall light for utility corridors and work rooms. It must be connected to the propane network and can be placed safely outdoors.</VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>propane wall lamp</VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>
  <VHGE_Helixien.description>Propane gas.</VHGE_Helixien.description>
  <VHGE_Helixien.label>propane</VHGE_Helixien.label>
  <Facility_IVDrip.description>A Med-Tek intravenous drip stand for rapidly delivering lost fluids to a patient, helping immunity gain and blood loss recovery when placed directly adjacent to a hospital bed or surgical table. Only works for hospital beds or surgical tables; normal beds will not benefit. Attaching more than one stand to the same bed has no effect.</Facility_IVDrip.description>
  <Facility_IVDrip.label>Med-Tek IV stand</Facility_IVDrip.label>
  <Facility_VitalsCentre.description>A large Med-Tek centre for monitoring the vitals of several patients at once, improving tend quality, surgery success, and immunity gain when linked to hospital beds or surgical suites.</Facility_VitalsCentre.description>
  <Facility_VitalsCentre.label>Med-Tek vitals centre</Facility_VitalsCentre.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>A bedside Mama Dolce feeding device that delivers nutrient paste directly to bedridden patients when linked to a nutrient vat. Practical, clinical, and just unsettling enough to feel authentic.</VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>A compact Corvega feeder that outputs nutrient paste from the pipe network for routine worker consumption.</VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>A Mama Dolce nutrient grinder that reduces organic feedstocks into pipeline-ready paste stock. Efficient, impersonal, and very much in the spirit of industrial pre-War food engineering.</VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>A Mama Dolce paste tap that dispenses prepared nutrient meals from the vat network. It is the kind of practical cafeteria hardware a large contractor would install by the hundred.</VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>A Corvega storage vat for holding large volumes of processed nutrient paste. Destroying one makes exactly the kind of industrial mess you would expect.</VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedBattery.description>A sealed Poseidon battery unit with far better efficiency than common storage cells. These pre-War housings are rainproof and less prone to catastrophic discharge.</VFE_AdvancedBattery.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.description>A high-efficiency Poseidon solar array marketed as the Industrial Helios Two, built to pull significantly more charge from direct sunlight than ordinary civilian panels.</VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.label>industrial Helios Two</VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.description>A Poseidon hydro unit designed to draw industrial power from moving water. Crowded installations create turbulence and reduce output.</VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.label>industrial hydro turbine</VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.description>A pre-War Poseidon utility turbine built for industrial output. It needs broad clear approaches to keep airflow stable and advertises the sort of oversized confidence Poseidon loved to stamp on its public works.</VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.label>industrial wind turbine</VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.label>
  <VFE_LargeAdvancedBattery.description>A large sealed Poseidon battery bank built for dependable utility storage. Unlike older packs, these housings withstand rain without exploding.</VFE_LargeAdvancedBattery.description>
  <VFE_LargeBattery.description>A large Poseidon battery bank meant to hold reserve power for later demand. Fully charged units are dangerous when exposed to rain or fire.</VFE_LargeBattery.description>
  <VFE_SmallBattery.description>A compact reserve battery for local circuits and small industrial loads. Charged units can still blow when exposed to rain or fire.</VFE_SmallBattery.description>
  <VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.description>A powered Corvega assembly bench fitted for turning raw stock into industrial and spacer-grade components.</VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.description>
  <VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.label>Corvega assembly bench</VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.label>
  <VFE_FueledSmelter.description>A fuel-fed foundry station for recovering usable metal from slag and scrap items.</VFE_FueledSmelter.description>
  <VFE_FueledSmelter.label>fueled foundry</VFE_FueledSmelter.label>
  <VFE_TableButcherElectric.description>A motorized butcher line with a rotary saw for fast, precise carcass breakdown. It consumes a heavy amount of power.</VFE_TableButcherElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableButcherElectric.label>industrial butcher line</VFE_TableButcherElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.description>A powered Corvega chem lab with heaters, vessels, and gauges for efficient batch processing of compounds and drugs.</VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.label>industrial chem lab</VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableMachiningLarge.description>A large Corvega machining platform with advanced tooling and floor space for rapid fabrication of technical equipment. It consumes power.</VFE_TableMachiningLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableMachiningLarge.label>Corvega machining platform</VFE_TableMachiningLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableSmithyLarge.description>A powered Corvega forge station for weapons, tools, and heavy benchwork. It draws a substantial load from the grid.</VFE_TableSmithyLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableSmithyLarge.label>Corvega forge station</VFE_TableSmithyLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.description>An industrial masonry saw with powered cutters for turning chunks into building blocks at assembly-line speed.</VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.label>industrial masonry saw</VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableStoveLarge.description>A large industrial cooking line with multiple ovens and burners for rapid meal production under heavy settlement demand.</VFE_TableStoveLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableStoveLarge.label>industrial galley range</VFE_TableStoveLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableTailorLarge.description>A large industrial tailoring bench with powered sewing equipment for rapid clothing output. It can still limp along without power at reduced speed.</VFE_TableTailorLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableTailorLarge.label>industrial tailoring bench</VFE_TableTailorLarge.label>
  <VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.description>A large Poseidon groundwater reclamation pump that gradually strips pollution from broad terrain and condenses the recovered waste into haulable toxic packs.</VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.description>
  <VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.label>Poseidon reclamation pump</VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.label>
  <VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.description>A compact high-draw reclamation pump that clears polluted terrain quickly by burning a heavy amount of grid power and packing the recovered contaminants into toxic wastepacks.</VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.description>
  <VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.label>high-draw reclamation pump</VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.label>
  <VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.description>A sealed industrial locker for holding toxic waste products and reclaimed hazardous packs without letting them leak into the local environment.</VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.description>
  <VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.label>sealed waste locker</VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.label>
  <UnstablePowerCell.description>An unstable fusion battery built around a permanently active power core. It will run forever until something damages the housing badly enough to turn the whole unit into a catastrophic detonation.</UnstablePowerCell.description>
  <UnstablePowerCell.label>unstable fusion battery</UnstablePowerCell.label>
  <VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>A large ultratech shield projector with the unmistakable feel of a Poseidon black-budget installation. It consumes enormous power while active and can set the surrounding area ablaze if it absorbs too much punishment too quickly.</VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>A compact ultratech shield projector that reads like one of Poseidon's more secretive defense contracts. It throws up a potent energy field when a threat is present and idles at far lower draw the rest of the time.</VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>A specialized Corvega anti-air turret that intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its defensive radius. It cannot engage ground targets, but it looks every bit like a pre-War perimeter solution.</VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>An armored portable turret with Corvega targeting electronics and reinforced plating. Extra armor helps it survive incoming fire, but the control package remains just dumb enough to be dangerous around friendlies.</VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>A twin-barreled autocannon turret with Corvega fire-control electronics. It trades finesse for volume of fire and remains a power-hungry, violently practical defensive platform.</VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Flame.description>A portable flamer turret with Corvega control electronics and a brutally simple fuel system. It can engulf enemies and terrain in fire, and it remains as unsafe as any honest pre-War weapon platform should be.</VFES_Turret_Flame.description>
  <VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>A refined automated turret with Corvega targeting hardware, military-grade stabilization, and hardened casing. Its dumb AI brain still cannot be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>A heavy automatic turret whose multi-barrel mechanism unleashes sustained fire at high speed. Corvega control systems keep it cycling, but they do not make it subtle.</VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>A Corvega searchlight combining an intensely bright lamp with a mirrored reflector, useful for illuminating and dazzling targets across a defensive perimeter.</VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>A compact automatic turret fitted with a semi-automatic shotgun and Corvega targeting electronics. Short-ranged, nasty, and still not smart enough to trust completely.</VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>
  <Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>An outdoor utility lamp with an integrated Poseidon solar collector. It charges by day and provides dependable lighting after dark.</Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.description>A compact Wattz Electronics air scrubber that filters smoke, dust, and hazardous particulates while improving room cleanliness and indoor air quality.</VFES_AirPurifier.description>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.label>wattz air scrubber</VFES_AirPurifier.label>
  <VTE_IndustrialCooler.description>A large Appalachia Freeze wall cooler for serious refrigeration and industrial climate control. Cold air exits one side while hot exhaust is dumped out the other.</VTE_IndustrialCooler.description>
  <VTE_IndustrialHeater.description>A large Wattz industrial heater that fits into a wall and pushes serious utility heat. It can automatically cycle to a target temperature.</VTE_IndustrialHeater.description>
  <VTE_LargeCeilingFan.description>A large Wattz ceiling fan for workshops, warehouses, and other rooms that need stronger air circulation.</VTE_LargeCeilingFan.description>
  <VTE_SmallCeilingFan.description>A Wattz ceiling fan for slow, steady air circulation in smaller rooms.</VTE_SmallCeilingFan.description>
  <VTE_StandingCooler.description>A freestanding Appalachia Freeze cooling unit for open rooms that need relief from summer heat without full freezer performance.</VTE_StandingCooler.description>
  <VTE_WallHeater.description>A Wattz wall heater that fits into a wall and keeps rooms warm without wasting floor space.</VTE_WallHeater.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedCooler.description>An Appalachia Freeze wall-mounted cooler for compact freezer rooms and tight utility spaces.</VTE_WallMountedCooler.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedHeater.description>A compact Wattz wall-mounted heater for utility corridors, workshops, and smaller rooms that still need dependable automatic temperature control.</VTE_WallMountedHeater.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedVent.description>A simple Wattz wall vent for equalizing temperatures between adjacent rooms without opening a passageway.</VTE_WallMountedVent.description>
  <VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>A small crate containing heavy uranium shells. Used by gauss artillery to reload. A crate is fed directly into adjacent Hellion artillery when it needs to be rearmed.</VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>
  <VGE_CopilotConsole.description>An auxiliary interface that allows a copilot to assist in launching and piloting a Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_CopilotConsole.description>
  <VGE_GaussGun.description>A compact electromagnetic cannon that launches dense uranium slugs at extreme velocities. Designed for local bombardment and medium-range interception, it can also target hostile orbital craft. Requires a linked targeting terminal with an operator to function. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_GaussGun.description>
  <VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.description>A massive reactor assembly that channels a salvaged reactor core into immense electrical output. Its reinforced coils can handle extreme load, making it one of the most potent power sources available for Hellion systems. Adjacent reactor-core power cells multiply the output by 15% each.</VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.description>
  <VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.label>reactor-core power coil</VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.label>
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>A heavy reactor package built for the largest Hellion frames and orbital support hulls. It sustains an enormous lift field, allowing massive aircraft to rise under their own power while operating near a planetary gravity well.

When launched, anything on Hellion deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map.

These oversized assemblies were intended for pre-War logistics craft and mobile aerospace platforms, and they demand immense fabrication capacity to keep operational.</VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>heavy Hellion reactor</VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>A compact reactor package adapted for a light Hellion. It generates the lift field needed for rapid vertical launch and short-range atmospheric insertion, but it is not suited to true interplanetary travel.

When launched, anything on Hellion deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map.

Often salvaged from scout craft, courier platforms, and other pre-War aerospace projects, these reactors are valued for their agility and relatively modest support requirements.</VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>light Hellion reactor</VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>
  <VGE_GravshipCapacitor.description>Stores large amounts of electricity for later use. Constructed in Hellion deck plating, Hellion capacitors do not obstruct movement.</VGE_GravshipCapacitor.description>
  <VGE_GravshipCapacitor.label>Hellion capacitor</VGE_GravshipCapacitor.label>
  <VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>A rapid-fire gun for point-defense use aboard the Hellion.</VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>
  <VGE_PilotBridge.description>An interface that allows launching and piloting a heavy Hellion. It draws power directly from the heavy Hellion reactor.</VGE_PilotBridge.description>
  <VGE_PilotCockpit.description>An interface that allows launching and piloting a light Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_PilotCockpit.description>
  <VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>A specialized defensive turret built exclusively for the Hellion. It intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its protective radius, but cannot engage ground targets. Interception chance scales with the target's velocity.</VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>
  <VGE_SolarPanelling.description>Produces electricity from sunlight. Does not work in darkness or under artificial light. It does not obstruct movement or provide cover, but it can only be constructed on Hellion deck plating.</VGE_SolarPanelling.description>
  <VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>A control station dedicated to operating a single Hellion artillery piece. Requires a crew member to manually aim and fire the weapon. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>
  <AncientGravReactor.description>An ancient generator powered by a reactor core. Once capable of producing massive amounts of power, it has now fallen into disrepair. The containment shield is leaking, causing toxic fallout to blanket the whole region.

Hack or destroy the reactor to obtain the core. Be warned, it may explode if damaged.</AncientGravReactor.description>
  <AncientGravReactor.label>ancient reactor</AncientGravReactor.label>
  <FuelOptimizer.description>A control unit that synchronizes the Hellion reactor with its VTOL thrust systems. It reduces the fuel needed for Hellion flight.

One Hellion can support two fuel regulators.</FuelOptimizer.description>
  <FuelOptimizer.label>fuel regulator</FuelOptimizer.label>
  <GravAnchor.description>Prevents the local map from being destroyed during a Hellion launch.

Mooring masts stabilize the launch zone around the aircraft and keep the surrounding settlement intact during departure. They cannot be constructed on the Hellion itself, because doing so would prevent takeoff entirely.</GravAnchor.description>
  <GravAnchor.label>mooring mast</GravAnchor.label>
  <Gravcore.description>A compact pre-War reactor core recovered from prototype Hellion systems and related military hardware. It is useless by itself, but it can be integrated into advanced Hellion support equipment.</Gravcore.description>
  <Gravcore.label>reactor core</Gravcore.label>
  <GravcorePowerCell.description>A compact generator built around a salvaged reactor core, adapted to provide steady power for the Hellion's onboard systems.</GravcorePowerCell.description>
  <GravcorePowerCell.label>reactor-core power cell</GravcorePowerCell.label>
  <GravEngine.description>The pre-War reactor assembly at the heart of the Hellion. It sustains the aircraft's vertical lift envelope and powers the heavy systems needed for long-range atmospheric and orbital operations.

When launched, anything on deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map. Without a mooring mast, launching the Hellion will abandon your current map.

The Hellion was designed as an unfinished military prototype, requiring rare components, specialist fabrication, and a great deal of salvage to keep flying.</GravEngine.description>
  <GravEngine.label>Hellion reactor</GravEngine.label>
  <GravFieldExtender.description>A support assembly used to expand the Hellion's airframe. It increases the amount of deck plating the craft can carry and must be built near the Hellion reactor.

One Hellion can support up to six airframe extenders.</GravFieldExtender.description>
  <GravFieldExtender.label>airframe extender</GravFieldExtender.label>
  <GravlitePanel.description>A lightweight pre-War airframe panel used to assemble and reinforce Hellion components. It is durable, heat-resistant, and ideal for advanced aerospace construction.

Requires vacstone blocks, which can be obtained from orbital asteroids.</GravlitePanel.description>
  <GravlitePanel.label>airframe panel</GravlitePanel.label>
  <GravshipHull.description>An airtight armored hull section sized for the Hellion's frame. It seals the craft against vacuum exposure and locks directly into the underlying deck plating, so it can only be built as part of the Hellion.</GravshipHull.description>
  <GravshipHull.label>Hellion hull</GravshipHull.label>
  <GravshipShieldGenerator.description>A defensive projector that protects the Hellion by generating a short-lived repulsor screen against incoming rounds and mortar fire. Those inside the field can still shoot out.

It must be charged before use. One Hellion can support two shield projectors.</GravshipShieldGenerator.description>
  <GravshipShieldGenerator.label>Hellion shield projector</GravshipShieldGenerator.label>
  <LargeThruster.description>An advanced VTOL thruster with a heat-resistant vacstone liner. It greatly increases the Hellion's operational range. Thrusters require an unobstructed exhaust area free of large buildings and Hellion deck plating.

Requires vacstone blocks, which can be obtained from orbital asteroids.

One Hellion can support up to six heavy VTOL thrusters.</LargeThruster.description>
  <LargeThruster.label>heavy VTOL thruster</LargeThruster.label>
  <PilotConsole.description>A hardened flight console used to launch and pilot the Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</PilotConsole.description>
  <PilotConsole.label>cockpit console</PilotConsole.label>
  <PilotSubpersonaCore.description>A low-grade navigation core tuned for Hellion flight. It reduces the chance of an accident when flying the Hellion, though it cannot fully compensate for pilot error.

One Hellion can support up to two navigation cores.</PilotSubpersonaCore.description>
  <PilotSubpersonaCore.label>navigation core</PilotSubpersonaCore.label>
  <ShipChunk_Mech.description>A chunk of robot craft made of steel and salvaged airframe panels. It looks like it was torn free during re-entry or blasted off by heavy weapons.

Deconstruct it to obtain valuable resources.</ShipChunk_Mech.description>
  <SignalJammer.description>An electronic countermeasures suite that masks the Hellion's signature and helps it approach heavily defended landing sites.</SignalJammer.description>
  <SignalJammer.label>ECM suite</SignalJammer.label>
  <SmallThruster.description>A compact VTOL thruster that increases the Hellion's operational range. Thrusters require an unobstructed exhaust area free of large buildings and Hellion deck plating.

One Hellion can support up to four small VTOL thrusters.</SmallThruster.description>
  <SmallThruster.label>small VTOL thruster</SmallThruster.label>
  <RobCo_Assaultron.description>Một robot chiến đấu hai chân do RobCo Industries sản xuất cho quân đội Hoa Kỳ. Nó có màu sơn màu ô liu với các dấu hiệu quân sự, hai cánh tay có móng vuốt để cận chiến và một tia laser gắn trên đầu có khả năng bắn ra một chùm tia tích điện ở khoảng cách xa. Nhanh và hung hãn, Assaultron được thiết kế cho vai trò tấn công tiền tuyến. Một số đơn vị được trang bị máy tạo trường tàng hình, cho phép chúng che giấu khi tiếp cận.</RobCo_Assaultron.description>
  <RobCo_Assaultron.label>tấn công</RobCo_Assaultron.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronDominator.description>Một biến thể săn sát thủ Assaultron chuyên dụng được chế tạo dựa trên bộ phát trường tàng hình tích hợp và gói lưỡi dao tấn công tầm gần chuyên dụng. Nó từ bỏ tia laser đầu tiêu chuẩn để đổi lấy các cách tiếp cận được che giấu nhanh hơn và các cuộc giao tranh cận chiến nguy hiểm hơn.</RobCo_AssaultronDominator.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronDominator.label>Kẻ thống trị tấn công</RobCo_AssaultronDominator.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.description>Khung gầm Assaultron đã được sửa đổi nhiều, được chế tạo để giống với mật mã Sheepsquatch huyền thoại trong văn hóa dân gian Appalachian. Lớn hơn một chiếc Assaultron tiêu chuẩn và được trang bị một tia laser ở đầu được nâng cấp, nó có thể được chế tạo như một công cụ đe dọa bởi bất kỳ ai có quyền truy cập vào bàn làm việc của robot và có khiếu hài hước đen tối.</RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.label>chuồng cừu</RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.description>Một lưỡi kiếm cẳng tay kiểu Assaultron tích hợp được tối ưu hóa để chém và đâm thủng nhanh chóng ở cự ly gần.</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.label>lưỡi kiếm tấn công</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.tools.0.label>lưỡi kiếm tấn công</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.description>Đầu laser kiểu Assaultron nhỏ gọn có chu kỳ bắn nhanh hơn các máy chiếu chùm tia nặng hơn. Điều này làm cho nó phù hợp hơn cho các cuộc giao tranh nhanh và cận chiến.</RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.label>RobCo Laser đầu tấn công</RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.label>
  <RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.description>Máy chiếu chùm tia gắn trên đầu công suất cao được thiết kế dựa trên chu kỳ sạc dài và bán kính nổ lớn. Việc phóng điện tạo ra nhiệt lượng đáng kể và hiệu quả nhất khi bắn từ phạm vi dự kiến.</RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.description>
  <RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.label>RobCo laze đầu cừu</RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Cyberdog.description>Một chú chó robot quân sự được phát triển bởi RobCo Industries cho Quân đội Hoa Kỳ. Nó kết hợp một bộ não chó được bảo quản với một cơ thể máy móc, mang lại cho nó bản năng của loài chó và một vũ khí vỏ cây siêu âm để chiến đấu tầm xa. Cyberdog được triển khai với vai trò trinh sát, bảo vệ động vật và đồng hành chiến đấu cùng với quân nhân.</RobCo_Cyberdog.description>
  <RobCo_Cyberdog.label>chó mạng</RobCo_Cyberdog.label>
  <RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.description>Máy chiếu âm thanh tầm ngắn được sử dụng bởi các đơn vị an ninh RobCo. Nó phát ra một xung âm thanh chấn động có thể phá vỡ các mục tiêu cơ học mà không cần dựa vào sát thương vật lý trực tiếp.</RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.description>
  <RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.label>máy phát âm vỏ cây</RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.label>
  <RobCo_Eyebot.description>Một máy bay không người lái giám sát và phát sóng nhỏ do RobCo Industries sản xuất. Nó sử dụng ăng-ten roi và loa tích hợp để truyền tín hiệu vô tuyến và các chương trình phát sóng được ghi sẵn, đồng thời được trang bị hệ thống nhận dạng khuôn mặt tiên tiến. Eyebot mang theo vũ khí laser nhẹ để tự vệ. Được Enclave triển khai rộng rãi để tuyên truyền và trinh sát, nó nhanh và khó nắm bắt nhưng cực kỳ mỏng manh trong chiến đấu trực tiếp.</RobCo_Eyebot.description>
  <RobCo_Eyebot.label>Eyebot</RobCo_Eyebot.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotCrashed.description>Phần còn lại của một chiếc Vertibot - một máy bay không người lái VTOL của quân đội trước Thế chiến - đã bị hạ và không còn khả năng bay nữa. Bất chấp tình trạng của nó, hệ thống vũ khí trên tàu và các giao thức phòng thủ tự động vẫn hoạt động một phần. Nó sẽ tấn công bất cứ thứ gì đi vào chu vi của nó.</RobCo_EyebotCrashed.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotCrashed.label>robot vertibot bị rơi</RobCo_EyebotCrashed.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.description>Eyebot cải tiến được xây dựng trên khung Duraframe thử nghiệm. Nó có các bộ phận bên trong được gia cố để có độ bền cao hơn thiết bị tiêu chuẩn và mang theo vũ khí năng lượng mạnh hơn. Đơn vị Duraframe được ghi chép nhiều nhất, được chỉ định là ED-E, được trang bị một khẩu pháo Tesla và mang dữ liệu nghiên cứu nhạy cảm của Enclave đi khắp vùng đất hoang trong nhiều thập kỷ trước khi được thu hồi.</RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.label>Khung durabot Eyebot</RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.label>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>Một đơn vị máy bay không người lái nhỏ gọn được sinh ra và chỉ đạo bởi nền tảng chỉ huy Hydra. Nó mang theo một nguồn năng lượng tập trung và hoạt động dưới sự phối hợp phụ thuộc từ đơn vị mẹ của nó. Các đơn vị Eye of Hydra riêng lẻ được bọc thép nhẹ nhưng tấn công với số lượng lớn từ nhiều góc độ cùng một lúc. Việc tiêu diệt Hydra mẹ sẽ đưa chúng trở lại các giao thức tấn công tự động cơ bản.</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>Con mắt của Hydra</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>Một nền tảng dựa trên Mister Gutsy được sửa đổi nhiều, được thiết kế để hoạt động như một trung tâm chỉ huy máy bay không người lái. Hydra mang theo một hệ thống tích hợp để triển khai và điều phối các đơn vị Eye of Hydra, hiệu quả chiến đấu của chúng được nâng cao nhờ hào quang chiến thuật được phát từ nền tảng trung tâm. Mảng vũ khí của riêng nó rất đáng kể và việc phá hủy nó sẽ làm gián đoạn bất kỳ máy bay không người lái nào mà nó đã triển khai.</RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>Hydra</RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.description>Một biến thể Mister Handy được thiết kế để chăm sóc trẻ em và giám sát việc nhà. Nó được lập trình với một gói hành vi mở rộng bao gồm chăm sóc trẻ sơ sinh, phát hiện mối nguy hiểm, nghi thức và các quy trình kỷ luật. Miss Nanny giữ lại một cánh tay laser để bảo vệ gia đình và được bán cho các gia đình trước Chiến tranh như một giải pháp chăm sóc trẻ chuyên dụng.</RobCo_MissNanny.description>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.label>cô bảo mẫu</RobCo_MissNanny.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>Một thiết bị Mister Handy được cấu hình lại cho công việc nông nghiệp. Nó được trang bị các cánh tay công cụ phù hợp cho việc trồng trọt, thu hoạch và bảo trì đồng ruộng cùng với các cảm biến giám sát cây trồng. Được bán cho các tổ chức nông nghiệp trước chiến tranh, Mister Farmhand vẫn giữ lại một cánh tay laser để bảo vệ nơi làm việc.</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>ông nông dân</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>Một biến thể quân sự hóa của nền tảng Mister Handy, do Quân đội Hoa Kỳ ủy quyền. Nó thay thế các cánh tay công cụ dân sự bằng một bánh xe plasma và súng phun lửa, đồng thời chạy gói tính cách Sergeant Major v1.0. Mister Gutsy có lớp giáp nặng hơn Handy tiêu chuẩn và được triển khai tại các khu vực chiến đấu bao gồm cả mặt trận Anchorage.</RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>Ông Gutsy</RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.description>Một robot giúp việc gia đình bay lơ lửng do General Atomics International hợp tác với RobCo Industries sản xuất. Nó được trang bị ba cánh tay có khớp nối chấp nhận các phụ kiện đính kèm công cụ bao gồm cưa sắt, máy cắt laser và súng phun lửa, cùng với ba thân quang học. Mạng lưới thần kinh của nó cho phép trò chuyện gần với tri giác và một đơn vị được bảo trì tốt có khả năng hoạt động tự chủ trong nhiều thế kỷ.</RobCo_MisterHandy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.label>Ông tiện dụng</RobCo_MisterHandy.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydraArray.tools.0.label>người xé xác</RobCo_GutsyHydraArray.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MissNannyBlaster.tools.0.label>cánh tay thao tác</RobCo_MissNannyBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhandBlaster.tools.0.label>sản phẩm gia súc</RobCo_MisterFarmhandBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsyArray.tools.0.label>người xé xác</RobCo_MisterGutsyArray.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandyBlaster.tools.0.label>lưỡi cưa</RobCo_MisterHandyBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <MechanoidTransponder.description>Bộ phát đáp trước chiến tranh của RobCo Industries.</MechanoidTransponder.description>
  <MechanoidTransponder.label>RobCo Bộ phát đáp</MechanoidTransponder.label>
  <NanostructuringChip.description>Phần còn lại đã cạn kiệt của một tế bào tổng hợp Sentry Bot.</NanostructuringChip.description>
  <NanostructuringChip.label>Sentry Bot Fusion Core đã cạn kiệt</NanostructuringChip.label>
  <PowerfocusChip.description>Phần đầu bị cắt rời của một Assaultron bị hỏng.</PowerfocusChip.description>
  <PowerfocusChip.label>đầu Assaultron phế liệu</PowerfocusChip.label>
  <SignalChip.description>Vẫn là các bộ phận chức năng của bộ đẩy đơn vị Mister Handy.</SignalChip.description>
  <SignalChip.label>máy đẩy tiện dụng được trục vớt</SignalChip.label>
  <SubcoreBasic.description>phần cứng dân sự RobCo.</SubcoreBasic.description>
  <SubcoreBasic.label>mạch cơ bản</SubcoreBasic.label>
  <SubcoreRegular.description>Phần cứng RobCo cấp quân sự.</SubcoreRegular.description>
  <SubcoreRegular.label>Mạch cấp quân sự</SubcoreRegular.label>
  <UnfinishedSubcore.description>các bộ phận robot RobCo chưa hoàn thành.</UnfinishedSubcore.description>
  <UnfinishedSubcore.label>chưa hoàn thành RobCo Phần</UnfinishedSubcore.label>
  <RobCo_Liberator.description>Một robot chiến đấu bốn chân nhỏ liên kết với các phe phái liên kết với Trung Quốc trong Khối thịnh vượng chung. Nó được chế tạo xung quanh một vũ khí laser tích hợp duy nhất và bốn chân cơ học để di chuyển nhanh chóng trên địa hình không bằng phẳng. Liberator được bọc thép nhẹ nhưng nhanh nhẹn và thường gặp trong các nhóm lớn tấn công đồng thời từ nhiều hướng.</RobCo_Liberator.description>
  <RobCo_Liberator.label>người giải phóng</RobCo_Liberator.label>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.description>Súng trường laser cấp quân sự được tích hợp vào robot chiến đấu Liberator của Trung Quốc.</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.description>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.label>súng laser giải phóng</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.label>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.tools.0.label>tay servo</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrime.description>Một cỗ máy chiến tranh khổng lồ trước Chiến tranh do RobCo Industries và General Atomics International đồng phát triển cho Quân đội Hoa Kỳ. Nó cao khoảng 20 mét và được trang bị hai khẩu pháo năng lượng gắn trên đầu và nguồn cung cấp bom hạt nhân chiến thuật để phá hủy các vị trí kiên cố. Ban đầu được thiết kế để giải phóng Anchorage khỏi lực lượng Trung Quốc, nó chưa bao giờ được triển khai trước Đại chiến do mất điện.</RobCo_LibertyPrime.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrime.label>Liberty Prime</RobCo_LibertyPrime.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.description>Một khẩu pháo xung năng lượng cao được tích hợp vào Liberty Prime, để lại cú ném hạt nhân mini cho hệ thống phóng chuyên dụng của nó.</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.label>pháo xung prime tự do</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>nắm đấm nguyên tử</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_BallisticAuto.label>vụ nổ đạn đạo tự động</RobCo_Bullet_BallisticAuto.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserMedium.label>laser chùm tia trung bình</RobCo_Bullet_LaserMedium.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimePulse.label>xung thủ tự do</RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimePulse.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronRocket.label>tên lửa securitron</RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronRocket.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_WarMachinePulse.label>xung máy chiến tranh</RobCo_Bullet_WarMachinePulse.label>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.inspectString>Có thể được phân tích bởi một thợ cơ khí.</RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.inspectString>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.jobString>Phân tích chip bạch kim</RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.jobString>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.description>Một chip lưu trữ dữ liệu bạch kim được khôi phục từ kho quản lý RobCo được niêm phong. Nó chứa gói hệ điều hành RobCo trước chiến tranh và có giá trị vượt xa trọng lượng kim loại của nó.</RobCo_PlatinumChip.description>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.label>chip bạch kim</RobCo_PlatinumChip.label>
  <RobCo_Collectron.description>Một biến thể Protectron được lập trình lại để thu thập và trục vớt tài nguyên. Nó đã được nhiều phe phái sau chiến tranh áp dụng để tự động hóa việc thu thập các vật liệu cụ thể. Collectron hoạt động tự chủ trong một khu vực xác định và sẽ bảo vệ vùng thu thập của nó khỏi bị can thiệp.</RobCo_Collectron.description>
  <RobCo_Collectron.label>bộ sưu tập</RobCo_Collectron.label>
  <RobCo_Constructron.description>Một thiết bị Protectron được cấu hình cho công việc xây dựng và cơ sở hạ tầng. Nó mang theo các phụ kiện dụng cụ hàn và lắp ráp thay cho các tia laser cầm tay tiêu chuẩn và được triển khai tại các địa điểm xây dựng và cơ sở công nghiệp trước Thế chiến. Các giao thức ứng phó với mối đe dọa tiêu chuẩn vẫn hoạt động.</RobCo_Constructron.description>
  <RobCo_Constructron.label>cấu trúc</RobCo_Constructron.label>
  <RobCo_Factotron.description>Một biến thể Protectron được lập trình cho các nhiệm vụ trong nhà máy và sản xuất. Nó được thiết kế để hoạt động trên dây chuyền lắp ráp và sàn sản xuất, thực hiện nhiều nhiệm vụ phụ sản xuất với độ chính xác cao. Factotron là một trong những biến thể Protectron ít gặp hơn ở vùng đất hoang sau chiến tranh.</RobCo_Factotron.description>
  <RobCo_Factotron.label>nhân tố</RobCo_Factotron.label>
  <RobCo_Protectron.description>Một robot an ninh và tiện ích trước chiến tranh được triển khai rộng rãi do RobCo Industries sản xuất. Nó có một đầu hình vòm lớn với ba cảm biến quang học, bộ phát laser kép gắn trên tay và một đầu laser. Được cung cấp năng lượng bởi pin phân hạch, Protectron được sử dụng ở các văn phòng, bệnh viện và cơ sở công cộng trên khắp nước Mỹ. Nó chậm và kém khả năng chiến đấu trực tiếp hơn các robot quân sự chuyên dụng.</RobCo_Protectron.description>
  <RobCo_Protectron.label>Bảo vệ</RobCo_Protectron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.description>Thiết bị Protectron được trang bị một phụ kiện khoan hạng nặng thay cho tia laser cầm tay tiêu chuẩn, dành cho công việc khai thác và khai quật. Nó được ký hợp đồng với các hoạt động khai thác trước chiến tranh để khai thác tài nguyên dưới lòng đất. Tay khoan làm cho nó chậm hơn so với Protectron tiêu chuẩn nhưng mang lại cho nó khả năng ở cự ly gần đáng kể.</RobCo_Utilitron.description>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.label>tiện ích</RobCo_Utilitron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>máy khoan</RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.inspectString>Có thể được phân tích bởi một người thực dân.</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.inspectString>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.jobString>Phân tích khung Eyebot bị hỏng</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.jobString>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.description>Những mảnh vỡ của Eyebot. Thợ cơ khí có thể nghiên cứu các bộ phận này để giúp đạt được cấp độ nghiên cứu RobCo cao hơn.</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.description>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.label>khung Eyebot bị hỏng</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.label>
  <RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.description>Tăng thêm hiệu suất của bảng điều khiển liên lạc.</RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.description>
  <RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.label>RobCo ăng-ten</RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.label>
  <RobCo_CommsConsole.description>Bảng điều khiển liên lạc có chức năng RobCo nhóm ông chủ.</RobCo_CommsConsole.description>
  <RobCo_CommsConsole.label>RobCo bảng điều khiển liên lạc</RobCo_CommsConsole.label>
  <RobCo_MechbandDish.description>Tăng đáng kể hiệu suất của bảng điều khiển liên lạc.</RobCo_MechbandDish.description>
  <RobCo_MechbandDish.label>RobCo món ăn</RobCo_MechbandDish.label>
  <RobCo_Receiver.description>Tăng hiệu suất của bảng điều khiển liên lạc.</RobCo_Receiver.description>
  <RobCo_Receiver.label>RobCo người nhận</RobCo_Receiver.label>
  <RobCo_Robobrain.description>Một robot chiến đấu có bánh xích cỡ lớn do General Atomics International sản xuất cho Quân đội Hoa Kỳ. Nó chứa bộ não linh trưởng hoặc con người sống trong một mái vòm gel y sinh, được nối trực tiếp vào hệ thống điều khiển của nó. Robobrain được trang bị móng vuốt điều khiển, vũ khí laser tích hợp và thiết bị gây choáng Mesmetron. Thành phần não sinh học của nó cung cấp trí thông minh chiến thuật đặc biệt và khả năng xử lý vũ khí tiêu chuẩn của con người.</RobCo_Robobrain.description>
  <RobCo_Robobrain.label>não robot</RobCo_Robobrain.label>
  <RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.description>Một khẩu súng tiêm có độ chính xác cao, bắn ra những mũi kim kim loại chứa đầy hợp chất độc hại. Nó được thiết kế để gây thương tích cho mục tiêu khi va chạm và cung cấp chất độc ở tầm xa hơn hầu hết các loại vũ khí phụ.</RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.description>
  <RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.label>RobCo ống tiêm</RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.label>
  <RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.description>Một đơn vị Securitron có bộ hạn chế hành vi bị lỗi, khiến nó rơi vào tình trạng gây hấn bừa bãi. Nó vẫn giữ được đầy đủ khả năng chiến đấu của Mark II - tia laser Gatling, bệ phóng tên lửa và vũ khí sốc điện - nhưng không có sự công nhận phe phái, đánh giá mối đe dọa hoặc các giao thức xuống thang. Nó tấn công tất cả các mục tiêu trong phạm vi mà không có sự phân biệt.</RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.description>
  <RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.label>điên cuồng Securitron</RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkI.description>Robot an ninh RobCo Industries PDQ-88b được chế tạo trên một khung gầm một bánh nặng. Mark I mang súng tiểu liên 9mm ở tay phải và hiển thị hình ảnh sĩ quan cảnh sát trước Chiến tranh trên mặt màn hình CRT. Nó có thân bằng hợp kim titan và hệ thống tự động sửa chữa tích hợp. Các đơn vị Mark I chạy phần mềm chiến đấu cơ bản và kém hiệu quả hơn trong các cuộc giao tranh phức tạp so với biến thể Mark II nâng cấp.</RobCo_SecuritronMkI.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkI.label>Securitron nhãn hiệu I</RobCo_SecuritronMkI.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkII.description>Một PDQ-88b Securitron chạy gói phần mềm Mark II, mang toàn bộ vũ khí của nó lên mạng: laser X-25 Gatling, súng phóng tên lửa M-235 và súng phóng lựu G-28. Màn hình CRT của nó hiển thị hình ảnh một người lính chứ không phải cảnh sát. Mark II là lực lượng sẵn sàng chiến đấu dự định của Robert House để bảo vệ New Vegas và Mojave.</RobCo_SecuritronMkII.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkII.label>Securitron mark II</RobCo_SecuritronMkII.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.description>Nền tảng laser được nâng cấp được tích hợp vào Securitron Mark II với pin tên lửa trên tàu.</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.label>tia laser của cảnh sát securitron</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.tools.0.label>dùi cui điện áp cao</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.description>Bộ lặp đạn đạo tích hợp được gắn trên nền tảng bảo mật Securitron Mark I.</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.label>bộ lặp đạn đạo securitron</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.tools.0.label>dùi cui sốc</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>Robot canh gác RobCo của Industries được trang bị súng ngắn ba nòng và tia laser Gatling, được thiết kế để trấn áp liên tục các mục tiêu bộ binh và bọc thép hạng nhẹ. Bot canh gác là nền tảng chiến đấu chuyên dụng của RobCo, được xây dựng dựa trên một con chip nhân cách tổng hợp đơn giản chỉ chứa các thói quen chiến đấu. Annihilator là biến thể sản xuất tiêu chuẩn của dòng này.</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>kẻ hủy diệt canh gác</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>Một bot canh gác mang theo một bộ vũ khí kết hợp đầy đủ: súng ngắn, súng phóng tên lửa, súng phun lửa và súng phóng lựu chùm. Đây là một trong những đơn vị tự trị được trang bị vũ khí mạnh nhất gặp phải ở vùng đất hoang. Bộ xử lý trung tâm của nó chứa một con chip cấu trúc nano, cho thấy nó đã được sử dụng làm nền tảng thử nghiệm cho các chương trình công nghệ nano tiên tiến trước hoặc sau chiến tranh.</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>robot tử thần</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>Một biến thể robot canh gác được trang bị hệ thống súng phun lửa công nghiệp và hộp nhiên liệu có thể nạp lại để hoạt động kéo dài. Ban đầu được thiết kế để diệt trừ sâu bệnh trên quy mô lớn và ngăn chặn khu vực, nó có khả năng duy trì hỏa lực cháy trên một khu vực rộng. Biến thể Pestcontrol đã được tiếp thị cho các khách hàng nông nghiệp và chính phủ trước chiến tranh.</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>canh gác kiểm soát dịch hại</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>Một biến thể bot canh gác được cấu hình cho các hoạt động tấn công công sự và chống thiết giáp. Hệ thống vũ khí chính của nó là một bệ phóng tên lửa công suất cao phù hợp để phá hủy các công trình được gia cố. Nó chạy trên đế bánh xe mecanum cho phép di chuyển trên hầu hết các địa hình. Áo giáp bot canh gác tiêu chuẩn và các giao thức chiến đấu được giữ lại.</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>robot canh gác bao vây</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachine.description>Một nền tảng chiến đấu tự động khổng lồ kết hợp hỏa lực của robot canh gác hạng nặng với hệ thống vận chuyển cơ khí tích hợp để triển khai máy bay không người lái Liberator. War Machine phát tín hiệu phối hợp chiến thuật nhằm nâng cao hiệu quả chiến đấu của các đơn vị Liberator gần đó. Nó được trang bị pin xung nhiều lần và găng tay chiến tranh được gia cố để giao chiến ở cự ly gần.</RobCo_WarMachine.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachine.label>cỗ máy chiến tranh</RobCo_WarMachine.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.description>Một pin xung duy trì được tích hợp vào các điểm cứng trên thân của War Machine.</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.label>pin xung máy chiến tranh</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>găng tay chiến tranh</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_Electroshock.label>bu lông sốc điện</RobCo_Bullet_Electroshock.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserAssaultron.label>RobCo Laser đầu tấn công</RobCo_Bullet_LaserAssaultron.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserAuto.label>tia laser tự động</RobCo_Bullet_LaserAuto.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserHigh.label>tia laser chùm cao</RobCo_Bullet_LaserHigh.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserLow.label>tia laser chùm tia thấp</RobCo_Bullet_LaserLow.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserSheepsquatch.label>RobCo tia laser đầu Assaultron bị sạc quá mức</RobCo_Bullet_LaserSheepsquatch.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LiberatorLaser.label>tia laser giải phóng</RobCo_Bullet_LiberatorLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimeMiniNuke.label>hạt nhân mini Liberty Prime</RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimeMiniNuke.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_ScurrybotLaser.label>laser scurrybot</RobCo_Bullet_ScurrybotLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronLaser.label>laser securitron</RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SentryRocket.label>tên lửa canh gác</RobCo_Bullet_SentryRocket.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SonicBark.label>vỏ âm thanh</RobCo_Bullet_SonicBark.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_Syringe.label>RobCo ống tiêm</RobCo_Bullet_Syringe.label>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.description>A wood-fueled station for brewing wasteland extracts.</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.description>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.label>fueled extract lab</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.label>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.description>An electrically powered station for brewing wasteland extracts.</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.description>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.label>electric extract lab</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.label>
  <VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.description>An extract is causing the user to lose memories quickly, shortening both positive and negative memories far faster than normal.</VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.label>amnesia extract</VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.description>A patched-up practice target mounted on a crude stand. It is kept around as a placeholder range fixture for anyone still trying to train their aim.</VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.description>
  <VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.label>archery target</VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.label>
  <VFEM2_ComaDraught.description>An extract is shutting the user's body down into a deep coma-like state.</VFEM2_ComaDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_ComaDraught.label>coma extract</VFEM2_ComaDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.description>An extract is boosting the user's global work speed while slowing energy loss, but it also raises the risk of a heart attack and leaves them with a major sleep-rate crash afterward.</VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.label>efficiency extract</VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_FertilityDraught.description>An extract is artificially increasing the user's fertility. The boost is strong enough to give even infertile people a chance to become parents.</VFEM2_FertilityDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_FertilityDraught.label>fertility extract</VFEM2_FertilityDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_FocusDraught.description>An extract is heightening the user's ability to learn, letting them gain knowledge faster, eat faster, rest quicker, and gain more psyfocus while the potent phase lasts. The effects reverse when it fades.</VFEM2_FocusDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_FocusDraught.label>focus extract</VFEM2_FocusDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_HealingDraught.description>An extract is improving this person's natural wound regeneration, letting them recover from injuries significantly faster than normal.</VFEM2_HealingDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_HealingDraught.label>healing extract</VFEM2_HealingDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.description>An extract is improving this person's immune system, making them more capable of fighting off diseases and infections at the cost of making them sleepier.</VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.label>immunization extract</VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_InspirationDraught.description>An extract is providing mental clarity, helping the user focus on skills they are passionate about at the cost of diminished combat capability.</VFEM2_InspirationDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_InspirationDraught.label>inspiration extract</VFEM2_InspirationDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.description>An extract is dulling the user's sense of pain at the cost of greatly reduced focus and productivity.</VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.label>painkiller extract</VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_Plant_Grape.description>A hardy wasteland vine that yields dark, bloody fruit when harvested. Its juice is prized for rough trade liquor and survival tonics, and the plant can be harvested repeatedly once established.</VFEM2_Plant_Grape.description>
  <VFEM2_Plant_Grape.label>bloody vine</VFEM2_Plant_Grape.label>
  <VFEM2_PoisonDraught.description>An extract is poisoning the user and rapidly degrading their condition.</VFEM2_PoisonDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_PoisonDraught.label>poison extract</VFEM2_PoisonDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.description>An extract is hardening the user's skin into a built-in layer of armor that resists burns and physical trauma, though it makes them much less attractive.</VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.label>stoneskin extract</VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_StrengthDraught.description>An extract is sharpening the user's strength and reflexes, improving combat ability at the cost of higher social fight chance and a higher mental break threshold.</VFEM2_StrengthDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_StrengthDraught.label>strength extract</VFEM2_StrengthDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_TorturerDraught.description>An extract is causing severe pain to the user, leaving them unable to move. Prisoners lose resistance quickly, and slaves become fully suppressed.</VFEM2_TorturerDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_TorturerDraught.label>torturer extract</VFEM2_TorturerDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_TrainingDummy.description>A straw-stuffed practice dummy lashed to a post. It is little more than a placeholder training fixture, but still lets people work on their form without risking a real fight.</VFEM2_TrainingDummy.description>
  <VFEM2_TrainingDummy.label>training dummy</VFEM2_TrainingDummy.label>
  <Building_ChemshineBarrel.description>A barrel for fermenting rot gut.</Building_ChemshineBarrel.description>
  <Building_ChemshineBarrel.label>rot gut barrel</Building_ChemshineBarrel.label>
  <ChemBoiler.label>crude oil boiler</ChemBoiler.label>
  <Chemlamp.label>oil lamp</Chemlamp.label>
  <ChemlampPost.label>oil lamp post</ChemlampPost.label>
  <Plant_Chemroot.description>A mutated offshoot of ginseng whose roots burrow deep through loose soil until they tap underground oil pockets. Farmers cultivate radseng for the chemfuel-rich sludge in its roots, even though a bad spark can turn the field into an inferno.</Plant_Chemroot.description>
  <Plant_Chemroot.label>radseng</Plant_Chemroot.label>
  <TableFaro.description>A travel-worn gaming table used for caravan games and roadside wagers. Allows up to two players at a time.</TableFaro.description>
  <TableFaro.label>caravan table</TableFaro.label>
  <DeathrestAccelerator.description>A blood pump used to hasten recovery from vitamin deficiency.</DeathrestAccelerator.description>
  <DeathrestAccelerator.label>vitaminpump</DeathrestAccelerator.label>
  <DeathrestCapacitySerum.description>A serum designed to increase the body's ability to withstand Wendigo sickness.</DeathrestCapacitySerum.description>
  <DeathrestCapacitySerum.label>Wendigo Capacity Serum</DeathrestCapacitySerum.label>
  <DeathrestCasket.description>A containment casket for those suffering from cannibal's vitamin deficiency syndrome known as "The Shakes".</DeathrestCasket.description>
  <DeathrestCasket.label>the box</DeathrestCasket.label>
  <GlucosoidPump.description>A blood pump used to create muscle mineral reserves.</GlucosoidPump.description>
  <GlucosoidPump.label>mineralpump</GlucosoidPump.label>
  <HemogenAmplifier.description>A blood pump used to increase hemogen absorption.</HemogenAmplifier.description>
  <HemogenAmplifier.label>proteinpump</HemogenAmplifier.label>
  <Hemopump.description>A blood pump used to help with bloodflow and relax muscles.</Hemopump.description>
  <Hemopump.label>bloodpump</Hemopump.label>
  <PsychofluidPump.description>A blood pump for stabilizing mental symptoms, relaxing their mind and helping them to focus.</PsychofluidPump.description>
  <PsychofluidPump.label>chempump</PsychofluidPump.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothMutagen.description>A brutal FEV-3 mutagenic package that collapses a super mutant subject into a gigantic, tame behemoth war-beast. Only first- and second-generation super mutants survive the process.</WestTek_BehemothMutagen.description>
  <WestTek_BehemothMutagen.label>behemoth mutagen</WestTek_BehemothMutagen.label>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.inspectString>Can be analyzed by a colonist.</WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.inspectString>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.jobString>Analyze FEV culture</WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.jobString>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.description>A stabilized culture kept alive for higher-order Forced Evolutionary Virus work. Guaranteed transformation results when used in procedures.

A colonist can analyze this culture to unlock FEV-3 research.</WestTek_FEVCulture.description>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.label>FEV culture</WestTek_FEVCulture.label>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.inspectString>Can be analyzed by a colonist.</WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.inspectString>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.jobString>Analyze FEV probe</WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.jobString>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.description>A crude pre-refinement sample of Forced Evolutionary Virus growth medium. It is unstable and difficult to handle safely.

A colonist can analyze this probe to unlock FEV-1 research.</WestTek_FEVProbe.description>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.label>FEV probe</WestTek_FEVProbe.label>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.inspectString>Can be analyzed by a colonist.</WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.inspectString>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.jobString>Analyze FEV sample</WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.jobString>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.description>A concentrated viral sample suitable for controlled testing. More stable than raw probe material.

A colonist can analyze this sample to unlock FEV-2 research.</WestTek_FEVSample.description>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.label>FEV sample</WestTek_FEVSample.label>
  <WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.description>A highly stabilized Forced Evolutionary Virus dose reserved for colonist-directed procedures. Guaranteed transformation results when used in procedures.</WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.description>
  <WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.label>isolated FEV dosage</WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.label>
  <WestTek_NightkinMutagen.description>A specialized FEV mutagenic package that stabilizes a Nightkin stealth field in an existing West Tek super mutant. Only first- and second-generation West Tek super mutants can survive the implantation.</WestTek_NightkinMutagen.description>
  <WestTek_NightkinMutagen.label>nightkin mutagen</WestTek_NightkinMutagen.label>
  <WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.description>A cleaner Forced Evolutionary Virus dose suitable for more controlled procedures. Lethality is reduced compared to wild samples.</WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.description>
  <WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.label>refined FEV dosage</WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.label>
  <WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.description>An unstable Forced Evolutionary Virus dose. The virus is not yet controlled enough to produce consistent results.</WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.description>
  <WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.label>unrefined FEV dosage</WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.label>
  <GR_ArchoGrowthcell.label>archotech growth sac</GR_ArchoGrowthcell.label>
  <GR_ElectroWomb.description>A compact incubation tank built to mature unstable West Tek specimens from growth cell to full release.</GR_ElectroWomb.description>
  <GR_ElectroWomb.label>incubation tank</GR_ElectroWomb.label>
  <GR_GenePod.description>A West Tek growth vat where unstable strain templates are drowned in Forced Evolutionary Virus and coaxed into viable test organisms.</GR_GenePod.description>
  <GR_GenePod.label>FEV vat</GR_GenePod.label>
  <GR_GeneticExtractionTable.description>A West Tek extraction rig that renders subject tissue into condensed strain samples for later recombination and vat work.</GR_GeneticExtractionTable.description>
  <GR_GeneticExtractionTable.label>strain extraction table</GR_GeneticExtractionTable.label>
  <GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.description>An advanced West Tek workbench for compounding boosters, stabilizers, and implant-grade augment parts for mutant research.</GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.description>
  <GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.label>augmentation bench</GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.label>
  <GR_GenoframeAwful.label>strain frame (awful)</GR_GenoframeAwful.label>
  <GR_GenoframeExcellent.label>strain frame (excellent)</GR_GenoframeExcellent.label>
  <GR_GenoframeGood.label>strain frame (good)</GR_GenoframeGood.label>
  <GR_GenoframeLegendary.label>strain frame (legendary)</GR_GenoframeLegendary.label>
  <GR_GenoframeMasterwork.label>strain frame (masterwork)</GR_GenoframeMasterwork.label>
  <GR_GenoframeNormal.description>A stabilized West Tek strain frame used by the FEV vat as the baseline lattice for new experimental growth stock.</GR_GenoframeNormal.description>
  <GR_GenoframeNormal.label>strain frame (normal)</GR_GenoframeNormal.label>
  <GR_GenoframePoor.label>strain frame (poor)</GR_GenoframePoor.label>
  <GR_GenoframeUnfinished.label>unfinished strain frame</GR_GenoframeUnfinished.label>
  <GR_GrowthCell.description>A portable containment sac holding an unstable FEV embryo until it can be transferred into a West Tek incubation tank.</GR_GrowthCell.description>
  <GR_GrowthCell.label>FEV growth sac</GR_GrowthCell.label>
  <GR_HumanoidGenetic.label>humanoid strain</GR_HumanoidGenetic.label>
  <GR_InsectoidGenetic.label>insectoid strain</GR_InsectoidGenetic.label>
  <GR_LargeElectroWomb.description>A heavy growth tank for larger prototypes and mature mutant stock that would never fit inside a compact incubation chamber.</GR_LargeElectroWomb.description>
  <GR_LargeElectroWomb.label>large incubation tank</GR_LargeElectroWomb.label>
  <GR_TemplateGenetic.label>blank strain template</GR_TemplateGenetic.label>
  <GR_ThrumboGenetic.label>colossus strain</GR_ThrumboGenetic.label>
  <GR_TissueGrinder.description>A brutal West Tek processing bench that tears specimen tissue down into usable strain templates and recovers viable experimental material from corpses.</GR_TissueGrinder.description>
  <GR_TissueGrinder.label>tissue macerator</GR_TissueGrinder.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.description>A hood worn by followers of the Unity.</WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.label>unity hood</WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.description>A ceremonial robe worn by members of the Unity and other FEV cultists.</WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.label>unity robe</WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.description>Heavier scavenged plating intended for large mutant bruisers expected to absorb return fire.</WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.label>brute armor</WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.description>Crude field armor assembled for ordinary super mutant shock troops.</WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.label>grunt armor</WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.description>Command armor reserved for high-value mutant leaders and vat-born enforcers.</WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.label>master armor</WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.label>
  <WestTek_Centaur.description>Centaurs are hostile FEV predators built from failed human stock and finished into hunting beasts. West Tek's field strain keeps the low-slung, many-limbed silhouette but now uses the tougher Wasteland Compendium combat profile instead of the earlier lightweight animal tuning.</WestTek_Centaur.description>
  <WestTek_Centaur.label>centaur</WestTek_Centaur.label>
  <WestTek_Centaur.tools.0.label>tentacle</WestTek_Centaur.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_Centaur.tools.1.label>teeth</WestTek_Centaur.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.description>Floaters are fast, flammable FEV horrors that drift on their own gas bladders and crowd prey in packs.</WestTek_Floater.description>
  <WestTek_Floater.label>floater</WestTek_Floater.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.tools.0.label>fore mouth</WestTek_Floater.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.tools.1.label>ovipositor</WestTek_Floater.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.tools.2.label>head</WestTek_Floater.tools.2.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.description>An ancient FEV giant restored to West Tek's mutant catalogue.</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.description>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.label>super mutant behemoth</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.0.label>left fist</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.1.label>right fist</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.2.label>head</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.2.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.description>A stabilized behemoth strain conditioned to obey West Tek handlers.</WestTek_TameBehemoth.description>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.label>tame behemoth</WestTek_TameBehemoth.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.0.label>left fist</WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.1.label>right fist</WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.2.label>head</WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.2.label>
  <WestTek_Leather_FEVMutant.label>nodulous skin</WestTek_Leather_FEVMutant.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.description>An oversized steel pipe with a fire hydrant welded to its end.</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.description>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.label>fire hydrant club</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.0.label>pipe</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.1.label>hose</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.1.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy armor used by Whitespring secret service units to break fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>An ornate heavy armor awarded to high-ranking Whitespring secret service operatives. Embedded cryptex threads enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with short-range thrust capabilities for quick movement in urban environments. Urban scouts prefer close-quarters engagements and quick strikes rather than static defense.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>urban scout armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor specialized for cold and arctic operations, fitted with a shoulder-mounted launcher. Arctic marines specialize in breaching cold-climate fortifications.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>arctic marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet used by Whitespring patriots, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>patriot marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of armor used by Whitespring patriots. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and ceremonial, patriot marine armor marks membership and rank. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>patriot marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A beret styled with the Whitespring insignia, worn by enclave personnel of certain ranks.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>Whitespring Beret</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A cap worn by senior Whitespring researchers, denoting a leadership role in cryptid studies.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>Whitespring Scientist Cap</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for cryptid research focus. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>cryptex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for cryptid research focus. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>cryptex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>cryptex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special cryptid-focusing materials. These enhance cryptid sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>cryptex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>cryptex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, formal longcoat used by Whitespring patriots and officers. Embroidered with the enclave sigils, it marks membership and rank.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>patriot longcoat</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.description>Vertibot is a spacer-tech, unmanned aerial vehicle equipped with advanced sensors and a missile payload. Designed for autonomous long-range operations, it's commonly used by the Whitespring Enclave for reconnaissance and bombardment. Its ability to release powerful missile salvos makes it effective against various targets. This vertibot is temporarily disabled due to the recharge cycle.</VFED_Aerodrone.description>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.label>vertibot</VFED_Aerodrone.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>A large, overcharged vertibot battery. Will release a strong electromagnetic pulse when damaged, potentially disabling nearby defenses.</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>vertibot battery pack</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>A large military crate of vertibot munitions. Will explode when damaged, sending armed shells flying in random directions.</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>vertibot munitions crate</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>A multi-use personal stealthboy cloak device engineered based on experimental Whitespring technology. Allows the user to become completely invisible for a brief duration, after which the device requires a short amount of time to recharge.</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>Stealthboy</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing extremely valuable items. May contain critical intel. Due to the special restrictions, only senior Whitespring officials are capable of opening it.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary device capable of intercepting Whitespring communication. When activated, it will begin intel scraping, emitting a pulse in regular intervals. Each pulse has a chance of generating a small amount of intel, but it may also increase your visibility and even alert a Whitespring strike force. After 10 pulses, the machine burns out and triggers a fiery explosion.</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>A crashed Whitespring vertibot.</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>crashed vertibot</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.description>A dossier containing critical information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to plan high-profile assassination attempts, but it can also be exchanged into standard intel via the contraband system.</VFED_CriticalIntel.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary declassifier is a single-use, ultra-tech device consisting of a brain-scan apparatus and a long, thick needle. It is primarily used by Whitespring Brotherhood expeditionaries for data extraction. By inserting the needle into the skull of a senior official, memories can be downloaded from their brain, forming valuable Brotherhood expeditionary intel. The amount of intel received is determined by the rank of the target official. The person affected by a Brotherhood Expeditionary Declassifier dies in the process, and when used on neutral visitors, it is treated as an act of war.</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>Brotherhood declassifier</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>A spacer-tech vertibird designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>Brotherhood vertibird</VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>Brotherhood vertibird (incoming)</VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>Brotherhood vertibird (leaving)</VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>Whitespring propaganda</VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>A chunk of a Whitespring flagship. It seems to have been torn off by some kind of powerful weapon.\n\nHaving landed not long ago, it still contains useful resources which you can acquire by deconstructing it.</VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>Kovac-Muldoon debris</VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>
  <VFED_FuelTank.description>A large fuel tank used to refuel Whitespring vertibirds. Will detonate if damaged beyond a certain point, potentially triggering a chain reaction.</VFED_FuelTank.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>The governmental APC is a formidable armored transport truck, known for its impressive cargo capacity. Its armor is impenetrable, ensuring the safety of its contents throughout transit. Once in motion, the APC’s doors remain sealed until it reaches its predetermined destination. While attempting to loot its cargo is futile due to built-in self-destruct protocols, its robust exterior makes it an ideal shield on the battlefield.</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>governmental APC</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>An advanced shielding apparatus, the Whitespring mega high-shield projects a vast momentum repulsor field, allowing shots to exit but preventing any from entering. Specifically calibrated for high angles, it's adept at deflecting incoming mortar rounds, vertibot strikes and even orbital slicer beams. The unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield. Draws huge amounts of power.</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>governmental mega high-shield</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>An underground hydroponics bay used by the Whitespring Enclave to feed its personnel. Fully automated and connected to water mains, these farms require no labor to operate.</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>Whitespring underfarm</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>
  <VFED_Intel.description>A dossier containing information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to obtain prewar tech from the Brotherhood expeditionaries, or to gain access to quests and even assassination missions on Whitespring officials.</VFED_Intel.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>Decommissioned Whitespring technology since the invention of psylink neuroformers, psychic amplifier upgrades a psylink in the user's mind. It cannot form a psylink by itself, and can only be used by colonists with already present psylink. The user presses the device over the eyes, where it links to the brain directly and restructures part of it. Afterwards, the device disintegrates into worthless ash.</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>cryptid amplifier</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>
  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>A small surveillance buoy usually deployed around temporary convoy stops. Linked directly with a patrolling vertibot, once triggered, it will send down a small missile salvo on its location.</VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing valuables. May contain intel. Opening it requires bypassing several security protocols and takes a short while.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_SupplyCrate.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>A Whitespring computer interface. Linked to the surveillance console, the display bank shows live footage from all surveillance pillars in the sector.</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>
  <VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>A large pillar with a series of sensors, cameras and motion detectors. Thanks to the sophisticated face recognition system, surveillance pillar can detect the presence of Brotherhood expeditionaries in radius and will increase the visibility of whichever faction has sent them. Can be disabled via electromagnetic pulse, or by simply cutting off the power grid.</VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>A compact stack of data discs produced exclusively by the Whitespring Enclave for knowledge transcription. They are primarily designed for preserving information. When ignited, they release a dense cloud of blinding smoke and sparks, capable of engulfing a wide area in flames.</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>data disc stack</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>
  <VFED_Techprinter.description>The Data Printer is a marvel of technological innovation, designed to capture and preserve the intricate knowledge residing within a scientist’s mind. These advanced machines imprint this invaluable information directly onto data discs. Techprints provide foundational knowledge for researchers, shedding light on innovations from more advanced societies.</VFED_Techprinter.description>
  <VFED_Techprinter.label>data printer</VFED_Techprinter.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>orbital cannon capacitor bank</VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>This terminal serves as the primary interface for operating the Orbital Cannon batteries. Equipped with sophisticated controls and targeting systems, the Orbital Cannon Control Station ensures precision and coordination when deploying the formidable firepower of the Orbital Cannons. Operators need to be within its radius to control it.</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>orbital cannon control station</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>Whitespring suite</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.description>A non-alcoholic, pleasantly light, citrusy, and slightly bitter aperitif that owes its flavors and aromas to sweet and bitter oranges, rhubarb, and Whitespring craftsmanship. Its recipe is guarded by Whitespring hospitality offices, and few on the rim have managed to recreate it. Drinking it induces heavy but painless vomiting, completely clearing the stomach and resetting the palate.\n\nWhitespring officials prize aperitif for letting them indulge in even more of the settlement's finest cuisine.</VFEE_Aperitif.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>A high-tech helmet with a solid plasteel-weave shell and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system backed by real-time firing solutions. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>Whitespring light helmet</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>A high-tech suit of powered armor with layered plasteel-weave plates and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system that also assists the user's movement. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>Whitespring light armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>Brotherhood expeditionary armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>Brotherhood expeditionary helmet</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>Whitespring heavy armor</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>Whitespring heavy helmet</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>An exceedingly complex facemask fitted with advanced technology reserved for senior Whitespring scientists. It is designed for designated researchers so they can advance the Whitespring Enclave's needs without rest.\n\nThe inlaid techprint synchronizes with the wearer's brain while they perform research, effectively doubling research speed while restoring rest and recreation.</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>Whitespring scientist helmet</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.label>Whitespring chair</VFEE_GrandChair.label>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>A majestic rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>grand Whitespring rug</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.label>Whitespring table</VFEE_GrandTable.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>Whitespring sign</VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>A stoney bas relief of Whitespring imagery for decorating a floor.</VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>Whitespring slab</VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>An intricate rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>large Whitespring rug</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>orbital beam</VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>Whitespring mirror</VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>grand presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>large presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>small presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.label>Whitespring stool</VFEE_RoyalStool.label>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.label>presidential plaque</VFEE_SteleSmall.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential desk chair can serve as a focus for ceremonial duties and cryptid meditation.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>presidential desk chair</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>A spacer-tech Whitespring gunship designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system. Equipped with a twin-linked autocannon for ground support, these XVB02s often land in the middle of the battlefield to extract stranded troops.</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>XVB02</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.label>Vertibird Landing Beacon</ShipLandingBeacon.label>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>A command staff issued to Whitespring executive officers during inspections, briefings, and emergency command duty. Its cryptex head sharpens cryptid insight and helps regulate neural strain, while the embedded attunement core rejects any wielder outside the assigned chain of command.</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>cryptex command staff</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>
  <GrandThrone.description>An ornate grand chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential grand chair grants the occupant a sense of authority and dignity.</GrandThrone.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>presidential grand chair</GrandThrone.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword refined for Whitespring security officers. Its mono-molecular edge cuts through armor with ease, while an embedded cryptex core sharpens the wielder's cryptid insight and stabilizes the weapon's high-speed response.

The cryptex core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once that bond is established, the blade responds with extreme speed and precision and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>cryptex molecular blade</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored officer's sword wrapped in a sheath of captive plasma. Targets are sliced by the inner edge and burned by the surrounding field, giving Whitespring officers a close-range weapon that can cut and cauterize in the same strike.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the sword responds with unusual speed and control and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>plasma officer sword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A Whitespring warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. On impact it discharges a powerful pulse in addition to the physical blow, making it especially effective against power armor, robots, and other advanced hardware.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the hammer tracks the wielder's timing and strike rhythm with unusual accuracy and rejects any hand outside its assigned operator.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>pulse hammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <Throne.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential chair may be used as a focus for certain duties and ceremonies.</Throne.description>
  <Throne.label>presidential chair</Throne.label>
  <ShuttleIncoming.label>vertibird (incoming)</ShuttleIncoming.label>
  <ShuttleLeaving.label>vertibird (leaving)</ShuttleLeaving.label>
</LanguageData>
