<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AbandonedSettlement.description>The reactor-core signal is coming from somewhere in this settlement. Search the abandoned buildings to recover the core.</AbandonedSettlement.description>
  <AncientReactor.description>An ancient reactor is hidden within nearby ruins. The reactor is cracked and leaking toxic fallout over the whole region. Locate and disable it to obtain a reactor core and stop the fallout.</AncientReactor.description>
  <AncientStockpile.description>You have detected the signal of a reactor core emanating from an ancient underground stockpile. The location is marked on the world map.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</AncientStockpile.description>
  <CrashedMechanoidPlatform.description>The remains of an orbital platform are strewn nearby. Be careful, the wreckage contains hostile robots.

The reactor-core signal is coming from somewhere within the crash site.</CrashedMechanoidPlatform.description>
  <FrozenTerraformer.description>You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The core is powering a malfunctioning ancient terraformer. Its location is marked on the world map.

The terraformer is cooling the local region to dangerously low temperatures. Be prepared for cold weather.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</FrozenTerraformer.description>
  <GravshipWreckage.description>The crash site of a Hellion prototype.</GravshipWreckage.description>
  <GravshipWreckage.label>Hellion wreckage</GravshipWreckage.label>
  <InsectLair.description>You have detected the signal of a reactor core emanating from a cave system deep underground. The entrance is marked on the world map.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to upgrade your Hellion.</InsectLair.description>
  <MechanoidRelay.description>The reactor-core signal is coming from a robot communication relay here. Disassemble it to acquire the reactor core.</MechanoidRelay.description>
  <OrbitalAncientPlatform.description>You have detected the signal of a reactor core.

Be careful - orbital locations are extremely dangerous. Ensure your Hellion is fully enclosed with airtight walls and equip your colonists with vacsuits. Plan your return trip, as living in orbit for long periods is very difficult.</OrbitalAncientPlatform.description>
  <OrbitalMechanoidPlatform.description>You have detected the signal of a reactor core on this platform. There is a heavy robot presence.

Be careful, orbital locations are extremely dangerous. Ensure your Hellion is fully enclosed with airtight walls and equip your colonists with vacsuits. Plan your return trip, as living in orbit for long periods is very difficult.</OrbitalMechanoidPlatform.description>
</LanguageData>