<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Lyons_Shield.description>Shields combine combat prowess with genuine compassion, serving as both warriors and protectors. They embody Elder Lyons' belief that power must be used to defend those who cannot defend themselves.</FCP_IdeoRole_Lyons_Shield.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Lyons_Shield.label>shield of the people</FCP_IdeoRole_Lyons_Shield.label>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Outcast_Defender.description>Defenders are Outcast specialists who excel at both securing technology and eliminating threats. They combine technical expertise with ruthless efficiency, ensuring the mission succeeds at any cost.</FCP_IdeoRole_Outcast_Defender.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Outcast_Defender.label>defender</FCP_IdeoRole_Outcast_Defender.label>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Paladin.description>Paladins are the Brotherhood's finest warriors, masters of power armor combat and tactical leadership. They lead squads into the most dangerous situations and serve as examples of martial excellence.</FCP_IdeoRole_Paladin.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Paladin.label>paladin</FCP_IdeoRole_Paladin.label>
  <FCP_Precept_BoS_Hierarchy_Absolute.description>The Brotherhood's strength comes from discipline and hierarchy. Every member knows their place and their duty. Orders flow from Elder to Paladin to Knight to Initiate without question.</FCP_Precept_BoS_Hierarchy_Absolute.description>
  <FCP_Precept_BoS_Hierarchy_Absolute.label>chain of command is absolute</FCP_Precept_BoS_Hierarchy_Absolute.label>
  <FCP_Precept_BoS_Technology_Control.description>Advanced technology is too dangerous to be left in the hands of the unprepared. The Brotherhood has a sacred duty to preserve, control, and safeguard all pre-war technology to prevent another apocalypse.</FCP_Precept_BoS_Technology_Control.description>
  <FCP_Precept_BoS_Technology_Control.label>technology must be controlled</FCP_Precept_BoS_Technology_Control.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Isolationism.description>The wasteland is full of threats - raiders, mutants, and fools who would misuse technology. The Brotherhood endures by keeping to itself, trading only when necessary, and never revealing our full strength to outsiders.</FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Isolationism.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Isolationism.label>isolation preserves us</FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Isolationism.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Purity.description>The Brotherhood's strength comes from its founding bloodlines. Those born into the Brotherhood carry the legacy of Roger Maxson and the original Mariposa survivors. Outsiders can never truly understand our mission.</FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Purity.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Purity.label>bloodline purity is sacred</FCP_Precept_Lost_Hills_Purity.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Lyons_Protection_Priority.description>Technology is a tool, not an end unto itself. The Brotherhood exists to serve humanity, not just preserve artifacts. Those with power have a duty to shield the weak.</FCP_Precept_Lyons_Protection_Priority.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Lyons_Protection_Priority.label>protect those who cannot protect themselves</FCP_Precept_Lyons_Protection_Priority.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Midwest_Expansionism.description>Territory means resources, recruits, and security. The Midwest Brotherhood does not hide in bunkers - we claim land, build outposts, and protect the people within our borders. A Brotherhood that does not grow will eventually die.</FCP_Precept_Midwest_Expansionism.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Midwest_Expansionism.label>expansion secures our future</FCP_Precept_Midwest_Expansionism.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Midwest_Recruitment.description>The Brotherhood cannot survive on bloodlines alone. Tribals, wastelanders, even former enemies - anyone with skill and dedication can earn their place in the Brotherhood. Recruitment is not weakness; it is wisdom.</FCP_Precept_Midwest_Recruitment.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Midwest_Recruitment.label>worthy outsiders strengthen us</FCP_Precept_Midwest_Recruitment.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Outcast_Isolationism.description>The Brotherhood cannot trust wastelanders with technology or secrets. Outsiders lack discipline, understanding, and loyalty. They're resources at best, threats at worst.</FCP_Precept_Outcast_Isolationism.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Outcast_Isolationism.label>outsiders are liabilities</FCP_Precept_Outcast_Isolationism.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Outcast_Technology_Obsession.description>Nothing is more important than recovering and preserving pre-war technology. Not wastelander lives, not politics, not sentiment. The mission is everything.</FCP_Precept_Outcast_Technology_Obsession.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Outcast_Technology_Obsession.label>technology above all</FCP_Precept_Outcast_Technology_Obsession.label>
  <FCP_Precept_Role_EnclaveOfficer.description>An elite officer of the Enclave, trained in leadership and advanced combat tactics. They excel at research, combat, and maintaining discipline.</FCP_Precept_Role_EnclaveOfficer.description>
  <FCP_Precept_Role_EnclaveOfficer.label>Enclave officer</FCP_Precept_Role_EnclaveOfficer.label>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Khan_Chemist.description>Khan chemists are the lifeblood of the tribe's economy. They produce the chems that the Khans trade for weapons, supplies, and respect. A master chemist is valued as highly as the tribe's greatest warriors.</FCP_IdeoRole_Khan_Chemist.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Khan_Chemist.label>khan chemist</FCP_IdeoRole_Khan_Chemist.label>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Ranger.description>The Rangers, especially the Veteran Rangers, have a fearsome reputation with friend and foe alike. In the Mojave, posters can be seen of them and some NCR troopers believe they "chew nails and spit napalm." Even men of Caesar's Legion speak of the Rangers with respect, calling them "the best the profligates have to offer."</FCP_IdeoRole_Ranger.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Ranger.label>NCR ranger</FCP_IdeoRole_Ranger.label>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Party_Leader.description>The Communist Party Leader is the highest authority in the People's Republic of China, representing the core values of the party and the nation. This role is responsible for guiding the people, maintaining unity, and advancing the country's collective goals and progress.</FCP_IdeoRole_Party_Leader.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Party_Leader.label>PRC party leader</FCP_IdeoRole_Party_Leader.label>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Governor.description>The Governor is the elected leader of the colony, embodying the ideals of prosperity, freedom, and progress. Responsible for guiding citizens, upholding American values, and ensuring a brighter future for all.</FCP_IdeoRole_Governor.description>
  <FCP_IdeoRole_Governor.label>U.S. governor</FCP_IdeoRole_Governor.label>
</LanguageData>
