<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;A s商场 irradiated creature has been captured by wasteland raiders and is being held in their camp. The local settlement is offering payment and a containment cage for its safe rescue - these creatures are valuable for research and companionship in the harsh wasteland.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;A massive apex predator of the wasteland has been captured by heavily fortified raiders who plan to weaponize it against their enemies. This is an extremely 危险 creature, evolved to survive in the harshest post-nuclear conditions. Successfully rescue it and you'll receive state-of-the-art containment technology capable of h老旧ing such a formidable beast.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>任务描述-&gt;掠夺者完成了不可能的任务——他们囚禁了荒原上最可怕的掠食者之一。这个阿尔法样本代表了多年来对辐射和环境危害的进化适应。救援需要大量力量，但回报包括战前军事科学家开发的先进遏制系统。</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>任务描述-&gt;情报报告显示袭击者捕获了可能是其物种的最后一个——一个巨大的荒地庞然大物。这种生物的科学和战术价值怎么强调都不为过。发动全面的救援行动，并拥有后世界末日世界最先进的生物收容系统。</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>任务描述-&gt; 一只中型掠食者已被装备精良的袭击者捕获，他们计划在角斗中使用它。这种生物已经很好地适应了受辐射的荒地，并且可以为任何定居点带来宝贵的补充。营救它并获得强化收容系统作为奖励。</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription-&gt;Raiders have caged a 危险 but valuable wasteland predator, likely planning to sell it to the highest bidder. The local authorities want this creature rescued and properly contained before it falls into the wrong hands. A military-grade cage awaits successful mercenaries.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription-&gt;A formidable wasteland hunter sits trapped in a raider camp, its natural ferocity slowly being broken by captivity. Liberation of this creature would not only be a merciful act but also earn you a professional-grade containment cage - perfect for housing 危险 specimens.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;A s商场 irradiated creature has been captured by wasteland raiders and is being held in their camp. The local settlement is offering payment and a containment cage for its safe rescue - these creatures are valuable for research and companionship in the harsh wasteland.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription-&gt;Raiders have trapped a s商场 wasteland animal for their sick entertainment. Help liberate this innocent creature from their makeshift prison, and you'll be rewarded with a proper cage to keep it safe from the dangers of the post-nuclear world.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>任务描述-&gt;一种无害的荒地生物落入了无情的掠夺者手中。当地人希望在袭击者决定将其作为下一顿大餐之前将其救出。你的奖励：一个坚固的笼子和那些在这个荒凉的世界里仍然关心生命的人的感激之情。</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
</LanguageData>
