<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFET_Agriculture.description>Learn to grow various staple crops. Unlocks growing job.</VFET_Agriculture.description>
  <VFET_Agriculture.label>agriculture</VFET_Agriculture.label>
  <VFET_AnimalHandling.description>Acquire the knowledge to manage, tame, and accommodate animals. Unlocks handing job, as well as animal taming and slaughtering.</VFET_AnimalHandling.description>
  <VFET_AnimalHandling.label>animal handling</VFET_AnimalHandling.label>
  <VFET_Bow.description>Unlock the ability to craft the staple of ranged combat - a short bow.</VFET_Bow.description>
  <VFET_Bow.label>bow</VFET_Bow.label>
  <VFET_Construction.description>Learn the absolute basic techniques of building and structural design. Unlocks the ability to build walls and roofs.</VFET_Construction.description>
  <VFET_Construction.label>construction</VFET_Construction.label>
  <VFET_Cultivation.description>Expand crop variety with more specific, difficult to grow plants, such as smokeleaf or psychoid plant.</VFET_Cultivation.description>
  <VFET_Cultivation.label>cultivation</VFET_Cultivation.label>
  <VFET_Culture.description>Unlock the ability to conduct research, as well as develop ideological thoughts. Unlocks intellectual job.</VFET_Culture.description>
  <VFET_Culture.label>culture</VFET_Culture.label>
  <VFET_Fire.description>Unlock the capability to utilize and manage fire for various purposes. Unlocks firefighting job.</VFET_Fire.description>
  <VFET_Fire.label>fire</VFET_Fire.label>
  <VFET_Furniture.description>Introduce basic furniture crafting for improved living conditions.</VFET_Furniture.description>
  <VFET_Furniture.label>furniture</VFET_Furniture.label>
  <VFET_Hunting.description>Establish methods for effective hunting and resource processing. Unlocks hunting job and allows you to craft throwspikes.</VFET_Hunting.description>
  <VFET_Hunting.label>hunting</VFET_Hunting.label>
  <VFET_Medicine.description>Introduce basic herbal treatment methods.</VFET_Medicine.description>
  <VFET_Medicine.label>medicine</VFET_Medicine.label>
  <VFET_Mining.description>Develop methods to extract resources from the earth using force. Unlocks mining job.</VFET_Mining.description>
  <VFET_Mining.label>mining</VFET_Mining.label>
  <VFET_Tribalwear.description>Learn to craft traditional tribal attire for various purposes.</VFET_Tribalwear.description>
  <VFET_Tribalwear.label>tribalwear</VFET_Tribalwear.label>
  <VFET_Weapons.description>Introduce basic weaponry for defense against enemies.</VFET_Weapons.description>
  <VFET_Weapons.label>weapons</VFET_Weapons.label>
</LanguageData>
