<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Lucky38_MakeSpices.description>Blend broc flower and carrot flower into a preserved seasoning mix fit for Lucky 38 kitchens.</Lucky38_MakeSpices.description>
  <Lucky38_MakeSpices.label>make spices</Lucky38_MakeSpices.label>
  <Lucky38_MakeSyrup.description>Render down maize or xander root into a thick preserved syrup suited for Lucky 38 desserts and bar stock.</Lucky38_MakeSyrup.description>
  <Lucky38_MakeSyrup.label>make syrup</Lucky38_MakeSyrup.label>
  <Lucky38_MakeSyrupFromCarrot.description>Render down carrots into a thick preserved syrup suited for Lucky 38 desserts and bar stock.</Lucky38_MakeSyrupFromCarrot.description>
  <Lucky38_MakeSyrupFromCarrot.label>make syrup from carrot</Lucky38_MakeSyrupFromCarrot.label>
  <VBE_MakeCigarettes.description>Roll coyote tobacco chew into cigarettes.</VBE_MakeCigarettes.description>
  <VBE_MakeCigars.description>Roll coyote tobacco chew into cigars with a bit of gold trim for a more refined smoke.</VBE_MakeCigars.description>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailFine.description>Make a fine atomic cocktail, mixed precisely from multiple ingredients.</VBE_MakeCocktailFine.description>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailFine.label>make fine atomic cocktail</VBE_MakeCocktailFine.label>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailGourmet.description>Make a gourmet atomic cocktail where every factor has been calculated for maximum flavor and body.</VBE_MakeCocktailGourmet.description>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailGourmet.label>make gourmet atomic cocktail</VBE_MakeCocktailGourmet.label>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailLavish.description>Make a lavish atomic cocktail mixed from a wide variety of ingredients and chilled to perfection before serving.</VBE_MakeCocktailLavish.description>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailLavish.label>make lavish atomic cocktail</VBE_MakeCocktailLavish.label>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailSimple.description>Make a simple atomic cocktail quickly mixed from a duo of ingredients.</VBE_MakeCocktailSimple.description>
  <VBE_MakeCocktailSimple.label>make simple atomic cocktail</VBE_MakeCocktailSimple.label>
  <VBE_MakeEnergyDrink.description>Make guarana by fortifying homebrew sarsaparilla with caffeine and a radioactive kick. It delivers fast energy and a later crash.</VBE_MakeEnergyDrink.description>
  <VBE_MakeEnergyDrink.label>make guarana</VBE_MakeEnergyDrink.label>
  <VBE_MakeSodaSyrup.description>Make homebrew sarsaparilla syrup by reducing fruit juice and sweetener into a thick bottling concentrate.</VBE_MakeSodaSyrup.description>
  <VBE_MakeSodaSyrup.label>make homebrew sarsaparilla syrup</VBE_MakeSodaSyrup.label>
  <VBE_MakeSodaSyrupBulk.description>Make homebrew sarsaparilla syrup by mixing natural fruit juice with sugar or preserved syrup. This recipe is much more efficient.</VBE_MakeSodaSyrupBulk.description>
  <VBE_MakeSodaSyrupBulk.label>make homebrew sarsaparilla syrup (efficient)</VBE_MakeSodaSyrupBulk.label>
  <VCE_HotSauce.description>Create hot sauce from peppers or jalapenos. It keeps the same throat-burning kick while fitting the Lucky 38 pantry better.</VCE_HotSauce.description>
  <VCE_Ketchup.description>Create ketchup from tomatoes or tatos. A thick sauce with the same sweet tang Lucky 38 diners expect from the pre-war original.</VCE_Ketchup.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>Create brahmin shroom butter from milk and smokeleaf. Rich, fatty, and wildly irresponsible, it is the sort of condiment only a place like the Lucky 38 would serve on purpose.</VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>make brahmin shroom butter</VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.label>make xander root paste</VCE_WasabiPaste.label>
</LanguageData>