<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VAE_Apparel_HeavyMarineArmor.description>A suit of heavy powered armor. Double layers of plasteel-weave plates are incredibly effective at both projectiles and explosions. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily. A built in blast shield allows wearer to survive a direct rocket hit, upon which the shields require time to recharge.\n\nArmor like this is often used by imperial heavy stormtroopers during mechanoid conflicts, as it transforms a soldier into a humanoid tank.</VAE_Apparel_HeavyMarineArmor.description>
  <VAE_Apparel_HeavyMarineArmor.label>heavy marine armor</VAE_Apparel_HeavyMarineArmor.label>
  <VAE_Apparel_LightMarineArmor.description>A suit of light semi-powered armor. Thin plasteel plates are effective at stopping small calibre gunshots and melee attacks whilst also permitting the user to move quickly and undetected.\n\nArmor like this is often used by imperial scouting parties.</VAE_Apparel_LightMarineArmor.description>
  <VAE_Apparel_LightMarineArmor.label>light marine armor</VAE_Apparel_LightMarineArmor.label>
  <VAE_Headgear_HeavyMarineHelmet.description>A heavy marine armor helmet, with double-layered plasteel plating and a built-in camera with a display HUD to get rid of the weakpoints like visors.\n\nArmor like this is often used by imperial heavy stormtroopers during mechanoid conflicts, as it transforms a soldier into a humanoid tank.</VAE_Headgear_HeavyMarineHelmet.description>
  <VAE_Headgear_HeavyMarineHelmet.label>heavy marine helmet</VAE_Headgear_HeavyMarineHelmet.label>
  <VAE_Headgear_LightMarineHelmet.description>A light marine armor helmet, providing wearer with advanced situational awareness and protection despite having an exposed lower half of the face.\n\nArmor like this is often used by imperial scouting parties.</VAE_Headgear_LightMarineHelmet.description>
  <VAE_Headgear_LightMarineHelmet.label>light marine helmet</VAE_Headgear_LightMarineHelmet.label>
</LanguageData>
