<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VPE_GasCooler.description>An air-cooling machine that releases cooled air around itself. Can be used to create a walk-in freezer. Cannot be adjusted and will automatically lower temperature slightly below zero.</VPE_GasCooler.description>
  <VPE_GasCooler.label>gas cooler</VPE_GasCooler.label>
  <VPE_GasCrematorium.description>A huge stone crematorium which vaporizes corpses with extremely high temperatures. Operates on helixien gas.</VPE_GasCrematorium.description>
  <VPE_GasCrematorium.label>helixien gas crematorium</VPE_GasCrematorium.label>
  <VPE_GasDrill.description>A deep-crust drilling excavator for extracting minerals from deep under the surface. Use a ground-penetrating scanner to detect the resources. This drill will yield stone chunks if no resources are present. Can be repositioned freely.</VPE_GasDrill.description>
  <VPE_GasDrill.label>gas powered excavator</VPE_GasDrill.label>
  <VPE_GasHeater.description>A device that converts helixien gas into radiated heat. It can automatically turn itself on or off to reach a specific target temperature.</VPE_GasHeater.description>
  <VPE_GasHeater.label>gas heater</VPE_GasHeater.label>
  <VPE_GasPipe.description>A pipe that transmits helixien gas.</VPE_GasPipe.description>
  <VPE_GasPipe.label>gas pipe</VPE_GasPipe.label>
  <VPE_GasPipeSub.description>A pipe that transmits helixien gas. This pipe is hidden from view and is protected from gas explosions. Much more expensive to build than regular pipes</VPE_GasPipeSub.description>
  <VPE_GasPipeSub.label>subterranean gas pipe</VPE_GasPipeSub.label>
  <VPE_GasPipeValve.description>Switches gas flow on/off.</VPE_GasPipeValve.description>
  <VPE_GasPipeValve.label>gas pipe valve</VPE_GasPipeValve.label>
  <VPE_GasSmelter.description>Extracts usable metal from slag chunks and other mixed metal items. Operates on helixien gas.</VPE_GasSmelter.description>
  <VPE_GasSmelter.label>helixien gas smelter</VPE_GasSmelter.label>
  <VPE_GasStove.description>A gas-powered stove with an attached countertop for preparing meals.</VPE_GasStove.description>
  <VPE_GasStove.label>helixien gas stove</VPE_GasStove.label>
  <VPE_GasSunLamp.description>An industrial lamp which lights an area brightly enough to grow crops, but consumes a medium amount of helixien gas. Automatically turns itself off at night.</VPE_GasSunLamp.description>
  <VPE_GasSunLamp.label>gas sun lamp</VPE_GasSunLamp.label>
  <VPE_GasTank.description>A large steel tank for gas storage. Will explode if damaged.</VPE_GasTank.description>
  <VPE_GasTank.label>gas tank</VPE_GasTank.label>
  <VPE_HelixienGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming helixien gas. Must be connected to a gas pipe network.</VPE_HelixienGenerator.description>
  <VPE_HelixienGenerator.label>helixien gas powered generator</VPE_HelixienGenerator.label>
  <VPE_HelixienPump.description>An extractor machine mounted on helixien gas geyser. Self-powered, this machine pumps out valuable gas and needs to be connected to other gas-based utilities using the pipe network.</VPE_HelixienPump.description>
  <VPE_HelixienPump.label>helixien pump</VPE_HelixienPump.label>
  <VPE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.description>Produces a large amount of power by consuming helixien gas. Must be connected to a gas pipe network.</VPE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.description>
  <VPE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.label>industrial helixien gas powered generator</VPE_IndustrialHelixienGenerator.label>
</LanguageData>
