<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_BlackTea.description>A particularly bitter tea cut with creamy milk, wakes one up and helps cure ailments.</VBE_BlackTea.description>
  <VBE_BlackTea.label>black tea</VBE_BlackTea.label>
  <VBE_CannibalCoffee.description>For a very particular… refined coffee drinker.</VBE_CannibalCoffee.description>
  <VBE_CannibalCoffee.label>cannibal coffee</VBE_CannibalCoffee.label>
  <VBE_DalgonaCoffee.description>A trendy, newer drink in the world of coffee rumored to originate from far off steamworlds. Coffee granules are rapidly mixed with sugar to form a thick, luxuriously sweet foam. Afterwards the foam is dispersed over deeply chilled milk before drinking. Arguably the perfect drink to sip on while studying or reading.</VBE_DalgonaCoffee.description>
  <VBE_DalgonaCoffee.label>dalgona coffee</VBE_DalgonaCoffee.label>
  <VBE_EarlGreyTea.description>A very strong and semi-sweet fruity tea. Floral notes dance around one's pallet at even the most dull scent. People who finish the drink feel strangely urged to colonize.</VBE_EarlGreyTea.description>
  <VBE_EarlGreyTea.label>earl grey tea</VBE_EarlGreyTea.label>
  <VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.description>An espresso machine brews coffee by forcing pressurized water near boiling point through a "puck" of ground coffee and a filter in order to produce a thick, concentrated coffee called espresso. This particular machine also has the possibility of brewing tea using a separate system.</VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.description>
  <VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.label>espresso machine</VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.label>
  <VBE_GreenTea.description>A light, citrusy green tea spiked with sugar to create a buttery, almost nutty flavor.</VBE_GreenTea.description>
  <VBE_GreenTea.label>green tea</VBE_GreenTea.label>
  <VBE_IrishCoffee.description>Whiskey and coffee blended thoroughly before forming a head and being topped with a spoonful of whipped cream. Perfect for those who just got out of bed and are already wanting to go back to it.</VBE_IrishCoffee.description>
  <VBE_IrishCoffee.label>irish coffee</VBE_IrishCoffee.label>
  <VBE_Kombucha.description>A sugary tea left out to ferment, after fermenting the end product is a sweet and sour, sometimes even naturally fizzy drink known as kombucha. Praised for health benefits, though some remain skeptical. Kombucha acts as a home remedy against the flu, reducing its severity by 5%.</VBE_Kombucha.description>
  <VBE_Kombucha.label>kombucha tea</VBE_Kombucha.label>
  <VBE_LatteCoffee.description>Potent espresso mixed with fresh milk to help ease bitterness before pouring and serving. Lattes have a reputation of being particularly meant for “sophisticated” individuals.</VBE_LatteCoffee.description>
  <VBE_LatteCoffee.label>latte coffee</VBE_LatteCoffee.label>
  <VBE_Lemonade.description>A sweet beverage mixed together with lemon juice, sugar, and water.</VBE_Lemonade.description>
  <VBE_Lemonade.label>lemonade</VBE_Lemonade.label>
  <VBE_LemonCoffee.description>A particularly strange combination. Already acidic coffee garnished with a wedge of more acidic lemon, meant to be juiced into the coffee before quickly consumed while hot. An acquired taste to be sure but lauded by those who do prefer it. Specially indicated to combat intestinal parasites.</VBE_LemonCoffee.description>
  <VBE_LemonCoffee.label>espresso romano</VBE_LemonCoffee.label>
  <VBE_LemonTea.description>A dark tea cut with water, chilled and garnished with a wedge of bright lemon.</VBE_LemonTea.description>
  <VBE_LemonTea.label>lemon tea</VBE_LemonTea.label>
  <VBE_LemonTree.description>A tall tree native to both deserts and tropics alike. Bright, sour lemons grow profusely on this tree, some lemons may even mature early and fall to the ground before the primary harvest is ready.</VBE_LemonTree.description>
  <VBE_LemonTree.label>lemon tree</VBE_LemonTree.label>
  <VBE_MasalaChai.description>A musty, warm, almost woody tea crafted by simple leaves and complex spices. Masala chai acts as a home remedy against wound infections, reducing the severity of a random infection by 5%.</VBE_MasalaChai.description>
  <VBE_MasalaChai.label>masala chai</VBE_MasalaChai.label>
  <VBE_MintCoffee.description>Bitter espresso mixed with cream or milk, then further mixed with mint oil and garnished. Cool and velvety coffee gives way to an even cooler, soothing aftertaste, not to mention great smelling breath.</VBE_MintCoffee.description>
  <VBE_MintCoffee.label>mint coffee</VBE_MintCoffee.label>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.description>Mint leaves are infamous for their cooling effect on one's mouth, as well as ease of seeping into an array of teas or delicately garnishing a dish. Mint leaves rot quite fast.</VBE_MintLeaves.description>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.label>mint leaves</VBE_MintLeaves.label>
  <VBE_MintPlant.description>A plant sprouting into an array of mint leaves. Mint leaves are infamous for their cooling effect on one's mouth, as well as ease of seeping into an array of teas or delicately garnishing a dish. Flourishes indoors and in plant pots, while being pleasant to look at.</VBE_MintPlant.description>
  <VBE_MintPlant.label>mint plant</VBE_MintPlant.label>
  <VBE_MintTea.description>Black tea leaves mixed with mint leaves and deeply steeped, then garnished with additional mint leaves. Leaves your breath surprisingly fresh.</VBE_MintTea.description>
  <VBE_MintTea.label>mint tea</VBE_MintTea.label>
  <VBE_MochaCoffee.description>Coffee mixed with sweet and luxurious chocolate, very fun to drink. Those of snobbish persuasion would argue mocha is more of a dessert than an actual coffee drink.</VBE_MochaCoffee.description>
  <VBE_MochaCoffee.label>mocha coffee</VBE_MochaCoffee.label>
  <VBE_NoonChai.description>An ancient Kashmiri tea mixing tea leaves, a pinch of salt and baking soda, which results in an striking pink beverage that is famous for being not only delicious but also healthy for the body. Used for treating muscle parasites.</VBE_NoonChai.description>
  <VBE_NoonChai.label>noon chai</VBE_NoonChai.label>
  <VBE_PumpkinCoffee.description>Cheap, mass produced generic coffee seeped in an array of spices, oddly excluding any actual pumpkin. Thousands of years ago, this type of coffee was stereotypically consumed by red-haired hipsters with man buns.</VBE_PumpkinCoffee.description>
  <VBE_PumpkinCoffee.label>pumpkin spice coffee</VBE_PumpkinCoffee.label>
  <VBE_Yuenyeung.description>A mixture of coffee and tea. Tea and coffee drinkers respectively set their differences aside while concocting this unholy amalgamation. It is usually served cold, but whether it’s served hot or cold it’s equally confusing to the imbiber.</VBE_Yuenyeung.description>
  <VBE_Yuenyeung.label>yuenyeung</VBE_Yuenyeung.label>
  <VCE_RawLemon.description>An acid and sour tasting fruit. The juice, zest, and pulp are often used in cooking, often on fish and other meat for better taste. Lemon is also used to flavour drinks, such as lemonade, or mixed with tea and coffee.</VCE_RawLemon.description>
  <VCE_RawLemon.label>lemons</VCE_RawLemon.label>
</LanguageData>