<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.description>A reinforced exoskeletal frame designed to support the weight and systems of advanced power armor. On its own, the Power Armor Frame offers basic protection and increased carrying capacity, but it truly shines when fitted with full armor plating. Essential for anyone hoping to operate pre-war power armor suits in the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.label>power armor frame</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_Frame.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.description>The T-45 was the first power armor model deployed in the field, offering soldiers unprecedented protection and strength. Though now considered outdated, its heavy plating and servo-assisted joints still provide formidable defense and enhanced mobility to any wastelander lucky enough to find a working suit.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.label>T-45 power armor</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T45Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.description>The T-51 is a legendary pre-war power armor, renowned for its superior protection and advanced design. Its titanium composite shell and improved servos make it lighter and more durable than earlier models, granting its wearer unmatched resilience and strength on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.label>T-51 power armor</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T51Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.description>The T-60 represents the pinnacle of pre-war military engineering, combining the best features of earlier models with enhanced armor and reliability. Favored by the Brotherhood of Steel, the T-60 offers exceptional protection, advanced environmental sealing, and a menacing presence on any battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.label>T-60 power armor</FCP_Apparel_Power_Armor_T60Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor with a paint scheme inspired by the iconic Abraxo Cleaner branding. Clean, crisp, and unmistakable - this corporate paint job brings pre-war advertising aesthetics to the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.label>T-51 power paints abraxo power armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Abraxo_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor emblazoned with dazzling flame decals that turn heads and strike fear into the hearts of enemies. This iconic hot rod design brings wasteland style to the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>T-51 hotrodder flame job power armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor in bold, vibrant hot pink that makes a statement. This eye-catching color scheme ensures you'll never be overlooked on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>T-51 hotrodder hotpink power armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor with menacing shark teeth painted in the style of pre-war fighter planes. This aggressive paint scheme shows your enemies you mean business.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>T-51 hotrodder shark paint power armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor with colorful Sugar Bombs cereal branding. Sweet and explosive, this playful paint scheme combines nostalgia with intimidation.</FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.label>T-51 power paints sugar bombs power armor</FCP_Apparel_T51_Sugar_Bombs_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>T-60 power armor emblazoned with dazzling flame decals that turn heads and strike fear into the hearts of enemies. This iconic hot rod design brings wasteland style to the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>T-60 hotrodder flame job power armor</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Flames_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>T-60 power armor in bold, vibrant hot pink that makes a statement. This eye-catching color scheme ensures you'll never be overlooked on the battlefield.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>T-60 hotrodder hotpink power armor</FCP_Apparel_T60_Hotrod_Pink_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>T-60 power armor with menacing shark teeth painted in the style of pre-war fighter planes. This aggressive paint scheme shows your enemies you mean business.</FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>T-60 hotrodder shark paint power armor</FCP_Apparel_T60_Shark_Paint_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.description>The X-01 is the most advanced power armor ever developed before the Great War, shrouded in secrecy and rarely seen outside top-secret military installations. Its cutting-edge materials and systems provide unmatched protection, strength, and intimidation, making it the ultimate prize for any wasteland survivor.</FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.label>X-01 power armor</FCP_Apparel_X01_Power_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
