<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.description>A crude, homemade bolt-action rifle assembled from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While slow to fire and lacking in power compared to proper rifles, it is easy to produce and maintain, making it a common weapon among wasteland survivors.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.label>pipe bolt-action</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_BoltAction.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.description>A crude, homemade pistol cobbled together from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While unreliable and lacking in stopping power, it is easy to craft and maintain, making it a common sidearm among the most desperate wastelanders.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.label>pipe pistol</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.description>A crude, homemade revolver assembled from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While unreliable and slow to reload, it is easy to craft and maintain, making it a common sidearm among wasteland survivors.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.label>pipe revolver</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Revolver.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.description>A crude, homemade semi-automatic rifle assembled from scavenged pipes and scrap metal. While unreliable and inaccurate, it offers decent firepower for its simple construction, making it popular among raiders and settlers alike.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.label>pipe rifle</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.description>A crude, single-shot shotgun cobbled together from pipes and scrap. Devastating at close range but slow to reload, it's a favorite among desperate wastelanders who need stopping power on a budget.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.label>pipe shotgun</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Shotgun.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.description>A crude, long-barreled pipe rifle fitted with a makeshift scope. While nowhere near as accurate as a proper sniper rifle, it offers improved range for wastelanders who can't afford better equipment.</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.description>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.label>pipe sniper rifle</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_Pipe_Sniper.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>
