<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <BigMT_FEVSuperMutantAnalysis.description>Μελετήστε έναν αιχμάλωτο τρελό σούπερ μεταλλαγμένο σε μια πλατφόρμα κράτησης. Η μεταλλαγμένη από FEV βιολογία τους διαφέρει από τις τυπικές αλυσίδες έκθεσης σε FEV — η ​​Big MT χρησιμοποίησε μια τροποποιημένη παρτίδα. Η ανάλυσή του θα δημιουργήσει μια βάση για το ερευνητικό πρωτόκολλο West Tek.</BigMT_FEVSuperMutantAnalysis.description>
  <BigMT_FEVSuperMutantAnalysis.label>Ανάλυση υπερμεταλλαγμένων FEV</BigMT_FEVSuperMutantAnalysis.label>
  <BigMT_NightkinContainment.description>Αναπτύξτε διαδικασίες συγκράτησης για το nightkin — σούπερ μεταλλαγμένα δεύτερης γενιάς με ενσωματωμένη τεχνολογία Stealth Boy. Η ψυχική τους αστάθεια καθιστά τον τυπικό περιορισμό αναξιόπιστο. Η επιτυχής μελέτη αποδίδει ταξινομημένα δεδομένα Big MT σχετικά με τη νευρική ολοκλήρωση Stealth Boy και την προηγμένη παρτίδα FEV που χρησιμοποιείται σε άτομα δεύτερης γενιάς.</BigMT_NightkinContainment.description>
  <BigMT_NightkinContainment.label>πρωτόκολλο συγκράτησης nightkin</BigMT_NightkinContainment.label>
  <BigMT_WestTekSynthesis.description>Συνθέστε ένα ελεγχόμενο δείγμα της παραλλαγής Big MT FEV χρησιμοποιώντας δεδομένα που συλλέχθηκαν από τη μελέτη περιορισμού. Αυτή η ταξινομημένη έρευνα τροφοδοτείται απευθείας στο προηγμένο δέντρο διαδικασίας FEV του West Tek και ξεκλειδώνει το επόμενο επίπεδο έρευνας μετάλλαξης FEV. Η διαδικασία σύνθεσης απαιτεί κράμα Saturnite ως καταλυτικό μέσο.</BigMT_WestTekSynthesis.description>
  <BigMT_WestTekSynthesis.label>Σύνθεση West Tek FEV</BigMT_WestTekSynthesis.label>
  <PsychoidBrewing.label>brahmin dung fertilizer</PsychoidBrewing.label>
  <PsychoidBrewing.description>Mix brahmin dung into compost to cultivate brahmin shroom patches, allowing brewing of brahmin shroom kombucha at the campfire or cooking stove.</PsychoidBrewing.description>
  <DrugProduction.label>chem production</DrugProduction.label>
  <DrugProduction.description>Build a chem lab for basic substance synthesis. Further research is required to produce specific chems.</DrugProduction.description>
  <PsychiteRefining.label>brahmin shroom fermentation</PsychiteRefining.label>
  <PsychiteRefining.description>Process harvested brahmin shrooms into dried chips and fermented powder for consumption or trade.</PsychiteRefining.description>
  <WakeUpProduction.label>voodoo brewing</WakeUpProduction.label>
  <WakeUpProduction.description>Brew voodoo, a traditional stimulant concoction that eliminates the need for sleep and sharpens focus for extended work shifts.</WakeUpProduction.description>
  <GoJuiceProduction.label>brahmin shroom distillery</GoJuiceProduction.label>
  <GoJuiceProduction.description>Distill brahmin shrooms into a concentrated combat stimulant that improves shooting, melee, and movement while dulling pain.</GoJuiceProduction.description>
  <PenoxycylineProduction.label>antibiotics cultivation</PenoxycylineProduction.label>
  <PenoxycylineProduction.description>Cultivate and process a local antibiotic compound, preventing common wasteland infections before they take hold.</PenoxycylineProduction.description>
  <VPE_CasterGear.description>Craft ritual clothing, armor, and focus gear suited to occultists and their cryptic revelations.</VPE_CasterGear.description>
  <VPE_CasterGear.label>occult regalia</VPE_CasterGear.label>
  <VPE_EltexGear.description>Recover and tailor advanced relic-woven apparel, staves, and focus gear that amplify cryptid insight.</VPE_EltexGear.description>
  <VPE_EltexGear.label>relic regalia</VPE_EltexGear.label>
  <AtmosphericHeater.description>Build compact Poseidon home reactors that burn bioferrite and drive enormous amounts of heat into the surrounding air.</AtmosphericHeater.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.label>Poseidon home reactor</AtmosphericHeater.label>
  <BioferriteGenerator.description>Build power generators that burn bioferrite as a fuel. Bioferrite keeps its own identity here, but the hardware around it can still read like a desperate late-era Poseidon project.</BioferriteGenerator.description>
  <AirConditioning.description>Build Wattz heaters and Appalachia Freeze coolers to keep rooms livable in any season, or to maintain proper freezer temperatures.</AirConditioning.description>
  <Batteries.description>Develop Poseidon battery banks for storing reserve grid power with the sort of reassuring pre-War safety language that usually meant the opposite.</Batteries.description>
  <BiofuelRefining.description>Build refinery equipment that converts biological feedstock into oil for generators, burners, and industrial systems.</BiofuelRefining.description>
  <DeepDrilling.description>Build Corvega deep drills for extracting resources from underground. You will still need a ground-penetrating scanner to find the best seams.</DeepDrilling.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>Produce Radiation King flatscreen televisions for greater comfort and entertainment.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <HospitalBed.description>Construct Med-Tek hospital beds that improve medical outcomes and turn a rough frontier ward into something closer to a pre-War clinic.</HospitalBed.description>
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.description>Work with advanced microelectronics, unlocking Wattz utility electronics, Radiation King entertainment systems, and more sophisticated industrial control equipment.</MicroelectronicsBasics.description>
  <NutrientPaste.description>Build industrial food dispensers that turn organic feedstocks into edible paste with efficient, relentlessly impersonal pre-War engineering.</NutrientPaste.description>
  <SolarPanels.description>Build Poseidon Civilian Helios Two solar panels for domestic and settlement-scale electricity generation.</SolarPanels.description>
  <SolarPanels.label>civilian Helios Two</SolarPanels.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>Produce Radiation King tube televisions for recreational watching and proper retro-futurist living room culture.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Develop Med-Tek patient telemetry rigs that improve surgery outcomes and long-term recovery when mounted beside a hospital bed.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>Build Poseidon hydro generators on rivers to generate a steady supply of power.</WatermillGenerator.description>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.description>Construct basic Corvega works, including conveyors, underground transfer points, and factory hoppers for automating routine industrial tasks around the colony.</VFE_BasicFactories.description>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.label>Corvega basic works</VFE_BasicFactories.label>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.description>Construct specialized Corvega factory systems capable of manufacturing components, producing alloy stock, and handling other advanced automated production jobs.</VFE_ComplexFactories.description>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.label>Corvega advanced works</VFE_ComplexFactories.label>
  <VHGE_GasExtraction.description>Research propane deposits and the pipe-fed burner systems that let it function as a compact industrial fuel.</VHGE_GasExtraction.description>
  <VHGE_GasExtraction.label>propane extraction</VHGE_GasExtraction.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedBatteries.description>Develop pre-War Poseidon battery units capable of storing large amounts of energy with minimal loss.</VFE_AdvancedBatteries.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.description>Recover advanced Poseidon generation hardware, including solar arrays, hydro units, and high-capacity turbine systems.</VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.description>
  <VFE_IndustrialGenerators.description>Develop heavy-duty Poseidon generator systems built to store more fuel and feed more power into the grid.</VFE_IndustrialGenerators.description>
  <VFE_NuclearPower.description>Restore the harshest end of the pre-War power ladder: compact reactor systems with enormous output and equally severe failure risks.</VFE_NuclearPower.description>
  <VFE_TidalPower.description>Build Poseidon tidal generators on open water to supply steady industrial power from current and surf.</VFE_TidalPower.description>
  <VFE_Manufacturing.description>Establish larger Corvega production benches and powered industrial work centers for high-throughput fabrication, assembly, and finishing.</VFE_Manufacturing.description>
  <VFE_Manufacturing.label>Corvega manufacturing</VFE_Manufacturing.label>
  <VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.description>Develop basic waste recovery systems for turning toxic refuse into usable industrial feedstock.</VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.description>
  <VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.label>Poseidon waste recovery</VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.label>
  <VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.description>Expand waste recovery into sealed reclamation lines for alloy, isotope, and compacted refuse products.</VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.description>
  <VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.label>Poseidon advanced reclamation</VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.label>
  <VTE_HVAC.description>Build a reliable climate-control system connecting Wattz control hardware to Appalachia Freeze cooling equipment and related ventilation components.</VTE_HVAC.description>
  <VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>Construct astrofuel synthesizers that automatically convert chemfuel into astrofuel for Hellion use.</VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>
  <VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>Unlock smaller variants of workbenches designed for the Hellion. Compact enough to fit into tight quarters without sacrificing essential functions.</VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.description>Build Hellion-exclusive furniture such as bunk beds, lockers, and medbay beds to keep crew comfortable and functional during long voyages.</VGE_GravshipLiving.description>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.label>Hellion quarters</VGE_GravshipLiving.label>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.description>Construct Hellion solar panelling, reactor-core power cells, and astrofuel generators to supply energy for Hellion systems.</VGE_GravshipPower.description>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.label>Hellion power</VGE_GravshipPower.label>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>Construct Hellion artillery and point-defense turrets to fight hostile craft in orbit or provide bombardment from the sky.</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>Hellion weapon systems</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>
  <VGE_HeatDissipation.description>Harvest structural heat generated during Hellion launches and dissipate it safely. Excess heat can be converted into usable power.</VGE_HeatDissipation.description>
  <VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>Harvest and store oxygen for use on the Hellion. Unlocks construction of vacsuits and other survival gear needed to operate in vacuum.</VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>
  <AdvancedGravtech.description>Build advanced Hellion upgrades and support systems.</AdvancedGravtech.description>
  <AdvancedGravtech.label>advanced Hellion systems</AdvancedGravtech.label>
  <BasicGravtech.description>Rebuild the Hellion and use it to travel the planet. Without a mooring mast, launching the Hellion will abandon your current map.</BasicGravtech.description>
  <BasicGravtech.label>Hellion airframe</BasicGravtech.label>
  <StandardGravtech.description>Build more complex Hellion components and flight systems.</StandardGravtech.description>
  <StandardGravtech.label>Hellion systems</StandardGravtech.label>
  <RobCo_OS.description>Δημιουργήστε αντίστροφη μηχανική στο ανακτηθέν λειτουργικό σύστημα RobCo και προσαρμόστε το για χρήση σε ένα σύγχρονο δίκτυο μηχανικών. Αυτό απαιτείται για την ανάπτυξη της γραμμής Securitron του RobCo και των βαρύτερων πολεμικών μηχανών RobCo.</RobCo_OS.description>
  <RobCo_OS.label>RobCo ΛΣ</RobCo_OS.label>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.description>Learn to cultivate wasteland ingredients and brew different extracts at an extract lab.</VFEM2_Alchemy.description>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.label>extract brewing</VFEM2_Alchemy.label>
  <Deathrest.description>Research into advanced treatments for the Wendigo Shakes.</Deathrest.description>
  <Deathrest.label>Wendigo Shakes Treatment</Deathrest.label>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation.description>Push the same early mutation work into animal hosts, establishing stable nonhuman FEV handling.</WestTek_FaunaMutation.description>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation.label>fauna mutation</WestTek_FaunaMutation.label>
  <WestTek_FEV1.description>Catalog the first stable Forced Evolutionary Virus handling process. This research only becomes available after a colonist analyzes an FEV probe.</WestTek_FEV1.description>
  <WestTek_FEV1.label>FEV-1</WestTek_FEV1.label>
  <WestTek_FEV2.description>Refine the first-generation process into reliable sample handling and cleaner dosage production. This research only becomes available after a colonist analyzes an FEV sample.</WestTek_FEV2.description>
  <WestTek_FEV2.label>FEV-2</WestTek_FEV2.label>
  <WestTek_FEV3.description>Stabilize isolated Forced Evolutionary Virus cultures for controlled colonist-facing procedures. This research only becomes available after a colonist analyzes an FEV culture.</WestTek_FEV3.description>
  <WestTek_FEV3.label>FEV-3</WestTek_FEV3.label>
  <WestTek_FlatwormMutation.description>Probe low-order mutation pathways using resilient flatworm tissue. This crude foundation lets West Tek culture living FEV growth without immediately escalating to full humanoid conversion work.</WestTek_FlatwormMutation.description>
  <WestTek_FlatwormMutation.label>flatworm mutation</WestTek_FlatwormMutation.label>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation.description>Adapt early FEV culture techniques toward controlled plant-host mutation studies.</WestTek_FloraMutation.description>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation.label>flora mutation</WestTek_FloraMutation.label>
  <GR_GeneticAlteration.description>Recover West Tek tissue processing methods and build the extraction hardware needed to break subjects down into usable strain templates.</GR_GeneticAlteration.description>
  <GR_GeneticAlteration.label>West Tek tissue alteration</GR_GeneticAlteration.label>
  <GR_GeneticCompatibility.label>human strain compatibility</GR_GeneticCompatibility.label>
  <GR_GeneticDuplication.description>Duplicate proven strain templates and preserve valuable West Tek genomes for repeated use.</GR_GeneticDuplication.description>
  <GR_GeneticDuplication.label>strain duplication</GR_GeneticDuplication.label>
  <GR_GeneticEngineering.description>Use West Tek vats, incubation tanks, and booster benches to assemble new test organisms and forced-evolution prototypes.</GR_GeneticEngineering.description>
  <GR_GeneticEngineering.label>FEV prototyping</GR_GeneticEngineering.label>
  <GR_GeneticMechahybridization.label>cybernetic hybridization</GR_GeneticMechahybridization.label>
  <GR_HybridImplantology.label>bio-augment grafting</GR_HybridImplantology.label>
  <VFED_ImperialDefenses.description>Create Whitespring megaturrets: Kontarion, Onager and Palintone, as well as their ammunition.</VFED_ImperialDefenses.description>
  <VFED_ImperialDefenses.label>Whitespring defenses</VFED_ImperialDefenses.label>
  <VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.description>Craft powerful Whitespring mortar shells, such as shrapnel, armor piercing and cluster.</VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.description>
  <VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.label>Whitespring war solutions</VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.label>
  <VFED_RemoteDemolition.label>Whitespring war solutions</VFED_RemoteDemolition.label>
  <VFEE_JanissaryGear.description>Craft heavy trooper armor, light powered armor that’s commonly used by Whitespring recon troops. Note that these also require advanced components.</VFEE_JanissaryGear.description>
  <VFEE_NobleDecorations.description>Build presidential decor like Whitespring rugs, mirrors, grand chairs, Whitespring slabs, candelabras, and more.</VFEE_NobleDecorations.description>
  <VFEE_NobleDecorations.label>presidential decor</VFEE_NobleDecorations.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>Construct a presidential desk chair suited for senior Whitespring officials and their ceremonial duties.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>presidential desk chair</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
</LanguageData>
