<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <ComplexFurniture.description>Build complex furniture like beds, end tables, dining chairs, armchairs, dressers, tool cabinets, billiard tables, and poker tables, vents, sarcophagi, and more.</ComplexFurniture.description>
  <ComplexFurniture.label>complex furniture</ComplexFurniture.label>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>Build complex electronic joy sources such as flatscreen televisions, longwave radios and more.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.label>complex electronics</FlatscreenTelevision.label>
  <MF_BasicFurniture.description>Build simple furniture like simple beds, basic tables, stools, benches and more.</MF_BasicFurniture.description>
  <MF_BasicFurniture.label>basic furniture</MF_BasicFurniture.label>
  <MF_ModernFurniture.description>Learn to build furniture of the modern day that is focused on practicality over beauty, such as roulette tables, wardrobes, dart boards, punching bags and ergonomic beds.</MF_ModernFurniture.description>
  <MF_ModernFurniture.label>modern furniture</MF_ModernFurniture.label>
  <MF_RoyalFurniture.description>Build luxury furniture focused strongly on aesthetics and beauty over practicality, usually only seen in the houses of the wealthy elite. Including poster beds, royal chairs, tables and armchairs.</MF_RoyalFurniture.description>
  <MF_RoyalFurniture.label>artisan furniture</MF_RoyalFurniture.label>
  <MF_WasteDisposal.description>Learn to build small and large bins, objects that slowly clean the environment they are in.</MF_WasteDisposal.description>
  <MF_WasteDisposal.label>waste disposal</MF_WasteDisposal.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>Build basic electronic joy sources such as tube televisions, industrial radios, arcades and more.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <TubeTelevision.label>basic electronics</TubeTelevision.label>
  <VFES_Artillery.description>Learn how to construct field artillery capable of bombarding distant targets within a location's region on the world.</VFES_Artillery.description>
  <VFES_Artillery.label>artillery</VFES_Artillery.label>
  <VFES_ConcealedDefenses.description>Construct submersible barriers and turrets, perfect for indoor defenses.</VFES_ConcealedDefenses.description>
  <VFES_ConcealedDefenses.label>concealed defenses</VFES_ConcealedDefenses.label>
  <VFES_EMPCannon.description>Develop EMP cannons, useful throughout the galaxy with it's ability to stun mechanoids.</VFES_EMPCannon.description>
  <VFES_EMPCannon.label>EMP cannon</VFES_EMPCannon.label>
  <VFES_PulseChargedDefenses.description>Develop advanced charge cannons capable of keeping consistent firing speed.</VFES_PulseChargedDefenses.description>
  <VFES_PulseChargedDefenses.label>pulse-charged defenses</VFES_PulseChargedDefenses.label>
  <VFES_Railgun.description>Adapt spacecraft weaponry as part of your defensive systems.</VFES_Railgun.description>
  <VFES_Railgun.label>railgun</VFES_Railgun.label>
  <VFES_RepulsorTechnology.description>Build shield generators that project energy fields capable of repelling projectiles.</VFES_RepulsorTechnology.description>
  <VFES_RepulsorTechnology.label>repulsor technology</VFES_RepulsorTechnology.label>
  <VFES_SentryGuns.description>Craft self-powered, reliable sentry guns to be utilised in the field.</VFES_SentryGuns.description>
  <VFES_SentryGuns.label>sentry guns</VFES_SentryGuns.label>
  <VFES_SiegeEquipment.description>Construct medieval siege equipment.</VFES_SiegeEquipment.description>
  <VFES_SiegeEquipment.label>siege equipment</VFES_SiegeEquipment.label>
  <VWE_TrenchWarfare.description>Adapt a trench warfare doctrine with a selection of weapons for close-quarters combat.</VWE_TrenchWarfare.description>
  <VWE_TrenchWarfare.label>trench warfare</VWE_TrenchWarfare.label>
  <VFE_Manufacturing.description>Build manufacturing benches and efficient work center.</VFE_Manufacturing.description>
  <VFE_Manufacturing.label>manufacturing</VFE_Manufacturing.label>
  <VFE_Res_AdvancedHydroponics.description>Learn to construct artificial ecosystems, highly advanced terraria which vastly improve upon hydroponics.</VFE_Res_AdvancedHydroponics.description>
  <VFE_Res_AdvancedHydroponics.label>artificial ecosystems</VFE_Res_AdvancedHydroponics.label>
  <VFE_Res_FarmingTechniques.description>Develop a theoretical basis for larger-scale farming operations, including centralized feeding and dedicated scarecrows to keep your crops uneaten.</VFE_Res_FarmingTechniques.description>
  <VFE_Res_FarmingTechniques.label>farming techniques</VFE_Res_FarmingTechniques.label>
  <VFE_Res_Sprinkler.description>Assemble schematics for a device which can automatically water fields, increasing the speed at which crops grow.</VFE_Res_Sprinkler.description>
  <VFE_Res_Sprinkler.label>sprinklers</VFE_Res_Sprinkler.label>
  <VFE_Res_ArtfulDisplay.description>Create beautiful plinths to display artifacts and important colony goods.</VFE_Res_ArtfulDisplay.description>
  <VFE_Res_ArtfulDisplay.label>artful display</VFE_Res_ArtfulDisplay.label>
  <VFE_Res_Holograms.description>Adapt advanced display techniques to showcase three-dimensional models around your colony.</VFE_Res_Holograms.description>
  <VFE_Res_Holograms.label>holograms</VFE_Res_Holograms.label>
  <VFE_Res_Monuments.description>Create massive monuments, centerpieces of your colony, to commemorate those who passed and give inspiration to those still struggling.</VFE_Res_Monuments.description>
  <VFE_Res_Monuments.label>monuments</VFE_Res_Monuments.label>
  <VFE_Res_Obelisk.description>Learn how to sculpt tall, narrow shaped obelisks to commemorate important events.</VFE_Res_Obelisk.description>
  <VFE_Res_Obelisk.label>obelisks</VFE_Res_Obelisk.label>
  <VFE_Res_Pottery.description>Learn how to create beautiful vases and other vessels from simple materials.</VFE_Res_Pottery.description>
  <VFE_Res_Pottery.label>pottery</VFE_Res_Pottery.label>
  <VFE_Res_Rugs.description>Learn how to create beautiful rugs to decorate your colony.</VFE_Res_Rugs.description>
  <VFE_Res_Rugs.label>rugs</VFE_Res_Rugs.label>
  <VFE_Res_Statues.description>Sculpt accurate character-shaped sculptures, inscribed with artistic illustrations.</VFE_Res_Statues.description>
  <VFE_Res_Statues.label>statues</VFE_Res_Statues.label>
  <VFE_Res_WallCarvings.description>Master the techniques of wall carving to create beautiful pillars and reliefs.</VFE_Res_WallCarvings.description>
  <VFE_Res_WallCarvings.label>carvings</VFE_Res_WallCarvings.label>
  <VFE_Res_Wallpapers.description>Construct beautiful walls covered in wallpaper of your desired colour.</VFE_Res_Wallpapers.description>
  <VFE_Res_Wallpapers.label>wallpapers</VFE_Res_Wallpapers.label>
  <MechaniteRestoration.description>Use ultratech mechanites to aid in restoration of objects by constructing a mechanite repair shelf.</MechaniteRestoration.description>
  <MechaniteRestoration.label>mechanite restoration</MechaniteRestoration.label>
  <SpacerElectronics.description>Build advanced electronics usually only seen in advanced colonies and glitterworld buildings.</SpacerElectronics.description>
  <SpacerElectronics.label>spacer electronics</SpacerElectronics.label>
  <SpacerFurniture.description>Build advanced furniture usually only seen in advanced colonies and glitterworld buildings.</SpacerFurniture.description>
  <SpacerFurniture.label>spacer furniture</SpacerFurniture.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedBatteries.description>Build spacertech batteries, capable of efficiently storing large amounts of energy.</VFE_AdvancedBatteries.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedBatteries.label>advanced battery</VFE_AdvancedBatteries.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.description>Construct spacertech green power generators, including advanced solar panels and wind turbines.</VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.label>advanced power sources</VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.label>
  <VFE_GasExtraction.description>Research the helixien gas and it's ability to act as a combustible fuel.</VFE_GasExtraction.description>
  <VFE_GasExtraction.label>gas extraction</VFE_GasExtraction.label>
  <VFE_IndustrialGenerators.description>Build industrial-grade generators, capable of storing significantly more fuel and producing higher power.</VFE_IndustrialGenerators.description>
  <VFE_IndustrialGenerators.label>industrial generators</VFE_IndustrialGenerators.label>
  <VFE_NuclearPower.description>The ultimate power generation method, nuclear power is as sufficient as it is deadly.</VFE_NuclearPower.description>
  <VFE_NuclearPower.label>nuclear power</VFE_NuclearPower.label>
  <VFE_TidalPower.description>Build tidal generators on water to produce a large volume of sustainable green energy.</VFE_TidalPower.description>
  <VFE_TidalPower.label>tidal power</VFE_TidalPower.label>
  <DecalsProps.description>Unlocks a large number of customisable floor decals.</DecalsProps.description>
  <DecalsProps.label>decals</DecalsProps.label>
  <FarmProps.description>Grants access to a selection of farming related props.</FarmProps.description>
  <FarmProps.label>farm props</FarmProps.label>
  <FurnitureProps.description>Gives access too a variety of furniture props.</FurnitureProps.description>
  <FurnitureProps.label>furniture</FurnitureProps.label>
  <IndustrialProps.description>Unlocks industrial props and decorations.</IndustrialProps.description>
  <IndustrialProps.label>industrial props</IndustrialProps.label>
  <KitchenProps.description>Unlocks a selection of kitchen-based props.</KitchenProps.description>
  <KitchenProps.label>kitchen props</KitchenProps.label>
  <MedievalProps.description>Unlocks a number of medieval inspired decorations.</MedievalProps.description>
  <MedievalProps.label>medieval props</MedievalProps.label>
  <PlantProps.description>Unlocks a selection of fake plants and trees.</PlantProps.description>
  <PlantProps.label>plant props</PlantProps.label>
  <PowerProps.description>Unlocks a number of generators and other power-based props.</PowerProps.description>
  <PowerProps.label>power props</PowerProps.label>
  <SpacerProps.description>Unlocks a large number of spacer inspired props and decorations.</SpacerProps.description>
  <SpacerProps.label>spacer props</SpacerProps.label>
  <SpaceshipProps.description>Unlocks a selection of spaceship props.</SpaceshipProps.description>
  <SpaceshipProps.label>spaceship props</SpaceshipProps.label>
  <VehicleProps.description>Unlocks a wide selection of land vehicle props.</VehicleProps.description>
  <VehicleProps.label>vehicle props</VehicleProps.label>
  <VCE_Canning.description>Canning is a method of preserving food in which the food contents are processed and sealed in an airtight container (jars like Mason jars, and steel and tin cans). Canning provides a shelf life of several years. A freeze-dried canned product, such as canned dried lentils, could last as long as 30 years in an edible state. This research gives access to the canning machine.</VCE_Canning.description>
  <VCE_Canning.label>canning</VCE_Canning.label>
  <VCE_CheeseMaking.description>Cheesemaking (or caseiculture) is the craft of making cheese. The production of cheese, like many other food preservation processes, allows the nutritional and economic value of milk to be preserved in concentrated form. Cheesemaking allows the production of the cheese with diverse flavors and consistencies. This research gives access to the cheese press.</VCE_CheeseMaking.description>
  <VCE_CheeseMaking.label>cheese making</VCE_CheeseMaking.label>
  <VCE_CondimentsResearch.description>A condiment is a spice, sauce, or preparation that is added to food, either after or during cooking, to impart a specific flavor, to enhance the flavor, or to complement the dish. All condiments are created at the condiment prep table.</VCE_CondimentsResearch.description>
  <VCE_CondimentsResearch.label>food condiments</VCE_CondimentsResearch.label>
  <VCE_DeepFrying.description>Deep frying (also referred to as deep fat frying) is a cooking method in which food is submerged in hot fat, most commonly oil, as opposed to the shallow oil used in conventional frying done in a frying pan. This research gives access to the deep fryer.</VCE_DeepFrying.description>
  <VCE_DeepFrying.label>deep frying</VCE_DeepFrying.label>
  <VCE_Grilling.description>Grilling is a form of cooking that involves dry heat applied to the surface of food, commonly from above, below or from the side. Grilling usually involves a significant amount of direct, radiant heat, and tends to be used for cooking meat and vegetables quickly. This research gives access to the grill.</VCE_Grilling.description>
  <VCE_Grilling.label>grilling</VCE_Grilling.label>
  <VCE_SoupCooking.description>Soup is a primarily liquid food, generally served warm or hot, that is made by combining ingredients of meat or vegetables with stock, or water. Hot soups are additionally characterized by boiling solid ingredients in liquids in a pot until the flavors are extracted. This research also gives access to the electric pot necessary to cook soups.</VCE_SoupCooking.description>
  <VCE_SoupCooking.label>soup cooking</VCE_SoupCooking.label>
  <VCE_StewCooking.description>Stew is a form of a very nourishing meal, cooked in bulk over fire. This research also gives access to the wood-fired pot necessary to cook stews.</VCE_StewCooking.description>
  <VCE_StewCooking.label>stew cooking</VCE_StewCooking.label>
  <VCE_SoyFermentation.description>Soybean fermentation is the process by which soybeans are submitted to a chemical breakdown by bacteria, yeasts, or other microorganisms, transforming into new products. This research gives access to the soy sauce fermenter.</VCE_SoyFermentation.description>
  <VCE_SoyFermentation.label>soybean fermentation</VCE_SoyFermentation.label>
  <VBE_LiquorBrewing.description>Utilize advanced brewing techniques that allow distillation and fermenting of harder spirits with unique effects.</VBE_LiquorBrewing.description>
  <VBE_LiquorBrewing.label>liquor brewing</VBE_LiquorBrewing.label>
  <VBE_MixologyResearch.description>Allows construction of advanced machines that utilize electricity for perfect fermenting, industrial bottling, and the mixing of cocktails at the bar workbench.</VBE_MixologyResearch.description>
  <VBE_MixologyResearch.label>mixology</VBE_MixologyResearch.label>
  <VBE_Printing.description>Build a typwriter, which allows your colonists to write books significantly faster, as well as create newspapers for temporary joy boost.</VBE_Printing.description>
  <VBE_Printing.label>printing</VBE_Printing.label>
  <VBE_Writing.description>Construct a writing desk and have your colonists write books that pass their knowledge to other members of their society.</VBE_Writing.description>
  <VBE_Writing.label>writing</VBE_Writing.label>
  <VCE_SucculentSowing.description>Sow the beautiful, long lasting succulents.</VCE_SucculentSowing.description>
  <VCE_SucculentSowing.label>succulent sowing</VCE_SucculentSowing.label>
  <VBE_EspressoMachine.description>A more sophisticated method of brewing coffees and teas by using pressurized water.</VBE_EspressoMachine.description>
  <VBE_EspressoMachine.label>espresso machine</VBE_EspressoMachine.label>
  <VCE_VegMilkExtraction.description>Vegetable milk extraction allows the colonists to extract milk from rice, oats, almonds, coconuts and soybeans.</VCE_VegMilkExtraction.description>
  <VCE_VegMilkExtraction.label>vegetable milk</VCE_VegMilkExtraction.label>
  <GR_GeneticAlteration.description>Craft the Tissue Grinder and Genome Extractor Table to create genoframes and genomes respectively.</GR_GeneticAlteration.description>
  <GR_GeneticAlteration.label>genetic alteration</GR_GeneticAlteration.label>
  <GR_GeneticCompatibility.description>Grow bio-engineered implants for humans on the Implant augmentator.</GR_GeneticCompatibility.description>
  <GR_GeneticCompatibility.label>genetic compatibility</GR_GeneticCompatibility.label>
  <GR_GeneticDuplication.description>Manufacture Template Genomes through the Genome Recombinator and duplicate existing Genomes.</GR_GeneticDuplication.description>
  <GR_GeneticDuplication.label>genetic duplication</GR_GeneticDuplication.label>
  <GR_GeneticEngineering.description>Create new hybrids with the Genomorpher, gestate them in an Electrowomb and create boosters at the Genetics Tinkering Table.</GR_GeneticEngineering.description>
  <GR_GeneticEngineering.label>genetic creation</GR_GeneticEngineering.label>
  <GR_GeneticMechahybridization.description>Create Biomechanical Lab beacons to find mechahybridizers, and construct mechahybrid antennas to support more mechanoid hybrids.</GR_GeneticMechahybridization.description>
  <GR_GeneticMechahybridization.label>genetic mechahybridization</GR_GeneticMechahybridization.label>
  <GR_HybridImplantology.description>Grow bio-engineered implants for hybrids and animals alike on the Implant augmentator.</GR_HybridImplantology.description>
  <GR_HybridImplantology.label>genetic augmentation</GR_HybridImplantology.label>
  <VPE_CasterGear.description>Craft simple psycaster apparel, armor and gear using eltex.</VPE_CasterGear.description>
  <VPE_CasterGear.label>caster gear</VPE_CasterGear.label>
  <VPE_EltexGear.description>Tailor and craft complex eltex apparel, capable of improving psychic focus of your psycasters, as well as an eltex-infused staff.</VPE_EltexGear.description>
  <VPE_EltexGear.label>eltex gear</VPE_EltexGear.label>
  <VHGE_GasExtraction.description>Research the helixien gas and it's ability to act as a combustible fuel.</VHGE_GasExtraction.description>
  <VHGE_GasExtraction.label>gas extraction</VHGE_GasExtraction.label>
  <VFEE_JanissaryGear.description>Craft janissary armor, light powered armor that’s commonly used by imperial recon troops. Note that these also require advanced components.</VFEE_JanissaryGear.description>
  <VFEE_JanissaryGear.label>janissary gear</VFEE_JanissaryGear.label>
  <VFEE_NobleDecorations.description>Build noble decorations like royal rugs, mirrors, grand chairs, imperial slabs, candelabras, and more.</VFEE_NobleDecorations.description>
  <VFEE_NobleDecorations.label>noble decorations</VFEE_NobleDecorations.label>
  <VFEE_PipeOrgans.description>Craft the pipe organs, an incredibly advanced and intricate stationary musical instrument.</VFEE_PipeOrgans.description>
  <VFEE_PipeOrgans.label>pipe organs</VFEE_PipeOrgans.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>Construct the most grand, most beautiful stellic throne for your high ranking nobility.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>stellic throne</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
  <VVE_AerialVehicles.description>Learn to construct vehicles capable of travelling above the ground, such as a mosquito helicopter and a smuggler cargo airplane.</VVE_AerialVehicles.description>
  <VVE_AerialVehicles.label>aerial vehicles</VVE_AerialVehicles.label>
  <VVE_BasicVehicles.description>Learn to construct basic, inefficient vehicles, from prowler buggy to roadkill single-person tanks.</VVE_BasicVehicles.description>
  <VVE_BasicVehicles.label>basic vehicles</VVE_BasicVehicles.label>
  <VVE_CombatVehicles.description>Learn to construct complex combat vehicles, such as bulldog battle tanks, tango armored personnel carriers and warbird combat airplanes.</VVE_CombatVehicles.description>
  <VVE_CombatVehicles.label>combat vehicles</VVE_CombatVehicles.label>
  <VVE_ComplexVehicles.description>Learn to construct complex vehicles, such as wagons, roadrunners and snatchers, using the components you can easily fabricate.</VVE_ComplexVehicles.description>
  <VVE_ComplexVehicles.label>complex vehicles</VVE_ComplexVehicles.label>
  <VFED_ImperialDefenses.description>Create imperial megaturrets: Kontarion, Onager and Palintone, as well as their ammunition.</VFED_ImperialDefenses.description>
  <VFED_ImperialDefenses.label>imperial defenses</VFED_ImperialDefenses.label>
  <VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.description>Craft powerful imperial mortar shells, such as shrapnel, armor piercing and cluster.</VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.description>
  <VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.label>imperial war solutions</VFED_ImperialWarSolutions.label>
  <VFED_RemoteDemolition.description>Build advanced explosive traps with remote detonation mechanism.</VFED_RemoteDemolition.description>
  <VFED_RemoteDemolition.label>imperial war solutions</VFED_RemoteDemolition.label>
  <VVE_BattleTanks.description>Learn to build heavily armored battle tanks such as the marshal, equipped with a variety of weapons. In order to research this project, a marshal wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_BattleTanks.description>
  <VVE_BattleTanks.label>battle tanks</VVE_BattleTanks.label>
  <VVE_BigRigs.description>Learn to build large, long-distance trucks such as the big rig or hermano, capable of delivering large amounts of cargo over extremely long distances. In order to research this project, a big rig or hermano wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_BigRigs.description>
  <VVE_BigRigs.label>big rigs</VVE_BigRigs.label>
  <VVE_Cherokee.description>Learn to build a dual-rotor cargo helicopter called cherokee, capable of delivering thousands of kilograms of resources via air routes. In order to research this project, a cherokee wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_Cherokee.description>
  <VVE_Cherokee.label>cherokee</VVE_Cherokee.label>
  <VVE_ClassicCars.description>Learn to build fancy, classic cars such as the springbok. In order to research this project, a springbok wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_ClassicCars.description>
  <VVE_ClassicCars.label>classic cars</VVE_ClassicCars.label>
  <VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.description>Learn to build light armored vehicles such as the paladin or the badger, that can transport soldiers efficiently and effectively whilst providing them with fire support. In order to research this project, a paladin or badger wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.description>
  <VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.label>light armored vehicles</VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.label>
  <VVE_Louie.description>Learn to build a large transport helicopter called louie, that can deliver both cargo and troops over long distances with ease. In order to research this project, a louie wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_Louie.description>
  <VVE_Louie.label>louie</VVE_Louie.label>
  <VVE_OffroadJeeps.description>Learn to build offroad jeeps such as the nomad, that can traverse any terrain with ease. In order to research this project, a nomad wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_OffroadJeeps.description>
  <VVE_OffroadJeeps.label>offroad jeeps</VVE_OffroadJeeps.label>
  <VVE_RocketArtillery.description>Learn to build multiple launch rocket systems with the ability to blanket a whole area with missiles. In order to research this project, a burya wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_RocketArtillery.description>
  <VVE_RocketArtillery.label>rocket artillery</VVE_RocketArtillery.label>
  <VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.description>Learn to build a powerful, self-propelled artillery such as the famous udar, capable of raining artillery fire on enemies on the local map. In order to research this project, an udar wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.description>
  <VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.label>self-propelled artillery</VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.label>
  <VVE_SiegePods.description>Learn to build powerful siege pods that act as temporary, moving bases during assaults in enemy territory. In order to research this project, a goliath wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_SiegePods.description>
  <VVE_SiegePods.label>siege pods</VVE_SiegePods.label>
  <VVE_SuperCars.description>Learn to build fast and luxurious supercars such as the lightning. In order to research this project, a lightning wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_SuperCars.description>
  <VVE_SuperCars.label>supercars</VVE_SuperCars.label>
  <VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.description>Discover basic recycling, giving you the ability to recycle wastepacks into a variety of different resources.</VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.description>
  <VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.label>basic recycling</VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.label>
  <VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.description>Learn to recycle isotopacks and alloypacks into new resources and build garbage compactors to craft trashbricks.</VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.description>
  <VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.label>complex recycling</VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.label>
  <VTE_HVAC.description>Build a reliable air conditioning system connecting AC control units and compressors to AC units via air ducts.</VTE_HVAC.description>
  <VTE_HVAC.label>HVAC</VTE_HVAC.label>
  <AM_RecyclingAssembly.description>Learning how to basic disassemble and reassemble weapons, assembly is an easy task when using standardized components.</AM_RecyclingAssembly.description>
  <AM_RecyclingAssembly.label>recycling assembly</AM_RecyclingAssembly.label>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.description>Learn to plant various alchemical ingredients and combining them into different draughts at an alchemy lab.</VFEM2_Alchemy.description>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;alchemical studies</VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;unlocked the mysteries of transmutation and concocted potent elixirs</VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;discovered a rare herb, rumored to grant eternal youth</VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;became a feared poisoner, selling deadly brews to the highest bidder</VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;brewing alchemical draughts</VFEM2_Alchemy.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_Alchemy.label>alchemy</VFEM2_Alchemy.label>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.description>Learn how to keep bees to produce honey from nearby plants. Honey can be used in creation of sweetrolls and mead.</VFEM2_Beekeeping.description>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;apiculture</VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;studied the intricate social structures of bees</VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;cultivated vast apiaries, supplying nobles with the finest honey</VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;perfected the art of mead-making, becoming a renowned brewer</VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;tending to beehives</VFEM2_Beekeeping.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_Beekeeping.label>beekeeping</VFEM2_Beekeeping.label>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.description>Learn to build various tools and devices to enhance the productivity of the workbenches.</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.description>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;advanced craftsmanship</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;refined blacksmithing techniques, crafting tools of unmatched quality</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;introduced mechanical innovations that revolutionized production</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;formed a powerful guild, controlling the flow of masterwork goods</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;improving workshop efficiency</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.label>complex workshops</VFEM2_ComplexWorkshops.label>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.description>Adorn the colors of your faction and construct decorative banners and heraldic rugs.</VFEM2_Heraldry.description>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;heraldic traditions</VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;designed banners that struck fear or awe into the hearts of foes</VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;crafted family crests, immortalizing legacies in fabric and stone</VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;led the creation of a grand hall adorned with noble insignia</VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;designing heraldic symbols</VFEM2_Heraldry.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_Heraldry.label>heraldry</VFEM2_Heraldry.label>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.description>Craft ancient, chempowder operated ranged weapons that utilise the matchlock mechanics, such as arquebuses and hand cannons.</VFEM2_Matchlocks.description>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;early firearms</VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;perfected the art of matchlock guns, bringing an age of gunpowder warfare</VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;supplied mercenaries with devastating ranged weaponry</VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;unleashed fire and thunder on the battlefield, changing warfare forever</VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;crafting matchlock firearms</VFEM2_Matchlocks.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_Matchlocks.label>matchlocks</VFEM2_Matchlocks.label>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.description>Learn to construct various medieval structures, including cloth walls.</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.description>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;medieval construction</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;oversaw the construction of towering castles and bustling townships</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;engineered grand cathedrals, marvels of medieval craftsmanship</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;developed secret passages and fortifications for clandestine schemes</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;designing medieval structures</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.label>medieval architecture</VFEM2_MedievalArchitecture.label>
  <VFEM2_Wine.description>Plant grapes which can then be used to create wine must and eventually, high quality wine.</VFEM2_Wine.description>
  <VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;viniculture</VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;established a flourishing vineyard on the sun-kissed slopes</VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;experimented with fermentation techniques, crafting exquisite vintages</VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;became infamous for a revelry-fueled dynasty of wine merchants</VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;cultivating grapes and fermenting wine</VFEM2_Wine.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFEM2_Wine.label>wine</VFEM2_Wine.label>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.description>Haute cuisine is the pinnacle of culinary artistry, emphasizing meticulous preparation, refined techniques, and exquisite presentation. It transforms the finest ingredients into visually stunning and harmoniously balanced dishes, elevating dining to an experience of sophistication. This research also unlocks the haute section, a specialized workstation for crafting these masterful creations.</VCE_HauteCuisine.description>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;culinary artistry</VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;perfected the delicate balance of flavors, elevating cooking to an art form</VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;trained under master chefs, mastering techniques passed down through generations</VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;founded an elite dining establishment, attracting nobles and connoisseurs alike</VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;crafting exquisite haute dishes</VCE_HauteCuisine.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VCE_HauteCuisine.label>haute cuisine</VCE_HauteCuisine.label>
  <Therapy.description>Build a therapy couch and chair and treat the wellbeing of your colonists.</Therapy.description>
  <Therapy.label>therapy</Therapy.label>
  <VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>Construct astrofuel synthesizers that automatically convert chemfuel into astrofuel for gravship use.</VGE_AstrofuelRefining.description>
  <VGE_AstrofuelRefining.label>astrofuel refining</VGE_AstrofuelRefining.label>
  <VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>Unlock smaller variants of workbenches designed for gravships. Compact enough to fit into tight quarters without sacrificing essential functions.</VGE_CompactWorkspaces.description>
  <VGE_CompactWorkspaces.label>compact workspaces</VGE_CompactWorkspaces.label>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.description>Build gravship-exclusive furniture such as bunk beds, lockers, and medbay beds to keep crew comfortable and functional in long voyages.</VGE_GravshipLiving.description>
  <VGE_GravshipLiving.label>gravship living</VGE_GravshipLiving.label>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.description>Construct gravship solar panelling, gravcore power cells, and astrofuel generators to supply energy for gravship systems.</VGE_GravshipPower.description>
  <VGE_GravshipPower.label>gravship power</VGE_GravshipPower.label>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>Construct gravship artillery and point defense turrets to fight other ships in orbit or provide bombardments from the sky.</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.description>
  <VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>gravship weaponry</VGE_GravshipWeaponry.label>
  <VGE_HeatDissipation.description>Harvest structural heat generated during gravship launches and dissipate it safely. Excess heat can be converted into usable power. Heatsink capacity and power output is increased.</VGE_HeatDissipation.description>
  <VGE_HeatDissipation.label>heat dissipation</VGE_HeatDissipation.label>
  <VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>Harvest and store oxygen for use on gravships. Unlocks construction of vacsuits and other survival gear needed to operate in vacuum.</VGE_OxygenNetwork.description>
  <VGE_OxygenNetwork.label>oxygen network</VGE_OxygenNetwork.label>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.description>Construct basic factories, conveyor belts with splitters, mergers, filters and underground conveyors, as well as factory hoppers to automate certain tasks around the colony.</VFE_BasicFactories.description>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;industrial efficiency</VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;pioneered the first integrated production lines</VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;transformed a small workshop into a cornerstone of the industrial revolution</VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;saw beyond the chaos of factory floors to the beauty of synchronized machinery</VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;laying the groundwork for modern manufacturing</VFE_BasicFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.label>basic factories</VFE_BasicFactories.label>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.description>Construct complex, specific factories capable of manufacturing components, creating plasteel alloy and much more.</VFE_ComplexFactories.description>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>subject-&gt;automated fabrication</VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>subject_story-&gt;unveiled the potential of autonomous machines in electronics production</VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>subject_story-&gt;bridged the gap between raw materials and advanced technology</VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>subject_story-&gt;revolutionized the production of high-tech components and alloys, making them accessible to all</VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.3>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>subject_gerund-&gt;streamlining the creation of electronics and alloys</VFE_ComplexFactories.generalRules.rulesStrings.4>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.label>complex factories</VFE_ComplexFactories.label>
  <AdvancedShowers.description>Build powered showers which halves the time spent showering and improves comfort.</AdvancedShowers.description>
  <AdvancedShowers.label>power showers</AdvancedShowers.label>
  <AdvancedToilets.description>Build smart toilets which are twice as water efficient as a standard toilets and provide more comfort.</AdvancedToilets.description>
  <AdvancedToilets.label>smart toilets</AdvancedToilets.label>
  <CentralHeating.description>Build central heating systems with radiators, hot water tanks, boilers and thermostats.</CentralHeating.description>
  <CentralHeating.label>central heating</CentralHeating.label>
  <DeepWells.description>Drill deeper wells to access a much larger area of ground water.</DeepWells.description>
  <DeepWells.label>deep wells</DeepWells.label>
  <ElectricPumps.description>Powered water pumps for pressurised continuous water pumping.</ElectricPumps.description>
  <ElectricPumps.label>electric pumps</ElectricPumps.label>
  <FireSuppression.description>Build sprinklers that when activated can suppress fires.</FireSuppression.description>
  <FireSuppression.label>fire suppression</FireSuppression.label>
  <HotTubs.description>Build hot tubs which can be used for hydrotherapy, relaxation and pleasure.</HotTubs.description>
  <HotTubs.label>hot tubs</HotTubs.label>
  <Irrigation.description>Build sprinklers that can irrigate soil to improve fertility.</Irrigation.description>
  <Irrigation.label>irrigation</Irrigation.label>
  <LargeWaterPumps.description>Build industrial scale water pumps and storage tanks.</LargeWaterPumps.description>
  <LargeWaterPumps.label>industrial scale pumps</LargeWaterPumps.label>
  <LogBoilers.description>Build log boilers which can be used to heat rooms and placed adjacent to baths to heat bathwater.</LogBoilers.description>
  <LogBoilers.label>heating</LogBoilers.label>
  <ModernFixtures.description>Build modern style bathroom fixtures like toilets and showers.</ModernFixtures.description>
  <ModernFixtures.label>modern bathroom fixtures</ModernFixtures.label>
  <MultiSplitAirCon.description>Build multi-split air conditioning systems with outdoor units piped to indoor units and freezers.</MultiSplitAirCon.description>
  <MultiSplitAirCon.label>multi-split air conditioning</MultiSplitAirCon.label>
  <Plumbing.description>Use pipes, plumbing fixtures, storage tanks, windwells and other apparatuses to deliver and drain water and sewage.</Plumbing.description>
  <Plumbing.label>plumbing</Plumbing.label>
  <SepticTanks.description>Build septic tanks which accumulate sewage and provide moderate treatment of sewage.</SepticTanks.description>
  <SepticTanks.label>septic tanks</SepticTanks.label>
  <SewageSludgeComposting.description>When properly treated and processed, sewage sludge becomes biosolids that offer a small boost to terrain fertility, useful for harsh environments with limited space to grow. Biosolids also produce a large boost to the fertility of sand which can make it fertile when combined with irrigation.</SewageSludgeComposting.description>
  <SewageSludgeComposting.label>sewage sludge composting</SewageSludgeComposting.label>
  <SewageTreatment.description>Build large sewage treatment systems which accumulate large amounts of sewage and provides fast treatment of sewage.</SewageTreatment.description>
  <SewageTreatment.label>sewage treatment</SewageTreatment.label>
  <SwimmingPools.description>Build swimming pools.</SwimmingPools.description>
  <SwimmingPools.label>swimming pools</SwimmingPools.label>
  <WashingMachines.description>Build washing machines that can wash clothes so well that you couldn't even tell someone died wearing it!.</WashingMachines.description>
  <WashingMachines.label>washing machines</WashingMachines.label>
  <WaterFiltration.description>Build water filtration systems which treats the water supply eliminating the risk of disease.</WaterFiltration.description>
  <WaterFiltration.label>water filtration</WaterFiltration.label>
</LanguageData>
