<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AnimusStone.description>A resonant cryptic stone studied by Whitespring researchers. It increases cryptid meditation focus and is often used in Enclave research facilities.</AnimusStone.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>cryptic stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring cryptid forces. Whitespring operatives use these to amplify cryptid focus during ritualized study.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine used by cryptid researchers to focus meditation and study. These shrines strengthen cryptid-focused meditation for Whitespring operatives.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy armor used by Whitespring secret service units to break fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>An ornate heavy armor awarded to high-ranking Whitespring secret service operatives. Embedded cryptex threads enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.
Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.
Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with short-range thrust capabilities for quick movement in urban environments. Urban scouts prefer close-quarters engagements and quick strikes rather than static defense.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>urban scout armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor specialized for cold and arctic operations, fitted with a shoulder-mounted launcher. Arctic marines specialize in breaching cold-climate fortifications.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>arctic marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet used by Whitespring patriots, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>patriot marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of armor used by Whitespring patriots. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.
Expensive and ceremonial, patriot marine armor marks membership and rank. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>patriot marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.
Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A beret styled with the Whitespring insignia, worn by Enclave personnel of certain ranks.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>Whitespring beret</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A cap worn by senior Whitespring researchers, denoting a leadership role in cryptid studies.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>Whitespring scientist cap</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for cryptid research focus. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>cryptex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for cryptid research focus. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>cryptex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>cryptex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special cryptid-focusing materials. These enhance cryptid sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>cryptex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>cryptex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, formal longcoat used by Whitespring patriots and officers. Embroidered with the Enclave sigils, it marks membership and rank.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>patriot longcoat</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.label>vertibird landing beacon</ShipLandingBeacon.label>
  <GrandThrone.description>An ornate grand chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential grand chair grants the occupant a sense of authority and dignity.</GrandThrone.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>presidential grand chair</GrandThrone.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword refined for Whitespring security officers. Its mono-molecular edge cuts through armor with ease, while an embedded cryptex core sharpens the wielder's cryptid insight and stabilizes the weapon's high-speed response.
The cryptex core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once that bond is established, the blade responds with extreme speed and precision and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>cryptex molecular blade</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored officer's sword wrapped in a sheath of captive plasma. Targets are sliced by the inner edge and burned by the surrounding field, giving Whitespring officers a close-range weapon that can cut and cauterize in the same strike.
Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the sword responds with unusual speed and control and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>plasma officer sword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A Whitespring warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. On impact it discharges a powerful pulse in addition to the physical blow, making it especially effective against power armor, robots, and other advanced hardware.
Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the hammer tracks the wielder's timing and strike rhythm with unusual accuracy and rejects any hand outside its assigned operator.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>pulse hammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <Throne.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential chair may be used as a focus for certain duties and ceremonies.</Throne.description>
  <Throne.label>presidential chair</Throne.label>
  <ShuttleIncoming.label>vertibird (incoming)</ShuttleIncoming.label>
  <ShuttleLeaving.label>vertibird (leaving)</ShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.description>Vertibot is a spacer-tech, unmanned aerial vehicle equipped with advanced sensors and a missile payload. Designed for autonomous long-range operations, it's commonly used by the Whitespring Enclave for reconnaissance and bombardment. Its ability to release powerful missile salvos makes it effective against various targets. This vertibot is temporarily disabled due to the recharge cycle.</VFED_Aerodrone.description>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.label>vertibot</VFED_Aerodrone.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>A large, overcharged vertibot battery. Will release a strong electromagnetic pulse when damaged, potentially disabling nearby defenses.</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>vertibot battery pack</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>A large military crate of vertibot munitions. Will explode when damaged, sending armed shells flying in random directions.</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>vertibot munitions crate</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>A multi-use personal stealthboy cloak device engineered based on experimental Whitespring technology. Allows the user to become completely invisible for a brief duration, after which the device requires a short amount of time to recharge.</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>stealthboy</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing extremely valuable items. May contain critical intel. Due to the special restrictions, only senior Whitespring officials are capable of opening it.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary device capable of intercepting Whitespring communication. When activated, it will begin intel scraping, emitting a pulse at regular intervals. Each pulse has a chance of generating a small amount of intel, but it may also increase your visibility and even alert a Whitespring strike force. After 10 pulses, the machine burns out and triggers a fiery explosion.</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>A crashed Whitespring vertibot.</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>crashed vertibot</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.description>A dossier containing critical information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to plan high-profile assassination attempts, but it can also be exchanged for standard intel via the contraband system.</VFED_CriticalIntel.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary declassifier is a single-use, ultra-tech device consisting of a brain-scan apparatus and a long, thick needle. It is primarily used by Whitespring Brotherhood expeditionaries for data extraction. By inserting the needle into the skull of a senior official, memories can be downloaded from their brain, forming valuable Brotherhood expeditionary intel. The amount of intel received is determined by the rank of the target official. The person affected by a Brotherhood Expeditionary Declassifier dies in the process, and when used on neutral visitors, it is treated as an act of war.</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>Brotherhood declassifier</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>A spacer-tech vertibird designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>Brotherhood vertibird</VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>Brotherhood vertibird (incoming)</VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>Brotherhood vertibird (leaving)</VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>Whitespring propaganda</VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>A chunk of a Whitespring flagship. It seems to have been torn off by some kind of powerful weapon.\n\nHaving landed not long ago, it still contains useful resources which you can acquire by deconstructing it.</VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>kovac-muldoon debris</VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>
  <VFED_FuelTank.description>A large fuel tank used to refuel Whitespring vertibirds. Will detonate if damaged beyond a certain point, potentially triggering a chain reaction.</VFED_FuelTank.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>The governmental APC is a formidable armored transport truck, known for its impressive cargo capacity. Its armor is impenetrable, ensuring the safety of its contents throughout transit. Once in motion, the APC’s doors remain sealed until it reaches its predetermined destination. While attempting to loot its cargo is futile due to built-in self-destruct protocols, its robust exterior makes it an ideal shield on the battlefield.</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>governmental APC</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>An advanced shielding apparatus, the Whitespring mega high-shield projects a vast momentum repulsor field, allowing shots to exit but preventing any from entering. Specifically calibrated for high angles, it's adept at deflecting incoming mortar rounds, vertibot strikes, and even orbital slicer beams. The unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield. Draws huge amounts of power.</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>governmental mega high-shield</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>An underground hydroponics bay used by the Whitespring Enclave to feed its personnel. Fully automated and connected to water mains, these farms require no labor to operate.</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>Whitespring underfarm</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>
  <VFED_Intel.description>A dossier containing information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to obtain pre-War tech from the Brotherhood expeditionaries, or to gain access to quests and even assassination missions on Whitespring officials.</VFED_Intel.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>Decommissioned Whitespring technology since the invention of psylink neuroformers, the psychic amplifier upgrades a psylink in the user's mind. It cannot form a psylink by itself, and can only be used by colonists with already present psylink. The user presses the device over the eyes, where it links to the brain directly and restructures part of it. Afterwards, the device disintegrates into worthless ash.</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>cryptid amplifier</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>
  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>A small surveillance buoy usually deployed around temporary convoy stops. Linked directly with a patrolling vertibot, once triggered, it will send down a small missile salvo on its location.</VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing valuables. May contain intel. Opening it requires bypassing several security protocols and takes a short while.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_SupplyCrate.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>A Whitespring computer interface. Linked to the surveillance console, the display bank shows live footage from all surveillance pillars in the sector.</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>
  <VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>A large pillar with a series of sensors, cameras, and motion detectors. Thanks to the sophisticated face recognition system, the surveillance pillar can detect the presence of Brotherhood expeditionaries in radius and will increase the visibility of whichever faction has sent them. Can be disabled via electromagnetic pulse, or by simply cutting off the power grid.</VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>A compact stack of data discs produced exclusively by the Whitespring Enclave for knowledge transcription. They are primarily designed for preserving information. When ignited, they release a dense cloud of blinding smoke and sparks, capable of engulfing a wide area in flames.</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>data disc stack</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>
  <VFED_Techprinter.description>The Data Printer is a marvel of technological innovation, designed to capture and preserve the intricate knowledge residing within a scientist’s mind. These advanced machines imprint this invaluable information directly onto data discs. Techprints provide foundational knowledge for researchers, shedding light on innovations from more advanced societies.</VFED_Techprinter.description>
  <VFED_Techprinter.label>data printer</VFED_Techprinter.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>orbital cannon capacitor bank</VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>This terminal serves as the primary interface for operating the Orbital Cannon batteries. Equipped with sophisticated controls and targeting systems, the Orbital Cannon Control Station ensures precision and coordination when deploying the formidable firepower of the Orbital Cannons. Operators need to be within its radius to control it.</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>orbital cannon control station</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.label>remote charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.description>A pair of high-explosive shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.label>remote incendiary charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.description>A pair of incendiary shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.label>remote EMP charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.description>A pair of EMP shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.label>remote smoke charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.description>A pair of smoke shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.label>remote firefoam charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.description>A pair of firefoam shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.label>remote antigrain charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.description>A pair of antigrain warheads connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.description>
  <VFED_BombPack_Deployed.label>deployed bomb pack</VFED_BombPack_Deployed.label>
  <VFED_BombPack_Deployed.description>A deployed bomb pack. It’s armed, and can be detonated with a press of a button.</VFED_BombPack_Deployed.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.label>IED shrapnel trap</VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.description>A pair of shrapnel shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>IED armor-piercing trap</VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>A pair of armor-piercing shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.label>IED cluster trap</VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.description>A pair of cluster shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.label>remote shrapnel charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.description>A pair of shrapnel shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>remote armor-piercing charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>A pair of armor-piercing shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.label>remote cluster charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.description>A pair of cluster shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Kontarion.label>kontarion</VFED_Turret_Kontarion.label>
  <VFED_Turret_Kontarion.description>A powerful, long-range weapon used by the Whitespring Enclave to take out enemy targets from afar. Kontarion turret fires ultra-dense uranium slugs at incredible speeds, penetrating even the heaviest armor. With its rapid-fire capabilities, tremendous accuracy and infinite range, it's a force to be reckoned with. It's more accurate at longer ranges, and can't fire at all close up. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of uranium slug ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Kontarion.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Kontarion.label>kontarion cannon</VFED_Gun_Kontarion.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Kontarion.description>A self-loading uranium slug cannon designed to attach to a turret.</VFED_Gun_Kontarion.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Palintone.label>palintone</VFED_Turret_Palintone.label>
  <VFED_Turret_Palintone.description>A powerful, anti-infantry weapon used by the Whitespring Enclave to defend unsafe outposts. Palintone turret fires large-caliber shells at incredible speeds, dealing heavy damage over significant ranges. It fires huge volleys of rounds that can provide suppressive fire and quickly shred lightly armored targets. With its devastating firepower, the Palintone turret is capable of keeping even the largest enemy forces at bay. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of autocannon ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Palintone.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Palintone.label>palintone cannon</VFED_Gun_Palintone.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Palintone.description>A self-loading cannon designed to attach to a turret.</VFED_Gun_Palintone.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Onager.label>onager</VFED_Turret_Onager.label>
  <VFED_Turret_Onager.description>A powerful, anti-armored weapon used by the Whitespring Enclave to destroy heavily armored targets with ease. Capable of launching missiles in bursts of 6, the Onager can deal devastating damage to enemy forces in a short amount of time. The Onager turret is most effective at short range, where its missiles can be accurately targeted at enemy positions. However, it cannot fire at enemies that are too close, as the missiles require a certain distance to arm and track their targets. Additionally, due to the sheer number of missiles it fires, the Onager is not as accurate as other turrets, and can sometimes miss its targets. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of missile ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Onager.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Onager.label>onager cannon</VFED_Gun_Onager.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Onager.description>A self-loading rocket launcher designed to attach to a turret.</VFED_Gun_Onager.description>
  <VFFED_Bullet_Onager.label>onager</VFFED_Bullet_Onager.label>
  <VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>striker turret</VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>
  <VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>A stationary, powerful turret. Will self-destruct if it is sufficiently damaged.</VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.label>uranium slug ammo box</VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.label>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.description>A small-sized box containing uranium slug ammunition. Used by Kontarion turrets to reload. May explode when damaged.</VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.description>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.label>autocannon ammo box</VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.label>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.description>A small-sized box containing autocannon ammunition. Used by Palintone turrets to reload. May explode when damaged.</VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.description>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.label>missile ammo box</VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.label>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.description>A small-sized box containing missiles. Used by Onager turrets to reload. May explode when damaged.</VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.label>supply crate</VFED_SupplyCrate.label>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.label>biosecured crate</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.label>
  <VFED_SurveillancePillar.label>surveillance pillar</VFED_SurveillancePillar.label>
  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.label>strike buoy</VFED_StrikeBuoy.label>
  <VFED_FuelTank.label>fuel tank</VFED_FuelTank.label>
  <VFED_SurveillanceStation.label>surveillance console</VFED_SurveillanceStation.label>
  <VFED_SurveillanceStation.description>A large console designed to link to surrounding surveillance pillars. Provides users with all the necessary data related to enemy movements in a given sector.</VFED_SurveillanceStation.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.label>surveillance display bank</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.label>
  <VFED_WaterMain.label>water main</VFED_WaterMain.label>
  <VFED_WaterMain.description>A large node connecting all the nearby water mains. Required for the underfarms to operate.</VFED_WaterMain.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.description>A capacitor bank that transforms electricity into raw energy for the Zeus cannon. Will release a large EMP shockwave when destroyed, potentially disabling the Zeus cannon itself.</VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannon.label>orbital cannon</VFED_ZeusCannon.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannon.description>A relic of ancient Sophiamundan technology, the Orbital Cannon is a closely guarded secret of the Whitespring Enclave. This formidable artillery piece has the unique ability to convert vast quantities of electricity into potent energy blasts. With unmatched range, it can pierce the atmosphere to target and obliterate objects in orbit. A testament to lost engineering brilliance, it stands as both a weapon and a symbol of the Whitespring Enclave's might.\n\nIt has a long charging cycle, after which it will aim at the target and release a devastating energy blast.</VFED_ZeusCannon.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.label>burnout intel scraper</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.label>
  <VFED_Biodecoder.label>biodecoder</VFED_Biodecoder.label>
  <VFED_Biodecoder.description>A biodecoder is a single-use ultratech device that is designed to strip biocoding off any item. It uses a complex process to unlatch the biocoding from the original item, which transfers the biocoding onto the biodecoder, breaking it in the process. Biodecoder can also be used on biosecured crate to open them. This device is often used in sensitive operations where the presence of biocoding could compromise the mission.</VFED_Biodecoder.description>
  <VFED_Intel.label>intel</VFED_Intel.label>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.label>critical intel</VFED_CriticalIntel.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.label>shrapnel shell</VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.description>Mortar shell that is designed to explode mid-air and release a large number of sharp projectiles. These projectiles are specifically designed to cut through light armored enemies, inflicting serious injuries or fatalities. Projectiles are ejected with the same vector as the mortar shell, and may be stopped by obstacles.</VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shell_Shrapnel.label>shrapnel shell</VFED_Bullet_Shell_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shrapnel.label>shrapnel</VFED_Bullet_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>armor-piercing shell</VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.description>Armor-piercing shells are designed to explode upon impact and destroy anything they hit, completely bypassing the armor of the target. Their explosion radius is almost non-existent, and armored targets need to be hit directly for the shell to destroy them. They are very accurate and travel at extreme speeds.</VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>armor-piercing shell</VFED_Bullet_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Cluster.label>cluster shell</VFED_Shell_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Cluster.description>Mortar shell that is designed to split mid-air and release three high-explosive shells. Separated shells are ejected in random directions, following the same vector as the cluster shell. Explosions cover a high area but the accuracy of the shells leave a lot to be desired.</VFED_Shell_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shell_Cluster.label>cluster shell</VFED_Bullet_Shell_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_BombPack.label>bomb pack</VFED_Apparel_BombPack.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_BombPack.description>A single-use man-portable explosive device. Deployed on the ground, it becomes armed and can be detonated with a press of a button. It generates a big explosion thanks to a wired-in antigrain warhead, making it capable of destroying critical infrastructure and personnel alike.</VFED_Apparel_BombPack.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneStrikeIncoming.label>vertibot strike</VFED_AerodroneStrikeIncoming.label>
  <VFED_Spark.label>spark</VFED_Spark.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.label>pulse cycler</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.description>A modified charged-shot revolver that incorporates mechanoid technology. Recovered thump cannons have been reversed engineered to allow for a powerful charge revolver with two shooting modes to be created. Charged shot mode will eliminate any close targets with a powerful, armor-piercing blast, whilst a Thump shot mode allows users to incapacitate enemies and break any defenses they might be hiding behind. Modes can be changed with a press of a button.</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.description>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.0.label>Single shot (Charged shot)</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.0.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.1.label>Single shot (Thump shot)</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.1.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.0.label>handle</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.0.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.1.label>barrel</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.1.label>
  <VFED_Bullet_ChargedShot.label>pulse shot</VFED_Bullet_ChargedShot.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_ThumpShot.label>concussion shot</VFEE_Bullet_ThumpShot.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Fletchling.label>acid scattergun</VFED_Gun_Fletchling.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Fletchling.description>A modification to the extremely rare fletcher rifle, fletchling is a shotgun commonly used by Whitespring Brotherhood expeditionaries. The mere possession of it can be seen as an act of war against the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. Each fletchling shot releases a number of small acidifier darts that may hit several targets, causing extreme amounts of pain and acid burns. Lethal to organics and almost useless against non-organics, such as mechanoids. \n\nTargets hit by these flechettes will be inflicted with an unstable variant of acidifier fluids, designed to dissolve the target from the inside rather than destroy their equipment. The acid will rampage through the target’s body and usually results in vital organs being dissolved, however lethality isn’t guaranteed.</VFED_Gun_Fletchling.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Fletchling.tools.0.label>barrel</VFED_Gun_Fletchling.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_FletchlingDart.label>fletcher dart</VFEE_Bullet_FletchlingDart.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>Whitespring suite</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.description>A non-alcoholic, pleasantly light, citrusy, and slightly bitter aperitif that owes its flavors and aromas to sweet and bitter oranges, rhubarb, and Whitespring craftsmanship. Its recipe is guarded by Whitespring hospitality offices, and few on the rim have managed to recreate it. Drinking it induces heavy but painless vomiting, completely clearing the stomach and resetting the palate.\n\nWhitespring officials prize aperitif for letting them indulge in even more of the settlement's finest cuisine.</VFEE_Aperitif.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>A high-tech helmet with a solid plasteel-weave shell and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system backed by real-time firing solutions. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>Whitespring light helmet</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>A high-tech suit of powered armor with layered plasteel-weave plates and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system that also assists the user's movement. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>Whitespring light armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>Brotherhood expeditionary armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>Brotherhood expeditionary helmet</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>Whitespring heavy armor</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>Whitespring heavy helmet</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>An exceedingly complex facemask fitted with advanced technology reserved for senior Whitespring scientists. It is designed for designated researchers so they can advance the Whitespring Enclave's needs without rest.\n\nThe inlaid techprint synchronizes with the wearer's brain while they perform research, effectively doubling research speed while restoring rest and recreation.</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>Whitespring scientist helmet</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.label>Whitespring chair</VFEE_GrandChair.label>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>A majestic rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>grand Whitespring rug</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.label>Whitespring table</VFEE_GrandTable.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>Whitespring sign</VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>A stony bas relief of Whitespring imagery for decorating a floor.</VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>Whitespring slab</VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>An intricate rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>large Whitespring rug</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>orbital beam</VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>Whitespring mirror</VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>grand presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>large presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>small presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.label>Whitespring stool</VFEE_RoyalStool.label>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.label>presidential plaque</VFEE_SteleSmall.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential desk chair can serve as a focus for ceremonial duties and cryptid meditation.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>presidential desk chair</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>A spacer-tech Whitespring gunship designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system. Equipped with a twin-linked autocannon for ground support, these XVB02s often land in the middle of the battlefield to extract stranded troops.</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>XVB02</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.label>aperitif</VFEE_Aperitif.label>
  <VFEE_Poison.label>poison</VFEE_Poison.label>
  <VFEE_Poison.description>text_todo</VFEE_Poison.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.description>A torso-sized piece of material sculpted into an artistic form.</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.description>A person-sized piece of material sculpted into an artistic form.</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.description>A huge sculpture sized to dominate a room.</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.description>
  <VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.label>double autocannon</VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.label>
  <VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.description>A powerful, twin-linked autocannon.</VFEI_TurretArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.description>A luxurious, beautiful gold-inlaid table fit for the highborn, it is a work of art in itself. People eat off tables when chairs are placed facing them.</VFEE_GrandTable.description>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.description>A comfortable and elegant chair, it is a work of art in itself. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</VFEE_GrandChair.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.description>A decorative strip of cloth hanging from a vertical wooden frame. Appropriate for presidential rooms.</VFEE_ImperialBanner.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.description>A luxurious gold-inlaid stool fit for the nobility. Can be used at tables, work stations, and elsewhere.</VFEE_RoyalStool.description>
  <VFEE_Candelabra.label>candelabra</VFEE_Candelabra.label>
  <VFEE_Candelabra.description>An elaborate, artistic electrical standing lamp that lights an area. People need light to move and work at full speed.</VFEE_Candelabra.description>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.description>A beautiful and elegant mirror. Gives a small comfort bonus to all nearby beds. Placing more than one mirror near the same bed has no effect.</VFEE_RoyalMirror.description>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.description>A slender, modest slab with limited engravings on the sides. Steles have been used since ancient times to memorialize individuals, battles, and other important events.</VFEE_SteleSmall.description>
  <VFEE_Bomb.label>bomb</VFEE_Bomb.label>
  <VFEE_Bomb.description>A small, makeshift bomb. Can be easily defused if found on time.</VFEE_Bomb.description>
  <VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.label>unfinished organ</VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.label>
  <VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.description>An unfinished organ.</VFEE_UnfinishedOrgan.description>
  <VFEE_PipeOrgan.label>organ</VFEE_PipeOrgan.label>
  <VFEE_PipeOrgan.description>An exceedingly complex stationary musical instrument crafted at a smithy. A series of tuned pipes are played from the keyboard which releases pressurized air to produce the desired pitch, which lasts as long as the key is pressed. The complex and intricate design, along with the unique sound it produces, make it an ideal apparatus for instigating concerts of the nobility as its music reaches far and wide.</VFEE_PipeOrgan.description>
  <VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>striker turret</VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>
  <VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>A redesigned cargo pod designed to bury stabilizing legs upon impact and deploy a powerful turret. Has a limited battery and ammunition pool, and will self-destruct if either run out or it is sufficiently damaged.</VFEE_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>
  <VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.label>striker gun</VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.description>A powerful turret mounted on the striker drop pod.</VFEE_Gun_StrikerTurret.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.\n\nOriginally a standard cataphract helmet, this has been modified to include a gunlink at the cost of removing the faceplate, sacrificing defense to improve offensive capabilities.</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.\n\nIncludes a plasteel-plated gas mask that offers full protection against gas-related attacks, such as toxic environments.</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.description>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.description>A glorious, long and flowing robe embroidered with intricately complex decorative designs.</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.description>A suit of heavy powered armor, built for maximum protection at the cost of mobility. Heavy layered plasteel-weave plates with solid ablative coatings stop all but the most well-aimed or powerful attacks. Neuro-memetic assistors prevent the suit's massive weight from immobilizing the wearer entirely, but the suit is still quite cumbersome.\n\nOriginally an elaborate suit of prestige armor, this has been modified to make greater use of eltex weave in order to improve the performance of psycasters. This comes at a cost of removing interfering armor plating, but enhances psychic sensitivity and neural heat dissipation.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.description>A set of pauldrons and neck guard that extends down the wearer’s chest made from layered plasteel-weave plates. While it offers high protection for those areas, it is more of a status symbol and is intended to be worn over clothing and under armor without affecting mobility.</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttleIncoming.label>armored shuttle (incoming)</VFEI_ArmoredShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttleLeaving.label>armored shuttle (leaving)</VFEI_ArmoredShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFEE_DropPodIncoming_Building.label>drop pod (incoming)</VFEE_DropPodIncoming_Building.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.label>shock officer blade</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.description>A defensive melee weapon usually assigned to Whitespring field officers of rank Private or above. While armor penetration is comparable to plasteel blades, the primary function is to dispense acidifer fluids and toxic vapors upon inflicted cuts. The effect only lasts a few seconds and is inflicted roughly half of the time due to the limited size of the weapon.</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.description>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.0.label>handle</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.1.label>point</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.1.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.2.label>edge</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_ToxbladeBladelink.tools.2.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.label>shock blade</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.description>A defensive melee weapon usually assigned to Whitespring field officers of rank Private or above. While armor penetration is comparable to plasteel blades, the primary function is to dispense acidifer fluids and toxic vapors upon inflicted cuts. The effect only lasts a few seconds and is inflicted roughly half of the time due to the limited size of the weapon.</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.description>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.0.label>handle</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.1.label>point</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.1.label>
  <VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.2.label>edge</VFEE_MeleeWeapon_Toxblade.tools.2.label>
  <VEE_Gun_Fletcher.label>marksman rifle</VEE_Gun_Fletcher.label>
  <VEE_Gun_Fletcher.description>An ultra-long range sniper rifle which fires fin-stabilized flechettes with acidifier injectors. Due to their lethality and danger of falling into enemy hands, they are always biocoded and will self-destruct if their owner either dies or is disarmed. Lethal to organics and almost useless against non-organics, such as mechanoids.\n\nTargets hit by these flechettes will be inflicted with an unstable variant of acidifier fluids, designed to dissolve the target from the inside rather than destroy their equipment. The acid will rampage through the target’s body and usually results in vital organs being dissolved, however lethality isn’t guaranteed.</VEE_Gun_Fletcher.description>
  <VEE_Gun_Fletcher.tools.0.label>barrel</VEE_Gun_Fletcher.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_FletcherDart.label>acid dart</VFEE_Bullet_FletcherDart.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.label>pulse thumper</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.description>A modified charged-shot assault shotgun that incorporates mechanoid technology. Recovered thump cannons have been reversed engineered to produce a portable ranged weapon capable of firing blunt projectiles. Quite powerful but short ranged, with high performance against structures and heavily armored targets.</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.description>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.0.label>stock</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.1.label>barrel</VFEE_Gun_ChargeThumper.tools.1.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_ChargeThumper.label>concussion charge</VFEE_Bullet_ChargeThumper.label>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>A command staff issued to Whitespring executive officers during inspections, briefings, and emergency command duty. Its cryptex head sharpens cryptid insight and helps regulate neural strain, while the embedded attunement core rejects any wielder outside the assigned chain of command.</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>cryptex command staff</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>
</LanguageData>
