<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VNPE_Filth_Paste.description>A puddle of nutrient paste.</VNPE_Filth_Paste.description>
  <VNPE_Filth_Paste.label>nutrient sludge</VNPE_Filth_Paste.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>A bedside device that feeds a person lying in bed whenever they are hungry, provided that nutrient paste dripper is connected to a nutrient paste vat. It must be placed directly adjacent to and facing the head of the bed. Placing more than one nutrient paste dripper near the same bed has no effect.</VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.label>nutrient paste dripper</VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>A small pipe output that allows colonists and citizens to pick up nutrient paste.</VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.label>nutrient paste feeder</VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>A machine that synthesizes edible nutrient paste from organic feedstocks placed in adjacent hoppers. It consumes less ingredients and time than any other meal production method - but nobody likes eating nutrient paste. Accepts raw food, but not rough plant matter like hay. It does not actually dispense the nutrient paste, but it allows it to be pumped into vats and dispensers in the network.</VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.label>nutrient paste grinder</VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPastePipe.description>Light steel pipes for transporting the sludge known as nutrient paste from grinders and storage vats to dispensers.</VNPE_NutrientPastePipe.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPastePipe.label>nutrient paste pipe</VNPE_NutrientPastePipe.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>A hopper-like storage basin meant to hold dispensed nutrient paste meal from the vats. Can be used by colonists and prisoners. Nutrient paste meal dispensed and ready for pick-up can deteriorate.</VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.label>nutrient paste tap</VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteValve.description>Switches nutrient paste flow on/off.</VNPE_NutrientPasteValve.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteValve.label>nutrient paste valve</VNPE_NutrientPasteValve.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>A large tank that can store up to 75 nutrient paste meals in it. Makes a big mess when destroyed.</VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.label>nutrient paste vat</VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.label>
  <VNPE_UndergroundNutrientPastePipe.description>Subterranean steel pipes for transporting the sludge known as nutrient paste from grinders and storage vats to dispensers.</VNPE_UndergroundNutrientPastePipe.description>
  <VNPE_UndergroundNutrientPastePipe.label>subterranean nutrient paste pipe</VNPE_UndergroundNutrientPastePipe.label>
</LanguageData>