<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation.description>Push the same early mutation work into animal hosts, establishing stable nonhuman FEV handling.</WestTek_FaunaMutation.description>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation.label>fauna mutation</WestTek_FaunaMutation.label>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation2.description>Force the S'Lanter genome into a Skinwalker-capable state, granting controlled access to an unstable transformation form.</WestTek_FaunaMutation2.description>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation2.label>forced mutation</WestTek_FaunaMutation2.label>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation3.description>Domesticate S'Lanter-derived subjects into a stable S'Nuffy fauna line and unlock specialized genome packages.</WestTek_FaunaMutation3.description>
  <WestTek_FaunaMutation3.label>forced domestication</WestTek_FaunaMutation3.label>
  <WestTek_FEV1.description>Catalog the first stable Forced Evolutionary Virus handling process. This research only becomes available after a colonist analyzes an FEV probe.</WestTek_FEV1.description>
  <WestTek_FEV1.label>FEV-1</WestTek_FEV1.label>
  <WestTek_FEV2.description>Refine the first-generation process into reliable sample handling and cleaner dosage production. This research only becomes available after a colonist analyzes an FEV sample.</WestTek_FEV2.description>
  <WestTek_FEV2.label>FEV-2</WestTek_FEV2.label>
  <WestTek_FEV3.description>Stabilize isolated Forced Evolutionary Virus cultures for controlled colonist-facing procedures. This research only becomes available after a colonist analyzes an FEV culture.</WestTek_FEV3.description>
  <WestTek_FEV3.label>FEV-3</WestTek_FEV3.label>
  <WestTek_FlatwormMutation.description>Probe low-order mutation pathways using resilient flatworm tissue. This crude foundation lets West Tek culture living FEV growth without immediately escalating to full humanoid conversion work.</WestTek_FlatwormMutation.description>
  <WestTek_FlatwormMutation.label>flatworm mutation</WestTek_FlatwormMutation.label>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation.description>Adapt early FEV culture techniques into living plant symbiotes and surgical flora prostheses.</WestTek_FloraMutation.description>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation.label>flora mutation</WestTek_FloraMutation.label>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation2.description>Weaponize plant-host mutation into contagious Spore Carriers that can spread flora mutation through direct infection.</WestTek_FloraMutation2.description>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation2.label>forced pollination</WestTek_FloraMutation2.label>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation3.description>Cultivate stable humanoid flora strains, transforming compatible humans with exactly one plant symbiote into Numen.</WestTek_FloraMutation3.description>
  <WestTek_FloraMutation3.label>forced cultivation</WestTek_FloraMutation3.label>
</LanguageData>
