<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VVE_BangBus_Blueprint.description>A basic passenger transport, the Bangbus is a relatively cheap piece of machinery to construct to transport people across roads of flat terrain. Not recommended to use in the winter season or in snowy terrain, or both, as the light plates of armour that protect the passengers similarly negatively affects its acceleration.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x5\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_BangBus_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_BangBus_Blueprint.label>bang bus</VVE_BangBus_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Bulldog_Blueprint.description>A general main battle tank, the Bulldog is an improved combat vehicle that performs well in any engagement. Performs better in less favourable terrain with all sides armoured, the thinnest plating being at the rear near the engine.\n\nDifferent to other tier 2 vehicles, this has regular fuel efficiency and is quite visible, which is still an improvement over the tier 1 tank.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Bulldog_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Bulldog_Blueprint.label>bulldog</VVE_Bulldog_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Bunsen_Blueprint.description>A basic light tank, the Bunsen is a modified armoured vehicle suited for taking on enemy fortifications and exposed infantry. Special light plating to prevent self-immolation, combined with its main weapon drawing directly from its enlarged fuel tanks, leave it a very precarious model to field.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances, however it’s also less fuel efficient on the world map.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Bunsen_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Bunsen_Blueprint.label>bunsen</VVE_Bunsen_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Charley_Blueprint.description>A general motorcycle, the Charley is a very effective single-person vehicle with a small cargo capacity. Performs well on any road except during winter season or snowy terrain, or both, with an increased speed on the world map.\n\nSimilar to other tier 2 vehicles, this has double fuel efficiency on the world map which makes them more efficient than tier 1 vehicles. They are also less visible due to improved manufacturing.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Charley_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Charley_Blueprint.label>charley</VVE_Charley_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Dinghy_Blueprint.description>A very basic motorised boat, the Dingy is an incredibly cheap and discrete method of transportation over water. Has a good cargo capacity, however it is likely to get frozen solid in the winter times and moves slowly on rivers. The exposed rear-mounted engine is vulnerable to attacks and the hull plating should not be expected to wither projectile weapons.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x5\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Dinghy_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Dinghy_Blueprint.label>dinghy</VVE_Dinghy_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Dirtbike_Blueprint.description>A basic off-road motorcycle, the Dirtbike is a very cheap vehicle that allows a single user to travel quickly, efficiently and quietly. Incredibly light and practically paper-thin on armour, it performs poorly in the winter or in the snow, or both, and has absolutely no cargo capacity.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Dirtbike_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Dirtbike_Blueprint.label>dirtbike</VVE_Dirtbike_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Frog_Blueprint.description>A basic reusable transport pod, the Frog is a relatively cheap vehicle that is the first option when it comes to flying without crashing into the ground. Several times faster than conventional transport pods with acceptable armour for its single passenger, making it an ideal ambush vehicle.\n\nEven worse than other tier 1 vehicles, fuel efficiency isn’t a thing with this transportation. Care must be taken to either refuel at the landing site or travel with enough spare fuel to make the trip back.\n\nBeing a flying vehicle, it is extremely obvious when on the move.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Frog_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Frog_Blueprint.label>frog</VVE_Frog_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Highwayman_Blueprint.description>A basic infantry fighting vehicle, the Highwayman is the cheapest weaponized option for transporting three people. Hardened against small-arms fire but very vulnerable at the rear, intended to provide mobile fire support for infantry and travel quickly along paved roads.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances, however it’s also less fuel efficient on the world map.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Highwayman_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Highwayman_Blueprint.label>highwayman</VVE_Highwayman_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Mosquito_Blueprint.description>A general-purpose aircraft, the Mosquito is an extremely fast and mobile mode of transportation. While it doesn’t require a landing strip, it is slower than aeroplanes and has less cargo capacity.\n\nSimilar to other tier 2 vehicles, this has double fuel efficiency on the world map which makes them more efficient than tier 1 vehicles.\n\nBeing a flying vehicle, it is extremely obvious when on the move.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Pilot x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Mosquito_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Mosquito_Blueprint.label>mosquito</VVE_Mosquito_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Mule_Blueprint.description>A basic cargo transport, the Mule is a relatively cheap vehicle that can carry a large amount of cargo across smooth roads of flat terrain. Not recommended to use in the winter season or in snowy terrain, or both, and it is very lightly armoured to save weight.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances. Unlike other tier 1 vehicles, this one performs better on the world map by being slightly faster and more fuel efficient.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Mule_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Mule_Blueprint.label>mule</VVE_Mule_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Prowler_Blueprint.description>A basic off-road exploration vehicle, the Prowler is relatively cheap to construct and is an effective all-weather option for efficient travel over steep terrain. Very lightly armoured with a vulnerable rear-mounted engine, it’s best to keep this single-user automobile away from combat.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Prowler_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Prowler_Blueprint.label>prowler</VVE_Prowler_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Roadkill_Blueprint.description>A basic medium tank, the Roadkill is a comparatively cheap armoured vehicle suited for short engagements. Very respectfully armoured from frontal attacks, however side attacks can disable movement and the exposed rear-mounted engine makes it vulnerable to flanking.\n\nWhile other tier 1 vehicles are gas guzzlers, this one burns through fuel at an alarming rate and is extremely slow to repair.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Roadkill_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Roadkill_Blueprint.label>roadkill</VVE_Roadkill_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Roadrunner_Blueprint.description>A general cargo transporter, the Roadrunner is an excellent vehicle for getting a lot of material from one location to another. Best suited on flat roads and will struggle somewhat on hills, snow or winter tiles.\n\nSimilar to other tier 2 vehicles, this has double fuel efficiency on the world map which makes them more efficient than tier 1 vehicles. They are also less visible due to improved manufacturing.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Roadrunner_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Roadrunner_Blueprint.label>roadrunner</VVE_Roadrunner_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Scytheman_Blueprint.description>A juryrigged multiple rocket launcher system, the Scytheman is a repurposed farming vehicle intended to saturate a location with inaccurate volleys of explosives. Due to the design, it is not intended to fire successive volleys or be exposed to enemy fire.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances. Performs worse in the winter but slightly better on the flat, open road.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Scytheman_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Scytheman_Blueprint.label>scytheman</VVE_Scytheman_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Smuggler_Blueprint.description>A general-purpose aircraft, the Smuggler is an extremely fast and effective mode of transportation. While it is faster and can carry more cargo than helicopters, it requires a landing strip to both take off and land.\n\nDifferent to other tier 2 vehicles, this has regular fuel efficiency on the world map but moves significantly faster in return.\n\nBeing a flying vehicle, it is extremely obvious when on the move.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Pilot x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Smuggler_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Smuggler_Blueprint.label>smuggler</VVE_Smuggler_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Snatcher_Blueprint.description>A general passenger transport, the Snatcher is a solid vehicle for transporting people to different locations. Best suited on flat roads and will seriously struggle in snow or on hills.\n\nSimilar to other tier 2 vehicles, this has double fuel efficiency on the world map which makes them more efficient than tier 1 vehicles. They are also less visible due to improved manufacturing.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x5\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Snatcher_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Snatcher_Blueprint.label>snatcher</VVE_Snatcher_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Tango_Blueprint.description>A general purpose armoured personnel carrier, the Tango is a slow but hardy troop transport. Ample cargo holds, hardened armour, all-terrain capability and a turret that can fire either mobile or stationary, the main downside is fuel consumption and slightly thinner plating on the rear.\n\nDifferent to other tier 2 vehicles, this has regular fuel efficiency and is quite visible, its high fuel consumption rate putting a limit on the effective range.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1, Passenger x4\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Tango_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Tango_Blueprint.label>tango</VVE_Tango_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Toad_Blueprint.description>A squad and mortar deployment pod, the Toad is a somewhat expensive vehicle to quickly mount a siege on a nearby locale without exposing your gunners to danger. With more armour than a tank and a design made to be deployed from orbit, it makes for a semi-disposable assault vehicle.\n\nFuel efficiency is not the design of this vehicle, consider only deploying on short distances with enough fuel to make it back.\n\nBeing a flying vehicle, it is extremely obvious when on the move.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Operator x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Toad_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Toad_Blueprint.label>toad</VVE_Toad_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Traveller_Blueprint.description>A basic road vehicle suited for flat terrain, the Traveller is a relatively cheap and fast option that still performs quite amicably in cold weather and snowy conditions. The light armour and exposed front-mounted engine leans to its cadence of running away from trouble rather than towards it.\n\nSimilar to other tier 1 vehicles, this is a gas guzzler and best used for medium distances. The extra speed and acceleration make it even less fuel-efficient as well as more time-consuming to repair.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Traveller_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Traveller_Blueprint.label>traveller</VVE_Traveller_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Trawler_Blueprint.description>A general-purpose boat, the Trawler is an effective long distance transportation across open waters. Performs rather poorly on rivers and has to travel slowly during the winter season.\n\nSimilar to other tier 2 vehicles, this has double fuel efficiency on the world map which makes them more efficient than tier 1 vehicles. They are also less visible due to improved manufacturing.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Trawler_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Trawler_Blueprint.label>trawler</VVE_Trawler_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Wagon_Blueprint.description>A general all-rounder vehicle, the Wagon performs well in all categories with a good cargo and passenger capacity. Best suited on flat roads and will struggle somewhat on hills, snow or winter tiles.\n\nSimilar to other tier 2 vehicles, this has double fuel efficiency on the world map which makes them more efficient than tier 1 vehicles. They are also less visible due to improved manufacturing.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Wagon_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Wagon_Blueprint.label>wagon</VVE_Wagon_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Warbird_Blueprint.description>A general-purpose fighter plane, the Warbird is an incredibly fast and effective attack craft. With minimal cargo intended for holding maintenance equipment and fuel, its primary purpose is to engage other aircraft and initiate strafing manoeuvres.\n\nDifferent to other tier 2 vehicles, this has regular fuel efficiency on the world map but moves significantly faster in return.\n\nBeing a flying vehicle, it is extremely obvious when on the move.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Pilot x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Warbird_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Warbird_Blueprint.label>warbird</VVE_Warbird_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Wisent_Blueprint.description>A military-grade all-purpose transporter, the Wisent is a powerful truck capable of transporting both plentiful cargo and soldiers into hostile territory. Terrible fuel economy, however it can quickly navigate through rough terrain.\n\nCounter to other tier 2 vehicles, this is less efficient but more effective when travelling away from roads. Passengers sitting in the back will be exposed to enemy fire and the armour plating is only suited for minimal small arms fire.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x7\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Wisent_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Wisent_Blueprint.label>wisent</VVE_Wisent_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Badger_Blueprint.description>A tracked, armoured fighting vehicle, the Badger is designed to transport scouts and infantry while providing covering fire to suppress enemy troops. Reinforced side armour plating, ability to deploy blindsmoke and a powerful anti-infantry automated gun make it a powerful vehicle in small combat engagement. It’s relatively vulnerable to attacks from behind, and the short range of the turret means it is outclassed by most designated tanks.\n\nCompared to previous generations, this IFV is designed to quickly drop infantry off at a desired location and provide light covering fire. Lack of armor piercing on fired projectiles make it weak against enemy tanks.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1, Passenger x4\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Badger_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Badger_Blueprint.label>badger</VVE_Badger_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_BigRig_Blueprint.description>A dedicated cargo transporter, the Big Rig is the epitome of bulk material transportation. While best suited on flat roads, it still has a powerful enough engine to effectively charge through difficult terrain.\n\nA surprisingly quick, gas-guzzling cargo transporter that has terrible acceleration, but very little can slow it down once it gets up to speed.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_BigRig_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_BigRig_Blueprint.label>big rig</VVE_BigRig_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Burya_Blueprint.description>A dedicated multiple launch rocket system platform, the Burya is a long-range siege and area denial weapon that can be operated by a two-man crew for faster loading speeds. Capable of firing continuous volleys of long range missiles, Burya can blanket whole areas in anti-infantry rocket explosions.\n\nSlow-moving and vulnerable to enemy fire, Burya needs to deploy before it can open fire, which may leave it stranded in enemy territory.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x2\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Burya_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Burya_Blueprint.label>burya</VVE_Burya_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Cherokee_Blueprint.description>A heavy duty transport aircraft, the Cherokee is a hulking monstrosity of aeronautical engineering. Very slow due to all the bulk, equally thirsty, and sports massive cargo capacity. Plan accordingly.\n\nA dedicated transport helicopter with a modified cargo bay, it requires two pilots to operate and frequent refueling. However, nothing comes even close to bulk transportation at its tech level.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Pilot x2\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Cherokee_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Cherokee_Blueprint.label>cherokee</VVE_Cherokee_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Goliath_Blueprint.description>More of a movable mini-base than a deployment pod, Goliath is an expensive but powerful solution to any immovable enemy object. Equipped with four military turret stations and a long range rocket swarm turret at the top, this siege pod is capable of raining fire in 360 degree radius. Nearly impenetrable, it can serve as a portable base of operations, keeping all troops inside safe.\n\nIt’s incredibly heavy and lift off requires single-use boosters that separate once the trajectory and velocity is reached. In order to lift off again, the boosters need to be rebuilt.\n\nBeing a flying vehicle, it is extremely obvious when on the move.</VVE_Goliath_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Goliath_Blueprint.label>goliath</VVE_Goliath_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Hermano_Blueprint.description>A dedicated refrigeration vehicle, the Hermano is a decent cargo transporter with a specific niche in ferrying perishable goods. Decent in long-range travel along roads, it performs terribly in off-road or winter conditions.\n\nWhile there are better cargo transporters even in lower tiers, this truck can transport cargo in a frozen state, preventing spoilage. Due to the extra machinery, performance suffers and it should stay away from conflict zones.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Hermano_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Hermano_Blueprint.label>hermano</VVE_Hermano_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Lightning_Blueprint.description>A fast general purpose transporter, the Lightning is an excellent road vehicle for getting an appreciable amount of cargo in a very small time frame. Incredibly fast on flat roads and will struggle on hills, snow or winter tiles.\n\nAs it is designed for speed, trips should always be planned for staying on roads and having extra fuel, which can occupy most of the extra cargo space. It has terrible fuel efficiency due to the performance, so plan accordingly.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Lightning_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Lightning_Blueprint.label>lightning</VVE_Lightning_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Louie_Blueprint.description>An armoured transport aircraft, the Louie is a robust and agile mobile mode of transportation. Doesn’t require a landing strip and won’t fall apart at the first sign of fire.\n\nA relatively general purpose helicopter, it has both excellent cargo and passenger capacity. Has some armour for an aircraft, allowing it to deploy and extract from hot zones.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Pilot x1, Passenger x5\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Louie_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Louie_Blueprint.label>louie</VVE_Louie_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Marshal_Blueprint.description>A general main battle tank, the Marshal is an improved combat vehicle that performs well in any engagement. Performs better in less favourable terrain with all sides armoured, the thinnest plating being at the rear near the engine.\n\nMinimal armour improvements compared to previous tier tanks, instead it has a more powerful main gun and a secondary gun. Can fire while moving, as it requires one driver and two gunners; one for each weapon system.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1, Machine gunner x1\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Marshal_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Marshal_Blueprint.label>marshal</VVE_Marshal_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Nomad_Blueprint.description>An armoured all-rounder vehicle, the Nomad performs remarkably well in all categories with an excellent cargo and passenger capacity. Performs well in any and all terrain, with some minor issues in the cold.\n\nA relatively general purpose tier 3, effectively being a lightly armoured APC. While it excels in off road capabilities and works well in all situations, other vehicles perform even better on roads or in specialized tasks.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Nomad_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Nomad_Blueprint.label>nomad</VVE_Nomad_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Paladin_Blueprint.description>A general purpose armoured personnel carrier, the Paladin is a fast and hardy troop transport. Decent cargo holds, reinforced armour plating, all-terrain capability and a smoke grenade turret for screening troop deployment. The major downsides are no tracks for better terrain navigation and thinner plating on the rear.\n\nCompared to previous generations, this APC is designed to quickly drop infantry off at a desired location and quickly retreat. It can act as temporary cover but ideally it should be able to deploy its cargo and bring it home safely.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1, Passenger x6\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Paladin_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Paladin_Blueprint.label>paladin</VVE_Paladin_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Springbok_Blueprint.description>A general all-rounder vehicle, the Springbok performs well in all categories with a good cargo and passenger capacity. The old, robust build and loud engine negatively affect its fuel efficiency and visibility. Best suited on flat roads and will struggle somewhat on hills, snow or winter tiles.\n\nA slightly worse performer compared to tier 2 vehicles, it is instead a stylish vehicle to drive and will provide a mood boost to all passengers.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Springbok_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Springbok_Blueprint.label>springbok</VVE_Springbok_Blueprint.label>
  <VVE_Udar_Blueprint.description>A dedicated artillery unit, the Udar is a long-range siege weapon that can be operated by a two-man crew for faster loading speeds. Small and inefficient fuel reserves are its limiting factor, as it can drive through any terrain without issue.\n\nA priority target and defenseless by itself or in close range, especially with its thin rear plating, a well-defended Udar can lay down quick barrages of mortar shells and reposition out of danger.\n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x2\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</VVE_Udar_Blueprint.description>
  <VVE_Udar_Blueprint.label>udar</VVE_Udar_Blueprint.label>
</LanguageData>
