<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Fish_Salmon.description>A migratory fish with dark scales and rich flesh, common where cold rivers meet the sea.</Fish_Salmon.description>
  <Fish_Salmon.label>smoky salmon</Fish_Salmon.label>
  <Fish_Bass.description>A common freshwater predator known for sudden strikes and mild-tasting meat.</Fish_Bass.description>
  <Fish_Bass.label>chain pickerel</Fish_Bass.label>
  <Fish_Tilapia.description>A hardy freshwater fish found in warm rivers and ponds, often thriving where cleaner species cannot.</Fish_Tilapia.description>
  <Fish_Tilapia.label>withered radeye</Fish_Tilapia.label>
  <Fish_Cod.description>A coldwater coastal fish with thick scales and a stiff dorsal ridge, valued for its firm white flesh.</Fish_Cod.description>
  <Fish_Cod.label>armored spinefish</Fish_Cod.label>
  <Fish_Bluefish.description>A fast coastal hunter that chases bait schools in rough weather and open surf.</Fish_Bluefish.description>
  <Fish_Bluefish.label>stormswimmer</Fish_Bluefish.label>
  <Fish_Guppy.description>A small freshwater species prized for its unusual frilled gills; edible, but too small to provide much meat.</Fish_Guppy.description>
  <Fish_Guppy.label>axolotl</Fish_Guppy.label>
  <Fish_Frostfish.description>A large coldwater fish with pale flesh and a heavy body, usually found in deep glacier-fed rivers.</Fish_Frostfish.description>
  <Fish_Frostfish.label>potbelly kelt</Fish_Frostfish.label>
  <Fish_Catfish.description>A large whiskered bottom-feeder that prowls muddy channels and flooded ruins after dark.</Fish_Catfish.description>
  <Fish_Catfish.label>bloodwhisker</Fish_Catfish.label>
  <Fish_Piranha.description>A small but aggressive freshwater fish with sharp teeth and powerful jaws, often caught as a trophy species.</Fish_Piranha.description>
  <Fish_Piranha.label>kanawha piranha</Fish_Piranha.label>
  <Fish_Dogfish.description>A small shark-like coastal fish with rough skin and sharp teeth, common along rocky shorelines.</Fish_Dogfish.description>
  <Fish_Dogfish.label>sawgill</Fish_Dogfish.label>
  <Fish_Marlin.description>A huge open-water hunter with a spear-like snout, prized as a dangerous trophy catch.</Fish_Marlin.description>
  <Fish_Marlin.label>deathjaw</Fish_Marlin.label>
  <Fish_Tuna.description>A large migratory fish from warm seas, known for oily flesh and strong sustained runs.</Fish_Tuna.description>
  <Fish_Tuna.label>bluefin zapper</Fish_Tuna.label>
  <Fish_Flounder.description>A flat coastal fish that buries itself in silt and ambushes prey along the seafloor.</Fish_Flounder.description>
  <Fish_Flounder.label>ashen ambusher</Fish_Flounder.label>
  <Fish_Toxfish.description>A polluted-water mutant fish. Unsafe raw, but still usable in cooked meals with low nutritional value.</Fish_Toxfish.description>
  <Fish_Toxfish.label>glowing gulpy</Fish_Toxfish.label>
</LanguageData>