<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VVE_BattleTanks.description>Learn to build heavily armored battle tanks such as the marshal, equipped with a variety of weapons. In order to research this project, a marshal wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_BattleTanks.description>
  <VVE_BattleTanks.label>battle tanks</VVE_BattleTanks.label>
  <VVE_BigRigs.description>Learn to build large, long-distance trucks such as the big rig or hermano, capable of delivering large amounts of cargo over extremely long distances. In order to research this project, a big rig or hermano wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_BigRigs.description>
  <VVE_BigRigs.label>big rigs</VVE_BigRigs.label>
  <VVE_Cherokee.description>Learn to build a dual-rotor cargo helicopter called cherokee, capable of delivering thousands of kilograms of resources via air routes. In order to research this project, a cherokee wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_Cherokee.description>
  <VVE_Cherokee.label>cherokee</VVE_Cherokee.label>
  <VVE_ClassicCars.description>Learn to build fancy, classic cars such as the springbok. In order to research this project, a springbok wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_ClassicCars.description>
  <VVE_ClassicCars.label>classic cars</VVE_ClassicCars.label>
  <VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.description>Learn to build light armored vehicles such as the paladin or the badger, that can transport soldiers efficiently and effectively whilst providing them with fire support. In order to research this project, a paladin or badger wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.description>
  <VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.label>light armored vehicles</VVE_LightArmoredVehicles.label>
  <VVE_Louie.description>Learn to build a large transport helicopter called louie, that can deliver both cargo and troops over long distances with ease. In order to research this project, a louie wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_Louie.description>
  <VVE_Louie.label>louie</VVE_Louie.label>
  <VVE_OffroadJeeps.description>Learn to build offroad jeeps such as the nomad, that can traverse any terrain with ease. In order to research this project, a nomad wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_OffroadJeeps.description>
  <VVE_OffroadJeeps.label>offroad jeeps</VVE_OffroadJeeps.label>
  <VVE_RocketArtillery.description>Learn to build multiple launch rocket systems with the ability to blanket a whole area with missiles. In order to research this project, a burya wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_RocketArtillery.description>
  <VVE_RocketArtillery.label>rocket artillery</VVE_RocketArtillery.label>
  <VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.description>Learn to build a powerful, self-propelled artillery such as the famous udar, capable of raining artillery fire on enemies on the local map. In order to research this project, an udar wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.description>
  <VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.label>self-propelled artillery</VVE_SelfpropelledArtillery.label>
  <VVE_SiegePods.description>Learn to build powerful siege pods that act as temporary, moving bases during assaults in enemy territory. In order to research this project, a goliath wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_SiegePods.description>
  <VVE_SiegePods.label>siege pods</VVE_SiegePods.label>
  <VVE_SuperCars.description>Learn to build fast and luxurious supercars such as the lightning. In order to research this project, a lightning wreck needs to be found and restored.</VVE_SuperCars.description>
  <VVE_SuperCars.label>supercars</VVE_SuperCars.label>
</LanguageData>
