<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GlobalWarming.description>Global temperatures have suddenly risen to dangerous levels.

Flora and Fauna is suffering from these changes as biomes shift into their warmer counterparts. Resources become scarce, forcing factions into conflict.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</GlobalWarming.description>
  <GlobalWarming.label>global warming</GlobalWarming.label>
  <IceAge.description>Atmospheric composition of the planet drastically changed resulting in a significant drop in temperature.

Flora and Fauna is suffering from these changes as biomes shift into their colder counterparts. Resources become scarce, forcing factions into conflict.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</IceAge.description>
  <IceAge.label>ice age</IceAge.label>
  <LongNight.description>A space entity of unimaginable size has covered a local star, resulting in a long lasting eclipse.

Terrified of this supernatural phenomenon, other factions will use this time to wage war and conflict across the surface.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</LongNight.description>
  <LongNight.label>long night</LongNight.label>
  <PsychicBloom.description>A strong psychic pulse emitted by a long forgotten entity changed the very genetical structure of local flora. Whilst the sky filled with a seemingly endless auroras, colourful flowers started sprouting everywhere. 

All pawns will gain a positive mood buff for the time of the event. The rapidly spreading flowers will overgrow everything, including your fields. 

It will last anywhere between a few days to a season.</PsychicBloom.description>
  <PsychicBloom.label>psychic bloom</PsychicBloom.label>
  <PsychicRain.description>A dangerous psychic entity caused disturbance on subatomic levels, resonating across all particles of the atmosphere.

A seemingly endless supernatural rain has begun, altering the very composition of time. Any person or creature not under the roof will age significantly faster.

It will last anywhere between a season to several years.</PsychicRain.description>
  <PsychicRain.label>psychic rain</PsychicRain.label>
  <Drought.description>An unusual drought has set in.

Drought is devastating for plant life and will quickly destroy all the crops not planted in the hydroponics. Be sure to quickly harvest any plants you can.</Drought.description>
  <Drought.label>drought</Drought.label>
  <HailStorm.description>A freak, small scale hail storm is ravaging the local area. Any person or creature not hiding under the roof risks getting injured by ice pellets.</HailStorm.description>
  <HailStorm.label>hail storm</HailStorm.label>
  <SpaceBattle.description>A space battle is raging in the sky, may last up to 1 day.</SpaceBattle.description>
  <SpaceBattle.label>space battle</SpaceBattle.label>
  <VPE_Hurricane.description>A Staticlord is creating a hurricane.</VPE_Hurricane.description>
  <VPE_Hurricane.label>forced hurricane</VPE_Hurricane.label>
  <VPE_IntenseShadows.description>text.todo</VPE_IntenseShadows.description>
  <VPE_IntenseShadows.label>intensified shadows</VPE_IntenseShadows.label>
  <VPE_PsychicFlashstorm.description>A freak localized storm is blasting a small area with repeated lightning strikes.</VPE_PsychicFlashstorm.description>
  <VPE_PsychicFlashstorm.label>flashstorm</VPE_PsychicFlashstorm.label>
  <VPE_PsychicFlashstorm.letterText>A freak localized flashstorm is striking a small area with lightning. This can cause massive fires.</VPE_PsychicFlashstorm.letterText>
  <VPE_RaidPause.description>A Chronopath is pausing a raid.</VPE_RaidPause.description>
  <VPE_RaidPause.label>paused raid</VPE_RaidPause.label>
  <VPE_TimeQuake.description>A massive temporal disturbance.</VPE_TimeQuake.description>
  <VPE_TimeQuake.label>time quake</VPE_TimeQuake.label>
  <VRE_BloodMoonCondition.description>One of the moons of this planet has orbited into the rimworld’s umbra, making sanguophages go mad with hunger.</VRE_BloodMoonCondition.description>
  <VRE_BloodMoonCondition.label>blood moon</VRE_BloodMoonCondition.label>
  <VRE_BloodMoonCondition.letterText>One of the moons of this planet has orbited into the rimworld’s umbra, blocking all direct sunlight from illuminating the moon’s surface. This resulted in the moon taking on a crimson color - a phenomena known as the blood moon.\n\nDuring this time, sanguophage mechanites will go into overdrive, driving hemogen-starved bloodfeeders out of their caves. Any bloodfeeder sanguophage with more than half hemogen supply gone will enter the hemohunter mental state. Hemogen will drain significantly quicker during blood moon.</VRE_BloodMoonCondition.letterText>
  <VFED_DivineInferno.description>The Empire has initiated a Divine Inferno protocol on your colony and are moving all required slicer beam satellites into position. Once they meet over your colony, they will glass it with numerous pillars of fire. This can be prevented by reducing your visibility back to Hidden visibility level.</VFED_DivineInferno.description>
  <VFED_DivineInferno.label>divine inferno</VFED_DivineInferno.label>
  <VFED_MissileRain.label>missile rain</VFED_MissileRain.label>
  <Spaceports_KesslerSyndrome.description>A debris cascade is sweeping the local orbit-space. All shuttle travel has been rendered impossible.</Spaceports_KesslerSyndrome.description>
  <Spaceports_KesslerSyndrome.label>kessler syndrome</Spaceports_KesslerSyndrome.label>
  <Spaceports_KesslerSyndrome.letterText>You’ve just received a wide-band warning of a massive ongoing debris cascade within the planet’s local orbit-space.\n\nLikely set in motion years ago by a freak impact event, the cascade has just recently reached critical mass - and now thousands of years worth of derelict satellites and spacecraft are coming home to roost.\n\nAll shuttle travel has been rendered impossible until the cascade terminates and atmospheric friction cleans out the primary transit zones. The warning says this could take anywhere from a season to over a year. If you're lucky, it will end sooner than predicted.</Spaceports_KesslerSyndrome.letterText>
  <VQE_UnnaturalColdSnap.description>An unnatural cold snap is freezing the region.</VQE_UnnaturalColdSnap.description>
  <VQE_UnnaturalColdSnap.label>cold snap</VQE_UnnaturalColdSnap.label>
  <VQE_AncientSiloUnderground.description>It's dark and damp here.</VQE_AncientSiloUnderground.description>
  <VQE_AncientSiloUnderground.label>ancient silo</VQE_AncientSiloUnderground.label>
  <VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.description>Detonation of Deadlife dust warheads in the upper atmosphere has permanently altered planetary conditions. A dense death pall now blankets the world. This pall reanimates all unburied corpses exposed to the open air.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.description>
  <VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.label>shambler apocalypse</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.label>
  <VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.letterText>Detonation of Deadlife dust warheads in the upper atmosphere has permanently altered planetary conditions. A dense death pall now blankets the world.\n\nThis pall reanimates all unburied corpses exposed to the open air. Any non-mechanoid corpse not under a roof will rise again as a shambler. Burned or fully destroyed corpses are unaffected.\n\nWhile the death pall is active, no normal weather transitions can occur. Rain will not fall, and fires may spread unchecked.\n\nOn a global scale, the death pall will linger for anywhere from three seasons to several years. In its wake, roaming Shambler hordes will now traverse the world, overrunning settlements and hunting down caravans.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.letterText>
  <VGE_AsteroidShower.description>An asteroid shower has crossed into your gravship’s sector. Countless fragments of vacstone streak across the void, some slamming into the hull with explosive force. Most will burn away or miss, but not all.</VGE_AsteroidShower.description>
  <VGE_AsteroidShower.label>asteroid shower</VGE_AsteroidShower.label>
  <VGE_AsteroidShower.letterText>An asteroid shower has crossed into your gravship’s sector. Countless fragments of vacstone streak across the void, some slamming into the hull with explosive force. Most will burn away or miss, but not all.</VGE_AsteroidShower.letterText>
  <VGE_Comet.description>A massive comet is passing nearby, its brilliant tail lighting up the void around your gravship. The spectacle inspires awe among the crew, raising their spirits until it will fade from view.</VGE_Comet.description>
  <VGE_Comet.label>comet</VGE_Comet.label>
  <VGE_Comet.letterText>A massive comet is passing nearby, its brilliant tail lighting up the void around your gravship. The spectacle inspires awe among the crew, raising their spirits until it will fade from view.</VGE_Comet.letterText>
  <VGE_DustCloud.description>A dense cosmic dust cloud has drifted across your sector, shrouding your gravship in particulate haze. Visibility is almost zero, and targeting systems are struggling to lock onto anything. The dust will eventually clear as the cloud drifts away.</VGE_DustCloud.description>
  <VGE_DustCloud.label>dust cloud</VGE_DustCloud.label>
  <VGE_DustCloud.letterText>A dense cosmic dust cloud has drifted across your sector, shrouding your gravship in particulate haze. Visibility is almost zero, and targeting systems are struggling to lock onto anything. The dust will eventually clear as the cloud drifts away.</VGE_DustCloud.letterText>
  <VGE_GravitationalAnomaly.description>A powerful gravity distortion has enveloped your gravship, preventing any kind of launch until it subsides. The anomaly will remain for the next few days before naturally fading away. Until then, all gravship launch rituals are unavailable and the ship will be unable to move from this location.\n\nWhile the anomaly persists, your systems will passively collect gravdata, but only if an active gravship research project is selected.</VGE_GravitationalAnomaly.description>
  <VGE_GravitationalAnomaly.label>gravitational anomaly</VGE_GravitationalAnomaly.label>
  <VGE_GravitationalAnomaly.letterText>A powerful gravity distortion has enveloped your gravship, preventing any kind of launch until it subsides. The anomaly will remain for the next few days before naturally fading away. Until then, all gravship launch rituals are unavailable and the ship will be unable to move from this location.\n\nWhile the anomaly persists, your systems will passively collect gravdata, but only if an active gravship research project is selected.</VGE_GravitationalAnomaly.letterText>
  <VGE_MicrometeorStorm.description>A micrometeor storm is pelting the area with tiny, high-velocity debris. Exposed structures and people are slowly damaged by the constant bombardment.\n\nThe storm is expected to last about a day.</VGE_MicrometeorStorm.description>
  <VGE_MicrometeorStorm.label>micrometeor storm</VGE_MicrometeorStorm.label>
  <VGE_MicrometeorStorm.letterText>A micrometeor storm is pelting the area with tiny, high-velocity debris. Exposed structures and people are slowly damaged by the constant bombardment.\n\nThe storm is expected to last about a day.</VGE_MicrometeorStorm.letterText>
  <VGE_SpaceDebris.description>A drifting cloud of ancient wreckage has crossed our flight path. Pieces of metal and scrap hurtle past the ship. Some will miss, others might not.\n\nThe debris will pass us by in about 12 hours.</VGE_SpaceDebris.description>
  <VGE_SpaceDebris.label>space debris</VGE_SpaceDebris.label>
  <VGE_SpaceDebris.letterText>A drifting cloud of ancient wreckage has crossed our flight path. Pieces of metal and scrap hurtle past the ship. Some will miss, others might not.\n\nThe debris will pass us by in about 12 hours.</VGE_SpaceDebris.letterText>
  <VGE_SpaceSolarFlare.description>A solar flare has begun.\n\nWhile this solar flare will not disable electronic devices, it will quickly heat all exposed surfaces, potentially causing heatstroke and fires.\n\nIt should pass in about a day.</VGE_SpaceSolarFlare.description>
  <VGE_SpaceSolarFlare.label>solar flare</VGE_SpaceSolarFlare.label>
  <VGE_SpaceSolarFlare.letterText>A solar flare has begun.\n\nWhile this solar flare will not disable electronic devices, it will quickly heat all exposed surfaces, potentially causing heatstroke and fires.\n\nIt should pass in about a day.</VGE_SpaceSolarFlare.letterText>
  <VGE_ToxicDustCloud.description>A drifting cloud of highly toxic cosmic dust has enveloped your gravship. Microscopic particulates are seeping into every exposed space, corroding surfaces and poisoning the crew. The dust cloud will persist only briefly, but its effects are immediate and dangerous.</VGE_ToxicDustCloud.description>
  <VGE_ToxicDustCloud.label>toxic dust cloud</VGE_ToxicDustCloud.label>
  <VGE_ToxicDustCloud.letterText>A drifting cloud of highly toxic cosmic dust has enveloped your gravship. Microscopic particulates are seeping into every exposed space, corroding surfaces and poisoning the crew. The dust cloud will persist only briefly, but its effects are immediate and dangerous.</VGE_ToxicDustCloud.letterText>
  <VQEA_AncientComplex.description>It's dark and damp here.</VQEA_AncientComplex.description>
  <VQEA_AncientComplex.label>ancient complex</VQEA_AncientComplex.label>
  <VEE_ColossalFauna.description>All fauna in this area is much larger than usual.</VEE_ColossalFauna.description>
  <VEE_ColossalFauna.label>colossal fauna</VEE_ColossalFauna.label>
  <VEE_FertileRainsGameCondition.description>Unusually nutrient-rich rainfall is sweeping across the region, boosting plant growth for its duration.</VEE_FertileRainsGameCondition.description>
  <VEE_FertileRainsGameCondition.label>fertile rain</VEE_FertileRainsGameCondition.label>
  <VEE_GeomagneticStorm.description>An intense geomagnetic event blankets the region, completely disabling all electrical devices.</VEE_GeomagneticStorm.description>
  <VEE_GeomagneticStorm.label>geomagnetic storm</VEE_GeomagneticStorm.label>
  <VEE_Microfauna.description>All fauna in this area is much smaller than usual.</VEE_Microfauna.description>
  <VEE_Microfauna.label>microfauna</VEE_Microfauna.label>
  <VEE_NoWind.description>Winds are almost completely absent in this area.</VEE_NoWind.description>
  <VEE_NoWind.label>no wind</VEE_NoWind.label>
  <VEE_RagingWind.description>Winds are extraordinarily stronger in this area.</VEE_RagingWind.description>
  <VEE_RagingWind.label>raging winds</VEE_RagingWind.label>
  <VEE_RottenStench.description>Acrid vapors seep from the ground, blanketing the area in a foul smell that burns the lungs and sours the mood.</VEE_RottenStench.description>
  <VEE_RottenStench.label>rotten stench</VEE_RottenStench.label>
  <VEE_SkygazingSpot.description>A serene atmospheric phenomenon encourages colonists to spend more time gazing at the sky. Increases the chance of skygazing and boosts the joy it provides.</VEE_SkygazingSpot.description>
  <VEE_SkygazingSpot.label>skygazing spot</VEE_SkygazingSpot.label>
  <VEE_TidalFlooding.description>In this extremely flat coastal plain the tides push far inland, regularly submerging large stretches of land.</VEE_TidalFlooding.description>
  <VEE_TidalFlooding.label>tidal flooding</VEE_TidalFlooding.label>
</LanguageData>
