<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <AccessControlButton>Flight control</AccessControlButton>
    <AccessControlDesc>Specify what kind of vertibird traffic is allowed to use this pad.</AccessControlDesc>
    <LetterTraderShuttleArrival>A Brotherhood quartermaster vertibird from {0} is landing. They are a {1}.</LetterTraderShuttleArrival>
    <Spaceports_AirspaceLockdown>Flight lockdown</Spaceports_AirspaceLockdown>
    <Spaceports_AirspaceLockdownDesc>Due to hostiles, or because it was manually activated, one or more of your colonies has entered flight lockdown. No new vertibird traffic will arrive, but any landed craft can still depart. 

Colonies currently under flight lockdown:
</Spaceports_AirspaceLockdownDesc>
    <Spaceports_AllTypes>All vertibirds</Spaceports_AllTypes>
    <Spaceports_AutoEvac>Emergency scramble in progress</Spaceports_AutoEvac>
    <Spaceports_AutoEvacDesc>Due to hostiles, one or more of your colonies has initiated automatic evacuation of landed visitors and crews. 

Colonies currently performing emergency scrambles:
</Spaceports_AutoEvacDesc>
    <Spaceports_BeaconAtCap>
Flight traffic at user-defined limit - landings suspended.</Spaceports_BeaconAtCap>
    <Spaceports_BeaconKessler>
Debris hazard in the flight corridor - landings impossible.</Spaceports_BeaconKessler>
    <Spaceports_BeaconNoPads>
No active vertibird pads detected - flight network offline.</Spaceports_BeaconNoPads>
    <Spaceports_BeaconOK>
Flight network online.</Spaceports_BeaconOK>
    <Spaceports_BeaconPadsFull>
All vertibird pads are occupied - landings suspended.</Spaceports_BeaconPadsFull>
    <Spaceports_BeaconUnpowered>
Beacon unpowered - flight network offline.</Spaceports_BeaconUnpowered>
    <Spaceports_CallTaxi>Request transit vertibird</Spaceports_CallTaxi>
    <Spaceports_CallTaxiDisabled>beacon is unpowered - cannot reach Brotherhood flight control.</Spaceports_CallTaxiDisabled>
    <Spaceports_CallTaxiInfo>Service: One-way transit vertibird
Fare: 500 silver
Boarding: first open pad</Spaceports_CallTaxiInfo>
    <Spaceports_CallTaxiTooltip>Request a one-way Brotherhood-chartered vertibird for 500 silver.</Spaceports_CallTaxiTooltip>
    <Spaceports_DismissAll>Scramble all</Spaceports_DismissAll>
    <Spaceports_DismissAllTooltip>Force all vertibirds on the map to lift off and depart immediately, regardless of whether all required cargo is loaded.</Spaceports_DismissAllTooltip>
    <Spaceports_GizmoDisabled>you do not control this vertibird, or it is incapable of taking off.</Spaceports_GizmoDisabled>
    <Spaceports_GroupVisitorsLanding>A Brotherhood vertibird from {0} is landing with visitors.</Spaceports_GroupVisitorsLanding>
    <Spaceports_ImmediateDeparture>Scramble</Spaceports_ImmediateDeparture>
    <Spaceports_ImmediateDepartureTooltip>Force this vertibird to lift off and depart immediately, regardless of whether all required cargo is loaded.</Spaceports_ImmediateDepartureTooltip>
    <Spaceports_JustGuests>Allied guests only</Spaceports_JustGuests>
    <Spaceports_JustTraders>Quartermasters only</Spaceports_JustTraders>
    <Spaceports_JustVisitors>Visitors only</Spaceports_JustVisitors>
    <Spaceports_ManualAirspaceLockdown>Flight lockdown</Spaceports_ManualAirspaceLockdown>
    <Spaceports_ManualAirspaceLockdownTooltip>Manually toggle vertibird traffic lockdown.</Spaceports_ManualAirspaceLockdownTooltip>
    <Spaceports_None>No flights</Spaceports_None>
    <Spaceports_RecallAll>Recall all crews</Spaceports_RecallAll>
    <Spaceports_RecallAllTooltip>Force all landed parties to board their vertibirds and depart immediately.</Spaceports_RecallAllTooltip>
    <Spaceports_RecallParty>Recall passengers</Spaceports_RecallParty>
    <Spaceports_RecallPartyTooltip>Force this vertibird's passengers to board immediately and depart.</Spaceports_RecallPartyTooltip>
    <Spaceports_SingleVisitorLanding>A Brotherhood vertibird from {1} is landing with a visiting patron. {PAWN_titleIndef} named {PAWN_nameFull} is onboard.</Spaceports_SingleVisitorLanding>
    <Spaceports_Uplink>Brotherhood uplink established...</Spaceports_Uplink>
    <Spaceports_VisitorsLeaving>Visitors from {0} are departing by Brotherhood vertibird.</Spaceports_VisitorsLeaving>

    <Spaceports_DryModeWarning>Warning: without water access, the aviation fuel processor will run at 33% efficiency.</Spaceports_DryModeWarning>
    <Spaceports_DryModeWarningDBH>Warning: the aviation fuel processor requires water piping to operate at full efficiency.</Spaceports_DryModeWarningDBH>
    <Spaceports_FFTerrain>Aviation fuel processor must be placed in shallow water, a river, or on terrain that supports Heavy.</Spaceports_FFTerrain>
    <Spaceports_FuelLevel>Aviation fuel reserves: {0}</Spaceports_FuelLevel>
    <Spaceports_ModeDry>Operating mode: dry (reduced yield)</Spaceports_ModeDry>
    <Spaceports_ModeWet>Operating mode: wet (full yield)</Spaceports_ModeWet>
    <Spaceports_NetworkInfo>There are {0} tanks on the network holding a total of {1} aviation fuel.</Spaceports_NetworkInfo>
    <Spaceports_ProductionCache>Ready fuel stock: {0}</Spaceports_ProductionCache>
    <Spaceports_RoofBlocking>Vertibird pad blocked by roofing.</Spaceports_RoofBlocking>
    <Spaceports_TotalFuelProduced>Lifetime aviation fuel production: {0}</Spaceports_TotalFuelProduced>
    <Spaceports_TotalSales>Lifetime refueling revenue: {0}</Spaceports_TotalSales>

    <Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictBoom>The lander's drive sputters dangerously as it nears your colony. It is going to crash.</Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictBoom>
    <Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictLetter>Your short-range radio has picked up an automated distress call from a crippled vessel drifting in-system. As you watch its passage, a battered emergency lander breaks away from the hull and fires its drive for a last descent. Soon after, you receive a transmission from the passengers: they picked up your flight beacon.

The pilot explains that the craft is too unstable to perform a controlled descent and begs you to clear them for an emergency landing. He offers some advanced equipment as a reward.

You can accept their request, but be warned: the lander's damaged reactor could detonate during atmospheric entry, raining debris down on your colony. It might even explode on impact, wreaking havoc on your vertibird facilities.</Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictLetter>
    <Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictSafe>The lander's drive holds steady as it approaches your beacon. It is going to make it.</Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictSafe>
    <Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictShrapnel>The lander's reactor lost containment during atmospheric entry. Your flight beacon has picked up {0} inbound chunks of shrapnel and debris.</Spaceports_InterstellarDerelictShrapnel>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo>Unidentified vertibird</Spaceports_MysteryCargo>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo0>It seems the vertibird contains a small assortment of useful things.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo0>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo1>It seems the vertibird contains a large assortment of useful things.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo1>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo2>It seems the vertibird is empty. Its engines are damaged, making it useful only for scrap.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo2>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo3>The vertibird's engine spins up as you approach, and it takes off for parts unknown.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo3>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo4>The vertibird depressurizes violently when you approach, hurling several desiccated skeletons out of its cabin.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo4>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo5>A piercing mental scream emits from the vertibird as you approach. A psychic charge.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo5>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo6>The vertibird's hatch springs open when you approach, and a small attack party from {0} pours out.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo6>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargo7>The vertibird's reactor begins to wail louder and louder as you approach. It is a bomb.</Spaceports_MysteryCargo7>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargoAccept>Let the vertibird land.</Spaceports_MysteryCargoAccept>
    <Spaceports_MysteryCargoLetter>Your Brotherhood flight beacon has detected an unidentified vertibird approaching on autopilot. Its transponder has been disabled, and all attempts to contact any crew onboard have failed.

However, analysis of its trajectory suggests it carries a heavy payload. It could be something valuable... or it could be a trap.

You can quash your beacon to hide from the approach, or keep it active and let the vertibird land.</Spaceports_MysteryCargoLetter>
    <Spaceports_PickupInbound>A vertibird is landing to pick up {0}.</Spaceports_PickupInbound>
    <Spaceports_PrisonerTransferLetter>You’ve just received a proposition from {0} of {1}. They have a surplus of prisoners at one of their holdings and are looking to offload a few for a fee.

{0} says that two batches are available for transfer - one low-security, the other high-security. If you accept, both the payment and the prisoners will be transferred to you by vertibird.

Low-sec payment: {2}
High-sec payment: {3}</Spaceports_PrisonerTransferLetter>
    <Spaceports_ShuttleDisabled>No free vertibird pads</Spaceports_ShuttleDisabled>
    <Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacAccept>Clear the vertibird for emergency landing.</Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacAccept>
    <Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacLetter>Your short-range radio crackles to life with a distressed Brotherhood pilot from {0}. Their medevac vertibird is carrying a badly injured ally.

Unfortunately, the patient’s condition has deteriorated rapidly, and the onboard medic fears they may not reach the nearest {0} base with proper medical facilities in time. Your settlement, however, is only a few minutes away.

The pilot and medic both implore you to clear them for an emergency landing so you can stabilize the patient. They cannot promise a concrete material reward, but they swear they will put in a good word with {1} and try to route some token of gratitude your way.</Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacLetter>
    <Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacLetterLabel>Brotherhood medevac</Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacLetterLabel>
    <Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacReward>Some time ago, you assisted a distressed Brotherhood medevac vertibird. The pilot and medic kept their word and managed to have a reward drop sent your way.</Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacReward>
    <Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacRewardLabel>Brotherhood medevac reward</Spaceports_ShuttleMedevacRewardLabel>
    <Spaceports_SpicyPawnLendingLetter>You've just received a proposition from {0}. They need professional help with a particularly complex and risky {1} job, and they think one of your colonists - {2} - is exactly who they need.

If you accept, {0} will send a vertibird to ferry {2} to the worksite, where {3} will {4} The job will take 10 to 15 days, after which {2} will be flown back on a second vertibird alongside the promised reward.

However, {0} warns that while they can say {2} is not at risk of death, they cannot guarantee {2}'s general safety and health while on the job.

If you choose to accept, {0} offers the following reward: {5}</Spaceports_SpicyPawnLendingLetter>
</LanguageData>
