<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.description>The highest rank that achievable in the United States Army without a political ally. This is one of the highest command positions with the ability to call in reinforcements at the company level and higher including special forces.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.label>US Army Colonel</FCP_Title_USA_Army_COL.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.description>The first rank within the United States Army's commissioned officer corps. This is the lowest command position with the ability to call in reinforcements and supplies much faster and with greater quality and quantity.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.label>US Army Lieutenant</FCP_Title_USA_Army_LT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.description>The lowest rank within the United States Army. There isn't a lot of respect in this role, nor is the pay well.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.label>US Army Private</FCP_Title_USA_Army_PVT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.description>The first rank within the United States' non commissioned officer corps. This is the first step in a professional military carrer with reaL power and responsibilities.</FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.label>US Army Sergeant</FCP_Title_USA_Army_SGT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.description>.</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.label>US Marine Colonel</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Colonel.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.description>The lowest rank within the United States Marine Corps. There isn't a lot of respect in this role, nor is the pay well.</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.label>US Marine Private</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_PVT.label>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.description>The first rank within the United States Marine Corps' non commissioned officer corps. This is the first step in a professional military career with real power and responsibilities.</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.description>
  <FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.label>US Marine Sergeant</FCP_Title_USA_Marine_Sergeant.label>
</LanguageData>