<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VPE_Archon.description>High priest revelations enthrone a leader who binds followers, drains rivals, and rules through presence and pain.</VPE_Archon.description>
  <VPE_Archon.label>high priest</VPE_Archon.label>
  <VPE_Archotechist.description>Blacksite savant revelations channel forbidden machine-thought, insanity, and weaponized neural overload.</VPE_Archotechist.description>
  <VPE_Archotechist.label>blacksite savant</VPE_Archotechist.label>
  <VPE_Chronopath.description>Doomwatcher revelations distort age, growth, and duration by clawing at the edges of time.</VPE_Chronopath.description>
  <VPE_Chronopath.label>doomwatcher</VPE_Chronopath.label>
  <VPE_Conflagrator.description>Ashcaller revelations weaponize fire, heat, and raw destructive energy in spectacular rituals.</VPE_Conflagrator.description>
  <VPE_Conflagrator.label>ashcaller</VPE_Conflagrator.label>
  <VPE_Empath.description>Mesmerist revelations soothe minds, break panic, and flood nearby followers with unnatural calm.</VPE_Empath.description>
  <VPE_Empath.label>mesmerist</VPE_Empath.label>
  <VPE_Frostshaper.description>Rimebinder revelations shape cold, ice, and entropy into barriers, traps, and killing frost.</VPE_Frostshaper.description>
  <VPE_Frostshaper.label>rimebinder</VPE_Frostshaper.label>
  <VPE_Harmonist.description>Omenweaver revelations trade fortune for misfortune, tilting the balance of events through ritual gamble.</VPE_Harmonist.description>
  <VPE_Harmonist.label>omenweaver</VPE_Harmonist.label>
  <VPE_Necropath.description>Gravecaller revelations spread dread, exploit corpses, and drag the dead back into service.</VPE_Necropath.description>
  <VPE_Necropath.label>gravecaller</VPE_Necropath.label>
  <VPE_Nightstalker.description>Nightstalker revelations reward ambush, darkness, and silent execution under a veil of unnatural shadow.</VPE_Nightstalker.description>
  <VPE_Nightstalker.label>nightstalker</VPE_Nightstalker.label>
  <VPE_Protector.description>Wardkeeper revelations shield allies, reinforce flesh, and drag researchers out of fatal danger.</VPE_Protector.description>
  <VPE_Protector.label>wardkeeper</VPE_Protector.label>
  <VPE_Skipmaster.description>Gatewalker revelations tear short-lived holes through space, moving people and objects by occult shortcut.</VPE_Skipmaster.description>
  <VPE_Skipmaster.label>gatewalker</VPE_Skipmaster.label>
  <VPE_Staticlord.description>Stormcaller revelations command lightning, blackout machinery, and turn weather into a weapon.</VPE_Staticlord.description>
  <VPE_Staticlord.label>stormcaller</VPE_Staticlord.label>
  <VPE_Technomancer.description>Relic engineer revelations wake dead circuitry, empower scavenged technology, and stitch occult insight into hardware.</VPE_Technomancer.description>
  <VPE_Technomancer.label>relic engineer</VPE_Technomancer.label>
  <VPE_Warlord.description>Battle medium revelations are selfish war rites that sharpen reflexes, speed, and killing instinct.</VPE_Warlord.description>
  <VPE_Warlord.label>battle medium</VPE_Warlord.label>
  <VPE_Wildspeaker.description>Totem speaker revelations call on beasts, brambles, and shrine-bound wilderness spirits for survival and defense.</VPE_Wildspeaker.description>
  <VPE_Wildspeaker.label>totem speaker</VPE_Wildspeaker.label>
  <VPEH_Hemosage.description>Blood sage revelations burn hemogen as ritual fuel, turning blood into pain, sacrifice, and predatory miracles.</VPEH_Hemosage.description>
  <VPEH_Hemosage.label>blood sage</VPEH_Hemosage.label>
  <VPEP_Puppeteer.description>Idol puppeteer revelations break minds, enslave wills, and turn hollowed victims into extensions of the occultist.</VPEP_Puppeteer.description>
  <VPEP_Puppeteer.label>idol puppeteer</VPEP_Puppeteer.label>
</LanguageData>