<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Flake.label>dried brahmin shrooms</Flake.label>
  <Flake.description>A crumbly dehydrated preparation of brahmin shrooms, dried and pressed into brittle chips. Highly addictive, producing a brief but intense euphoric rush. A common street chem among wasteland settlements.</Flake.description>
  <GoJuice.label>destilled brahmin shrooms</GoJuice.label>
  <GoJuice.description>A concentrated distillate extracted from brahmin shrooms under heat and pressure. The resulting compound dramatically sharpens reflexes and dulls pain, making the user temporarily lethal in combat. Highly addictive with severe withdrawal effects.</GoJuice.description>
  <Luciferium.label>smooch</Luciferium.label>
  <Luciferium.description>A mysterious pre-war compound recovered from sealed medical bunkers. Steadily enhances all physical and mental capabilities over time. The body becomes permanently dependent — missing a dose triggers a violent and ultimately fatal withdrawal. Nobody knows who made it or why.</Luciferium.description>
  <Neutroamine.label>antiseptics</Neutroamine.label>
  <Neutroamine.description>Industrial antiseptic compounds stockpiled from pre-war medical and military supplies. Required as a base ingredient for synthesizing most wasteland drugs and medicines. Too concentrated to apply directly.</Neutroamine.description>
  <Penoxycyline.label>antibiotics</Penoxycyline.label>
  <Penoxycyline.description>Pre-war antibiotics recovered from military medical kits and hospital stockpiles. Prevents common wasteland infections — bloatfly fever, bayou fungus, and the new plague — before they take hold. Must be taken every five days to remain effective.\n\nThis only prevents new infections. It does not treat existing ones, even those not yet symptomatic.</Penoxycyline.description>
  <Plant_Psychoid.label>brahmin shrooms</Plant_Psychoid.label>
  <Plant_Psychoid.description>A psychoactive mushroom variety that grows readily in brahmin waste. Mildly hallucinogenic when eaten raw, but primarily cultivated as the base ingredient for a range of stronger preparations.</Plant_Psychoid.description>
  <PsychiteTea.label>brahmin shroom kombucha</PsychiteTea.label>
  <PsychiteTea.description>A lightly fermented kombucha brewed from brahmin shrooms and water. The fermentation process mellows the psychoactive content, producing a mildly mood-lifting drink with low addiction potential. Widely consumed across settlements as a social beverage.</PsychiteTea.description>
  <PsychoidLeaves.label>brahmin shrooms</PsychoidLeaves.label>
  <PsychoidLeaves.description>Freshly harvested brahmin shrooms, still moist and pungent. Mildly psychoactive when eaten raw. Primarily used as the base ingredient for kombucha, dried chips, and more refined chem preparations.</PsychoidLeaves.description>
  <WakeUp.label>voodoo</WakeUp.label>
  <WakeUp.description>A stimulant preparation brewed from herbs, pre-war compounds, and local ingredients following old traditions. Eliminates the need for sleep and sharpens focus for hours. Prolonged use degrades health and creates dependency.</WakeUp.description>
  <Yayo.label>fermented brahmin shrooms</Yayo.label>
  <Yayo.description>Powdered fermented brahmin shroom preparation, typically snorted for a rapid and intense euphoric effect. Highly addictive and damaging with prolonged use. A potent form of the brahmin shroom product line.</Yayo.description>
</LanguageData>
