<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Megascarab.description>A massive ant swollen to enormous size by generations of radiation exposure. Its powerful mandibles can shear through bone, and it will fight to the death for its colony.</Megascarab.description>
  <Megascarab.label>obrovský robotník mravec</Megascarab.label>
  <Megaspider.description>Najagresívnejší z obrovských mravcov. Tieto stvorenia bránia svoj úľ s neúprosnou dravosťou a silnými čeľusťami.</Megaspider.description>
  <Megaspider.label>obrí vojak mravec</Megaspider.label>
  <Spelopede.description>Obrovský mravec prispôsobený pre život v podzemí. Jeho pevný exoskelet a schopnosť kopania z neho robia impozantného obyvateľa tunela.</Spelopede.description>
  <Spelopede.label>obrovský mravec</Spelopede.label>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.description>Một cái kén ứ chứa kiến ​​lửa.</Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.description>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.label>Kén kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_CocoonFireAnt.label>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.description>Một cái kén ứ chứa kiến ​​lính lửa.</Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.description>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.label>Kén kiến ​​lính cứu hỏa</Arktos_CocoonFireSoldierAnt.label>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.description>Một cái kén ứ chứa kiến ​​thợ lửa.</Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.description>
  <Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.label>Kén kiến ​​công nhân cứu hỏa</Arktos_CocoonFireWorkerAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.description>Một loài kiến ​​lửa thích nghi với cuộc sống dưới lòng đất. Móng vuốt đào và khả năng phối hợp tổ ong của nó khiến nó trở thành cư dân đường hầm đáng gờm.</Arktos_FireAnt.description>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.label>kiến lửa</Arktos_FireAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.tools.0.label>móng vuốt đầu</Arktos_FireAnt.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAnt.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAnt.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.description>Một loài kiến ​​lửa có cánh được lai tạo để giao phối và trinh sát. Bản thân nó rất mong manh, nhưng những đàn máy bay không người lái vẫn rất nguy hiểm.</Arktos_FireAntDrone.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.label>máy bay không người lái kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntDrone.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.0.label>hàm dưới</Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAntDrone.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntHive.description>Một tổ kiến ​​lửa khổng lồ. Nếu được kích hoạt, nó sẽ sinh ra thêm kiến ​​lửa và tổ ong theo thời gian, cũng như thạch côn trùng có giá trị.</Arktos_FireAntHive.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntHive.label>tổ kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntHive.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.description>Giai đoạn non của kiến ​​lửa. Ấu trùng kiến ​​lửa được kiến ​​thợ nuôi dưỡng và trưởng thành thành giai cấp tiếp theo của tổ.</Arktos_FireAntLarva.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.label>ấu trùng kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntLarva.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.0.label>hàm dưới</Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAntLarva.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.description>Nữ hoàng của loài kiến ​​lửa khổng lồ. Cô neo giữ thuộc địa, đẻ thế hệ tiếp theo và biến bất kỳ tổ nào cô sống sót thành mối đe dọa lớn hơn.</Arktos_FireAntQueen.description>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.label>nữ hoàng kiến ​​lửa</Arktos_FireAntQueen.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.0.label>móng vuốt đầu</Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireAntQueen.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.description>Loài kiến ​​lửa hung hãn nhất. Những sinh vật này bảo vệ tổ của mình bằng sự hung dữ không ngừng, chất kitin dày và bộ hàm mạnh mẽ.</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.description>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.label>kiến lính lửa</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.0.label>móng vuốt đầu</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireSoldierAnt.tools.1.label>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.description>Một con kiến ​​lửa khổng lồ được thiết kế để có sức mạnh và khả năng phục hồi. Kiến thợ cứu hỏa có tính lãnh thổ quyết liệt và duy trì tổ của chúng với lòng trung thành tuyệt đối.</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.description>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.label>kiến thợ cứu hỏa</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.label>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.0.label>hàm dưới</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.0.label>
  <Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.1.label>cái đầu</Arktos_FireWorkerAnt.tools.1.label>
  <Fish_Salmon.description>Sťahujúca ryba s tmavými šupinami a bohatým mäsom, bežná tam, kde sa studené rieky stretávajú s morom.</Fish_Salmon.description>
  <Fish_Salmon.label>údený losos</Fish_Salmon.label>
  <Fish_Bass.description>Bežný sladkovodný dravec známy náhlymi útokmi a mäsom s jemnou chuťou.</Fish_Bass.description>
  <Fish_Bass.label>reťazová zberačka</Fish_Bass.label>
  <Fish_Tilapia.description>Odolná sladkovodná ryba nachádzajúca sa v teplých riekach a rybníkoch, ktorej sa často darí tam, kde čistejšie druhy nemôžu.</Fish_Tilapia.description>
  <Fish_Tilapia.label>zvädnuté radeoko</Fish_Tilapia.label>
  <Fish_Cod.description>Studenovodná pobrežná ryba s hrubými šupinami a tuhým chrbtovým chrbtom, cenená pre svoje pevné biele mäso.</Fish_Cod.description>
  <Fish_Cod.label>obrnený osteň</Fish_Cod.label>
  <Fish_Bluefish.description>Rýchly pobrežný lovec, ktorý prenasleduje školy návnad v drsnom počasí a otvorenom príboji.</Fish_Bluefish.description>
  <Fish_Bluefish.label>búrkový plavec</Fish_Bluefish.label>
  <Fish_Guppy.description>Malý sladkovodný druh cenený pre svoje nezvyčajné riasené žiabre; jedlé, ale príliš malé na to, aby poskytli veľa mäsa.</Fish_Guppy.description>
  <Fish_Guppy.label>axolotl</Fish_Guppy.label>
  <Fish_Frostfish.description>Veľká studenovodná ryba s bledým mäsom a ťažkým telom, ktorá sa zvyčajne vyskytuje v hlbokých riekach napájaných ľadovcami.</Fish_Frostfish.description>
  <Fish_Frostfish.label>brušný kelt</Fish_Frostfish.label>
  <Fish_Catfish.description>Veľký fúzatý spodný podávač, ktorý sa po zotmení potuluje po bahnitých kanáloch a zaplavených ruinách.</Fish_Catfish.description>
  <Fish_Catfish.label>krvavý fúz</Fish_Catfish.label>
  <Fish_Piranha.description>Malá, ale agresívna sladkovodná ryba s ostrými zubami a silnými čeľusťami, často lovená ako trofejný druh.</Fish_Piranha.description>
  <Fish_Piranha.label>kanawha piranha</Fish_Piranha.label>
  <Fish_Dogfish.description>Malá pobrežná ryba podobná žralokom s drsnou kožou a ostrými zubami, ktorá sa bežne vyskytuje na skalnatých pobrežiach.</Fish_Dogfish.description>
  <Fish_Dogfish.label>pílka</Fish_Dogfish.label>
  <Fish_Marlin.description>Obrovský lovec na voľnej vode s oštepovitým ňufákom, cenený ako nebezpečný trofejný úlovok.</Fish_Marlin.description>
  <Fish_Marlin.label>deathjaw</Fish_Marlin.label>
  <Fish_Tuna.description>Veľká sťahovavá ryba z teplých morí, známa svojim mastným mäsom a silným vytrvalým výbehom.</Fish_Tuna.description>
  <Fish_Tuna.label>zapper modroplutvý</Fish_Tuna.label>
  <Fish_Flounder.description>Plochá pobrežná ryba, ktorá sa zahrabáva do bahna a prepadáva korisť pozdĺž morského dna.</Fish_Flounder.description>
  <Fish_Flounder.label>popolavý ambusher</Fish_Flounder.label>
  <Fish_Toxfish.description>Zmutovaná ryba so znečistenou vodou. Nebezpečné surové, ale stále použiteľné vo varených jedlách s nízkou nutričnou hodnotou.</Fish_Toxfish.description>
  <Fish_Toxfish.label>žiariaci gýč</Fish_Toxfish.label>
  <Plant_TreeDrago.description>Odolná púštna juka so skrútenými končatinami a listami dýky. V starej Mojave tieto stromy označovali cesty, vodu a problémy na míle ďaleko.</Plant_TreeDrago.description>
  <Plant_TreeDrago.label>joshua tree</Plant_TreeDrago.label>
  <Plant_TreeSnagroot.description>Sčernený, takmer mŕtvy strom, ktorý prežil blízky atómový výbuch. Pri ťažbe dáva mizivé množstvo dreva.</Plant_TreeSnagroot.description>
  <Plant_TreeSnagroot.label>zuhoľnatený strom</Plant_TreeSnagroot.label>
  <Ambrosia.description>A mutated fruit with thick, fibrous leaves and an unusually sweet pulp. Its natural compounds cause mild euphoria, and prolonged consumption leads to dependence. Still, it remains one of the more bearable vices the wasteland has to offer.</Ambrosia.description>
  <Ambrosia.label>punga ovocie</Ambrosia.label>
  <VCEF_RawAnchovy.description>A small silvery bait fish that travels in dense schools through estuaries and coastal shallows.</VCEF_RawAnchovy.description>
  <VCEF_RawAnchovy.label>brook silverside</VCEF_RawAnchovy.label>
  <VCEF_RawAngelfish.description>A bright reef fish with tall fins and sharp territorial behavior despite its ornamental look.</VCEF_RawAngelfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawAngelfish.label>sunscream</VCEF_RawAngelfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawAnglerfish.description>A deepwater ambush predator that waits motionless in dark pools until prey comes within reach.</VCEF_RawAnglerfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawAnglerfish.label>bog lurker</VCEF_RawAnglerfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawClownfish.description>A banded saltwater fish once common in pre-war aquariums, now found around warm reef waters.</VCEF_RawClownfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawClownfish.label>brahfin</VCEF_RawClownfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawEel.description>A long, slick fish that slips through reeds, drainage pipes, and tidal pools with ease.</VCEF_RawEel.description>
  <VCEF_RawEel.label>purple radpole</VCEF_RawEel.label>
  <VCEF_RawGoldfish.description>A plump ornamental pond fish with bright scales, descended from escaped pre-war stock.</VCEF_RawGoldfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawGoldfish.label>blisterfish</VCEF_RawGoldfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawHaddock.description>A heavy coldwater fish with a rigid back ridge and faintly luminous scales in low light.</VCEF_RawHaddock.description>
  <VCEF_RawHaddock.label>glowing spinefish</VCEF_RawHaddock.label>
  <VCEF_RawHalibut.description>A huge broad flatfish from deep coastal waters, valued for thick cuts of meat.</VCEF_RawHalibut.description>
  <VCEF_RawHalibut.label>leatherback</VCEF_RawHalibut.label>
  <VCEF_RawHerring.description>A narrow-bodied shoal fish that runs in fast coldwater schools through inlets and coves.</VCEF_RawHerring.description>
  <VCEF_RawHerring.label>timber sawgill</VCEF_RawHerring.label>
  <VCEF_RawKoi.description>A glossy freshwater pond fish, likely descended from ornamental carp strains.</VCEF_RawKoi.description>
  <VCEF_RawKoi.label>bavarian creekfin</VCEF_RawKoi.label>
  <VCEF_RawLobster.description>A small armored crustacean with little meat, usually boiled in batches for stews.</VCEF_RawLobster.description>
  <VCEF_RawLobster.label>mirelurk hatchling</VCEF_RawLobster.label>
  <VCEF_RawMackerel.description>A fast coastal fish that travels in dense shoals along piers, reefs, and cold surf lines.</VCEF_RawMackerel.description>
  <VCEF_RawMackerel.label>bavarian tidefin</VCEF_RawMackerel.label>
  <VCEF_RawMinnow.description>A tiny river fish with a red belly, commonly found schooling in clear creeks.</VCEF_RawMinnow.description>
  <VCEF_RawMinnow.label>redbelly</VCEF_RawMinnow.label>
  <VCEF_RawPerch.description>A lean freshwater hunter with yellow eyes, common in cool lakes and slow rivers.</VCEF_RawPerch.description>
  <VCEF_RawPerch.label>walleye</VCEF_RawPerch.label>
  <VCEF_RawPufferfish.description>A round-bodied fish that inflates when threatened; edible, but not highly prized for taste.</VCEF_RawPufferfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawPufferfish.label>gulpy</VCEF_RawPufferfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawSprat.description>A tiny oily bait fish found in dense cold shoals, commonly netted during seasonal coastal runs.</VCEF_RawSprat.description>
  <VCEF_RawSprat.label>alpine sawgill</VCEF_RawSprat.label>
  <VCEF_RawSwordfish.description>A fast open-water predator with a long stabbing snout and a powerful strike.</VCEF_RawSwordfish.description>
  <VCEF_RawSwordfish.label>spikesnapper</VCEF_RawSwordfish.label>
  <VCEF_RawTrout.description>A coldwater game fish commonly caught in upland rivers and snowmelt lakes.</VCEF_RawTrout.description>
  <VCEF_RawTrout.label>ridge trout</VCEF_RawTrout.label>
  <MedicineUltratech.label>Liek Vault-Tec</MedicineUltratech.label>
  <VQED_MilitaryCrateOfDeadlifeShells.description>Zhrdzavená vojenská debna plná nábojov. Tieto delostrelecké náboje sú nabité zmesou podobnou prachu, ktorá sa po detonácii usadzuje na blízkych ľudských a zvieracích mŕtvolách a vyvoláva z nich divokých vlkodlakov a vlkodlakov. Mnohé z škrupín stratili svoju účinnosť, ale niektoré môžu stále fungovať.</VQED_MilitaryCrateOfDeadlifeShells.description>
  <VQE_AncientARCPart.description>Starý, zhrdzavený fragment prototypu reaktora. Pravdepodobne bol opustený, keď bol stavebný program Moldaveru zastavený. Stále je možné ho rozobrať a získať cenné fúzne komponenty.</VQE_AncientARCPart.description>
  <VQE_AncientARCPart.label>starodávna časť reaktora</VQE_AncientARCPart.label>
  <VQE_Genetron_Basic.description>Prototyp fúzneho jadra schopného generovať veľké množstvo energie z geotermálnych základov. Neskôr ho možno upgradovať na pokročilejšie varianty reaktora, keď budú obnovené správne výskumné poznámky a hardvér. Musí byť umiestnený na parný gejzír.</VQE_Genetron_Basic.description>
  <VQE_Genetron_Basic.label>prototyp fúzneho jadra</VQE_Genetron_Basic.label>
  <VQE_GenetronJunk.description>Skrútený kus krytu reaktora z jedného z opustených projektov Moldaveru. Cenné časti sú preč a všetko ostatné sa degradovalo na šrot.</VQE_GenetronJunk.description>
  <VQE_GenetronJunk.label>reaktorový odpad</VQE_GenetronJunk.label>
  <Flake.label>dried brahmin shrooms</Flake.label>
  <Flake.description>A crumbly dehydrated preparation of brahmin shrooms, dried and pressed into brittle chips. Highly addictive, producing a brief but intense euphoric rush. A common street chem among wasteland settlements.</Flake.description>
  <GoJuice.label>destilled brahmin shrooms</GoJuice.label>
  <GoJuice.description>A concentrated distillate extracted from brahmin shrooms under heat and pressure. The resulting compound dramatically sharpens reflexes and dulls pain, making the user temporarily lethal in combat. Highly addictive with severe withdrawal effects.</GoJuice.description>
  <Luciferium.label>smooch</Luciferium.label>
  <Luciferium.description>A mysterious pre-war compound recovered from sealed medical bunkers. Steadily enhances all physical and mental capabilities over time. The body becomes permanently dependent — missing a dose triggers a violent and ultimately fatal withdrawal. Nobody knows who made it or why.</Luciferium.description>
  <Neutroamine.label>antiseptics</Neutroamine.label>
  <Neutroamine.description>Industrial antiseptic compounds stockpiled from pre-war medical and military supplies. Required as a base ingredient for synthesizing most wasteland drugs and medicines. Too concentrated to apply directly.</Neutroamine.description>
  <Penoxycyline.label>antibiotics</Penoxycyline.label>
  <Penoxycyline.description>Pre-war antibiotics recovered from military medical kits and hospital stockpiles. Prevents common wasteland infections — bloatfly fever, bayou fungus, and the new plague — before they take hold. Must be taken every five days to remain effective.\n\nThis only prevents new infections. It does not treat existing ones, even those not yet symptomatic.</Penoxycyline.description>
  <Plant_Psychoid.label>brahmin shrooms</Plant_Psychoid.label>
  <Plant_Psychoid.description>A psychoactive mushroom variety that grows readily in brahmin waste. Mildly hallucinogenic when eaten raw, but primarily cultivated as the base ingredient for a range of stronger preparations.</Plant_Psychoid.description>
  <PsychiteTea.label>brahmin shroom kombucha</PsychiteTea.label>
  <PsychiteTea.description>A lightly fermented kombucha brewed from brahmin shrooms and water. The fermentation process mellows the psychoactive content, producing a mildly mood-lifting drink with low addiction potential. Widely consumed across settlements as a social beverage.</PsychiteTea.description>
  <PsychoidLeaves.label>brahmin shrooms</PsychoidLeaves.label>
  <PsychoidLeaves.description>Freshly harvested brahmin shrooms, still moist and pungent. Mildly psychoactive when eaten raw. Primarily used as the base ingredient for kombucha, dried chips, and more refined chem preparations.</PsychoidLeaves.description>
  <WakeUp.label>voodoo</WakeUp.label>
  <WakeUp.description>A stimulant preparation brewed from herbs, pre-war compounds, and local ingredients following old traditions. Eliminates the need for sleep and sharpens focus for hours. Prolonged use degrades health and creates dependency.</WakeUp.description>
  <Yayo.label>fermented brahmin shrooms</Yayo.label>
  <Yayo.description>Powdered fermented brahmin shroom preparation, typically snorted for a rapid and intense euphoric effect. Highly addictive and damaging with prolonged use. A potent form of the brahmin shroom product line.</Yayo.description>
  <VDE_Dryad_Gaubricmaker.label>schovávačka treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Gaubricmaker.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Nectarmaker.label>sapbrewer treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Nectarmaker.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Spitter.label>spitter treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Spitter.label>
  <VDE_Dryad_Stonedigger.label>stonedigger treeminder</VDE_Dryad_Stonedigger.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.description>Vysoká slávnostná pokrývka hlavy, ktorá mala označovať vodcu organizovanej viery alebo kultu pustatiny.</VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.label>vysoký kazateľský klobúk</VIEHAR_Apparel_BishopHat.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_BrimlessHat.description>Malý obyčajný klobúk, ktorý mal jemne spočívať na hlave. Tí, ktorí ho uprednostňujú, často tvrdia, že im dáva vzhľad starosvetského mystika.</VIEHAR_Apparel_BrimlessHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.description>Výrazná čiapka s okrajom zdobená odznakom hodnosti, ktorá má za každú cenu podnecovať podriadených k poslušnosti.</VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.label>čiapka dozorcu</VIEHAR_Apparel_CommisarHat.label>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_Fez.description>Kužeľovitý klobúk s plochým vrcholom zdobený čiernym strapcom, ktorý často nosia púštni obchodníci, šéfovia karaván a iné elity starých ciest.</VIEHAR_Apparel_Fez.description>
  <VIEHAR_Apparel_Rags.description>Súprava obnosených handier určených na zakrytie tela s minimálnym rozruchom. Neposkytujú takmer žiadnu ochranu ani teplo, ale jasne signalizujú život v prísnosti a tvrdej pustatinskej oddanosti.</VIEHAR_Apparel_Rags.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>Pozostatky Treefathera, nasekané a ponechané ako peň.</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>nasekaný peň Treefathera</ChoppedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Basic.description>Základný treeminder, podobný cicavcom a verný svojmu Treefatherovi. Podľa potreby sa môže premeniť na špecializované kasty.</Dryad_Basic.description>
  <Dryad_Basic.label>treeminder</Dryad_Basic.label>
  <DryadCocoon.description>Kokon, v ktorom sa stromobežník premení na novú kastu, vedený koreňmi Treefathera s FEV.</DryadCocoon.description>
  <DryadCocoon.label>kukla stromomila</DryadCocoon.label>
  <DryadHealingPod.description>Lusk naplnený regeneračnou šťavou Treefather, ktorý sa používa na liečenie zranených stromoradí.</DryadHealingPod.description>
  <DryadHealingPod.label>liečivý struk</DryadHealingPod.label>
  <GaumakerCocoon.description>Kokon, kde sa klíčky spájajú a vytvárajú nový struk Treefather, ktorý pokračuje v symbiotickom cykle.</GaumakerCocoon.description>
  <GaumakerCocoon.label>klíčiaci kokon</GaumakerCocoon.label>
  <GauranlenSeed.description>Semeno od Treefathera, schopné vypestovať nový zmutovaný strom a začať symbiotický cyklus.</GauranlenSeed.description>
  <GauranlenSeed.label>Semeno Treefather</GauranlenSeed.label>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.description>Náplasť machu, ktorá rastie okolo Treefathera, skrášľuje oblasť a pomáha pri produkcii stromoradia.</Plant_MossGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_MossGauranlen.label>Stromový mach</Plant_MossGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.description>Lusk vyrobený Treefatherom, obsahujúci semená nových stromovopohľadov.</Plant_PodGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_PodGauranlen.label>Treefather pod</Plant_PodGauranlen.label>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>Zmutovaný strom naplnený FEV, schopný produkovať stromoradie a struky. Jeho korene siahajú hlboko a spájajú ho s tajomstvami pustatiny.</Plant_TreeGauranlen.description>
  <Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>Stromový otec</Plant_TreeGauranlen.label>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>Pozostatky Treefathera, rozbité a ponechané ako peň.</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.description>
  <SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>rozbil peň Treefathera</SmashedStump_Gauranlen.label>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies.</Dryad_Barkskin.description>
  <Dryad_Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Dryad_Barkskin.label>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.description>A treeminder caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. It is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Berrymaker.description>
  <Dryad_Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Dryad_Berrymaker.label>
  <Dryad_Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Carrier.description>
  <Dryad_Carrier.label>portling</Dryad_Carrier.label>
  <Dryad_Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation.</Dryad_Clawer.description>
  <Dryad_Clawer.label>scratchling</Dryad_Clawer.label>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process.</Dryad_Gaumaker.description>
  <Dryad_Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Dryad_Gaumaker.label>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Medicinemaker.description>
  <Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Dryad_Medicinemaker.label>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Dryad_Woodmaker.description>
  <Dryad_Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Dryad_Woodmaker.label>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.description>Pomalá, potácajúca sa kasta treeminder, ktorá sa špecializuje na výrobu punga. Spolu so stromom Gauranlen môže táto dryáda neustále vytvárať ovocie punga. Je to však pomalé a neefektívne v práci alebo boji.\n\nVo všeobecnosti sú treeminders stvorenia podobné cicavcom, ktoré majú symbiotický vzťah s otcom stromu. Rozmnožujú sa spolu so svojím stromom, ktorý obsahuje vzorky FEV. Treemindi sa môžu premeniť na rôzne špecializované kasty.</Dryad_Pungaling.description>
  <Dryad_Pungaling.label>štipľavý treeminder</Dryad_Pungaling.label>
  <ShuttleCrashing.label>vertibird (crashing)</ShuttleCrashing.label>
  <TransportPod.description>Automated cargo bots used to deliver people and supplies across the planet.</TransportPod.description>
  <TransportPod.label>cargo bot</TransportPod.label>
  <AnimusStone.description>A resonant cryptic stone studied by Whitespring researchers. It increases cryptid meditation focus and is often used in enclave research facilities.</AnimusStone.description>
  <AnimusStone.label>cryptic stone</AnimusStone.label>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.description>A stump left behind after an Mothman totem has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</ChoppedStump_Anima.description>
  <ChoppedStump_Anima.label>chopped Mothman stump</ChoppedStump_Anima.label>
  <NatureShrine_Large.description>A large shrine for honoring cryptid forces. Whitespring operatives use these to amplify cryptid focus during ritualized study.</NatureShrine_Large.description>
  <NatureShrine_Large.label>large cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Large.label>
  <NatureShrine_Small.description>A small shrine used by cryptid researchers to focus meditation and study. These shrines strengthen cryptid-focused meditation for Whitespring operatives.</NatureShrine_Small.description>
  <NatureShrine_Small.label>small cryptic shrine</NatureShrine_Small.label>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.description>Mysterious black eggs with a red glow. Tribal peoples find that these eggs grow around the base of a Mothman totem as they meditate. It seems to reflect some kind of strengthening of the totem's cryptic power.\n\nWasteland scientists have tried to study the phenomenon, but the eggs fail to hatch when observed too closely.\n\nAnimals refuse eat Mothman eggs. Tribal stories say this is done out of respect and fear.</Plant_GrassAnima.description>
  <Plant_GrassAnima.label>Mothman eggs</Plant_GrassAnima.label>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.description>A Mothman totem used by Appalachia cultists to focus their meditation and worship.</Plant_TreeAnima.description>
  <Plant_TreeAnima.label>Mothman totem</Plant_TreeAnima.label>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.description>The remnants of an Mothman totem destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</SmashedStump_Anima.description>
  <SmashedStump_Anima.label>smashed Mothman stump</SmashedStump_Anima.label>
  <Chemshine.description>A harsh, flammable wasteland liquor distilled from chemfuel. Rot gut dulls pain and misery for a while, but it leaves the drinker soaked in volatile fumes and can turn a bad death into a fireball.</Chemshine.description>
  <Chemshine.label>rot gut</Chemshine.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>Pozlátená pálenica s veľmi jemným remeselným spracovaním určená na vyzrievanie muštu do pitnej podoby.</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>punshine stále</VBE_AmbrandyDistillery.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>Nakrájané a lisované ovocie punga pripravené na dozrievanie smerom k pungashine.</VBE_AmbrandyMush.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>pungashine kaša</VBE_AmbrandyMush.label>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>Úplne vyzretý základ likéru punga, pripravený na destiláciu na pungashin.</VBE_AmbrandyMust.description>
  <VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>pungashine mušt</VBE_AmbrandyMust.label>
  <VBE_Cigarettes.description>Malá zrolovaná papierová trubica voľne plnená žuvačkou z kojotieho tabaku. Ponúka krátku eufóriu, miernu stimuláciu a rovnaký zatuchnutý zápach pustatiny, ktorý fajčiarov núti vracať sa.</VBE_Cigarettes.description>
  <VBE_Cigars.description>Hustá cigara šúľaná zo žuvania kojotieho tabaku a hotová pre drahšie, premyslené fajčenie. Pod efektnou prezentáciou nesie drsnú púštnu horkosť.</VBE_Cigars.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.description>Ostrá šumivá fľaša guarany zakončená horkosťou a rádioaktívnou pachuťou. Vpredu tvrdo narazí a na druhej strane necháva čakať náraz.</VBE_EnergyDrink.description>
  <VBE_EnergyDrink.label>guarana</VBE_EnergyDrink.label>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.description>Jemný atomový kokteil, precízne namiešaný z viacerých ingrediencií.</VBE_FineCocktail.description>
  <VBE_FineCocktail.label>jemný atómový koktail</VBE_FineCocktail.label>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>Zázrak mixológie, kde každý pohár, obloha a miešanie boli vyladené do gurmánskeho atómového kokteilu.</VBE_GourmetCocktail.description>
  <VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>gurmánsky atómový koktail</VBE_GourmetCocktail.label>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.description>Bohatý atómový koktail namiešaný zo širokej škály ingrediencií a pred podávaním dokonale vychladený.</VBE_LavishCocktail.description>
  <VBE_LavishCocktail.label>bohatý atómový koktail</VBE_LavishCocktail.label>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>Odolný stojan s kojotím tabakom vhodný pre Mohavské a iné suché pustatinné podnebie. Po vytvrdnutí sa z listov stane žuvanie kojotieho tabaku na fajčenie, valcovanie alebo obchodovanie.</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.description>
  <VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>kojotí tabak</VBE_Plant_Tobacco.label>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.description>Vákuovo uzavreté plechovky na predvojnovú instantnú kávu. Horké, stabilné a stále dostatočne silné na to, aby ukotvilo každú raňajkovú službu Lucky 38.</VBE_RawCoffee.description>
  <VBE_RawCoffee.label>instantná káva</VBE_RawCoffee.label>
  <VBE_RawTea.description>Sušené predvojnové čajové lístky uložené v dóze Lucky 38. Držia sa dobre a stále strmé do riadneho použiteľného pohára.</VBE_RawTea.description>
  <VBE_RawTea.label>sušené čajové lístky</VBE_RawTea.label>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.description>Vyliečené vrecko na žuvanie kojotieho tabaku. Dostatočne suché na fajčenie, rolovanie alebo balenie do bohatších zmesí s prašným kúskom, ktorý fajčiari v pustatine očakávajú.</VBE_RawTobacco.description>
  <VBE_RawTobacco.label>žuvanie kojotieho tabaku</VBE_RawTobacco.label>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>Jednoduchý atomový kokteil rýchlo namiešaný z dua ingrediencií.</VBE_SimpleCocktail.description>
  <VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>jednoduchý atómový koktail</VBE_SimpleCocktail.label>
  <VBE_Soda.description>Sladká šumivá fľaša domácej sarsaparilly. Je to viac osviežujúce ako výživné, ale vychladená fľaša stále pôsobí ako predvojnový luxus.</VBE_Soda.description>
  <VBE_Soda.label>domáca sarsaparilla</VBE_Soda.label>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.description>Jednotka na plnenie domácej sarsaparilly všetko v jednom. Sirup sa premieša, sýti oxidom uhličitým, ochladí sa a naplní sa do sterilizovaných fliaš.</VBE_SodaFountain.description>
  <VBE_SodaFountain.label>domáca fontána sarsaparilla</VBE_SodaFountain.label>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.description>Hustý, intenzívne sladký základ pre domácu sarsaparillu. Pred podávaním sa má nakrájať, sýtiť oxidom uhličitým a plniť do fliaš.</VBE_SodaSyrup.description>
  <VBE_SodaSyrup.label>domáci sirup sarsaparilla</VBE_SodaSyrup.label>
  <CashRegister_CashRegister.description>Registračný stôl pre salónikové služby, jedálenské stoly a domáce účty. Nerobí nič samo o sebe, ale ukotvuje prevádzku pred domom.</CashRegister_CashRegister.description>
  <CashRegister_CashRegister.label>registračný pult</CashRegister_CashRegister.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineBlue.description>Prémiová automatová banka Lucky 38 postavená na hranie s vysokými limitmi, leštená mosadz a hladný dom.</HC_SlotMachineBlue.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineBlue.label>šťastných 38 kotúčov s vysokými valcami</HC_SlotMachineBlue.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineGreen.description>Banka s automatmi z éry House vyladená pre pravidelných zákazníkov a spoľahlivú nočnú prevádzku.</HC_SlotMachineGreen.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineGreen.label>šťastných 38 štandardných kotúčov</HC_SlotMachineGreen.label>
  <HC_SlotMachineRed.description>Rekultivovaný hrací automat Vault 21 so skromným vkladom a odpúšťajúcou hranou domu.</HC_SlotMachineRed.description>
  <HC_SlotMachineRed.label>trezor 21 centov sloty</HC_SlotMachineRed.label>
  <VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.description>A polished Lucky 38 Luxobrew coffee pot rebuilt for high-volume service. It handles espresso pulls, reheating chilled coffee, and tea blends from a single compact station.</VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.description>
  <VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.label>luxobrew coffee pot</VBE_EspressoMachineBuilding.label>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.description>Bright carrot flowers used to freshen brewed drinks and garnish wasteland dishes.</VBE_MintLeaves.description>
  <VBE_MintLeaves.label>carrot flowers</VBE_MintLeaves.label>
  <VBE_MintPlant.description>A stand of carrot flowers used for bright herbal garnish in teas and coffee blends.</VBE_MintPlant.description>
  <VBE_MintPlant.label>carrot flower patch</VBE_MintPlant.label>
  <Chocolate.description>Starostlivo zabalená skrýša predvojnovej čokolády. Bohaté, sladké a stále dostatočne dekadentné na ukotvenie dezertov a sirupov.</Chocolate.description>
  <Chocolate.label>konzervovaná čokoláda</Chocolate.label>
  <VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>Vzácna predvojnová lekárska suspenzia prebalená pre kuchyňu Lucky 38. Keď sa aqua cura zloží do jedla, zaplaví telo núdzovými opravnými nanitmi, ktoré môžu pritiahnuť stravníka späť zo smrti.</VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.description>
  <VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>aqua cura</VCE_DigestibleResurrectorNanites.label>
  <VCE_RawSpices.description>Konzervovaná zmes predvojnového kuchynského korenia zapečatená v špajzi Lucky 38. V každej plechovke prežije dostatok na rozjasnenie dusených pokrmov, omáčok a grilov.</VCE_RawSpices.description>
  <VCE_RawSugar.description>Zapečatené balíčky predvojnového cukru získané zo starých kuchýň a špajz. Uchováva na neurčito a stále dodáva rovnaký rýchly príval sladkosti.</VCE_RawSugar.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>Hutné, opojné maslo stúlené na pôžitkárske varenie Lucky 38. Bohato sa šíri, tvrdo zasiahne a premení akékoľvek jedlo na zlý nápad s vynikajúcou chuťou.</VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>brahmin shroom maslo</VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>
  <VCEV_CookingBook.description>Zbitá kuchárska kniha plná vynovených receptov, poznámok o ingredienciách a predvojnových kuchynských trikov.

Po prečítaní dá čitateľovi novú obľúbenú ingredienciu alebo jedlo a potom sa rozpadne z jedného príliš veľkého počtu rúk v kuchyni.</VCEV_CookingBook.description>
  <VCEV_CookingBook.label>pustatina kuchárska kniha</VCEV_CookingBook.label>
  <Gastronomy_Waiting.description>Prijíma objednávky a podáva jedlá pre hostí vo vašich salónikoch a jedálňach.</Gastronomy_Waiting.description>
  <CashRegister_Mech.description>Automatizovaný servisný terminál pre obsluhu mechanoidov. Odtiaľto môžete riadiť stravovanie a prevádzky pred domom.</CashRegister_Mech.description>
  <CashRegister_Mech.label>autonómny servisný terminál</CashRegister_Mech.label>
  <SmallHotSpring.description>Starostlivo opracovaný horúci prameň vybudovaný nad parným gejzírom. Jeho minerálne vody ponúkajú meditatívnu relaxáciu, mierne regeneračné účinky a prémiové vybavenie kúpeľov až pre štyroch pešiakov naraz.</SmallHotSpring.description>
  <SmallHotSpring.label>letovisko horúci prameň</SmallHotSpring.label>
  <HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.label>vyberať poplatky za kúpele</HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.label>
  <HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.verb>vyberať poplatky za kúpele</HospitalitySpa_WithdrawVendingMachineEarnings.verb>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>Bizarná archotech signálna erupcia, ktorá z ničoho nič privolá vertibirda. Akákoľvek inteligencia odpovie, je ochotná poskytnúť jeden zázračný výťažok.</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.description>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>vzplanutie signálu vertibirdu</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.label>
  <Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>pop signálne vzplanutie</Apparel_ArchoShuttle.verbs.0.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>Jednorazový poľný transpondér používaný na vyžiadanie vyzdvihnutia vertibirdu Brotherhood.</Apparel_ShuttleComm.description>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>Poľný transpondér Bratstva</Apparel_ShuttleComm.label>
  <Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>zavolajte vyzdvihnutie vertibirdu</Apparel_ShuttleComm.verbs.0.label>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.description>Maják IFF s dlhým dosahom a stožiar na riadenie premávky používaný bunkami Bratstva a dôveryhodnými spojencami na propagovanie bezpečného priblíženia vertibirdov, koordináciu pristátí a vysielanie dostupnosti tankovania.</Spaceports_Beacon.description>
  <Spaceports_Beacon.label>Letový maják bratstva</Spaceports_Beacon.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>Servisný terminál, ktorý predáva letecké palivo vertibirdom Brotherhood a iným autorizovaným lietadlám. Musí byť umiestnená vedľa podložky vertibird; akonáhle je platba overená, čerpadlá vo vnútri podložky čerpajú palivo z nádrží v rovnakej elektrickej sieti.</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>tankovací terminál vertibird</Spaceports_FuelDispenser.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>Priemyselný procesor, ktorý rafinuje prchavé suroviny a vodu na letecké palivo pre vertibirdy Brotherhood. Funguje najlepšie s prístupom vody a premení nadbytočné chemfuel na predajné letové zásoby.</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>procesor leteckého paliva</Spaceports_FuelProcessor.label>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.description>Chladiaca nádrž na spracované letecké palivo. Udržujte ho napájaný, inak sa vývar začne odparovať.</Spaceports_FuelTank.description>
  <Spaceports_FuelTank.label>nádrž na letecké palivo</Spaceports_FuelTank.label>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>Tvrdená pristávacia plocha s navádzacími svetlami, prípojkami na dobíjanie paliva a šifrovaným transpondérom pre vertibirdov Bratstva. Udržujte ho napájaný a čistý a hosťujúce hliadky, ubytovne, obchodníci a spriaznení pasažieri tu môžu pristáť.</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.description>
  <Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>Bratská podložka vertibird</Spaceports_ShuttleLandingPad.label>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>Označuje konfigurovateľný bod, kde sa po pristátí bude zhromažďovať hosťujúci personál Bratstva, obchodníci a spriaznení pasažieri. Ak sa nenájde žiadny platný bod, zostanú blízko svojho vertibirda.</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.description>
  <Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>bod zhromažďovania vertibirdov</Spaceports_VisitorSpot.label>
  <VCE_Chirashizushi.label>mirelurk miska (jednoduchá)</VCE_Chirashizushi.label>
  <VCE_DeepFriedSushi.label>hlboko vyprážané číhať</VCE_DeepFriedSushi.label>
  <VCE_Futomaki.label>futolurk (okázalý)</VCE_Futomaki.label>
  <VCE_Gunkanmaki.label>gunkanlurk (gurmán)</VCE_Gunkanmaki.label>
  <VCE_Nigiri.label>Murkiri (v pohode)</VCE_Nigiri.label>
  <VCE_Norimaki.label>norilurk (jednoduché)</VCE_Norimaki.label>
  <VCE_Oshizushi.label>oshilurk (gurmán)</VCE_Oshizushi.label>
  <VCE_RawSoybean.description>Tart pustatina brusnice. Môžu sa jesť surové, varené do konzerv alebo fermentované na hustú stolovú omáčku.</VCE_RawSoybean.description>
  <VCE_RawSoybean.label>brusnice</VCE_RawSoybean.label>
  <VCE_RawWasabi.label>koreň xandera</VCE_RawWasabi.label>
  <VCE_Soybean.description>Odolný krík brusníc pestovaný pre ostré červené bobule. Ovocie sa uvarí do bohatej omáčky, ktorá zastupuje starosvetský reťazec fermentovaných korenín.</VCE_Soybean.description>
  <VCE_Soybean.label>brusnicový ker</VCE_Soybean.label>
  <VCE_SoyFermenter.label>kadička s brusnicovou omáčkou</VCE_SoyFermenter.label>
  <VCE_SoySauce.description>Bohatá brusnicová redukcia používaná ako dip, glazúra a slano-sladká omáčka na záver na sushi a morské plody z pustiny.</VCE_SoySauce.description>
  <VCE_SoySauce.label>brusnicová omáčka</VCE_SoySauce.label>
  <VCE_Temaki.label>temlurk (okázalý)</VCE_Temaki.label>
  <VCE_Uramaki.label>uralurk (v pohode)</VCE_Uramaki.label>
  <VCE_Wasabi.description>Náplasť z koreňa xandera cenená pre svoje štipľavé uhryznutie. Keď sa rozomelie na pastu, je to silné korenie na jedlá z morských plodov a ryže.</VCE_Wasabi.description>
  <VCE_Wasabi.label>xander root patch</VCE_Wasabi.label>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.description>Ostrá pasta vyrobená z mletého koreňa xanderu a používaná ako štipľavé korenie do sushi a iných jedál z morských plodov.</VCE_WasabiPaste.description>
  <VCE_WasabiPaste.label>pasta z koreňov xander</VCE_WasabiPaste.label>
  <Therapist.description>Pomôžte kolonistom a patrónom prekonať stres, traumu a závislosť v súkromnej poradni.</Therapist.description>
  <Therapist.gerundLabel>poradenstvo</Therapist.gerundLabel>
  <Therapist.labelShort>poradca</Therapist.labelShort>
  <MedievalVendingMachine.description>Nízkotechnický kiosk pre zákazníkov, ktorý nepotrebuje elektrinu.</MedievalVendingMachine.description>
  <MedievalVendingMachine.label>servisný kiosk</MedievalVendingMachine.label>
  <VendingMachine.description>Predvojnový kiosk zásobený návštevníkmi, návštevou kasín a davom nečinných salónikov.</VendingMachine.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.description>A Poseidon home reactor powered by scavenged dark archotechnology. It burns bioferrite to agitate atmospheric gases, raising the outdoor temperature while flooding the area with waste heat.</AtmosphericHeater.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.label>Poseidon home reactor</AtmosphericHeater.label>
  <BioferriteGenerator.description>An experimental generator that works by pressurizing and igniting bioferrite, then harvesting energy from the resulting heat. The fuel remains bioferrite, but the chassis and control layout read like a harsh Poseidon prototype.</BioferriteGenerator.description>
  <BioferriteShaper.description>A specialized shaping bench that uses heat and electromagnetic stimulation to temporarily coax bioferrite into a pliable state. The material remains bioferrite, but the surrounding hardware fits cleanly into a Fallout-style industrial workshop.</BioferriteShaper.description>
  <SerumCentrifuge.description>A Med-Tek serum lab that uses scavenged archotechnology to create single-use injectable serums. Clean, expensive, and morally questionable in exactly the right pre-War way.</SerumCentrifuge.description>
  <SerumCentrifuge.label>Med-Tek serum lab</SerumCentrifuge.label>
  <RB_FloorLamp.description>A floor-mounted Wattz lamp that lights an area using electricity. It is less powerful than a standing lamp, but it looks right at home in a retro-futurist sitting room.</RB_FloorLamp.description>
  <Chemfuel.description>A refined liquid fuel suitable for generators, burners, and industrial feed systems. In a saner age Poseidon would have sold it through a smiling subsidiary with a patriotic slogan.</Chemfuel.description>
  <Chemfuel.label>oil</Chemfuel.label>
  <PS_ChemfuelTank.description>An industrial storage tank meant for oil delivered through the pipe network. Tanks can be siphoned for usable fuel as needed, but even light damage can turn leaking vapors into a violent fireball.</PS_ChemfuelTank.description>
  <PS_ChemfuelTank.label>oil tank</PS_ChemfuelTank.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.description>A basin meant to feed stored oil into the network and fill connected tanks.</VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.label>oil drain</VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.description>Steel pipes designed to move usable oil from deepchem refineries to oil tanks for storage or to oil-fed structures for automatic refilling.</VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.label>oil pipe</VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelTap.description>A basin meant to hold dispensed oil from storage tanks for later use.</VCHE_ChemfuelTap.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelTap.label>oil tap</VCHE_ChemfuelTap.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelValve.description>Switches oil flow on or off.</VCHE_ChemfuelValve.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelValve.label>oil valve</VCHE_ChemfuelValve.label>
  <VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.description>Buried steel pipes designed to move usable oil from deepchem refineries to oil tanks for storage or to oil-fed structures for automatic refilling.</VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.description>
  <VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.label>subterranean oil pipe</VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.label>
  <Battery.description>A Poseidon reserve battery for holding excess electricity. Charged units remain dangerous when exposed to rain or fire, regardless of what the brochure claims.</Battery.description>
  <BiofuelRefinery.description>A Poseidon refinery that converts biological matter into oil for generators, burners, and industrial storage systems.</BiofuelRefinery.description>
  <BiofuelRefinery.label>oil refinery</BiofuelRefinery.label>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming oil. It must be periodically refueled by hand unless your settlement has the industrial habits of an actual Poseidon facility.</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>oil generator</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>
  <CommsConsole.description>A Wattz communications console for contacting other factions and orbital traders. Big, expensive, and full of humming pre-War electronics.</CommsConsole.description>
  <Cooler.description>An Appalachia Freeze cooling unit that pushes cold air to one side and hot exhaust to the other. It can preserve food or simply make summer tolerable if the rest of the grid holds.</Cooler.description>
  <DeepDrill.description>A Corvega deep-crust drilling rig for extracting minerals from far below the surface. Use a ground-penetrating scanner to detect the best seams.</DeepDrill.description>
  <DrugLab.description>A powered industrial chem lab with containers, heaters, and measurement devices for efficient batch processing of drugs and compounds.</DrugLab.description>
  <ElectricCrematorium.description>A heavy industrial crematorium that vaporizes corpses at extreme temperatures. It is efficient, impersonal, and unmistakably pre-War in temperament.</ElectricCrematorium.description>
  <ElectricSmelter.description>A Corvega reclamation smelter that extracts usable metal from slag and mixed scrap. It consumes a lot of power and throws off serious industrial heat.</ElectricSmelter.description>
  <ElectricSmelter.label>Corvega reclamation smelter</ElectricSmelter.label>
  <FabricationBench.description>A Corvega fabrication bench equipped with advanced tools for producing sophisticated machines and components from simpler materials.</FabricationBench.description>
  <FirefoamPopper.description>A Wattz safety device that sprays fire-retardant foam when it detects a blaze. Exactly the kind of sensible utility hardware that survives long after the corporation that sold it is gone.</FirefoamPopper.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>A Radiation King flatscreen television with crystal-clear image and rich color. Trust the king for all your TV and radio needs.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <GeothermalGenerator.description>A Poseidon geothermal plant that taps deep heat for steady, high-output power. It is exactly the kind of hulking civic infrastructure Poseidon loved to dominate a skyline with.</GeothermalGenerator.description>
  <GeothermalGenerator.label>geothermal plant</GeothermalGenerator.label>
  <Heater.description>A Wattz Electronics heating unit that converts electricity into controlled room heat. It automatically cycles to reach a target temperature.</Heater.description>
  <HiTechResearchBench.description>A Wattz high-tech research bench with computers and electronic measurement equipment. It enables rapid research and more advanced technical projects.</HiTechResearchBench.description>
  <HospitalBed.description>A Med-Tek hospital bed specially designed for clinical care. Adjustable support geometry and integrated instruments improve patient outcomes over ordinary beds.</HospitalBed.description>
  <MegascreenTelevision.description>A huge Radiation King television for settlements that want their entertainment loud, bright, and impossible to ignore.</MegascreenTelevision.description>
  <NutrientPasteDispenser.description>An industrial dispenser that synthesizes edible nutrient paste from feedstocks placed in adjacent hoppers. Efficient, joyless, and exactly the sort of machine a large contractor would call progress.</NutrientPasteDispenser.description>
  <OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>A Wattz orbital trade beacon used to mark goods for exchange with orbital merchants. Dependable, compact, and built for practical frontier commerce.</OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>
  <PowerConduit.description>A bundle of utility cables for moving power around a settlement. It can be placed under walls and other structures as part of a proper pre-War grid.</PowerConduit.description>
  <SolarGenerator.description>A Poseidon Civilian Helios Two solar panel array for settlement-scale power generation. It delivers its best output under full daylight and clear skies.</SolarGenerator.description>
  <SolarGenerator.label>civilian Helios Two</SolarGenerator.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>A Radiation King tube television built around bulky old display hardware and a distinctly pre-War sense of domestic prestige.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <VanometricPowerCell.description>A compact power cell that generates free energy forever without conventional fuel. Even by pre-War standards it feels less like engineering and more like a secret Poseidon program nobody was meant to understand.</VanometricPowerCell.description>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>A Med-Tek patient telemetry unit that improves tend quality, surgery success, and recovery when mounted directly beside a hospital bed.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>A Poseidon hydro unit designed to draw steady power from moving water. Crowded placements create turbulence and reduce output.</WatermillGenerator.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.label>hydro turbine</WatermillGenerator.label>
  <WindTurbine.description>A utility-grade wind turbine for civilian settlements. It needs a broad, clear approach to keep airflow stable.</WindTurbine.description>
  <WindTurbine.label>civilian wind turbine</WindTurbine.label>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>A large Corvega automated field machine that combines sowing and harvesting across a designated outdoor zone. It deposits harvested goods into attached factory hoppers or drops them on the ground if hoppers are not present, and can be set to cycle automatically once most plants in the zone are fully grown.</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>agri-industrial harvester</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>A Corvega automated refinery that converts biological matter such as wood and plant stock into chemfuel.

Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>Corvega oil refinery</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>An automated Corvega deep extraction rig for pulling stone and buried metals up from the crust. Works machinery needs hoppers for intake and output, throws off serious heat, and can be overclocked at the cost of even greater draw and temperature.</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>Corvega drill platform</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>An industrial Corvega masonry saw capable of cutting stone chunks into usable blocks.

Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>automated masonry line</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>A Corvega automated smelter that extracts usable metal from slag chunks, broken-down weapons, apparel, stone chunks, and mechanoid corpses using strong electromagnets and industrial heat.

Factory buildings need factory hoppers for input and output. They produce significant heat and consume much power, but can be overclocked for higher efficiency, increasing both heat generation and power consumption. Needs to be constructed on factory floor.</VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>A basic industrial conveyor for moving materials between work cells with minimal labor handling.</VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>industrial conveyor</VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>Stores feedstock and finished goods for automated Corvega works machinery.</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>works hopper</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>A buried intake point that lets an industrial conveyor run beneath short stretches of ground before resurfacing.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>buried conveyor intake</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>A buried discharge point that brings an underground conveyor back to the surface near the next work cell.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>buried conveyor discharge</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>A tall propane floodlight that illuminates a massive area. It is not bright enough for crop growth, but it provides dependable yard lighting when connected to the propane network.</VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>propane floodlight</VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.description>A propane-fed standing lamp for utility lighting. It must be connected to the propane network and can be placed safely outdoors.</VHGE_GasLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.label>propane lamp</VHGE_GasLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>An industrial lamp bright enough for crop growth, but it burns a steady supply of propane. It shuts itself off at night.</VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>propane sun lamp</VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>A propane-fed wall light for utility corridors and work rooms. It must be connected to the propane network and can be placed safely outdoors.</VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>propane wall lamp</VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>
  <VHGE_Helixien.description>Propane gas.</VHGE_Helixien.description>
  <VHGE_Helixien.label>propane</VHGE_Helixien.label>
  <Facility_IVDrip.description>A Med-Tek intravenous drip stand for rapidly delivering lost fluids to a patient, helping immunity gain and blood loss recovery when placed directly adjacent to a hospital bed or surgical table. Only works for hospital beds or surgical tables; normal beds will not benefit. Attaching more than one stand to the same bed has no effect.</Facility_IVDrip.description>
  <Facility_IVDrip.label>Med-Tek IV stand</Facility_IVDrip.label>
  <Facility_VitalsCentre.description>A large Med-Tek centre for monitoring the vitals of several patients at once, improving tend quality, surgery success, and immunity gain when linked to hospital beds or surgical suites.</Facility_VitalsCentre.description>
  <Facility_VitalsCentre.label>Med-Tek vitals centre</Facility_VitalsCentre.label>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>A bedside Mama Dolce feeding device that delivers nutrient paste directly to bedridden patients when linked to a nutrient vat. Practical, clinical, and just unsettling enough to feel authentic.</VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>A compact Corvega feeder that outputs nutrient paste from the pipe network for routine worker consumption.</VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>A Mama Dolce nutrient grinder that reduces organic feedstocks into pipeline-ready paste stock. Efficient, impersonal, and very much in the spirit of industrial pre-War food engineering.</VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>A Mama Dolce paste tap that dispenses prepared nutrient meals from the vat network. It is the kind of practical cafeteria hardware a large contractor would install by the hundred.</VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>A Corvega storage vat for holding large volumes of processed nutrient paste. Destroying one makes exactly the kind of industrial mess you would expect.</VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedBattery.description>A sealed Poseidon battery unit with far better efficiency than common storage cells. These pre-War housings are rainproof and less prone to catastrophic discharge.</VFE_AdvancedBattery.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.description>A high-efficiency Poseidon solar array marketed as the Industrial Helios Two, built to pull significantly more charge from direct sunlight than ordinary civilian panels.</VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.label>industrial Helios Two</VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.description>A Poseidon hydro unit designed to draw industrial power from moving water. Crowded installations create turbulence and reduce output.</VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.label>industrial hydro turbine</VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.description>A pre-War Poseidon utility turbine built for industrial output. It needs broad clear approaches to keep airflow stable and advertises the sort of oversized confidence Poseidon loved to stamp on its public works.</VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.label>industrial wind turbine</VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.label>
  <VFE_LargeAdvancedBattery.description>A large sealed Poseidon battery bank built for dependable utility storage. Unlike older packs, these housings withstand rain without exploding.</VFE_LargeAdvancedBattery.description>
  <VFE_LargeBattery.description>A large Poseidon battery bank meant to hold reserve power for later demand. Fully charged units are dangerous when exposed to rain or fire.</VFE_LargeBattery.description>
  <VFE_SmallBattery.description>A compact reserve battery for local circuits and small industrial loads. Charged units can still blow when exposed to rain or fire.</VFE_SmallBattery.description>
  <VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.description>A powered Corvega assembly bench fitted for turning raw stock into industrial and spacer-grade components.</VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.description>
  <VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.label>Corvega assembly bench</VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.label>
  <VFE_FueledSmelter.description>A fuel-fed foundry station for recovering usable metal from slag and scrap items.</VFE_FueledSmelter.description>
  <VFE_FueledSmelter.label>fueled foundry</VFE_FueledSmelter.label>
  <VFE_TableButcherElectric.description>A motorized butcher line with a rotary saw for fast, precise carcass breakdown. It consumes a heavy amount of power.</VFE_TableButcherElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableButcherElectric.label>industrial butcher line</VFE_TableButcherElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.description>A powered Corvega chem lab with heaters, vessels, and gauges for efficient batch processing of compounds and drugs.</VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.label>industrial chem lab</VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableMachiningLarge.description>A large Corvega machining platform with advanced tooling and floor space for rapid fabrication of technical equipment. It consumes power.</VFE_TableMachiningLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableMachiningLarge.label>Corvega machining platform</VFE_TableMachiningLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableSmithyLarge.description>A powered Corvega forge station for weapons, tools, and heavy benchwork. It draws a substantial load from the grid.</VFE_TableSmithyLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableSmithyLarge.label>Corvega forge station</VFE_TableSmithyLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.description>An industrial masonry saw with powered cutters for turning chunks into building blocks at assembly-line speed.</VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.label>industrial masonry saw</VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableStoveLarge.description>A large industrial cooking line with multiple ovens and burners for rapid meal production under heavy settlement demand.</VFE_TableStoveLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableStoveLarge.label>industrial galley range</VFE_TableStoveLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableTailorLarge.description>A large industrial tailoring bench with powered sewing equipment for rapid clothing output. It can still limp along without power at reduced speed.</VFE_TableTailorLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableTailorLarge.label>industrial tailoring bench</VFE_TableTailorLarge.label>
  <VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.description>A large Poseidon groundwater reclamation pump that gradually strips pollution from broad terrain and condenses the recovered waste into haulable toxic packs.</VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.description>
  <VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.label>Poseidon reclamation pump</VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.label>
  <VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.description>A compact high-draw reclamation pump that clears polluted terrain quickly by burning a heavy amount of grid power and packing the recovered contaminants into toxic wastepacks.</VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.description>
  <VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.label>high-draw reclamation pump</VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.label>
  <VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.description>A sealed industrial locker for holding toxic waste products and reclaimed hazardous packs without letting them leak into the local environment.</VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.description>
  <VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.label>sealed waste locker</VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.label>
  <UnstablePowerCell.description>An unstable fusion battery built around a permanently active power core. It will run forever until something damages the housing badly enough to turn the whole unit into a catastrophic detonation.</UnstablePowerCell.description>
  <UnstablePowerCell.label>unstable fusion battery</UnstablePowerCell.label>
  <VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>A large ultratech shield projector with the unmistakable feel of a Poseidon black-budget installation. It consumes enormous power while active and can set the surrounding area ablaze if it absorbs too much punishment too quickly.</VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>A compact ultratech shield projector that reads like one of Poseidon's more secretive defense contracts. It throws up a potent energy field when a threat is present and idles at far lower draw the rest of the time.</VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>A specialized Corvega anti-air turret that intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its defensive radius. It cannot engage ground targets, but it looks every bit like a pre-War perimeter solution.</VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>An armored portable turret with Corvega targeting electronics and reinforced plating. Extra armor helps it survive incoming fire, but the control package remains just dumb enough to be dangerous around friendlies.</VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>A twin-barreled autocannon turret with Corvega fire-control electronics. It trades finesse for volume of fire and remains a power-hungry, violently practical defensive platform.</VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Flame.description>A portable flamer turret with Corvega control electronics and a brutally simple fuel system. It can engulf enemies and terrain in fire, and it remains as unsafe as any honest pre-War weapon platform should be.</VFES_Turret_Flame.description>
  <VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>A refined automated turret with Corvega targeting hardware, military-grade stabilization, and hardened casing. Its dumb AI brain still cannot be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>A heavy automatic turret whose multi-barrel mechanism unleashes sustained fire at high speed. Corvega control systems keep it cycling, but they do not make it subtle.</VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>A Corvega searchlight combining an intensely bright lamp with a mirrored reflector, useful for illuminating and dazzling targets across a defensive perimeter.</VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>A compact automatic turret fitted with a semi-automatic shotgun and Corvega targeting electronics. Short-ranged, nasty, and still not smart enough to trust completely.</VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>
  <Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>An outdoor utility lamp with an integrated Poseidon solar collector. It charges by day and provides dependable lighting after dark.</Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.description>A compact Wattz Electronics air scrubber that filters smoke, dust, and hazardous particulates while improving room cleanliness and indoor air quality.</VFES_AirPurifier.description>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.label>wattz air scrubber</VFES_AirPurifier.label>
  <VTE_IndustrialCooler.description>A large Appalachia Freeze wall cooler for serious refrigeration and industrial climate control. Cold air exits one side while hot exhaust is dumped out the other.</VTE_IndustrialCooler.description>
  <VTE_IndustrialHeater.description>A large Wattz industrial heater that fits into a wall and pushes serious utility heat. It can automatically cycle to a target temperature.</VTE_IndustrialHeater.description>
  <VTE_LargeCeilingFan.description>A large Wattz ceiling fan for workshops, warehouses, and other rooms that need stronger air circulation.</VTE_LargeCeilingFan.description>
  <VTE_SmallCeilingFan.description>A Wattz ceiling fan for slow, steady air circulation in smaller rooms.</VTE_SmallCeilingFan.description>
  <VTE_StandingCooler.description>A freestanding Appalachia Freeze cooling unit for open rooms that need relief from summer heat without full freezer performance.</VTE_StandingCooler.description>
  <VTE_WallHeater.description>A Wattz wall heater that fits into a wall and keeps rooms warm without wasting floor space.</VTE_WallHeater.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedCooler.description>An Appalachia Freeze wall-mounted cooler for compact freezer rooms and tight utility spaces.</VTE_WallMountedCooler.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedHeater.description>A compact Wattz wall-mounted heater for utility corridors, workshops, and smaller rooms that still need dependable automatic temperature control.</VTE_WallMountedHeater.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedVent.description>A simple Wattz wall vent for equalizing temperatures between adjacent rooms without opening a passageway.</VTE_WallMountedVent.description>
  <VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>A small crate containing heavy uranium shells. Used by gauss artillery to reload. A crate is fed directly into adjacent Hellion artillery when it needs to be rearmed.</VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>
  <VGE_CopilotConsole.description>An auxiliary interface that allows a copilot to assist in launching and piloting a Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_CopilotConsole.description>
  <VGE_GaussGun.description>A compact electromagnetic cannon that launches dense uranium slugs at extreme velocities. Designed for local bombardment and medium-range interception, it can also target hostile orbital craft. Requires a linked targeting terminal with an operator to function. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_GaussGun.description>
  <VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.description>A massive reactor assembly that channels a salvaged reactor core into immense electrical output. Its reinforced coils can handle extreme load, making it one of the most potent power sources available for Hellion systems. Adjacent reactor-core power cells multiply the output by 15% each.</VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.description>
  <VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.label>reactor-core power coil</VGE_GravcorePowerCoil.label>
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>A heavy reactor package built for the largest Hellion frames and orbital support hulls. It sustains an enormous lift field, allowing massive aircraft to rise under their own power while operating near a planetary gravity well.

When launched, anything on Hellion deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map.

These oversized assemblies were intended for pre-War logistics craft and mobile aerospace platforms, and they demand immense fabrication capacity to keep operational.</VGE_GravhulkEngine.description>
  <VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>heavy Hellion reactor</VGE_GravhulkEngine.label>
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>A compact reactor package adapted for a light Hellion. It generates the lift field needed for rapid vertical launch and short-range atmospheric insertion, but it is not suited to true interplanetary travel.

When launched, anything on Hellion deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map.

Often salvaged from scout craft, courier platforms, and other pre-War aerospace projects, these reactors are valued for their agility and relatively modest support requirements.</VGE_GravjumperEngine.description>
  <VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>light Hellion reactor</VGE_GravjumperEngine.label>
  <VGE_GravshipCapacitor.description>Stores large amounts of electricity for later use. Constructed in Hellion deck plating, Hellion capacitors do not obstruct movement.</VGE_GravshipCapacitor.description>
  <VGE_GravshipCapacitor.label>Hellion capacitor</VGE_GravshipCapacitor.label>
  <VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>A rapid-fire gun for point-defense use aboard the Hellion.</VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>
  <VGE_PilotBridge.description>An interface that allows launching and piloting a heavy Hellion. It draws power directly from the heavy Hellion reactor.</VGE_PilotBridge.description>
  <VGE_PilotCockpit.description>An interface that allows launching and piloting a light Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_PilotCockpit.description>
  <VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>A specialized defensive turret built exclusively for the Hellion. It intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its protective radius, but cannot engage ground targets. Interception chance scales with the target's velocity.</VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>
  <VGE_SolarPanelling.description>Produces electricity from sunlight. Does not work in darkness or under artificial light. It does not obstruct movement or provide cover, but it can only be constructed on Hellion deck plating.</VGE_SolarPanelling.description>
  <VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>A control station dedicated to operating a single Hellion artillery piece. Requires a crew member to manually aim and fire the weapon. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>
  <AncientGravReactor.description>An ancient generator powered by a reactor core. Once capable of producing massive amounts of power, it has now fallen into disrepair. The containment shield is leaking, causing toxic fallout to blanket the whole region.

Hack or destroy the reactor to obtain the core. Be warned, it may explode if damaged.</AncientGravReactor.description>
  <AncientGravReactor.label>ancient reactor</AncientGravReactor.label>
  <FuelOptimizer.description>A control unit that synchronizes the Hellion reactor with its VTOL thrust systems. It reduces the fuel needed for Hellion flight.

One Hellion can support two fuel regulators.</FuelOptimizer.description>
  <FuelOptimizer.label>fuel regulator</FuelOptimizer.label>
  <GravAnchor.description>Prevents the local map from being destroyed during a Hellion launch.

Mooring masts stabilize the launch zone around the aircraft and keep the surrounding settlement intact during departure. They cannot be constructed on the Hellion itself, because doing so would prevent takeoff entirely.</GravAnchor.description>
  <GravAnchor.label>mooring mast</GravAnchor.label>
  <Gravcore.description>A compact pre-War reactor core recovered from prototype Hellion systems and related military hardware. It is useless by itself, but it can be integrated into advanced Hellion support equipment.</Gravcore.description>
  <Gravcore.label>reactor core</Gravcore.label>
  <GravcorePowerCell.description>A compact generator built around a salvaged reactor core, adapted to provide steady power for the Hellion's onboard systems.</GravcorePowerCell.description>
  <GravcorePowerCell.label>reactor-core power cell</GravcorePowerCell.label>
  <GravEngine.description>The pre-War reactor assembly at the heart of the Hellion. It sustains the aircraft's vertical lift envelope and powers the heavy systems needed for long-range atmospheric and orbital operations.

When launched, anything on deck plating connected to the reactor will be transported to a new map. Without a mooring mast, launching the Hellion will abandon your current map.

The Hellion was designed as an unfinished military prototype, requiring rare components, specialist fabrication, and a great deal of salvage to keep flying.</GravEngine.description>
  <GravEngine.label>Hellion reactor</GravEngine.label>
  <GravFieldExtender.description>A support assembly used to expand the Hellion's airframe. It increases the amount of deck plating the craft can carry and must be built near the Hellion reactor.

One Hellion can support up to six airframe extenders.</GravFieldExtender.description>
  <GravFieldExtender.label>airframe extender</GravFieldExtender.label>
  <GravlitePanel.description>A lightweight pre-War airframe panel used to assemble and reinforce Hellion components. It is durable, heat-resistant, and ideal for advanced aerospace construction.

Requires vacstone blocks, which can be obtained from orbital asteroids.</GravlitePanel.description>
  <GravlitePanel.label>airframe panel</GravlitePanel.label>
  <GravshipHull.description>An airtight armored hull section sized for the Hellion's frame. It seals the craft against vacuum exposure and locks directly into the underlying deck plating, so it can only be built as part of the Hellion.</GravshipHull.description>
  <GravshipHull.label>Hellion hull</GravshipHull.label>
  <GravshipShieldGenerator.description>A defensive projector that protects the Hellion by generating a short-lived repulsor screen against incoming rounds and mortar fire. Those inside the field can still shoot out.

It must be charged before use. One Hellion can support two shield projectors.</GravshipShieldGenerator.description>
  <GravshipShieldGenerator.label>Hellion shield projector</GravshipShieldGenerator.label>
  <LargeThruster.description>An advanced VTOL thruster with a heat-resistant vacstone liner. It greatly increases the Hellion's operational range. Thrusters require an unobstructed exhaust area free of large buildings and Hellion deck plating.

Requires vacstone blocks, which can be obtained from orbital asteroids.

One Hellion can support up to six heavy VTOL thrusters.</LargeThruster.description>
  <LargeThruster.label>heavy VTOL thruster</LargeThruster.label>
  <PilotConsole.description>A hardened flight console used to launch and pilot the Hellion. It draws power directly from the Hellion reactor.</PilotConsole.description>
  <PilotConsole.label>cockpit console</PilotConsole.label>
  <PilotSubpersonaCore.description>A low-grade navigation core tuned for Hellion flight. It reduces the chance of an accident when flying the Hellion, though it cannot fully compensate for pilot error.

One Hellion can support up to two navigation cores.</PilotSubpersonaCore.description>
  <PilotSubpersonaCore.label>navigation core</PilotSubpersonaCore.label>
  <ShipChunk_Mech.description>A chunk of robot craft made of steel and salvaged airframe panels. It looks like it was torn free during re-entry or blasted off by heavy weapons.

Deconstruct it to obtain valuable resources.</ShipChunk_Mech.description>
  <SignalJammer.description>An electronic countermeasures suite that masks the Hellion's signature and helps it approach heavily defended landing sites.</SignalJammer.description>
  <SignalJammer.label>ECM suite</SignalJammer.label>
  <SmallThruster.description>A compact VTOL thruster that increases the Hellion's operational range. Thrusters require an unobstructed exhaust area free of large buildings and Hellion deck plating.

One Hellion can support up to four small VTOL thrusters.</SmallThruster.description>
  <SmallThruster.label>small VTOL thruster</SmallThruster.label>
  <RobCo_Assaultron.description>Dvojnohý bojový robot vyrobený spoločnosťou RobCo Industries pre armádu Spojených štátov. Obsahuje olivovú fádnu farbu s vojenskými znakmi, dve pazúrové ramená na boj zblízka a laser namontovaný na hlave, ktorý dokáže vystreliť nabitý lúč na diaľku. Rýchly a agresívny Assaultron bol navrhnutý pre útočné úlohy v prvej línii. Niektoré jednotky boli vybavené generátorom stealth poľa, ktorý im umožňoval maskovať sa v polovici priblíženia.</RobCo_Assaultron.description>
  <RobCo_Assaultron.label>Assaultron</RobCo_Assaultron.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronDominator.description>Špecializovaný variant lovca a zabijaka Assaultron postavený na integrovanom vysielači stealth-field a špeciálnej súprave ostria pre útok zblízka. Vzdáva sa štandardného hlavového lasera výmenou za rýchlejšie maskované priblíženie a nebezpečnejšie súboje na blízko.</RobCo_AssaultronDominator.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronDominator.label>Assaultron Dominator</RobCo_AssaultronDominator.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.description>Silne upravený podvozok Assaultronu, postavený tak, aby pripomínal legendárneho kryptida Sheepsquatch z Appalačského folklóru. Väčší ako štandardný Assaultron a vybavený vylepšenou hlavou lasera, bol pravdepodobne skonštruovaný ako nástroj zastrašovania tým, kto mal prístup k robotickému pracovnému stolu a čierny zmysel pre humor.</RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.label>ovčí drep</RobCo_AssaultronSheepsquatch.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.description>Integrovaná čepeľ predlaktia s Assaultronovým vzorom optimalizovaná pre rýchle sečné a bodavé údery na blízko.</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.label>Assaultronová čepeľ</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronBlade.tools.0.label>Assaultronová čepeľ</RobCo_AssaultronBlade.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.description>Kompaktný laser s Assaultronovým vzorom s rýchlejším cyklom vypaľovania ako projektory s ťažším lúčom. Vďaka tomu je vhodnejší na rýchle súboje a boj zblízka.</RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.description>
  <RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.label>RobCo Laser Assaultron</RobCo_AssaultronHeadLaser.label>
  <RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.description>Vysokovýkonný lúčový projektor namontovaný na hlave postavený na dlhom nabíjacom cykle a veľkom polomere výbuchu. Výboj produkuje značné teplo a je najúčinnejší, keď je vystrelený z odstupu.</RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.description>
  <RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.label>RobCo laser s ovčím drepom</RobCo_SheepsquatchHeadLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Cyberdog.description>Vojenský robotický pes vyvinutý spoločnosťou RobCo Industries pre armádu Spojených štátov. Kombinuje zachovaný psí mozog s mechanickým telom, ktoré mu dodáva psie inštinkty a zvukovú štekotovú zbraň na boj na diaľku. Cyberdogy boli nasadené ako prieskumníci, strážne zvieratá a bojoví spoločníci spolu s vojenským personálom.</RobCo_Cyberdog.description>
  <RobCo_Cyberdog.label>cyberdog</RobCo_Cyberdog.label>
  <RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.description>Akustický projektor s krátkym dosahom používaný bezpečnostnými jednotkami RobCo. Vysiela otrasový zvukový impulz, ktorý narúša mechanické ciele bez toho, aby sa spoliehal na priame fyzické poškodenie.</RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.description>
  <RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.label>zvukový žiarič kôry</RobCo_CyberdogSonicBark.label>
  <RobCo_Eyebot.description>Malý vznášajúci sa pozorovací a vysielací dron vyrobený spoločnosťou RobCo Industries. Používa bičové antény a integrované reproduktory na prenos rádiových signálov a vopred nahratých vysielaní a je vybavený pokročilými systémami rozpoznávania tváre. Eyebot nesie ľahkú laserovú zbraň na sebaobranu. Široko nasadzovaný Enklávou na propagandu a prieskum, je rýchly a nepolapiteľný, no v priamom boji mimoriadne krehký.</RobCo_Eyebot.description>
  <RobCo_Eyebot.label>Eyebot</RobCo_Eyebot.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotCrashed.description>Pozostatky Vertibota - predvojnového vojenského dronu VTOL - zvrhnutého a už neschopného letu. Napriek svojmu stavu zostávajú palubné zbraňové systémy a automatizované obranné protokoly čiastočne aktívne. Zapojí všetko, čo sa dostane do jeho obvodu.</RobCo_EyebotCrashed.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotCrashed.label>havaroval vertibot robot</RobCo_EyebotCrashed.label>
  <RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.description>Vylepšený Eyebot postavený na experimentálnom podvozku Duraframe. Obsahuje zosilnené vnútorné komponenty pre väčšiu odolnosť ako štandardná jednotka a nesie silnejšiu energetickú zbraň. Najviac zdokumentovaná jednotka Duraframe, označená ako ED-E, bola vybavená kanónom Tesla a niekoľko desaťročí prenášala citlivé údaje o výskume Enklávy po celej pustatine, kým bola obnovená.</RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.description>
  <RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.label>Eyebot duraframe</RobCo_EyebotDuraframe.label>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>Kompaktná dronová jednotka vytvorená a riadená veliteľskou platformou Hydra. Nesie sústredený energetický blaster a funguje pod koordináciou zo strany svojej rodičovskej jednotky. Jednotlivé jednotky Eye of Hydra sú ľahko obrnené, ale útočia v množstve z viacerých uhlov súčasne. Zničením materskej Hydry sa vrátia k základným protokolom autonómneho útoku.</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.description>
  <RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>Oko Hydry</RobCo_EyeOfHydra.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>Silne upravená platforma založená na Mister Gutsy navrhnutá tak, aby fungovala ako veliteľský uzol dronov. Hydra nesie integrovaný systém na nasadzovanie a koordináciu jednotiek Eye of Hydra, ktorých bojovú účinnosť zvyšuje taktická aura vysielaná z centrálnej platformy. Jeho vlastné zbraňové pole je značné a jeho zničenie naruší všetky drony, ktoré nasadil.</RobCo_GutsyHydra.description>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>Hydra</RobCo_GutsyHydra.label>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.description>Variant Mister Handy určený pre starostlivosť o deti a domáci dozor. Je naprogramovaný s rozsiahlym balíkom správania, ktorý zahŕňa starostlivosť o dojčatá, detekciu nebezpečenstiev, etiketu a disciplinárne protokoly. Slečna opatrovateľka si ponechala laserové rameno na ochranu domácnosti a bola predávaná predvojnovým rodinám ako špecializované riešenie starostlivosti o deti.</RobCo_MissNanny.description>
  <RobCo_MissNanny.label>Slečna Nanny</RobCo_MissNanny.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>Jednotka Mister Handy prekonfigurovaná na poľnohospodárske práce. Je vybavený nástrojovými ramenami vhodnými na sadenie, zber a údržbu poľa, spolu so snímačmi monitorovania plodín. Mister Farmhand, predaný do predvojnových poľnohospodárskych operácií, si zachováva laserové rameno na obranu pracoviska.</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.description>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>Pán Farmhand</RobCo_MisterFarmhand.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>Militarizovaný variant platformy Mister Handy, objednaný armádou Spojených štátov amerických. Nahrádza civilné nástrojové ramená plazmovým odlievačom a plameňometom a prevádzkuje osobný balík Sergeant Major v1.0. Mister Gutsy má ťažšie brnenie ako štandardné Handy a bol nasadený v bojových zónach vrátane frontu v Anchorage.</RobCo_MisterGutsy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>pán Gutsy</RobCo_MisterGutsy.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.description>Vznášajúci sa domáci služobný robot vyrobený spoločnosťou General Atomics International v spolupráci s RobCo Industries. Je vybavený tromi kĺbovými ramenami, ktoré prijímajú nástavce nástrojov vrátane pílky, laserovej rezačky a plameňometu, spolu s tromi optickými stopkami. Jeho neurónová sieť umožňuje takmer vnímajúcu konverzáciu a dobre udržiavaná jednotka je schopná autonómnej prevádzky po stáročia.</RobCo_MisterHandy.description>
  <RobCo_MisterHandy.label>pán Handy</RobCo_MisterHandy.label>
  <RobCo_GutsyHydraArray.tools.0.label>trhač</RobCo_GutsyHydraArray.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MissNannyBlaster.tools.0.label>rameno manipulátora</RobCo_MissNannyBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterFarmhandBlaster.tools.0.label>dobytok prod</RobCo_MisterFarmhandBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterGutsyArray.tools.0.label>trhač</RobCo_MisterGutsyArray.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_MisterHandyBlaster.tools.0.label>pílový list</RobCo_MisterHandyBlaster.tools.0.label>
  <MechanoidTransponder.description>Predvojnový transpondér od RobCo Industries.</MechanoidTransponder.description>
  <MechanoidTransponder.label>RobCo Transpondér</MechanoidTransponder.label>
  <NanostructuringChip.description>Vyčerpané zvyšky fúznej bunky Sentry Bot.</NanostructuringChip.description>
  <NanostructuringChip.label>vyčerpané jadro Sentry Bot Fusion Core</NanostructuringChip.label>
  <PowerfocusChip.description>Odrezaná hlava zlomeného Assaultrona.</PowerfocusChip.description>
  <PowerfocusChip.label>šrot hlavy Assaultrona</PowerfocusChip.label>
  <SignalChip.description>Stále funkčné časti motorovej lode Mister Handy.</SignalChip.description>
  <SignalChip.label>zachránené trysky Handy</SignalChip.label>
  <SubcoreBasic.description>civilný RobCo hardvér.</SubcoreBasic.description>
  <SubcoreBasic.label>základný obvod</SubcoreBasic.label>
  <SubcoreRegular.description>Hardvér RobCo vojenskej kvality.</SubcoreRegular.description>
  <SubcoreRegular.label>obvode na vojenskej úrovni</SubcoreRegular.label>
  <UnfinishedSubcore.description>nedokončené RobCo časti robota.</UnfinishedSubcore.description>
  <UnfinishedSubcore.label>nedokončené RobCo diely</UnfinishedSubcore.label>
  <RobCo_Liberator.description>Malý štvornohý bojový robot spojený s čínskymi frakciami v Commonwealthe. Je postavený na jednej integrovanej laserovej zbrani a štyroch mechanických nohách pre rýchly pohyb po nerovnom teréne. Liberator je ľahko obrnený, ale rýchly a zvyčajne sa s ním stretávame vo veľkých skupinách, ktoré útočia súčasne z viacerých smerov.</RobCo_Liberator.description>
  <RobCo_Liberator.label>osloboditeľa</RobCo_Liberator.label>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.description>Laserová puška vojenskej kvality integrovaná do čínskeho bojového robota Liberator.</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.description>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.label>liberátorová laserová puška</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.label>
  <RobCo_LiberatorLaser.tools.0.label>servo ruky</RobCo_LiberatorLaser.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrime.description>Masívny predvojnový stroj, ktorý spoločne vyvinuli RobCo Industries a General Atomics International pre armádu Spojených štátov. Je vysoký približne dvadsať metrov a je vybavený dvojitými energetickými delami namontovanými na hlave a zásobou taktických jadrových bômb na ničenie opevnených pozícií. Pôvodne bol navrhnutý na oslobodenie Anchorage od čínskych síl, ale nikdy nebol nasadený pred Veľkou vojnou kvôli poruchám napájania.</RobCo_LibertyPrime.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrime.label>Liberty Prime</RobCo_LibertyPrime.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.description>Vysokoenergetické pulzné delo integrované do Liberty Prime, ponechávajúc mini-nuke hod na jeho vyhradený odpaľovací systém.</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.description>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.label>Liberty prime pulzné delo</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.label>
  <RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>atomizovaná päsť</RobCo_LibertyPrimeMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_BallisticAuto.label>balistický automatický výbuch</RobCo_Bullet_BallisticAuto.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserMedium.label>laser so stredným lúčom</RobCo_Bullet_LaserMedium.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimePulse.label>sloboda primárny pulz</RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimePulse.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronRocket.label>sekuritrónová raketa</RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronRocket.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_WarMachinePulse.label>pulz vojnového stroja</RobCo_Bullet_WarMachinePulse.label>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.inspectString>Môže byť analyzovaný mechanizátorom.</RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.inspectString>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.jobString>Analyzujte platinový čip</RobCo_PlatinumChip.comps.0.jobString>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.description>Platinový čip na ukladanie údajov obnovený zo zapečateného trezoru správy RobCo. Obsahuje balík operačného systému z predvojnového obdobia RobCo a je cenný ďaleko za svojou váhou kovu.</RobCo_PlatinumChip.description>
  <RobCo_PlatinumChip.label>platinový čip</RobCo_PlatinumChip.label>
  <RobCo_Collectron.description>Variant Protectron preprogramovaný na zber a záchranu zdrojov. Prijali ho rôzne povojnové frakcie, aby zautomatizovali zhromažďovanie konkrétnych materiálov. Collectron funguje autonómne v rámci definovanej oblasti a bude brániť svoju zbernú zónu pred rušením.</RobCo_Collectron.description>
  <RobCo_Collectron.label>zberateľstvo</RobCo_Collectron.label>
  <RobCo_Constructron.description>Jednotka Protectron nakonfigurovaná na stavebné a infraštruktúrne práce. Namiesto štandardných ručných laserov nesie zváracie a montážne nástroje a bol nasadený na predvojnových stavbách a priemyselných zariadeniach. Štandardné protokoly reakcie na hrozby zostávajú aktívne.</RobCo_Constructron.description>
  <RobCo_Constructron.label>konštruktrón</RobCo_Constructron.label>
  <RobCo_Factotron.description>Variant Protectron naprogramovaný pre továrenské a výrobné úlohy. Bol navrhnutý tak, aby fungoval na montážnych linkách a výrobných poschodiach a presne vykonával širokú škálu výrobných čiastkových úloh. Faktotróny patria medzi menej bežne sa vyskytujúce varianty Protectronu v povojnovej pustatine.</RobCo_Factotron.description>
  <RobCo_Factotron.label>factotron</RobCo_Factotron.label>
  <RobCo_Protectron.description>Široko nasadený predvojnový obslužný a bezpečnostný robot vyrobený spoločnosťou RobCo Industries. Vyznačuje sa veľkou klenutou hlavou s tromi optickými senzormi, dvojitými ručne namontovanými laserovými žiaričmi a hlavovým laserom. Poháňaný štiepnou batériou bol Protectron používaný v kanceláriách, nemocniciach a verejných zariadeniach po celých Spojených štátoch. Je pomalý a menej schopný v priamom boji ako špecializované vojenské roboty.</RobCo_Protectron.description>
  <RobCo_Protectron.label>Protectron</RobCo_Protectron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.description>Jednotka Protectron vybavená ťažkým vrtným nástavcom namiesto štandardného ručného lasera, určená na banské a výkopové práce. Bola zazmluvnená na predvojnové banské operácie na ťažbu podzemných zdrojov. Vŕtacie rameno ho robí pomalším ako štandardný Protectron, ale dáva mu významnú schopnosť priblížiť sa.</RobCo_Utilitron.description>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.label>utilitron</RobCo_Utilitron.label>
  <RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>vŕtať</RobCo_Utilitron.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.inspectString>Môže byť analyzovaný kolonistom.</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.inspectString>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.jobString>Analyzujte zlomený rám Eyebotu</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.comps.0.jobString>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.description>Rozbité kúsky Eyebota. Mechanik môže študovať tieto časti, aby pomohol odomknúť vyššie úrovne výskumu RobCo.</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.description>
  <RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.label>zlomený rám Eyebotu</RobCo_BrokenEyebotFrame.label>
  <RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.description>Ďalej zvyšuje výkon komunikačnej konzoly.</RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.description>
  <RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.label>RobCo anténa</RobCo_BurnoutMechlinkBooster.label>
  <RobCo_CommsConsole.description>Komunikačná konzola s funkciou šéfskupiny RobCo.</RobCo_CommsConsole.description>
  <RobCo_CommsConsole.label>RobCo komunikačná konzola</RobCo_CommsConsole.label>
  <RobCo_MechbandDish.description>Výrazne zvyšuje výkon komunikačnej konzoly.</RobCo_MechbandDish.description>
  <RobCo_MechbandDish.label>RobCo jedlo</RobCo_MechbandDish.label>
  <RobCo_Receiver.description>Zvyšuje výkon komunikačnej konzoly.</RobCo_Receiver.description>
  <RobCo_Receiver.label>RobCo prijímač</RobCo_Receiver.label>
  <RobCo_Robobrain.description>Veľký pásový bojový robot vyrobený spoločnosťou General Atomics International pre armádu Spojených štátov. Nachádza sa v ňom živý primát alebo ľudský mozog v biomedicínskej gélovej kupole, zapojenej priamo do jeho riadiacich systémov. Robobrain je vybavený manipulačnými pazúrmi, integrovanou laserovou zbraňou a omračovacím zariadením Mesmetron. Jeho biologická mozgová zložka poskytuje výnimočnú taktickú inteligenciu a schopnosť manipulovať so zbraňami štandardnými pre ľudí.</RobCo_Robobrain.description>
  <RobCo_Robobrain.label>robobrain</RobCo_Robobrain.label>
  <RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.description>Presná injekčná pištoľ, ktorá vystreľuje kovové ihly naplnené toxickými zlúčeninami. Je navrhnutý tak, aby poranil cieľ pri náraze a vydal jed na väčšiu vzdialenosť ako väčšina bočných zbraní.</RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.description>
  <RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.label>RobCo striekačka</RobCo_RobobrainSyringer.label>
  <RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.description>Jednotka Securitron, ktorej obmedzovače správania zlyhali, čo ju zanechalo v stave bezohľadnej agresie. Zachováva si plnú bojovú schopnosť Mark II – Gatlingov laser, raketomety a elektrošokové zbrane – ale bez rozpoznávania frakcií, hodnotenia hrozieb alebo deeskalačných protokolov. Útočí na všetky ciele v dosahu bez rozdielu.</RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.description>
  <RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.label>berserk Securitron</RobCo_BerserkSecuritron.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkI.description>Bezpečnostný robot RobCo Industries PDQ-88b postavený na jedinom ťažkom jednokolesovom podvozku. Mark I nesie v pravom ramene 9 mm samopal a na obrazovke CRT zobrazuje predvojnový policajný dôstojník. Vyznačuje sa telom z titánovej zliatiny a integrovanými systémami autooprav. Jednotky Mark I používajú základný bojový softvér a sú menej efektívne v zložitých úlohách ako vylepšený variant Mark II.</RobCo_SecuritronMkI.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkI.label>Značka Securitron I</RobCo_SecuritronMkI.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkII.description>PDQ-88b Securitron so softvérovým balíkom Mark II, ktorý prináša kompletnú výzbroj zbraní online: laser X-25 Gatling, raketomety M-235 a granátomety G-28. Jeho CRT obrazovka zobrazuje skôr vojaka ako policajta. Mark II bola zamýšľaná bojová sila Roberta House na obranu New Vegas a Mojave.</RobCo_SecuritronMkII.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronMkII.label>Značka Securitron II</RobCo_SecuritronMkII.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.description>Vylepšená laserová platforma integrovaná do Securitron Mark II s palubnou raketovou batériou.</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.label>sekuritrónový policajný laser</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.tools.0.label>vysokonapäťový obušok</RobCo_SecuritronElectroshock.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.description>Integrovaný balistický opakovač namontovaný na bezpečnostnej platforme Securitron Mark I.</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.description>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.label>sekuritrónový balistický opakovač</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.label>
  <RobCo_SecuritronLaser.tools.0.label>šokový obušok</RobCo_SecuritronLaser.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>Strážny robot RobCo Industries vyzbrojený trojhlavňovým minigunom a Gatlingovým laserom, navrhnutý na trvalé potlačenie pechoty a ľahko obrnených cieľov. Strážny bot je vyhradená bojová platforma RobCo postavená na jednoduchom syntetickom čipe osobnosti, ktorý obsahuje iba bojové rutiny. Annihilator je štandardným výrobným variantom tejto rady.</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>anihilátor sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotAnnihilator.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>Strážny robot, ktorý nesie kompletnú sadu zbraní: minigun, raketomet, plameňomet a odpaľovač kazetových granátov. Je to jedna z najviac vyzbrojených autonómnych jednotiek, s ktorými sa v pustatine stretávame. Jeho centrálny procesor obsahuje čip na nanoštruktúru, čo naznačuje, že sa používal ako testovacie prostredie pre pokročilé nanotechnologické programy pred vojnou alebo po nej.</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>deathbot</RobCo_SentrybotDeathbot.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>Variant strážneho robota vybavený priemyselným plameňometným systémom a dobíjateľnou nádržou na palivo pre dlhšie operácie. Pôvodne navrhnutý na likvidáciu škodcov vo veľkom meradle a odmietnutie oblasti, je schopný nepretržitého zápalného ohňa v širokej oblasti. Variant Pestcontrol bol predávaný poľnohospodárskym a vládnym klientom pred vojnou.</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>strážca proti škodcom</RobCo_SentrybotPestcontrol.label>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>Variant strážneho robota nakonfigurovaný na útok na opevnenie a protipancierové operácie. Jeho primárnym zbraňovým systémom je stojan s vysokovýkonnými raketometmi vhodnými na demoláciu vystužených konštrukcií. Jazdí na rázvore kolies mecanum, ktorý umožňuje pohyb po väčšine terénu. Štandardné brnenie strážnych botov a bojové protokoly sú zachované.</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.description>
  <RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>siegebreaker sentrybot</RobCo_SentrybotSiegebreaker.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachine.description>Masívna autonómna bojová platforma kombinujúca palebnú silu ťažkých strážnych robotov s integrovaným mechanoidným nosným systémom na nasadenie dronov Liberator. Vojnový stroj vysiela taktický koordinačný signál, ktorý zvyšuje bojovú účinnosť blízkych jednotiek Liberator. Je vyzbrojený pulznou batériou s viacerými zábleskami a zosilnenými vojnovými rukavicami pre boj na blízko.</RobCo_WarMachine.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachine.label>vojnový stroj</RobCo_WarMachine.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.description>Batéria s trvalým pulzom integrovaná do pevných bodov trupu War Machine.</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.description>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.label>pulzná batéria vojnového stroja</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.label>
  <RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>vojnová rukavica</RobCo_WarMachineMiniNukeLauncher.tools.0.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_Electroshock.label>elektrošoková skrutka</RobCo_Bullet_Electroshock.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserAssaultron.label>RobCo Laser Assaultron</RobCo_Bullet_LaserAssaultron.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserAuto.label>automatický laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserAuto.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserHigh.label>diaľkový laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserHigh.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserLow.label>tlmený laser</RobCo_Bullet_LaserLow.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LaserSheepsquatch.label>RobCo prebitý laser hlavy Assaultron</RobCo_Bullet_LaserSheepsquatch.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LiberatorLaser.label>oslobodzovací laser</RobCo_Bullet_LiberatorLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimeMiniNuke.label>Liberty Prime mini-nuke</RobCo_Bullet_LibertyPrimeMiniNuke.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_ScurrybotLaser.label>scurrybot laser</RobCo_Bullet_ScurrybotLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronLaser.label>sekuritrónový laser</RobCo_Bullet_SecuritronLaser.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SentryRocket.label>strážna raketa</RobCo_Bullet_SentryRocket.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_SonicBark.label>zvuková kôra</RobCo_Bullet_SonicBark.label>
  <RobCo_Bullet_Syringe.label>RobCo injekčná striekačka</RobCo_Bullet_Syringe.label>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.description>A wood-fueled station for brewing wasteland extracts.</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.description>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.label>fueled extract lab</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench.label>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.description>An electrically powered station for brewing wasteland extracts.</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.description>
  <VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.label>electric extract lab</VFEM2_AlchemicalWorkbench_Electric.label>
  <VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.description>An extract is causing the user to lose memories quickly, shortening both positive and negative memories far faster than normal.</VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.label>amnesia extract</VFEM2_AmnesiaDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.description>A patched-up practice target mounted on a crude stand. It is kept around as a placeholder range fixture for anyone still trying to train their aim.</VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.description>
  <VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.label>archery target</VFEM2_ArcheryTarget.label>
  <VFEM2_ComaDraught.description>An extract is shutting the user's body down into a deep coma-like state.</VFEM2_ComaDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_ComaDraught.label>coma extract</VFEM2_ComaDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.description>An extract is boosting the user's global work speed while slowing energy loss, but it also raises the risk of a heart attack and leaves them with a major sleep-rate crash afterward.</VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.label>efficiency extract</VFEM2_EfficiencyDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_FertilityDraught.description>An extract is artificially increasing the user's fertility. The boost is strong enough to give even infertile people a chance to become parents.</VFEM2_FertilityDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_FertilityDraught.label>fertility extract</VFEM2_FertilityDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_FocusDraught.description>An extract is heightening the user's ability to learn, letting them gain knowledge faster, eat faster, rest quicker, and gain more psyfocus while the potent phase lasts. The effects reverse when it fades.</VFEM2_FocusDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_FocusDraught.label>focus extract</VFEM2_FocusDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_HealingDraught.description>An extract is improving this person's natural wound regeneration, letting them recover from injuries significantly faster than normal.</VFEM2_HealingDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_HealingDraught.label>healing extract</VFEM2_HealingDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.description>An extract is improving this person's immune system, making them more capable of fighting off diseases and infections at the cost of making them sleepier.</VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.label>immunization extract</VFEM2_ImmunizationDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_InspirationDraught.description>An extract is providing mental clarity, helping the user focus on skills they are passionate about at the cost of diminished combat capability.</VFEM2_InspirationDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_InspirationDraught.label>inspiration extract</VFEM2_InspirationDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.description>An extract is dulling the user's sense of pain at the cost of greatly reduced focus and productivity.</VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.label>painkiller extract</VFEM2_PainkillerDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_Plant_Grape.description>A hardy wasteland vine that yields dark, bloody fruit when harvested. Its juice is prized for rough trade liquor and survival tonics, and the plant can be harvested repeatedly once established.</VFEM2_Plant_Grape.description>
  <VFEM2_Plant_Grape.label>bloody vine</VFEM2_Plant_Grape.label>
  <VFEM2_PoisonDraught.description>An extract is poisoning the user and rapidly degrading their condition.</VFEM2_PoisonDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_PoisonDraught.label>poison extract</VFEM2_PoisonDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.description>An extract is hardening the user's skin into a built-in layer of armor that resists burns and physical trauma, though it makes them much less attractive.</VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.label>stoneskin extract</VFEM2_StoneskinDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_StrengthDraught.description>An extract is sharpening the user's strength and reflexes, improving combat ability at the cost of higher social fight chance and a higher mental break threshold.</VFEM2_StrengthDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_StrengthDraught.label>strength extract</VFEM2_StrengthDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_TorturerDraught.description>An extract is causing severe pain to the user, leaving them unable to move. Prisoners lose resistance quickly, and slaves become fully suppressed.</VFEM2_TorturerDraught.description>
  <VFEM2_TorturerDraught.label>torturer extract</VFEM2_TorturerDraught.label>
  <VFEM2_TrainingDummy.description>A straw-stuffed practice dummy lashed to a post. It is little more than a placeholder training fixture, but still lets people work on their form without risking a real fight.</VFEM2_TrainingDummy.description>
  <VFEM2_TrainingDummy.label>training dummy</VFEM2_TrainingDummy.label>
  <Building_ChemshineBarrel.description>A barrel for fermenting rot gut.</Building_ChemshineBarrel.description>
  <Building_ChemshineBarrel.label>rot gut barrel</Building_ChemshineBarrel.label>
  <ChemBoiler.label>crude oil boiler</ChemBoiler.label>
  <Chemlamp.label>oil lamp</Chemlamp.label>
  <ChemlampPost.label>oil lamp post</ChemlampPost.label>
  <Plant_Chemroot.description>A mutated offshoot of ginseng whose roots burrow deep through loose soil until they tap underground oil pockets. Farmers cultivate radseng for the chemfuel-rich sludge in its roots, even though a bad spark can turn the field into an inferno.</Plant_Chemroot.description>
  <Plant_Chemroot.label>radseng</Plant_Chemroot.label>
  <TableFaro.description>A travel-worn gaming table used for caravan games and roadside wagers. Allows up to two players at a time.</TableFaro.description>
  <TableFaro.label>caravan table</TableFaro.label>
  <DeathrestAccelerator.description>A blood pump used to hasten recovery from vitamin deficiency.</DeathrestAccelerator.description>
  <DeathrestAccelerator.label>vitaminpump</DeathrestAccelerator.label>
  <DeathrestCapacitySerum.description>A serum designed to increase the body's ability to withstand Wendigo sickness.</DeathrestCapacitySerum.description>
  <DeathrestCapacitySerum.label>Wendigo Capacity Serum</DeathrestCapacitySerum.label>
  <DeathrestCasket.description>A containment casket for those suffering from cannibal's vitamin deficiency syndrome known as "The Shakes".</DeathrestCasket.description>
  <DeathrestCasket.label>the box</DeathrestCasket.label>
  <GlucosoidPump.description>A blood pump used to create muscle mineral reserves.</GlucosoidPump.description>
  <GlucosoidPump.label>mineralpump</GlucosoidPump.label>
  <HemogenAmplifier.description>A blood pump used to increase hemogen absorption.</HemogenAmplifier.description>
  <HemogenAmplifier.label>proteinpump</HemogenAmplifier.label>
  <Hemopump.description>A blood pump used to help with bloodflow and relax muscles.</Hemopump.description>
  <Hemopump.label>bloodpump</Hemopump.label>
  <PsychofluidPump.description>A blood pump for stabilizing mental symptoms, relaxing their mind and helping them to focus.</PsychofluidPump.description>
  <PsychofluidPump.label>chempump</PsychofluidPump.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothMutagen.description>A brutal FEV-3 mutagenic package that collapses a super mutant subject into a gigantic, tame behemoth war-beast. Only first- and second-generation super mutants survive the process.</WestTek_BehemothMutagen.description>
  <WestTek_BehemothMutagen.label>behemoth mutagen</WestTek_BehemothMutagen.label>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.inspectString>Can be analyzed by a colonist.</WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.inspectString>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.jobString>Analyze FEV culture</WestTek_FEVCulture.comps.0.jobString>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.description>A stabilized culture kept alive for higher-order Forced Evolutionary Virus work. Guaranteed transformation results when used in procedures.

A colonist can analyze this culture to unlock FEV-3 research.</WestTek_FEVCulture.description>
  <WestTek_FEVCulture.label>FEV culture</WestTek_FEVCulture.label>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.inspectString>Can be analyzed by a colonist.</WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.inspectString>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.jobString>Analyze FEV probe</WestTek_FEVProbe.comps.0.jobString>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.description>A crude pre-refinement sample of Forced Evolutionary Virus growth medium. It is unstable and difficult to handle safely.

A colonist can analyze this probe to unlock FEV-1 research.</WestTek_FEVProbe.description>
  <WestTek_FEVProbe.label>FEV probe</WestTek_FEVProbe.label>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.inspectString>Can be analyzed by a colonist.</WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.inspectString>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.jobString>Analyze FEV sample</WestTek_FEVSample.comps.0.jobString>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.description>A concentrated viral sample suitable for controlled testing. More stable than raw probe material.

A colonist can analyze this sample to unlock FEV-2 research.</WestTek_FEVSample.description>
  <WestTek_FEVSample.label>FEV sample</WestTek_FEVSample.label>
  <WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.description>A highly stabilized Forced Evolutionary Virus dose reserved for colonist-directed procedures. Guaranteed transformation results when used in procedures.</WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.description>
  <WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.label>isolated FEV dosage</WestTek_IsolatedFEVDosage.label>
  <WestTek_NightkinMutagen.description>A specialized FEV mutagenic package that stabilizes a Nightkin stealth field in an existing West Tek super mutant. Only first- and second-generation West Tek super mutants can survive the implantation.</WestTek_NightkinMutagen.description>
  <WestTek_NightkinMutagen.label>nightkin mutagen</WestTek_NightkinMutagen.label>
  <WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.description>A cleaner Forced Evolutionary Virus dose suitable for more controlled procedures. Lethality is reduced compared to wild samples.</WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.description>
  <WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.label>refined FEV dosage</WestTek_RefinedFEVDosage.label>
  <WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.description>An unstable Forced Evolutionary Virus dose. The virus is not yet controlled enough to produce consistent results.</WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.description>
  <WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.label>unrefined FEV dosage</WestTek_UnrefinedFEVDosage.label>
  <GR_ArchoGrowthcell.label>archotech growth sac</GR_ArchoGrowthcell.label>
  <GR_ElectroWomb.description>A compact incubation tank built to mature unstable West Tek specimens from growth cell to full release.</GR_ElectroWomb.description>
  <GR_ElectroWomb.label>incubation tank</GR_ElectroWomb.label>
  <GR_GenePod.description>A West Tek growth vat where unstable strain templates are drowned in Forced Evolutionary Virus and coaxed into viable test organisms.</GR_GenePod.description>
  <GR_GenePod.label>FEV vat</GR_GenePod.label>
  <GR_GeneticExtractionTable.description>A West Tek extraction rig that renders subject tissue into condensed strain samples for later recombination and vat work.</GR_GeneticExtractionTable.description>
  <GR_GeneticExtractionTable.label>strain extraction table</GR_GeneticExtractionTable.label>
  <GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.description>An advanced West Tek workbench for compounding boosters, stabilizers, and implant-grade augment parts for mutant research.</GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.description>
  <GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.label>augmentation bench</GR_GeneticsTinkeringTable.label>
  <GR_GenoframeAwful.label>strain frame (awful)</GR_GenoframeAwful.label>
  <GR_GenoframeExcellent.label>strain frame (excellent)</GR_GenoframeExcellent.label>
  <GR_GenoframeGood.label>strain frame (good)</GR_GenoframeGood.label>
  <GR_GenoframeLegendary.label>strain frame (legendary)</GR_GenoframeLegendary.label>
  <GR_GenoframeMasterwork.label>strain frame (masterwork)</GR_GenoframeMasterwork.label>
  <GR_GenoframeNormal.description>A stabilized West Tek strain frame used by the FEV vat as the baseline lattice for new experimental growth stock.</GR_GenoframeNormal.description>
  <GR_GenoframeNormal.label>strain frame (normal)</GR_GenoframeNormal.label>
  <GR_GenoframePoor.label>strain frame (poor)</GR_GenoframePoor.label>
  <GR_GenoframeUnfinished.label>unfinished strain frame</GR_GenoframeUnfinished.label>
  <GR_GrowthCell.description>A portable containment sac holding an unstable FEV embryo until it can be transferred into a West Tek incubation tank.</GR_GrowthCell.description>
  <GR_GrowthCell.label>FEV growth sac</GR_GrowthCell.label>
  <GR_HumanoidGenetic.label>humanoid strain</GR_HumanoidGenetic.label>
  <GR_InsectoidGenetic.label>insectoid strain</GR_InsectoidGenetic.label>
  <GR_LargeElectroWomb.description>A heavy growth tank for larger prototypes and mature mutant stock that would never fit inside a compact incubation chamber.</GR_LargeElectroWomb.description>
  <GR_LargeElectroWomb.label>large incubation tank</GR_LargeElectroWomb.label>
  <GR_TemplateGenetic.label>blank strain template</GR_TemplateGenetic.label>
  <GR_ThrumboGenetic.label>colossus strain</GR_ThrumboGenetic.label>
  <GR_TissueGrinder.description>A brutal West Tek processing bench that tears specimen tissue down into usable strain templates and recovers viable experimental material from corpses.</GR_TissueGrinder.description>
  <GR_TissueGrinder.label>tissue macerator</GR_TissueGrinder.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.description>A hood worn by followers of the Unity.</WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.label>unity hood</WestTek_Apparel_UnityHood.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.description>A ceremonial robe worn by members of the Unity and other FEV cultists.</WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.label>unity robe</WestTek_Apparel_UnityRobe.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.description>Heavier scavenged plating intended for large mutant bruisers expected to absorb return fire.</WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.label>brute armor</WestTek_Apparel_BruteArmor.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.description>Crude field armor assembled for ordinary super mutant shock troops.</WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.label>grunt armor</WestTek_Apparel_GruntArmor.label>
  <WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.description>Command armor reserved for high-value mutant leaders and vat-born enforcers.</WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.description>
  <WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.label>master armor</WestTek_Apparel_MasterArmor.label>
  <WestTek_Centaur.description>Centaurs are hostile FEV predators built from failed human stock and finished into hunting beasts. West Tek's field strain keeps the low-slung, many-limbed silhouette but now uses the tougher Wasteland Compendium combat profile instead of the earlier lightweight animal tuning.</WestTek_Centaur.description>
  <WestTek_Centaur.label>centaur</WestTek_Centaur.label>
  <WestTek_Centaur.tools.0.label>tentacle</WestTek_Centaur.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_Centaur.tools.1.label>teeth</WestTek_Centaur.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.description>Floaters are fast, flammable FEV horrors that drift on their own gas bladders and crowd prey in packs.</WestTek_Floater.description>
  <WestTek_Floater.label>floater</WestTek_Floater.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.tools.0.label>fore mouth</WestTek_Floater.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.tools.1.label>ovipositor</WestTek_Floater.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_Floater.tools.2.label>head</WestTek_Floater.tools.2.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.description>An ancient FEV giant restored to West Tek's mutant catalogue.</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.description>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.label>super mutant behemoth</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.0.label>left fist</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.1.label>right fist</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.2.label>head</WestTek_SuperMutantBehemoth.tools.2.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.description>A stabilized behemoth strain conditioned to obey West Tek handlers.</WestTek_TameBehemoth.description>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.label>tame behemoth</WestTek_TameBehemoth.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.0.label>left fist</WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.1.label>right fist</WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.1.label>
  <WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.2.label>head</WestTek_TameBehemoth.tools.2.label>
  <WestTek_Leather_FEVMutant.label>nodulous skin</WestTek_Leather_FEVMutant.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.description>An oversized steel pipe with a fire hydrant welded to its end.</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.description>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.label>fire hydrant club</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.0.label>pipe</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.0.label>
  <WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.1.label>hose</WestTek_BehemothFireHydrantClub.tools.1.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>A suit of heavy armor used by Whitespring secret service units to break fortified positions in frontal assaults when no other option is available.</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphract.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>An ornate heavy armor awarded to high-ranking Whitespring secret service operatives. Embedded cryptex threads enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service armor</Apparel_ArmorCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>A heavily-armored high-tech helmet, with a solid plasteel-weave shell and indirect visual system for non-frontal view angles. It protects against all but the most powerful or luckily-aimed shots.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>patriot secret service helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetCataphractPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plasteel-weave plate.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>A variant of recon armor with short-range thrust capabilities for quick movement in urban environments. Urban scouts prefer close-quarters engagements and quick strikes rather than static defense.</Apparel_ArmorLocust.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>urban scout armor</Apparel_ArmorLocust.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>A variant of marine armor specialized for cold and arctic operations, fitted with a shoulder-mounted launcher. Arctic marines specialize in breaching cold-climate fortifications.</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>arctic marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarineGrenadier.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>A marine armor helmet used by Whitespring patriots, with a built-in status computer and layered plasteel-weave plates. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>patriot marine helmet</Apparel_ArmorMarineHelmetPrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>A suit of armor used by Whitespring patriots. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and ceremonial, patriot marine armor marks membership and rank. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.description>
  <Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>patriot marine armor</Apparel_ArmorMarinePrestige.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>A suit of light armor, designed to permit quick movement. Plasteel-weave plates block attacks without compromising mobility, and neuro-memetic assistors in the lower body allow a human to wear the armor and still move easily.

Expensive and beautiful, prestige armor like this is usually made for those of high status. Embedded cryptex threads also enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_ArmorReconPrestige.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.description>A beret styled with the Whitespring insignia, worn by enclave personnel of certain ranks.</Apparel_Coronet.description>
  <Apparel_Coronet.label>Whitespring Beret</Apparel_Coronet.label>
  <Apparel_Crown.description>A cap worn by senior Whitespring researchers, denoting a leadership role in cryptid studies.</Apparel_Crown.description>
  <Apparel_Crown.label>Whitespring Scientist Cap</Apparel_Crown.label>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>A tight skullcap designed for cryptid research focus. It provides no physical protection, but its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity.</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.description>
  <Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>cryptex skullcap</Apparel_EltexSkullcap.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>A lightweight helmet designed for cryptid research focus. While it provides little physical protection, its special materials enhance the wearer's cryptid sensitivity and dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>cryptex helmet</Apparel_PsyfocusHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>cryptex robe</Apparel_PsyfocusRobe.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>A shirt embedded with special cryptid-focusing materials. These enhance cryptid sensitivity and help dissipate neural heat.</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.description>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>cryptex shirt</Apparel_PsyfocusShirt.label>
  <Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>cryptex vest</Apparel_PsyfocusVest.label>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>A long, formal longcoat used by Whitespring patriots and officers. Embroidered with the enclave sigils, it marks membership and rank.</Apparel_RobeRoyal.description>
  <Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>patriot longcoat</Apparel_RobeRoyal.label>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.description>Vertibot is a spacer-tech, unmanned aerial vehicle equipped with advanced sensors and a missile payload. Designed for autonomous long-range operations, it's commonly used by the Whitespring Enclave for reconnaissance and bombardment. Its ability to release powerful missile salvos makes it effective against various targets. This vertibot is temporarily disabled due to the recharge cycle.</VFED_Aerodrone.description>
  <VFED_Aerodrone.label>vertibot</VFED_Aerodrone.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>A large, overcharged vertibot battery. Will release a strong electromagnetic pulse when damaged, potentially disabling nearby defenses.</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>vertibot battery pack</VFED_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>A large military crate of vertibot munitions. Will explode when damaged, sending armed shells flying in random directions.</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>vertibot munitions crate</VFED_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>A multi-use personal stealthboy cloak device engineered based on experimental Whitespring technology. Allows the user to become completely invisible for a brief duration, after which the device requires a short amount of time to recharge.</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.description>
  <VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>Stealthboy</VFED_Apparel_InvisibilityEngulfer.label>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing extremely valuable items. May contain critical intel. Due to the special restrictions, only senior Whitespring officials are capable of opening it.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary device capable of intercepting Whitespring communication. When activated, it will begin intel scraping, emitting a pulse in regular intervals. Each pulse has a chance of generating a small amount of intel, but it may also increase your visibility and even alert a Whitespring strike force. After 10 pulses, the machine burns out and triggers a fiery explosion.</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>A crashed Whitespring vertibot.</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.description>
  <VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>crashed vertibot</VFED_CrashedAerodrone.label>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.description>A dossier containing critical information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to plan high-profile assassination attempts, but it can also be exchanged into standard intel via the contraband system.</VFED_CriticalIntel.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>A Brotherhood expeditionary declassifier is a single-use, ultra-tech device consisting of a brain-scan apparatus and a long, thick needle. It is primarily used by Whitespring Brotherhood expeditionaries for data extraction. By inserting the needle into the skull of a senior official, memories can be downloaded from their brain, forming valuable Brotherhood expeditionary intel. The amount of intel received is determined by the rank of the target official. The person affected by a Brotherhood Expeditionary Declassifier dies in the process, and when used on neutral visitors, it is treated as an act of war.</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.description>
  <VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>Brotherhood declassifier</VFED_DeserterDeclassifier.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>A spacer-tech vertibird designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system.</VFED_DeserterShuttle.description>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>Brotherhood vertibird</VFED_DeserterShuttle.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>Brotherhood vertibird (incoming)</VFED_DeserterShuttleIncoming.label>
  <VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>Brotherhood vertibird (leaving)</VFED_DeserterShuttleLeaving.label>
  <VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>Whitespring propaganda</VFED_Filth_Propaganda.label>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>A chunk of a Whitespring flagship. It seems to have been torn off by some kind of powerful weapon.\n\nHaving landed not long ago, it still contains useful resources which you can acquire by deconstructing it.</VFED_FlagshipChunk.description>
  <VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>Kovac-Muldoon debris</VFED_FlagshipChunk.label>
  <VFED_FuelTank.description>A large fuel tank used to refuel Whitespring vertibirds. Will detonate if damaged beyond a certain point, potentially triggering a chain reaction.</VFED_FuelTank.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>The governmental APC is a formidable armored transport truck, known for its impressive cargo capacity. Its armor is impenetrable, ensuring the safety of its contents throughout transit. Once in motion, the APC’s doors remain sealed until it reaches its predetermined destination. While attempting to loot its cargo is futile due to built-in self-destruct protocols, its robust exterior makes it an ideal shield on the battlefield.</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>governmental APC</VFED_ImperialMaxpack.label>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>An advanced shielding apparatus, the Whitespring mega high-shield projects a vast momentum repulsor field, allowing shots to exit but preventing any from entering. Specifically calibrated for high angles, it's adept at deflecting incoming mortar rounds, vertibot strikes and even orbital slicer beams. The unit can be temporarily disabled by EMP attacks, either by shocking the projector unit itself, or using EMP munitions on the shield. Draws huge amounts of power.</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>
  <VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>governmental mega high-shield</VFED_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>An underground hydroponics bay used by the Whitespring Enclave to feed its personnel. Fully automated and connected to water mains, these farms require no labor to operate.</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.description>
  <VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>Whitespring underfarm</VFED_ImperialUnderfarm.label>
  <VFED_Intel.description>A dossier containing information about the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. In order to protect the information from the Whitespring counterintelligence, the information needs to be stored in a physical form. It can be used to obtain prewar tech from the Brotherhood expeditionaries, or to gain access to quests and even assassination missions on Whitespring officials.</VFED_Intel.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>Decommissioned Whitespring technology since the invention of psylink neuroformers, psychic amplifier upgrades a psylink in the user's mind. It cannot form a psylink by itself, and can only be used by colonists with already present psylink. The user presses the device over the eyes, where it links to the brain directly and restructures part of it. Afterwards, the device disintegrates into worthless ash.</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.description>
  <VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>cryptid amplifier</VFED_PsychicAmplifier.label>
  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>A small surveillance buoy usually deployed around temporary convoy stops. Linked directly with a patrolling vertibot, once triggered, it will send down a small missile salvo on its location.</VFED_StrikeBuoy.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.description>A small Whitespring crate containing valuables. May contain intel. Opening it requires bypassing several security protocols and takes a short while.\n\nAny attempt to destroy it will destroy the items as well.</VFED_SupplyCrate.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>A Whitespring computer interface. Linked to the surveillance console, the display bank shows live footage from all surveillance pillars in the sector.</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>
  <VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>A large pillar with a series of sensors, cameras and motion detectors. Thanks to the sophisticated face recognition system, surveillance pillar can detect the presence of Brotherhood expeditionaries in radius and will increase the visibility of whichever faction has sent them. Can be disabled via electromagnetic pulse, or by simply cutting off the power grid.</VFED_SurveillancePillar.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>A compact stack of data discs produced exclusively by the Whitespring Enclave for knowledge transcription. They are primarily designed for preserving information. When ignited, they release a dense cloud of blinding smoke and sparks, capable of engulfing a wide area in flames.</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.description>
  <VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>data disc stack</VFED_TechiteDiscStack.label>
  <VFED_Techprinter.description>The Data Printer is a marvel of technological innovation, designed to capture and preserve the intricate knowledge residing within a scientist’s mind. These advanced machines imprint this invaluable information directly onto data discs. Techprints provide foundational knowledge for researchers, shedding light on innovations from more advanced societies.</VFED_Techprinter.description>
  <VFED_Techprinter.label>data printer</VFED_Techprinter.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>orbital cannon capacitor bank</VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>This terminal serves as the primary interface for operating the Orbital Cannon batteries. Equipped with sophisticated controls and targeting systems, the Orbital Cannon Control Station ensures precision and coordination when deploying the formidable firepower of the Orbital Cannons. Operators need to be within its radius to control it.</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>orbital cannon control station</VFED_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>
  <VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>Whitespring suite</VFE_Apparel_StellicRobe.label>
  <VFEE_Aperitif.description>A non-alcoholic, pleasantly light, citrusy, and slightly bitter aperitif that owes its flavors and aromas to sweet and bitter oranges, rhubarb, and Whitespring craftsmanship. Its recipe is guarded by Whitespring hospitality offices, and few on the rim have managed to recreate it. Drinking it induces heavy but painless vomiting, completely clearing the stomach and resetting the palate.\n\nWhitespring officials prize aperitif for letting them indulge in even more of the settlement's finest cuisine.</VFEE_Aperitif.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>A high-tech helmet with a solid plasteel-weave shell and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system backed by real-time firing solutions. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>Whitespring light helmet</VFEE_Apparel_AbsolverHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>A high-tech suit of powered armor with layered plasteel-weave plates and multi-spectrum sensors that feed telemetry data to the wearer. While it provides excellent protection, its primary purpose is concealment through an intricate optical camouflage system that also assists the user's movement. Armor like this is reserved for the Whitespring Enclave's elite assassins due to limited production.</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>Whitespring light armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorAbsolver.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>Brotherhood expeditionary armor</VFEE_Apparel_ArmorDeserter.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>Brotherhood expeditionary helmet</VFEE_Apparel_DeserterHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>Whitespring heavy armor</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryCuirass.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>Whitespring heavy helmet</VFEE_Apparel_JanissaryHelmet.label>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>An exceedingly complex facemask fitted with advanced technology reserved for senior Whitespring scientists. It is designed for designated researchers so they can advance the Whitespring Enclave's needs without rest.\n\nThe inlaid techprint synchronizes with the wearer's brain while they perform research, effectively doubling research speed while restoring rest and recreation.</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.description>
  <VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>Whitespring scientist helmet</VFEE_Apparel_TechfriarCrown.label>
  <VFEE_GrandChair.label>Whitespring chair</VFEE_GrandChair.label>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>A majestic rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>grand Whitespring rug</VFEE_GrandRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_GrandTable.label>Whitespring table</VFEE_GrandTable.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>Whitespring sign</VFEE_ImperialBanner.label>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>A stoney bas relief of Whitespring imagery for decorating a floor.</VFEE_ImperialSlab.description>
  <VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>Whitespring slab</VFEE_ImperialSlab.label>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>An intricate rug with a Whitespring-style pattern, for decorating a floor.</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.description>
  <VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>large Whitespring rug</VFEE_LargeRoyalRug.label>
  <VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>orbital beam</VFEE_OrbitalSlicer.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>Whitespring mirror</VFEE_RoyalMirror.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>grand presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureGrand.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>large presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureLarge.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>small presidential sculpture</VFEE_RoyalSculptureSmall.label>
  <VFEE_RoyalStool.label>Whitespring stool</VFEE_RoyalStool.label>
  <VFEE_SteleSmall.label>presidential plaque</VFEE_SteleSmall.label>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential desk chair can serve as a focus for ceremonial duties and cryptid meditation.</VFEE_StellicThrone.description>
  <VFEE_StellicThrone.label>presidential desk chair</VFEE_StellicThrone.label>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>A spacer-tech Whitespring gunship designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system. Equipped with a twin-linked autocannon for ground support, these XVB02s often land in the middle of the battlefield to extract stranded troops.</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.description>
  <VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>XVB02</VFEI_ArmoredShuttle.label>
  <ShipLandingBeacon.label>Vertibird Landing Beacon</ShipLandingBeacon.label>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>A command staff issued to Whitespring executive officers during inspections, briefings, and emergency command duty. Its cryptex head sharpens cryptid insight and helps regulate neural strain, while the embedded attunement core rejects any wielder outside the assigned chain of command.</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.description>
  <VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>cryptex command staff</VPWE_MeleeWeapon_PsyfocusStaffBladelink.label>
  <GrandThrone.description>An ornate grand chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential grand chair grants the occupant a sense of authority and dignity.</GrandThrone.description>
  <GrandThrone.label>presidential grand chair</GrandThrone.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>A crystal-metallic longsword refined for Whitespring security officers. Its mono-molecular edge cuts through armor with ease, while an embedded cryptex core sharpens the wielder's cryptid insight and stabilizes the weapon's high-speed response.

The cryptex core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once that bond is established, the blade responds with extreme speed and precision and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>cryptex molecular blade</MeleeWeapon_MonoSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>A metal-cored officer's sword wrapped in a sheath of captive plasma. Targets are sliced by the inner edge and burned by the surrounding field, giving Whitespring officers a close-range weapon that can cut and cauterize in the same strike.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the sword responds with unusual speed and control and rejects any wielder outside its assigned handler.</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>plasma officer sword</MeleeWeapon_PlasmaSwordBladelink.label>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>A Whitespring warhammer with an embedded EMP capacitor. On impact it discharges a powerful pulse in addition to the physical blow, making it especially effective against power armor, robots, and other advanced hardware.

Its cryptex guidance core can attune to only one bearer at a time. Once linked, the hammer tracks the wielder's timing and strike rhythm with unusual accuracy and rejects any hand outside its assigned operator.</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.description>
  <MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>pulse hammer</MeleeWeapon_ZeusHammerBladelink.label>
  <Throne.description>An ornate chair used by the President for official addresses and meditation. Sitting in the presidential chair may be used as a focus for certain duties and ceremonies.</Throne.description>
  <Throne.label>presidential chair</Throne.label>
  <ShuttleIncoming.label>vertibird (incoming)</ShuttleIncoming.label>
  <ShuttleLeaving.label>vertibird (leaving)</ShuttleLeaving.label>
</LanguageData>
