<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFE_AnimalFeeder.description>A feeding trough. Food stored in this will not deteriorate, even if outside.</VFE_AnimalFeeder.description>
  <VFE_AnimalFeeder.label>animal feeder</VFE_AnimalFeeder.label>
  <VFE_Ecosystem.description>Grows plants quickly in an artificial, sealed ecosystem. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut.\n\nContains a built-in sun lamp to provide light for the plants.</VFE_Ecosystem.description>
  <VFE_Ecosystem.label>artificial ecosystem</VFE_Ecosystem.label>
  <VFE_Ecosystem_Tilable.description>Grows plants quickly in an artificial, sealed ecosystem which can be configured to effectively grow even picky plants. Requires a high amount of power to work; plants will die if power is cut. Contains a built-in sun lamp to provide light for the plants.\n\nThis version is modular and can be assembled in any shape necessary.</VFE_Ecosystem_Tilable.description>
  <VFE_Ecosystem_Tilable.label>tilable artificial ecosystem</VFE_Ecosystem_Tilable.label>
  <VFE_Hydroponics_Tilable.description>An artificial nutrient bath for growing plants. The nutrients pumps must work continuously; the plants will die if power is cut.\n\nThis version is modular and can be assembled in any shape necessary.</VFE_Hydroponics_Tilable.description>
  <VFE_Hydroponics_Tilable.label>tilable hydroponics basin</VFE_Hydroponics_Tilable.label>
  <VFE_PlanterBox.description>Grows plants in a box of soil. Does not require power to work.</VFE_PlanterBox.description>
  <VFE_PlanterBox.label>planter box</VFE_PlanterBox.label>
  <VFE_PlanterBox_Tilable.description>Grows plants in a box of soil. Does not require power to work.\n\nCan be constructed in any desired shape.</VFE_PlanterBox_Tilable.description>
  <VFE_PlanterBox_Tilable.label>tilable planter box</VFE_PlanterBox_Tilable.label>
  <VFE_Scarecrow.description>A humanoid figure made out of hay, dressed in old clothes to deter animals in a large radius. Small animals will be too afraid to approach.</VFE_Scarecrow.description>
  <VFE_Scarecrow.label>scarecrow</VFE_Scarecrow.label>
  <VFE_Sprinkler.description>A water sprinkler, providing an area around it with water. Enhances the growth of surrounding plants.</VFE_Sprinkler.description>
  <VFE_Sprinkler.label>sprinkler</VFE_Sprinkler.label>
</LanguageData>