<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.label>remote charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.description>A pair of high-explosive shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_HighExplosive.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.label>remote incendiary charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.description>A pair of incendiary shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Incendiary.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.label>remote EMP charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.description>A pair of EMP shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_EMP.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.label>remote smoke charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.description>A pair of smoke shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Smoke.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.label>remote firefoam charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.description>A pair of firefoam shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Firefoam.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.label>remote antigrain charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.description>A pair of antigrain warheads connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_AntigrainWarhead.description>
  <VFED_BombPack_Deployed.label>deployed bomb pack</VFED_BombPack_Deployed.label>
  <VFED_BombPack_Deployed.description>A deployed bomb pack. It’s armed, and can be detonated with a press of a button.</VFED_BombPack_Deployed.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.label>IED shrapnel trap</VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.description>A pair of shrapnel shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>IED armor-piercing trap</VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>A pair of armor-piercing shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.label>IED cluster trap</VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.description>A pair of cluster shells connected to a trigger which detonates on touch or bullet impact. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_TrapIED_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.label>remote shrapnel charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.description>A pair of shrapnel shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>remote armor-piercing charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>A pair of armor-piercing shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.label>remote cluster charge</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.description>A pair of cluster shells connected to a remote triggering mechanism. It can be detonated at will, but the fuse time might vary. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VFED_RemoteTrapIED_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Kontarion.label>kontarion</VFED_Turret_Kontarion.label>
  <VFED_Turret_Kontarion.description>A powerful, long-range weapon used by the Whitespring Enclave to take out enemy targets from afar. Kontarion turret fires ultra-dense uranium slugs at incredible speeds, penetrating even the heaviest armor. With its rapid-fire capabilities, tremendous accuracy and infinite range, it's a force to be reckoned with. It's more accurate at longer ranges, and can't fire at all close up. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of uranium slug ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Kontarion.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Kontarion.label>kontarion cannon</VFED_Gun_Kontarion.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Kontarion.description>A self-loading uranium slug cannon designed to attach to a turret.</VFED_Gun_Kontarion.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Palintone.label>palintone</VFED_Turret_Palintone.label>
  <VFED_Turret_Palintone.description>A powerful, anti-infantry weapon used by the Whitespring Enclave to defend unsafe outposts. Palintone turret fires large-caliber shells at incredible speeds, dealing heavy damage over significant ranges. It fires huge volleys of rounds that can provide suppressive fire and quickly shred lightly armored targets. With its devastating firepower, the Palintone turret is capable of keeping even the largest enemy forces at bay. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of autocannon ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Palintone.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Palintone.label>palintone cannon</VFED_Gun_Palintone.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Palintone.description>A self-loading cannon designed to attach to a turret.</VFED_Gun_Palintone.description>
  <VFED_Turret_Onager.label>onager</VFED_Turret_Onager.label>
  <VFED_Turret_Onager.description>A powerful, anti-armored weapon used by the Whitespring Enclave to destroy heavily armored targets with ease. Capable of launching missiles in bursts of 6, the Onager can deal devastating damage to enemy forces in a short amount of time. The Onager turret is most effective at short range, where its missiles can be accurately targeted at enemy positions. However, it cannot fire at enemies that are too close, as the missiles require a certain distance to arm and track their targets. Additionally, due to the sheer number of missiles it fires, the Onager is not as accurate as other turrets, and can sometimes miss its targets. May explode when damaged.\n\nIt consumes a lot of ammunition, and requires an adjacent crate of missile ammo in order to automatically reload. It cannot be reloaded by hand.</VFED_Turret_Onager.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Onager.label>onager cannon</VFED_Gun_Onager.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Onager.description>A self-loading rocket launcher designed to attach to a turret.</VFED_Gun_Onager.description>
  <VFFED_Bullet_Onager.label>onager</VFFED_Bullet_Onager.label>
  <VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>striker turret</VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.label>
  <VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>A stationary, powerful turret. Will self-destruct if it is sufficiently damaged.</VFED_Turret_StrikerTurret.description>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.label>uranium slug ammo box</VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.label>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.description>A small-sized box containing uranium slug ammunition. Used by Kontarion turrets to reload. May explode when damaged.</VFED_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.description>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.label>autocannon ammo box</VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.label>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.description>A small-sized box containing autocannon ammunition. Used by Palintone turrets to reload. May explode when damaged.</VFED_AmmoBox_Autocannon.description>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.label>missile ammo box</VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.label>
  <VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.description>A small-sized box containing missiles. Used by Onager turrets to reload. May explode when damaged.</VFED_AmmoBox_Missile.description>
  <VFED_SupplyCrate.label>supply crate</VFED_SupplyCrate.label>
  <VFED_BiosecuredCrate.label>biosecured crate</VFED_BiosecuredCrate.label>
  <VFED_SurveillancePillar.label>surveillance pillar</VFED_SurveillancePillar.label>
  <VFED_StrikeBuoy.label>strike buoy</VFED_StrikeBuoy.label>
  <VFED_FuelTank.label>fuel tank</VFED_FuelTank.label>
  <VFED_SurveillanceStation.label>surveillance console</VFED_SurveillanceStation.label>
  <VFED_SurveillanceStation.description>A large console designed to link to surrounding surveillance pillars. Provides users with all the necessary data related to enemy movements in a given sector.</VFED_SurveillanceStation.description>
  <VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.label>surveillance display bank</VFED_SurveillanceDisplayBank.label>
  <VFED_WaterMain.label>water main</VFED_WaterMain.label>
  <VFED_WaterMain.description>A large node connecting all the nearby water mains. Required for the underfarms to operate.</VFED_WaterMain.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.description>A capacitor bank that transforms electricity into raw energy for the Zeus cannon. Will release a large EMP shockwave when destroyed, potentially disabling the Zeus cannon itself.</VFED_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.description>
  <VFED_ZeusCannon.label>orbital cannon</VFED_ZeusCannon.label>
  <VFED_ZeusCannon.description>A relic of ancient Sophiamundan technology, the Orbital Cannon is a closely guarded secret of the Whitespring Enclave. This formidable artillery piece has the unique ability to convert vast quantities of electricity into potent energy blasts. With unmatched range, it can pierce the atmosphere to target and obliterate objects in orbit. A testament to lost engineering brilliance, it stands as both a weapon and a symbol of the Whitespring Enclave's might.\n\nIt has a long charging cycle, after which it will aim at the target and release a devastating energy blast.</VFED_ZeusCannon.description>
  <VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.label>burnout intel scraper</VFED_BurnoutIntelScraper.label>
  <VFED_Biodecoder.label>biodecoder</VFED_Biodecoder.label>
  <VFED_Biodecoder.description>A biodecoder is a single-use ultratech device that is designed to strip biocoding off any item. It uses a complex process to unlatch the biocoding from the original item, which transfers the biocoding onto the biodecoder, breaking it in the process. Biodecoder can also be used on biosecured crate to open them. This device is often used in sensitive operations where the presence of biocoding could compromise the mission.</VFED_Biodecoder.description>
  <VFED_Intel.label>intel</VFED_Intel.label>
  <VFED_CriticalIntel.label>critical intel</VFED_CriticalIntel.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.label>shrapnel shell</VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.description>Mortar shell that is designed to explode mid-air and release a large number of sharp projectiles. These projectiles are specifically designed to cut through light armored enemies, inflicting serious injuries or fatalities. Projectiles are ejected with the same vector as the mortar shell, and may be stopped by obstacles.</VFED_Shell_Shrapnel.description>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shell_Shrapnel.label>shrapnel shell</VFED_Bullet_Shell_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shrapnel.label>shrapnel</VFED_Bullet_Shrapnel.label>
  <VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>armor-piercing shell</VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.description>Armor-piercing shells are designed to explode upon impact and destroy anything they hit, completely bypassing the armor of the target. Their explosion radius is almost non-existent, and armored targets need to be hit directly for the shell to destroy them. They are very accurate and travel at extreme speeds.</VFED_Shell_ArmorPiercing.description>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>armor-piercing shell</VFED_Bullet_Shell_ArmorPiercing.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Cluster.label>cluster shell</VFED_Shell_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_Shell_Cluster.description>Mortar shell that is designed to split mid-air and release three high-explosive shells. Separated shells are ejected in random directions, following the same vector as the cluster shell. Explosions cover a high area but the accuracy of the shells leave a lot to be desired.</VFED_Shell_Cluster.description>
  <VFED_Bullet_Shell_Cluster.label>cluster shell</VFED_Bullet_Shell_Cluster.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_BombPack.label>bomb pack</VFED_Apparel_BombPack.label>
  <VFED_Apparel_BombPack.description>A single-use man-portable explosive device. Deployed on the ground, it becomes armed and can be detonated with a press of a button. It generates a big explosion thanks to a wired-in antigrain warhead, making it capable of destroying critical infrastructure and personnel alike.</VFED_Apparel_BombPack.description>
  <VFED_AerodroneStrikeIncoming.label>vertibot strike</VFED_AerodroneStrikeIncoming.label>
  <VFED_Spark.label>spark</VFED_Spark.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.label>pulse cycler</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.description>A modified charged-shot revolver that incorporates mechanoid technology. Recovered thump cannons have been reversed engineered to allow for a powerful charge revolver with two shooting modes to be created. Charged shot mode will eliminate any close targets with a powerful, armor-piercing blast, whilst a Thump shot mode allows users to incapacitate enemies and break any defenses they might be hiding behind. Modes can be changed with a press of a button.</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.description>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.0.label>Single shot (Charged shot)</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.0.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.1.label>Single shot (Thump shot)</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.verbs.1.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.0.label>handle</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.0.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.1.label>barrel</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.tools.1.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.comps.0.verbProps.0.label>Single shot (Charged shot)</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.comps.0.verbProps.0.label>
  <VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.comps.0.verbProps.1.label>Single shot (Thump shot)</VFED_Gun_ChargeCycler.comps.0.verbProps.1.label>
  <VFED_Bullet_ChargedShot.label>pulse shot</VFED_Bullet_ChargedShot.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_ThumpShot.label>concussion shot</VFEE_Bullet_ThumpShot.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Fletchling.label>acid scattergun</VFED_Gun_Fletchling.label>
  <VFED_Gun_Fletchling.description>A modification to the extremely rare fletcher rifle, fletchling is a shotgun commonly used by Whitespring Brotherhood expeditionaries. The mere possession of it can be seen as an act of war against the Shattered Whitespring Enclave. Each fletchling shot releases a number of small acidifier darts that may hit several targets, causing extreme amounts of pain and acid burns. Lethal to organics and almost useless against non-organics, such as mechanoids. \n\nTargets hit by these flechettes will be inflicted with an unstable variant of acidifier fluids, designed to dissolve the target from the inside rather than destroy their equipment. The acid will rampage through the target’s body and usually results in vital organs being dissolved, however lethality isn’t guaranteed.</VFED_Gun_Fletchling.description>
  <VFED_Gun_Fletchling.tools.0.label>barrel</VFED_Gun_Fletchling.tools.0.label>
  <VFEE_Bullet_FletchlingDart.label>fletcher dart</VFEE_Bullet_FletchlingDart.label>
</LanguageData>