<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEFactory_MakeBabyFood.description>Make baby food, a nutritionally balanced vegetarian mash for babies. While easy to make in large quantities, only babies appreciate its bland taste and mushy texture.</VFEFactory_MakeBabyFood.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeBabyFood.label>make baby food</VFEFactory_MakeBabyFood.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeKibble.description>Make animal kibble by combining raw meat and plants. 24 kibble will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so 15 vegetable and 15 meat will output 36 kibble.</VFEFactory_MakeKibble.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeKibble.label>make kibble</VFEFactory_MakeKibble.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeKibbleFromHay.description>Make animal kibble by combining raw meat and hay. Will always output 36 kibble.</VFEFactory_MakeKibbleFromHay.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeKibbleFromHay.label>make kibble from hay</VFEFactory_MakeKibbleFromHay.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeMassProducedMeal.description>Cook straightforward, mass-produced meals from a combination of meat and plant ingredients. A total of 2 nutrition will make 4 mass-produced meals.</VFEFactory_MakeMassProducedMeal.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeMassProducedMeal.label>make mass-produced meals</VFEFactory_MakeMassProducedMeal.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakePemmican.description>Make pemmican, a preserved combination of meat and plant food. It doesn't taste amazing, but lasts a long time without refrigeration. 32 pemmican will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so 5 vegetable and 5 meat will output 16 pemmican.</VFEFactory_MakePemmican.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakePemmican.label>make pemmican</VFEFactory_MakePemmican.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakePumpkinCoffee.description>Make pumpkin spice coffee, a cheap, mass produced generic coffee seeped in an array of spices, oddly excluding any actual pumpkin..</VFEFactory_MakePumpkinCoffee.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakePumpkinCoffee.label>make pumpkin spice coffee</VFEFactory_MakePumpkinCoffee.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeSimpleSoup.description>Prepare a simple uncooked soup quickly made from a few ingredients.</VFEFactory_MakeSimpleSoup.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeSimpleSoup.label>prepare simple soup</VFEFactory_MakeSimpleSoup.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeSurvivalMeal.description>Prepare packaged survival meals from a combination of meat and plant ingredients. Much of the ingredients are wasted in the preservation process. A total of 2.4 nutrition will make 4 survival meals.</VFEFactory_MakeSurvivalMeal.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeSurvivalMeal.label>make survival meal</VFEFactory_MakeSurvivalMeal.label>
</LanguageData>
