<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedEggs.description>Safely store boiled eggs in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely. 20 cans will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so for example 4 chicken eggs and one steel will output 20 cans.</VFEFactory_MakeCannedEggs.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedEggs.label>make canned eggs</VFEFactory_MakeCannedEggs.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedFish.description>Safely store fish in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely. 20 cans will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so for example 4 salmon and one steel will output 20 cans.</VFEFactory_MakeCannedFish.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedFish.label>make canned fish</VFEFactory_MakeCannedFish.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedFruit.description>Safely store fruit in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely. Preserved fruit can be used in the production of desserts. 20 cans will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so for example 20 apples plus one steel will output 20 cans.</VFEFactory_MakeCannedFruit.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedFruit.label>make canned fruit</VFEFactory_MakeCannedFruit.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedMeat.description>Safely store raw meat in a steel can. Canning extends its shelf life almost indefinitely. 20 cans will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so 20 meat plus one steel will output 20 cans.</VFEFactory_MakeCannedMeat.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedMeat.label>make canned meat</VFEFactory_MakeCannedMeat.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedProduce.description>Safely store vegetables in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely. 20 cans will be produced per every nutrition consumed, so for example 20 corn plus one steel will output 20 cans.</VFEFactory_MakeCannedProduce.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedProduce.label>make canned produce</VFEFactory_MakeCannedProduce.label>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedSoup.description>Safely store pre-cooked soup in steel cans. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely. Canned soup does not carry the benefits of being fine or lavish.</VFEFactory_MakeCannedSoup.description>
  <VFEFactory_MakeCannedSoup.label>make canned soup</VFEFactory_MakeCannedSoup.label>
</LanguageData>
