<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_AntiPowerArmor_Specialist.description>Trained to counter American T-51b power armor units, using specialized weapons and tactics. Experienced in urban ambushes and sabotage missions.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_AntiPowerArmor_Specialist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_AntiPowerArmor_Specialist.title>Anti-Power Armor Specialist</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_AntiPowerArmor_Specialist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Artillery_Crew.description>Operated heavy artillery batteries, bombarding enemy positions from afar. Skilled in teamwork, calculation, and surviving counter-battery fire in the war’s fiercest battles.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Artillery_Crew.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Artillery_Crew.title>Sino-American War Artillery Crew</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Artillery_Crew.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Battlefield_Medic.description>Rushed into danger to treat wounded soldiers under fire, often improvising with limited supplies. Trained in trauma care and evacuation procedures.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Battlefield_Medic.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Battlefield_Medic.title>Battlefield Medic</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Battlefield_Medic.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_ChemicalWarfare_Trooper.description>Deployed chemical agents and defended against gas attacks in the trenches. Trained in hazardous environments and emergency medical response.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_ChemicalWarfare_Trooper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_ChemicalWarfare_Trooper.title>Chemical Warfare Trooper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_ChemicalWarfare_Trooper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Combat_Cook.description>Prepared hot meals for troops in the field, often under bombardment. Learned to improvise with rations and keep morale high with a warm bowl of soup.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Combat_Cook.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Combat_Cook.title>Combat Cook</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Combat_Cook.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Conscriptee.description>Drafted into the PLA as the war escalated, given basic training before being sent to the front. Experience marked by propaganda, fear, and the struggle to survive the American advance.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Conscriptee.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Conscriptee.title>Sino-American War Conscriptee</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Conscriptee.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Engineer.description>Built fortifications and sabotaged enemy supply lines during the war. Specialized in explosives, field repairs, and tunnel warfare beneath the battlefields.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Engineer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Engineer.title>Sino-American War Combat Engineer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Engineer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Engineer.description>Repaired vehicles, weapons, and communications equipment on the battlefield. Adapted quickly to changing conditions and resource shortages.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Engineer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Engineer.title>Field Engineer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Engineer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Medic.description>Provided emergency care to wounded comrades in the trenches and bombed-out cities. Trained in battlefield medicine and chemical warfare survival.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Medic.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Medic.title>Sino-American War Field Medic</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Field_Medic.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Forward_Observer.description>Directed artillery and air strikes from the front lines, relaying coordinates under fire. Trained in reconnaissance, radio operation, and survival in hostile territory.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Forward_Observer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Forward_Observer.title>Forward Observer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Forward_Observer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Infantry.description>Served as a foot soldier in the People’s Liberation Army during the brutal Sino-American War. Fought in the frozen wastes of Alaska and the ruins of Shanghai, surviving on discipline and propaganda.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Infantry.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Infantry.title>Sino-American War Infantry</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Infantry.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Military_Police.description>Maintained order and discipline among troops, rooting out spies and enforcing martial law. Skilled in interrogation and close-quarters combat.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Military_Police.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Military_Police.title>Sino-American War Military Police</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Military_Police.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Officer.description>Led squads through the chaos of the Sino-American War, enforcing loyalty and discipline. Experienced in urban combat and countering American power armor assaults.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Officer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Officer.title>Sino-American War Officer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Officer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Psych_Warfare_Operative.description>Spread propaganda and misinformation to demoralize enemy troops and sway civilians. Skilled in persuasion, deception, and psychological tactics.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Psych_Warfare_Operative.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Psych_Warfare_Operative.title>Psychological Warfare Operative</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Psych_Warfare_Operative.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Radio_Operator.description>Kept units connected during the chaos of battle, relaying orders and calling for artillery strikes. Skilled in encryption and countering American electronic warfare.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Radio_Operator.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Radio_Operator.title>Sino-American War Radio Operator</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Radio_Operator.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Sapper.description>Specialized in demolitions and mine-laying, clearing obstacles and sabotaging enemy fortifications. Courageous and skilled in explosives under fire.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Sapper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Sapper.title>Sino-American War Sapper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Sapper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Scout.description>Operated ahead of the main force, gathering intelligence on American troop movements and power armor deployments. Trained in stealth, navigation, and survival in hostile territory.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Scout.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Scout.title>Sino-American War Scout</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Scout.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Stealth_Trooper.description>Elite infiltrator equipped with prototype stealth suits, trained for sabotage and assassination behind enemy lines. Feared by American GIs and legendary in the propaganda reels.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Stealth_Trooper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Stealth_Trooper.title>Chinese Stealth Trooper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Stealth_Trooper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Tank_Crew.description>Operated and maintained tanks in the PLA armored divisions, facing American Vertibirds and power armor on the battlefield. Skilled in teamwork, mechanics, and armored warfare.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Tank_Crew.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Tank_Crew.title>Sino-American War Tank Crew</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Army_Tank_Crew.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Air_Raid_Leader.description>Helped organize air raid drills at school, guiding classmates to shelters and keeping spirits high. Developed leadership and crisis management skills.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Air_Raid_Leader.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Air_Raid_Leader.title>Air Raid Drill Leader</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Air_Raid_Leader.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Apartment_Helper.description>Helped neighbors with chores in the communal housing block, learning cooperation and responsibility. Developed practical skills and a sense of community.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Apartment_Helper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Apartment_Helper.title>Apartment Helper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Apartment_Helper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Bookstore_Reader.description>Spent afternoons in the local bookstore, reading adventure stories and Party pamphlets. Developed a love for learning and imagination.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Bookstore_Reader.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Bookstore_Reader.title>Bookstore Reader</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Bookstore_Reader.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_City_Schoolchild.description>Attended crowded city schools, memorizing Party slogans and practicing duck-and-cover drills. Quick to learn and eager to please teachers.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_City_Schoolchild.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_City_Schoolchild.title>City Schoolchild</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_City_Schoolchild.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Kitchen_Helper.description>Assisted family members in preparing meals during rationing, learning basic cooking and the importance of sharing. Developed patience and a sense of responsibility.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Kitchen_Helper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Kitchen_Helper.title>Kitchen Helper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Kitchen_Helper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Helper.description>Spent weekends helping family sell food at the local market, learning to count change and greet customers. Developed a strong work ethic and people skills.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Helper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Helper.title>Market Helper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Helper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Runner.description>Ran errands for family and neighbors in the busy city market, learning to navigate crowds and barter for supplies. Developed resourcefulness and people skills.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Runner.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Runner.title>Market Runner</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Market_Runner.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Mechanic_Apprentice.description>Helped fix bicycles and scooters in the family shop, learning the basics of tools and repairs. Developed curiosity and practical skills.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Mechanic_Apprentice.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Mechanic_Apprentice.title>Mechanic's Apprentice</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Mechanic_Apprentice.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Museum_Explorer.description>Visited the city museum with family, fascinated by ancient artifacts and war exhibits. Developed curiosity and a love for history.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Museum_Explorer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Museum_Explorer.title>Museum Explorer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Museum_Explorer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Propaganda_Artist.description>Drew patriotic posters for school contests, inspired by Party slogans and war heroes. Developed artistic skill and a sense of national pride.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Propaganda_Artist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Propaganda_Artist.title>Propaganda Poster Artist</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Propaganda_Artist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Radio_Listener.description>Spent evenings listening to state broadcasts and war news with family. Learned to follow current events and discuss them with friends.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Radio_Listener.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Radio_Listener.title>Young Radio Listener</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Radio_Listener.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Farmer.description>Helped grow beans and greens on the rooftop garden, learning about plants and teamwork. Developed patience and a love for fresh food.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Farmer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Farmer.title>Rooftop Farmer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Farmer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Gardener.description>Helped parents tend rooftop vegetable gardens, learning patience and the basics of growing food in the city. Developed a green thumb and a love for nature.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Gardener.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Gardener.title>Rooftop Gardener</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Rooftop_Gardener.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Street_Performer.description>Learned to sing and dance for coins in busy city squares, entertaining neighbors and soldiers. Developed confidence and a flair for the dramatic.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Street_Performer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Street_Performer.title>Street Performer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Street_Performer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Textile_Helper.description>Assisted family members in sewing uniforms and blankets, learning patience and the basics of handiwork. Developed creativity and teamwork.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Textile_Helper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Textile_Helper.title>Textile Helper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Textile_Helper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Young_Pioneer.description>Joined the Young Pioneers, learning Party songs, marching in parades, and practicing air raid drills. Developed discipline and pride in serving the Republic.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Young_Pioneer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Young_Pioneer.title>Red Star Young Pioneer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Child_Young_Pioneer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Agricultural_Worker.description>Tended rice paddies and vegetable fields for the collective, working long hours to feed the nation and the army. Learned resilience and the value of cooperation.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Agricultural_Worker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Agricultural_Worker.title>Collective Farm Worker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Agricultural_Worker.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Apartment_Caretaker.description>Maintained communal housing blocks, fixing leaks and keeping the lights on during blackouts. Learned practical skills and the art of neighborly cooperation.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Apartment_Caretaker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Apartment_Caretaker.title>Apartment Caretaker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Apartment_Caretaker.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Black_Market_Trader.description>Operated in the shadows, trading rationed goods and forbidden items. Learned caution, secrecy, and the art of making deals under the watchful eyes of the state.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Black_Market_Trader.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Black_Market_Trader.title>Black Market Trader</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Black_Market_Trader.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Bookstore_Clerk.description>Worked at a city bookstore, recommending novels and educational texts to customers. Developed strong communication skills and a love for literature.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Bookstore_Clerk.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Bookstore_Clerk.title>Bookstore Clerk</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Bookstore_Clerk.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_City_Gardener.description>Tended public parks and rooftop gardens, growing food and flowers for the community. Developed patience, a green thumb, and pride in beautifying the city.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_City_Gardener.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_City_Gardener.title>City Gardener</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_City_Gardener.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Entertainer.description>Performed patriotic songs and operas for citizens and soldiers, boosting morale and spreading Party messages. Talented in music and public speaking.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Entertainer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Entertainer.title>State Entertainer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Entertainer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Factory_Worker.description>Worked long shifts assembling rifles and power cells for the war effort. Learned discipline, efficiency, and the importance of loyalty to the state.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Factory_Worker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Factory_Worker.title>PLA Munitions Factory Worker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Factory_Worker.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Homemaker.description>Managed a household, raised children, and kept the family safe during air raids. Skilled in cooking, cleaning, and rationing supplies.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Homemaker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Homemaker.title>State Homemaker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Homemaker.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Hospital_Nurse.description>Cared for wounded civilians and soldiers in crowded hospitals, working long shifts during air raids. Skilled in first aid, compassion, and crisis management.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Hospital_Nurse.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Hospital_Nurse.title>State Hospital Nurse</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Hospital_Nurse.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Librarian.description>Managed a local library, helping citizens find information and escape into stories. Developed a love for learning and a talent for organization.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Librarian.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Librarian.title>City Librarian</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Librarian.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Market_Vendor.description>Sold food and supplies in the city market, bartering with neighbors and soldiers alike. Developed strong communication skills and a knack for persuasion.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Market_Vendor.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Market_Vendor.title>Market Vendor</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Market_Vendor.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Museum_Guide.description>Led tours at the city museum, sharing stories of history and culture with visitors. Developed public speaking skills and a passion for education.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Museum_Guide.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Museum_Guide.title>Museum Guide</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Museum_Guide.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_News_Reporter.description>Reported on local events and war news, spreading Party-approved stories and keeping citizens informed. Skilled in writing, interviewing, and public speaking.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_News_Reporter.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_News_Reporter.title>News Reporter</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_News_Reporter.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Party_Official.description>Oversaw neighborhood meetings and enforced Party policies. Skilled in persuasion, organization, and keeping the community loyal to the state.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Party_Official.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Party_Official.title>Local Party Official</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Party_Official.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Police.description>Patrolled city streets, enforcing order and rooting out dissent. Trained in investigation, negotiation, and self-defense.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Police.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Police.title>State Police Officer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Police.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Postal_Worker.description>Delivered letters and packages across the city, braving air raids and blackouts. Learned the value of perseverance and community connection.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Postal_Worker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Postal_Worker.title>Postal Worker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Postal_Worker.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PowerPlant_Tech.description>Maintained the city’s reactors and generators, keeping the lights on during blackouts and air raids. Skilled in electrical repairs and crisis management.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PowerPlant_Tech.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PowerPlant_Tech.title>Power Plant Technician</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PowerPlant_Tech.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Propaganda_Artist.description>Created stirring posters and patriotic murals, inspiring citizens to support the war and fear the American invaders. Talented in art and persuasion.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Propaganda_Artist.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Propaganda_Artist.title>Propaganda Artist</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Propaganda_Artist.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PublicBath_Attendant.description>Kept the city’s public baths clean and welcoming, offering comfort and community in troubled times. Learned the value of hygiene and friendly conversation.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PublicBath_Attendant.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PublicBath_Attendant.title>Public Bath Attendant</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_PublicBath_Attendant.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Radio_Host.description>Broadcast patriotic news and war bulletins, keeping citizens informed and motivated. Skilled in public speaking and propaganda.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Radio_Host.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Radio_Host.title>State Radio Host</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Radio_Host.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Restaurant_Cook.description>Prepared meals for hungry workers and soldiers, making the most of rationed ingredients. Developed creativity in the kitchen and a reputation for hearty, comforting food.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Restaurant_Cook.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Restaurant_Cook.title>Restaurant Cook</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Restaurant_Cook.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Schoolchild.description>Grew up attending state-run schools, learning Party slogans and practicing air raid drills. Quick to memorize lessons and eager to please teachers.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Schoolchild.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Schoolchild.title>State Schoolchild</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Schoolchild.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Doctor.description>Practiced medicine in a crowded city hospital, treating wounds and radiation sickness. Dedicated to public health and the Party’s ideals.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Doctor.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Doctor.title>State Hospital Doctor</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Doctor.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Engineer.description>Designed and maintained infrastructure for the war effort, from power plants to bunkers. Analytical and inventive, loyal to the Party’s vision.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Engineer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Engineer.title>State Engineer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Engineer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Teacher.description>Taught children about science, history, and the virtues of the People’s Republic. Led air raid drills and encouraged vigilance against foreign spies.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Teacher.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Teacher.title>State School Teacher</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_State_Teacher.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Mechanic.description>Repaired bicycles, scooters, and delivery trucks for neighbors and local businesses. Learned resourcefulness and the art of improvisation with limited parts.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Mechanic.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Mechanic.title>Street Mechanic</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Mechanic.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Musician.description>Played patriotic songs and folk tunes in city squares, lifting spirits and spreading hope. Developed musical talent and a strong sense of community.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Musician.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Musician.title>Street Musician</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Musician.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Sweeper.description>Kept city streets clean and clear, even during air raid debris and ration shortages. Developed a strong work ethic and pride in public service.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Sweeper.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Sweeper.title>Street Sweeper</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Sweeper.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Vendor.description>Sold steamed buns and tea in the bustling city streets, trading news and rumors with customers and soldiers. Developed a sharp wit and a knack for negotiation.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Vendor.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Vendor.title>Street Vendor</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Street_Vendor.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Student.description>Attended university, studying engineering or medicine to serve the Republic. Quick to learn, but inexperienced in the realities of war.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Student.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Student.title>State University Student</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Student.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tailor.description>Sewed and mended clothes for neighbors and local shops, making do with limited materials. Developed creativity and skill in handiwork.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tailor.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tailor.title>Neighborhood Tailor</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tailor.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Textile_Worker.description>Produced uniforms and blankets for soldiers and civilians, working long hours at the loom. Learned patience, precision, and the importance of teamwork.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Textile_Worker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Textile_Worker.title>Textile Worker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Textile_Worker.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Theater_Performer.description>Acted in patriotic plays and operas, entertaining citizens and soldiers alike. Developed a flair for drama and a talent for inspiring hope in dark times.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Theater_Performer.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Theater_Performer.title>Theater Performer</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Theater_Performer.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tram_Operator.description>Operated city trams, transporting workers and families through busy streets and blackout drills. Learned punctuality, patience, and the importance of keeping the city moving.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tram_Operator.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tram_Operator.title>Tram Operator</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Tram_Operator.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Utility_Worker.description>Maintained power lines and water pipes in the city, keeping essential services running during air raids and blackouts. Skilled in repairs and crisis management.</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Utility_Worker.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Utility_Worker.title>Utility Worker</FCP_Backstory_PRC_Citizen_Utility_Worker.title>
</LanguageData>