<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFES_DD.description>Diego Dire believes the best stories are the violent ones, facing unfavourable odds and going down in a blaze of glory with exploding muffalos and drunks.</VFES_DD.description>
  <VFES_DD.label>diego dire</VFES_DD.label>
  <VPE_Basilicus.description>Basilicus enforces the will of the emperor wherever he goes, bestowing great powers on those who deserve it. Epic ballads become even more fantastic if everyone has access to psychic powers.</VPE_Basilicus.description>
  <VPE_Basilicus.label>basilicus bestower</VPE_Basilicus.label>
  <VFEE_AriadneArchduchess.description>Ariadne got tired of the unpredictability of the nobility, and whilst she will create a story of increasing tension, she will force dangerous events on you as your wealth increases. After all, it’s not fun to kick someone while they’re down.</VFEE_AriadneArchduchess.description>
  <VFEE_AriadneArchduchess.label>ariadne archduchess</VFEE_AriadneArchduchess.label>
  <VFED_Damocles.description>Damocles knows that the only way to defeat the Empire is to tread the fine line between all out war and espionage. Good events only come to those who fight. The story that unfolds will be that of increasing tension and desperation, focused on a small group of likeminded people surviving the onslaught together.</VFED_Damocles.description>
  <VFED_Damocles.label>damocles deserter</VFED_Damocles.label>
  <VFET_TalonTribal.description>Talon shuns technology and progress. Real strength lies in cultural foundations, and only by rejecting rapid progress will you be able to gain the respect of the spirits. Rapid technology unlocks will invoke bad events.</VFET_TalonTribal.description>
  <VFET_TalonTribal.label>talon tribal</VFET_TalonTribal.label>
  <VFEM_MaynardMedieval.description>Maynard Medieval weaves a tale of struggle and hardship, where every breakthrough is earned through sweat, blood, and sacrifice. The march of progress slows as tradition clings tight, demanding ever greater effort to pry knowledge from the grip of time. Research projects will cost more time the more of them you have completed.</VFEM_MaynardMedieval.description>
  <VFEM_MaynardMedieval.label>maynard medieval</VFEM_MaynardMedieval.label>
</LanguageData>
