<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Bullet_TeslaBlaster.label>tesla blaster bolt</Bullet_TeslaBlaster.label>
  <Gun_AutomatedMortar.label>automated mortar</Gun_AutomatedMortar.label>
  <Gun_TeslaBlaster.description>A specialized electrical weapon designed to be mounted on a turret.</Gun_TeslaBlaster.description>
  <Gun_TeslaBlaster.label>tesla blaster</Gun_TeslaBlaster.label>
  <VEFS_TrapLandmine.description>A sophisticated explosive charge connected to a pressure plate trigger which detonates immediately on touch. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VEFS_TrapLandmine.description>
  <VEFS_TrapLandmine.label>landmine</VEFS_TrapLandmine.label>
  <VEFS_TrapShockmine.description>A concealed high-tech trap that releases a localized EMP pulse when triggered. It resets automatically after a short cooldown. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps. Animals can sense these when calm.</VEFS_TrapShockmine.description>
  <VEFS_TrapShockmine.label>shockmine</VEFS_TrapShockmine.label>
  <VFES_ActiveArtilleryStrike.label>artillery strike</VFES_ActiveArtilleryStrike.label>
  <VFES_AmmoCrate.description>An ammo crate useful for storing shells. Improves firing rate of surrounding soldiers.</VFES_AmmoCrate.description>
  <VFES_AmmoCrate.label>ammo crate</VFES_AmmoCrate.label>
  <VFES_Artillery_ArtilleryGun.description>Artillery launcher. Lobs bombs over walls. Accurate and long-ranged.</VFES_Artillery_ArtilleryGun.description>
  <VFES_Artillery_ArtilleryGun.label>artillery gun</VFES_Artillery_ArtilleryGun.label>
  <VFES_Artillery_Catapult.description>A catapult is a ballistic device used to launch a projectile a great distance without the aid of gunpowder or other propellants. In use since ancient times, the catapult has proven to be one of the most persistently effective mechanisms in warfare.</VFES_Artillery_Catapult.description>
  <VFES_Artillery_Catapult.label>catapult</VFES_Artillery_Catapult.label>
  <VFES_Artillery_Rock.label>massive boulder</VFES_Artillery_Rock.label>
  <VFES_Artillery_Weapon.description>Artillery cannon capable of long range bombardment.</VFES_Artillery_Weapon.description>
  <VFES_Artillery_Weapon.label>artillery</VFES_Artillery_Weapon.label>
  <VFES_ArtilleryStrikeIncoming.label>artillery strike (incoming)</VFES_ArtilleryStrikeIncoming.label>
  <VFES_ArtilleryStrikeLeaving.label>artillery strike (leaving)</VFES_ArtilleryStrikeLeaving.label>
  <VFES_BarbedWire.description>A type of steel fencing wire consisting of sharp edges and points arranged at intervals. Not only does it slow movement of enemies, but it inflicts cuts and puncture wounds.</VFES_BarbedWire.description>
  <VFES_BarbedWire.label>barbed wire</VFES_BarbedWire.label>
  <VFES_BearTrap.description>A set of spikes under tension, connected to a touch-activated trigger. When the victim disturbs the trigger, the spikes spring forth and typically strike their legs or feet. The spikes will harmlessly go over victims that are too small, while victims that are too large will simply crush this trap. Since it is hidden in the surrounding terrain, it cannot be placed adjacent to other traps.</VFES_BearTrap.description>
  <VFES_BearTrap.label>bear trap</VFES_BearTrap.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_Ballista.label>ballista bolt</VFES_Bullet_Ballista.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_Catapult.label>massive boulder</VFES_Bullet_Catapult.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_ChargeComplex.label>charge shot</VFES_Bullet_ChargeComplex.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_ChargeRailgunShot.label>charge railgun shot</VFES_Bullet_ChargeRailgunShot.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_ChargeTurretShot.label>charge shot</VFES_Bullet_ChargeTurretShot.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_ConcealedTurret.label>concealed turret bullet</VFES_Bullet_ConcealedTurret.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_DoubleChargeLance.label>charge railgun shots</VFES_Bullet_DoubleChargeLance.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_EMPCannon.label>EMP shot</VFES_Bullet_EMPCannon.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_HMG.label>HMG bullet</VFES_Bullet_HMG.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_HMGComplex.label>HMG bullet</VFES_Bullet_HMGComplex.label>
  <VFES_Bullet_Invisible.label>invisible</VFES_Bullet_Invisible.label>
  <VFES_CavalrySpikes.description>Wooden stakes placed in a row to build defensive fortifications. Very cheap and quick to build, provides basic cover and deals damage to people trying to traverse them. Breaks after some time.</VFES_CavalrySpikes.description>
  <VFES_CavalrySpikes.label>cavalry spikes</VFES_CavalrySpikes.label>
  <VFES_Complex_Charge.description>A heavy, pulse-charged rapid-fire blaster mounted on a barricade to grant cover. Needs to be manned in order to fire. Requires plasteel to refurbish its barrel after heavy use.</VFES_Complex_Charge.description>
  <VFES_Complex_Charge.label>charge complex</VFES_Complex_Charge.label>
  <VFES_Complex_GraserCannon.description>A devastating gamma ray laser mounted on a barricade to grant cover. It fires a sweeping beam capable of piercing armor and igniting targets. Needs to be manned in order to fire. Requires plasteel to refurbish its emitter array after heavy use.</VFES_Complex_GraserCannon.description>
  <VFES_Complex_GraserCannon.label>graser cannon complex</VFES_Complex_GraserCannon.label>
  <VFES_Complex_HeavyIncineratorComplex.description>A heavy incinerator mounted on a barricade to grant cover. Needs to be manned in order to fire. It is equipped with a powerful mega-burner that requires bioferrite to reload.</VFES_Complex_HeavyIncineratorComplex.description>
  <VFES_Complex_HeavyIncineratorComplex.label>heavy incinerator complex</VFES_Complex_HeavyIncineratorComplex.label>
  <VFES_Complex_Hmg.description>A heavy machine gun mounted on sandbags to grant cover. Needs to be manned in order to fire. Requires steel to refurbish its barrel after heavy use.</VFES_Complex_Hmg.description>
  <VFES_Complex_Hmg.label>HMG complex</VFES_Complex_Hmg.label>
  <VFES_Complex_Minigun.description>A multi-barrel machine gun mounted on sandbags to grant cover and provide stability. Where most self-loading guns are powered by the energy from the gunpowder, the minigun uses an electric motor to rapidly cycle cartridges through the weapon. Needs to be manned in order to fire. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use.</VFES_Complex_Minigun.description>
  <VFES_Complex_Minigun.label>minigun complex</VFES_Complex_Minigun.label>
  <VFES_ComplexCharge_Top.description>A self-loading minigun designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_ComplexCharge_Top.description>
  <VFES_ComplexCharge_Top.label>minigun</VFES_ComplexCharge_Top.label>
  <VFES_ComplexGraserCannon_Top.description>A graser cannon designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_ComplexGraserCannon_Top.description>
  <VFES_ComplexGraserCannon_Top.label>graser cannon</VFES_ComplexGraserCannon_Top.label>
  <VFES_ComplexHeavyIncinerator_Top.description>A heavy incinerator designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_ComplexHeavyIncinerator_Top.description>
  <VFES_ComplexHeavyIncinerator_Top.label>heavy incinerator</VFES_ComplexHeavyIncinerator_Top.label>
  <VFES_ComplexHmg_Top.description>A self-loading HMG designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_ComplexHmg_Top.description>
  <VFES_ComplexHmg_Top.label>HMG</VFES_ComplexHmg_Top.label>
  <VFES_ComplexMinigun_Top.description>A self-loading minigun designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_ComplexMinigun_Top.description>
  <VFES_ComplexMinigun_Top.label>minigun</VFES_ComplexMinigun_Top.label>
  <VFES_ConcealedBarrier.description>A retractable, waist-high barrier for use as cover from incoming shots. It provides strong cover while deployed and is almost invisible when submerged. Barricades will block certain kinds of animals the same way that fences do. Requires power.</VFES_ConcealedBarrier.description>
  <VFES_ConcealedBarrier.label>concealed barrier</VFES_ConcealedBarrier.label>
  <VFES_DeployableBarrier.description>A submersible barrier which acts as a normal floor tile when unpowered. Provides excellent cover from ranged attacks. It only takes half as much damage when submerged.</VFES_DeployableBarrier.description>
  <VFES_DeployableBarrier.label>deployable barrier</VFES_DeployableBarrier.label>
  <VFES_Dugout.description>A long, narrow ditch dug into the ground. Crossing it requires climbing up and down, therefore it significantly slows down movement speed. People inside the dugout suffer weapon range penalty, but gain significant cover and protection from explosive damage.</VFES_Dugout.description>
  <VFES_Dugout.label>dugout</VFES_Dugout.label>
  <VFES_Gun_ArmoredTurret.description>A refined automatic gun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_ArmoredTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_ArmoredTurret.label>military turret gun</VFES_Gun_ArmoredTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_BallistaTurret.description>An ancient military siege engine in a form of a crossbow mounted on a wooden construct.</VFES_Gun_BallistaTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_BallistaTurret.label>ballista</VFES_Gun_BallistaTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_ChargeComplex.description>A charge gun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_ChargeComplex.description>
  <VFES_Gun_ChargeComplex.label>charge gun emplacement</VFES_Gun_ChargeComplex.label>
  <VFES_Gun_ChargeTurret.description>A charge rifle made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_ChargeTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_ChargeTurret.label>charged turret gun</VFES_Gun_ChargeTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_ConcealedTurret.description>A simple automatic gun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_ConcealedTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_ConcealedTurret.label>concealed turret gun</VFES_Gun_ConcealedTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_EMPTurret.description>An EMP coil gun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_EMPTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_EMPTurret.label>EMP cannon</VFES_Gun_EMPTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_FlameTurret.description>A flamethrower made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_FlameTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_FlameTurret.label>flame turret gun</VFES_Gun_FlameTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_FloorTurret.label>submersible military turret doublegun</VFES_Gun_FloorTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_HMGComplex.description>A mounted variant of a heavy machine gun.</VFES_Gun_HMGComplex.description>
  <VFES_Gun_HMGComplex.label>mounted HMG</VFES_Gun_HMGComplex.label>
  <VFES_Gun_MilitaryTurret.description>Two simple automatic guns made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_MilitaryTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_MilitaryTurret.label>military turret doublegun</VFES_Gun_MilitaryTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_None.description>A replica gun made of wood for a turret.</VFES_Gun_None.description>
  <VFES_Gun_None.label>decoy gun</VFES_Gun_None.label>
  <VFES_Gun_NonLethalTurret.description>A non-lethal rubber bullet gun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_NonLethalTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_NonLethalTurret.label>non-lethal turret gun</VFES_Gun_NonLethalTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_PointDefense.description>A rapid-fire gun for point-defense applications.</VFES_Gun_PointDefense.description>
  <VFES_Gun_PointDefense.label>point defense gun</VFES_Gun_PointDefense.label>
  <VFES_Gun_RailgunTurret.description>An advanced railgun designed to launch two electromagnetically accelerated projectiles simultaneously.</VFES_Gun_RailgunTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_RailgunTurret.label>charge railgun</VFES_Gun_RailgunTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_Searchlight.description>A searchlight for a turret.</VFES_Gun_Searchlight.description>
  <VFES_Gun_Searchlight.label>searchlight</VFES_Gun_Searchlight.label>
  <VFES_Gun_SentryTurret.description>A fully automatic gatling gun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_SentryTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_SentryTurret.label>sentry turret gun</VFES_Gun_SentryTurret.label>
  <VFES_Gun_ShotgunTurret.description>An automatic shotgun made to be mounted on a turret.</VFES_Gun_ShotgunTurret.description>
  <VFES_Gun_ShotgunTurret.label>shotgun turret gun</VFES_Gun_ShotgunTurret.label>
  <VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>A large, ultratech device that projects an extremely vast energy field around itself to protect everything inside, but consumes a huge amount of power when active. Works through walls.\n\nRepulsors only activate when there's an active threat present such as a raid or an artillery bombardment. Otherwise, they stay in an inactive state and consume much less power.\n\nCan set surrounding area on fire if enough damage is absorbed in a short period of time.</VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_LargeRepulsor.label>large repulsor</VFES_LargeRepulsor.label>
  <VFES_Platform.description>A long, narrow wooden platform. Crossing it requires climbing up and down, therefore it significantly slows down movement speed. Soldiers on top of the platform get significant weapon range increase, but also receive cover penalty due to being exposed.</VFES_Platform.description>
  <VFES_Platform.label>platform</VFES_Platform.label>
  <VFES_ShieldGenerator_Archotech.description>A self-powered archotech device that projects a very potent energy field around itself to protect everything inside. Works through walls.\n\nShield generators only activate when there's an active threat present such as a raid or an artillery bombardment. Otherwise, they stay in an inactive state and consume much less power.\n\nCan set surrounding area on fire if enough damage is absorbed in a short period of time.</VFES_ShieldGenerator_Archotech.description>
  <VFES_ShieldGenerator_Archotech.label>archotech shield generator</VFES_ShieldGenerator_Archotech.label>
  <VFES_ShieldGenerator_Large.description>An ultratech device that projects a large energy field around itself to protect everything inside, but consumes a huge amount of power when active. Works through walls.\n\nShield generators only activate when there's an active threat present such as a raid or an artillery bombardment. Otherwise, they stay in an inactive state and consume much less power.</VFES_ShieldGenerator_Large.description>
  <VFES_ShieldGenerator_Large.label>large shield generator</VFES_ShieldGenerator_Large.label>
  <VFES_ShieldGenerator_Small.description>An ultratech device that projects a potent energy field around itself to protect everything inside, but consumes a huge amount of power when active. Works through walls.\n\nShield generators only activate when there's an active threat present such as a raid or an artillery bombardment. Otherwise, they stay in an inactive state and consume much less power.\n\nCan set surrounding area on fire if enough damage is absorbed in a short period of time.</VFES_ShieldGenerator_Small.description>
  <VFES_ShieldGenerator_Small.label>small shield generator</VFES_ShieldGenerator_Small.label>
  <VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>An ultratech device that projects a potent energy field around itself to protect everything inside, but consumes a huge amount of power when active. Works through walls.\n\nRepulsors only activate when there's an active threat present such as a raid or an artillery bombardment. Otherwise, they stay in an inactive state and consume much less power.\n\nCan set surrounding area on fire if enough damage is absorbed in a short period of time.</VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_SmallRepulsor.label>small repulsor</VFES_SmallRepulsor.label>
  <VFES_Trench.description>A long, narrow ditch dug into the ground. Crossing it requires climbing up and down, therefore it significantly slows down movement speed. Soldiers inside the trench suffer weapon range penalty, but gain significant cover.</VFES_Trench.description>
  <VFES_Trench.label>trench</VFES_Trench.label>
  <VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>A specialized defensive turret that intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its protective radius, but cannot engage ground targets. Interception chance scales with the target's velocity. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use.</VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AntiAir.label>anti-air turret</VFES_Turret_AntiAir.label>
  <VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>An armored, portable automatic turret. Requires steel to refurbish its barrel after heavy use. Extra armor plating allows the turret to provide some cover, makes it more resistant to enemy fire and prevents explosion in case of severe damage. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.label>armored turret</VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Artillery.description>A manned artillery that launches all kinds of shells. Capable of inflicting devastating damage to both enemy forces and structures, this military machinery excels at laying down fire support for soldiers in the field.\n\nCapable of targeting other areas of the world within a medium radius.</VFES_Turret_Artillery.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Artillery.label>artillery</VFES_Turret_Artillery.label>
  <VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>A heavy automatic turret enhanced with 2 barrels. Its large-caliber shells do heavy damage over significant ranges, but its barrels must be refurbished after use. It cannot fire at close-up targets, and may explode when damaged.</VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.label>double autocannon</VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.label>
  <VFES_Turret_AutomatedMortar.description>An automated mortar that launches high-explosive shells. While it can inflict devastating damage, the mortar's inherent inaccuracy makes it more useful for attacking large fortifications than groups of enemies in the field. Due to a delicate firing mechanism, it's only calibrated to fire high-explosive shells.</VFES_Turret_AutomatedMortar.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AutomatedMortar.label>automated mortar</VFES_Turret_AutomatedMortar.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Ballista.description>An ancient military siege engine in the form of a crossbow mounted on a wooden construct. Bolts fired from this machine explode into splinters on impact.</VFES_Turret_Ballista.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Ballista.label>ballista</VFES_Turret_Ballista.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Catapult.description>A catapult is a ballistic device used to launch a projectile a great distance without the aid of gunpowder or other propellants. In use since ancient times, the catapult has proven to be one of the most persistently effective mechanisms in warfare.</VFES_Turret_Catapult.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Catapult.label>catapult</VFES_Turret_Catapult.label>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeComplex.description>A stationary charge cannon mounted on a metal barrier. Capable of sustaining fire until the barrel needs changing.</VFES_Turret_ChargeComplex.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeComplex.label>charge complex</VFES_Turret_ChargeComplex.label>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgun.description>A cutting-edge, pulse-charged, rail-assisted weapon system that fires a short burst of high-velocity projectiles, energized with unstable plasma as they leave the rail. The resulting shots pierce armor and bodies alike, but the turret requires new plasteel barrel after use. It cannot fire at close range, and may explode when damaged.</VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgun.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgun.label>charge railgun</VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgun.label>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgunTurret.description>A heavy railgun cannon usually mounted on spacecraft, utilising an array of advanced sensors which offer top-class accuracy. Requires components to be replaced in order to operate. May explode when damaged.</VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgunTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgunTurret.label>charge railgun</VFES_Turret_ChargeRailgunTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeTurret.description>An automatic turret with a charge pulser gun on top, utilising advanced sensors which offer improved accuracy. Requires plasteel to refurbish its barrel after heavy use. May explode when damaged.</VFES_Turret_ChargeTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ChargeTurret.label>charge turret</VFES_Turret_ChargeTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Concealed.description>A compact automatic turret equipped with retractable armor plating and a submersion mechanism. It is capable of submerging into the ground, becoming impossible to target. Requires steel to refurbish its barrel after heavy use. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_Concealed.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Concealed.label>concealed turret</VFES_Turret_Concealed.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Decoy.description>A cloth dummy holding a wooden rifle. Attracts enemy attention.</VFES_Turret_Decoy.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Decoy.label>decoy</VFES_Turret_Decoy.label>
  <VFES_Turret_EMPTurret.description>An electro-magnetic pulse cannon usually mounted on a spacecraft. Requires uranium rods to be replaced in order to operate. Can only target mechanoids and may explode if damaged.</VFES_Turret_EMPTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_EMPTurret.label>EMP cannon</VFES_Turret_EMPTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Flame.description>A portable flamethrower turret. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_Flame.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Flame.label>flame turret</VFES_Turret_Flame.label>
  <VFES_Turret_FloorTurret.description>A submersible military-grade double barreled automatic turret which acts as a normal floor tile when unpowered. It only takes half as much damage when submerged. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_FloorTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_FloorTurret.label>deployable turret</VFES_Turret_FloorTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_HMGComplex.description>A stationary heavy machine gun supported by some sandbags to grant cover.</VFES_Turret_HMGComplex.description>
  <VFES_Turret_HMGComplex.label>HMG complex</VFES_Turret_HMGComplex.label>
  <VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>A military-grade double barreled automatic turret. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.label>military turret</VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>A heavy automatic turret. Its multi-barrel mechanism unleashes sustained fire at high speed, shredding lightly armored targets at mid-range. It may explode when damaged. Requires steel to refurbish its barrels after heavy use.</VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Minigun.label>minigun turret</VFES_Turret_Minigun.label>
  <VFES_Turret_NonLethalTurret.description>A turret designed to fire rubber bullets at intruders or unruly colonists. It causes pain and blunt trauma with low chance of fatal injury, making it ideal for non-lethal suppression. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_NonLethalTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_NonLethalTurret.label>non-lethal turret</VFES_Turret_NonLethalTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>An apparatus combining an extremely luminous lamp and a mirrored parabolic reflector, useful for lighting up and dazzling targets.</VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Searchlight.label>searchlight</VFES_Turret_Searchlight.label>
  <VFES_Turret_SentryGun.description>A self-powered turret with a small gatling gun mounted on top. Light enough to be carried and deployed wherever. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_SentryGun.description>
  <VFES_Turret_SentryGun.label>sentry gun</VFES_Turret_SentryGun.label>
  <VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>A compact automatic turret fitted with a semi-automatic shotgun. Requires steel to refurbish its barrel after heavy use. May explode when damaged. Its dumb AI brain can't be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.label>shotgun turret</VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.label>
  <VFES_Turret_TeslaBlaster.description>A cutting-edge utility turret designed to counter the mechanoid advances. Four capacitors are charged to release a bolt of electricity. Upon impact, the power surge stuns affected mechanoid, before seeking to jump to another. Will only target mechanoids.</VFES_Turret_TeslaBlaster.description>
  <VFES_Turret_TeslaBlaster.label>tesla blaster</VFES_Turret_TeslaBlaster.label>
  <VFES_TurretDoubleAutocannon_Top.description>A self-loading large-bore double cannon designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_TurretDoubleAutocannon_Top.description>
  <VFES_TurretDoubleAutocannon_Top.label>double autocannon</VFES_TurretDoubleAutocannon_Top.label>
  <VFES_TurretMinigun_Top.description>A self-loading minigun designed to be attached to a turret.</VFES_TurretMinigun_Top.description>
  <VFES_TurretMinigun_Top.label>minigun</VFES_TurretMinigun_Top.label>
</LanguageData>