<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <IceAge.label>nuclear winter</IceAge.label>
  <IceAge.description>High-altitude ash and radioactive soot have choked the sky, plunging the region into a nuclear winter.

Flora and fauna are suffering as biomes slide toward their colder counterparts. Food and fuel become scarce, and wasteland factions grow more desperate by the day.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</IceAge.description>
  <IceAge.endMessage>The nuclear winter is easing.</IceAge.endMessage>
  <GlobalWarming.label>scorched summer</GlobalWarming.label>
  <GlobalWarming.description>Heat trapped beneath a filthy radioactive haze has driven local temperatures to punishing levels.

Flora and fauna are suffering as biomes drift toward their hotter counterparts. Water dries up, forage fails, and every faction in the wasteland feels the pressure.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</GlobalWarming.description>
  <GlobalWarming.endMessage>The scorched summer is breaking.</GlobalWarming.endMessage>
  <PsychicRain.label>temporal radstorm</PsychicRain.label>
  <PsychicRain.description>An unstable old-world weather anomaly has churned a temporal radstorm into the atmosphere.

The storm lashes the land with strange glowing rain that twists flesh and time alike. Anyone left in the open will age at a frightening pace.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</PsychicRain.description>
  <PsychicRain.endMessage>The temporal radstorm is passing.</PsychicRain.endMessage>
  <LongNight.label>ashen skies</LongNight.label>
  <LongNight.description>Orbital debris and black ash have smothered the sun, throwing the region into a long, ruinous twilight.

With the sky darkened and visibility ruined, wasteland factions take advantage of the confusion to raid, move, and settle scores under cover of gloom.

It can last anywhere between a season and several years.</LongNight.description>
  <LongNight.endMessage>The ashen skies are clearing.</LongNight.endMessage>
  <PsychicBloom.label>mutant bloom</PsychicBloom.label>
  <PsychicBloom.description>A surge of unstable spores and irradiated pollen has reshaped local plant life almost overnight.

The sky glows with strange color while mutant flowers spread through fields, roads, and ruins alike. Colonists feel oddly uplifted, but the overgrowth can smother your crops if left unchecked.

It can last anywhere between a few days and a season.</PsychicBloom.description>
  <PsychicBloom.endMessage>The mutant bloom is fading.</PsychicBloom.endMessage>
  <SpaceBattle.label>vertibird dogfight</SpaceBattle.label>
  <SpaceBattle.description>A running vertibird dogfight is raging overhead. Wreckage and missed shots can rain down across the area for several hours.</SpaceBattle.description>
  <SpaceBattle.endMessage>The vertibird dogfight is over.</SpaceBattle.endMessage>
  <SpaceBattle.letterText>Several vertibirds and old-world gunships have engaged in a running fight above the region. Missed shots and burning debris can impact the ground and start fires.</SpaceBattle.letterText>
  <VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.description>Detonation of Deadlife dust warheads in the upper atmosphere has permanently altered planetary conditions. A dense death pall now blankets the world. This pall reanimates unburied corpses exposed to the open air as feral ghouls.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.description>
  <VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.label>ghoul apocalypse</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.label>
  <VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.letterText>Detonation of Deadlife dust warheads in the upper atmosphere has permanently altered planetary conditions. A dense death pall now blankets the world.

This pall reanimates all unburied corpses exposed to the open air. Any non-mechanoid corpse not under a roof will rise again as a feral ghoul. Burned or fully destroyed corpses are unaffected.

While the death pall is active, no normal weather transitions can occur. Rain will not fall, and fires may spread unchecked.

On a global scale, the death pall will linger for anywhere from three seasons to several years. In its wake, roaming feral ghoul hordes will now traverse the world, overrunning settlements and hunting down caravans.</VQED_ShamblerApocalypse.letterText>
  <VFED_DivineInferno.description>The Whitespring Enclave has initiated an orbital inferno protocol on your colony and is moving the required orbital beam satellites into position. Once they align overhead, they will glass the colony with numerous pillars of fire. This can be prevented by reducing your visibility back to Hidden.</VFED_DivineInferno.description>
  <VFED_DivineInferno.label>orbital inferno</VFED_DivineInferno.label>
  <VFED_MissileRain.description>A Vertibot strike is underway. Take cover!</VFED_MissileRain.description>
  <VFED_MissileRain.label>vertibot bombardment</VFED_MissileRain.label>
</LanguageData>
