<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.description>A crude suit of power armor cobbled together from scavenged parts, rusted plating, and salvaged T-45 components. While it offers decent protection for a wastelander, it lacks the refinement and reliability of proper military power armor. The makeshift construction leaves gaps in coverage, and the improvised repairs make it noticeably heavier and more cumbersome than its pre-war counterparts. Still, in the wasteland, any power armor is better than none.</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.label>raider power armor</FCP_Apparel_Raider_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.description>A more refined raider power armor variant favored by the Scabbers gang. Built from better-maintained salvage and reinforced with additional scrap plating, it offers improved protection while maintaining the characteristic ramshackle appearance. The Scabbers take pride in their armor's intimidating spikes and rust-stained panels, wearing them as badges of honor. Despite being heavier than standard raider power armor, it provides noticeably better protection against the dangers of the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.label>scabber power armor</FCP_Apparel_Scabber_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.description>The pinnacle of raider power armor engineering, the Waster variant combines salvaged military-grade components with surprisingly competent craftsmanship. Though still crude by pre-war standards, it approaches the protection level of T-45 power armor while maintaining the brutal aesthetic raiders prefer. The heavy construction and layered plating make it a formidable sight on the battlefield. Waster bosses and elite raiders prize these suits above all other armor.</FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.label>waster power armor</FCP_Apparel_Waster_Power_Armor.label>
</LanguageData>
