<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.description>A dangerous mutated gecko with the ability to breathe fire. These fearsome creatures have developed specialized glands that allow them to expel flames at their enemies. Fire geckos are highly aggressive and territorial, making them extremely dangerous to encounter in the wild. Their unique physiology makes them resistant to heat and fire, and their hide is particularly valuable. They are typically found in hot, desert regions.</FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.label>fire gecko</FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Fire_Gecko.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Gecko.description>A large mutated gecko that has grown to the size of a small dog. These reptilian creatures are common throughout the wasteland, particularly in desert regions. While not particularly aggressive, they will defend themselves when threatened. Their meat is edible and their hide makes decent leather.</FCP_Animal_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Gecko.label>gecko</FCP_Animal_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.description>A large mutated gecko with distinctive golden scales that shimmer in the light. These creatures are prized for their valuable hide, which can be crafted into high-quality leather goods. Golden geckos are stronger and more aggressive than their common cousins, and their bite can deliver a mild poison. They are found in desert regions and rocky terrain.</FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.label>golden gecko</FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Golden_Gecko.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.description>A large mutated gecko with green scales and a more aggressive temperament than common geckos. Green geckos are tougher and more dangerous, with a stronger bite that can deliver toxins. They are commonly found in rocky areas and caves throughout the wasteland. Their hide is valuable and their meat is edible, though it must be properly prepared.</FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.description>
  <FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.label>green gecko</FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.label>
  <FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.tools.1.label>head</FCP_Animal_Green_Gecko.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>
