<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <WestTek_Gene_Atlantic.description>The Atlantic embody adaptability — forged by ocean winds and shifting tides. Their blood sings with salt and stubborn endurance.</WestTek_Gene_Atlantic.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_Atlantic.label>atlantic soul</WestTek_Gene_Atlantic.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_Cascadia.description>Children of misty forests and basalt mountains. The Cascadians are unshaken by rain or solitude, ever patient and feral at heart.</WestTek_Gene_Cascadia.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_Cascadia.label>cascadian wilds</WestTek_Gene_Cascadia.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_Ghoul.description>Scarred by centuries of decay, ghouls persist beyond reason; their will is the last thing to rot.</WestTek_Gene_Ghoul.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_Ghoul.label>ghoul resilience</WestTek_Gene_Ghoul.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_NatL.description>The Ninety-Nine Tribes carry ancestral echoes — every heart a drumbeat in a chorus of shared memory.</WestTek_Gene_NatL.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_NatL.label>nat'l diversity</WestTek_Gene_NatL.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_NuevoTexico.description>Dust storms and refinery fumes forged the Texicans — weathered souls fueled by stubborn pride and old oil.</WestTek_Gene_NuevoTexico.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_NuevoTexico.label>texico grit</WestTek_Gene_NuevoTexico.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_Numen.description>The Numen are entwined with the land — their spirits a living testament to survival against all odds.</WestTek_Gene_Numen.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_Numen.label>numen roots</WestTek_Gene_Numen.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_PureHuman.description>The Pure Humans embody the resilience of unaltered humanity — a steadfast spirit that endures through every trial.</WestTek_Gene_PureHuman.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_PureHuman.label>human spirit</WestTek_Gene_PureHuman.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_Slanter.description>The Slanters drift between worlds — dreamers and schemers with eyes like broken glass, caught between memory and myth.</WestTek_Gene_Slanter.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_Slanter.label>slanter echo</WestTek_Gene_Slanter.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_SuperMutant.description>The Super Mutants’ strength is legend — a fusion of pain and pride that outlived their makers.</WestTek_Gene_SuperMutant.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_SuperMutant.label>super mutant might</WestTek_Gene_SuperMutant.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_TwoCalifornia.description>Split between paradise and ruin, the Two Californians live in contradiction — both dreamers and survivors of their own myth.</WestTek_Gene_TwoCalifornia.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_TwoCalifornia.label>two-californian duality</WestTek_Gene_TwoCalifornia.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_VaultDweller.description>Raised under steel and silence, the Vault Dwellers’ heritage is order — a longing for structure even in chaos.</WestTek_Gene_VaultDweller.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_VaultDweller.label>vault heritage</WestTek_Gene_VaultDweller.label>
  <WestTek_Gene_Wendigo.description>The Wendigo embody hunger made flesh — a spirit of endless wanting that no feast can sate.</WestTek_Gene_Wendigo.description>
  <WestTek_Gene_Wendigo.label>wendigo hunger</WestTek_Gene_Wendigo.label>
</LanguageData>
