<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.description>The New California Republic is a faction based out of Shady Sands in the former state of California. It is a federal parliamentary republic, similar to the pre-war USA before it descended into authoritarianism. They represent the 老旧 world and its values. Roads, taxes, prisons, elections, and other phenomena long forgotten made a comeback with the NCR’s rise to power. It is seen by its citizens to be the sole haven of civilisation, democracy, and freedom in the wasteland. While there certainly is truth to that notion, the NCR also suffers from widespread corruption and oligarchic tendencies, for much power is held by exceedingly rich ranchers and farm owners. Furthermore, it uses its vast military, well supplied by their industrial centres, to aggressively expand their territory and claim the resources of neighbouring regions to sate the ever-growing hunger of its population.</FCP_Faction_NCR.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.label>新加州共和国</FCP_Faction_NCR.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>总统</FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>新加州人</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>新加州人</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>A rogue faction of former NCR s老旧iers and officers who have deserted the Republic. Disillusioned with the NCR's leadership, they now operate as a hostile paramilitary group, surviving through raids and mercenary work. Their organization is loose, but they are led by a cunning Rogue Colonel.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>流氓上校</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>新加州共和国是一个建立在法律、秩序和进步原则基础上的民主联邦。作为 NCR，你领导着一个殖民地，努力恢复文明并扩大其在荒原上的影响力。</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>NCR 玩家殖民地</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>州长</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>公民</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>公民</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>
