<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.description>这些怪异的变异啮齿动物生活在地下巨大的隧道网络中。它们繁殖迅速，受到干扰时会大量聚集。最初是简单的荒地害虫，它们的数量在地下区域激增，并在那里形成了广泛的洞穴系统。它们具有攻击性、领地意识，会攻击任何进入它们领地的东西。</FCP_Faction_Molerat.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.fixedName>鼹鼠群体</FCP_Faction_Molerat.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.label>鼹鼠群体</FCP_Faction_Molerat.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnSingular>鼹鼠</FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnsPlural>鼹鼠</FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.description>The 钢铁兄弟会 is one of the 老旧est still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their s商场 numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.fixedName>钢铁兄弟会</FCP_Faction_BoS.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.ideoDescription>在麦克森长老的领导下，兄弟会将纪律与目标统一起来。我们保护技术，我们保护人类免受自身侵害，我们消灭威胁我们未来的可憎事物。钢铁与我们同在。</FCP_Faction_BoS.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.label>钢铁兄弟会</FCP_Faction_BoS.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.leaderTitle>长老</FCP_Faction_BoS.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.royalFavorLabel>荣誉</FCP_Faction_BoS.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.description>The Lost Hills Chapter is the original 钢铁兄弟会, founded by Roger Maxson in the 废墟s of the Mariposa 军事基地. As the first and founding chapter, Lost Hills represents the purest form of the Brotherhood's ideals - technological preservation, military discipline, and isolationist philosophy. They are the keepers of the original Codex and consider themselves the supreme authority over all Brotherhood chapters. Their fortress in the Lost Hills bunker complex remains one of the most technologically advanced facilities in the wasteland, housing pre-war military hardware and the Brotherhood's most elite s老旧iers.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.fixedName>失落的山丘章节</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.ideoDescription>We are the original 钢铁兄弟会, keepers of the true Codex as written by Roger Maxson. Technology must be preserved by those of pure bloodline. Outsiders cannot be trusted with our 秘密s or our legacy. We are the shield that protects humanity's technological heritage - isolation is our strength, purity is our path.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.label>失落的山丘章节</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.leaderTitle>长老</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.royalFavorLabel>荣誉</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.description>The Midwestern 钢铁兄弟会 broke away from the main order during an airship expedition that crash-landed in the Midwest. Unlike their Western counterparts, the Midwestern chapter has adopted a more pragmatic and expansionist philosophy, actively recruiting tribals and wastelanders into their ranks. They maintain the Brotherhood's devotion to technology and military prowess, but have shed much of the isolationism that defines other chapters. Their territory spans vast stretches of the former American Midwest, making them one of the largest and most diverse Brotherhood chapters, though they remain estranged from Lost Hills' authority.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.fixedName>中西部兄弟会</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.ideoDescription>我们是兄弟会进化而来的。当我们的飞艇在中西部坠毁时，我们了解到生存需要适应。我们招募有价值的人——部落、废土人，甚至以前的敌人——因为力量来自团结，而不是孤立。法典指导我们，但不束缚我们。我们扩张、我们保护、我们忍耐。</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.label>中西部兄弟会</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.leaderTitle>一般的</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.royalFavorLabel>荣誉</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>阿巴拉契亚分会正处于十字路口。与失落山丘隔绝，被迫独立运作，你必须决定你的战团的道路：你会遵循“束缚之链”——要求技术保存高于一切的严格法典原则吗？或者你会打破传统，成为废土人民的保护者，证明兄弟会不仅仅是收藏家？你们的孤立意味着没有监督，没有增援，而是完全自由地定义兄弟会在这片土地上真正代表的是什么。</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>阿巴拉契亚分会</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>圣骑士</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uph老旧 their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>里昂的骄傲残余</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>长老</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>The Mojave Chapter of the 钢铁兄弟会 is a shadow of its former self, forced out of the 隐蔽 Valley bunker and now struggling to survive in the harsh Mojave wasteland. Once a proud and disciplined force, they have been reduced to a scattered group, clinging to their mission of safeguarding humanity's technological heritage. Despite their diminished state, their mastery of power armor and energy weapons ensures they remain a formidable presence in the region.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>莫哈韦分会</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>长老</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the 钢铁兄弟会, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uph老旧 the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>兄弟会弃儿</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>保护者</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>被遗弃者</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>被遗弃者</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>The 钢铁兄弟会 is one of the 老旧est still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their s商场 numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>钢铁兄弟会</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>长老</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uph老旧 their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.fixedName>里昂的骄傲残余</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.ideoDescription>莱昂斯长老告诉我们，没有同情心的技术是毫无价值的。我们是人民的盾牌，无辜者的保护者，并证明兄弟会不仅仅是文物的收藏家。</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.label>里昂的骄傲残余</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.leaderTitle>长老</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnSingular>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnsPlural>兄弟</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>骄傲荣誉</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the 钢铁兄弟会, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uph老旧 the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.fixedName>兄弟会弃儿</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.ideoDescription>We are the keepers of the true Brotherhood mission. Technology must be preserved at all costs. Outsiders cannot be trusted with the power of the 老旧 World. The Codex is law.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>兄弟会弃儿</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.leaderTitle>保护者</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnSingular>被遗弃者</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnsPlural>被遗弃者</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>技术脚本</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.0.nameType.name>凯撒</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.0.nameType.name>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.1.nameType.name>火星</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.1.nameType.name>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.description>Caesar’s Legion is the fearsome group which conquered most of the former states of Arizona, New Mexico, Colorado, and Utah. The Legion styles itself after the 古老 roman legionnaires and uses many low-tech weapons such as javelins and crude but effective melee weapons. They are cruel, warlike, and known to frequently commit massacres against civilians, which they view as dissolute and profligate. Caesar, or Edward Sallow as he was once known, leads his slave armies as an iron fisted dictator and pushes them ever forward to claim new territories for their leader, the self-proclaimed son of Mars himself. Before long, the Legion stood at the shores of the Colorado river and set their eyes on the gleaming towers of New Vegas and California beyond them.</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.fixedName>凯撒军团</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.ideoDescription>凯撒是火星之子，奉火星之命征服整个地球。为了促进这一征服，火星用火净化了地球，使人类陷入了最低潮。凯撒的神圣职责是将荒原从混乱和野蛮中拯救出来</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.label>凯撒军团</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.leaderTitle>凯撒</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnSingular>军团</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnsPlural>军团士兵</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.description>Ruthless remnants of the 老旧 world government, the 英克雷 believe themselves to be humanity’s rightful rulers. Isolated, technologically advanced, and fiercely nationalistic, they seek to restore civilization under their iron-fisted vision—no matter the cost to outsiders.</FCP_Faction_Enclave.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.fixedName>The 英克雷</FCP_Faction_Enclave.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.ideoDescription>The 英克雷 represents the continuation of the United States government, destined to reclaim and restore America. Only pure, untainted humans have the right to rebuild civilization. All others are aberrations to be removed or subjugated.</FCP_Faction_Enclave.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.label>The 英克雷</FCP_Faction_Enclave.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.leaderTitle>总统</FCP_Faction_Enclave.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnSingular>组分</FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnsPlural>成分</FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.royalFavorLabel>权威</FCP_Faction_Enclave.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.description>You are operatives of the 英克雷, the shadow government that considers itself the rightful heir to the United States of America. Armed with advanced pre-war technology and an unwavering belief in your genetic and technological superiority, you seek to restore America to its former glory - by any means necessary. The wasteland is filled with mutants and degenerates who have no place in the new America you will build.</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.label>The 英克雷</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.leaderTitle>上校</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnSingular>代理人</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnsPlural>代理商</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.description>大可汗是一个部落掠夺者社会，其根源可以追溯到战前加利福尼亚州的摩托党帮派。他们曾经是荒原上最强大的掠夺者部落之一，但与 NCR 和其他派系发生了多次冲突，导致他们的人数大幅减少。尽管遭遇挫折，可汗们仍然自豪并保持强烈的独立性，拒绝向任何人低头。他们已成为生产化学品的专家，并用这些化学品换取武器和补给品。可汗们看重力量、对部落的忠诚以及选择生活的自由——不受“文明”社会的法律和税收的约束。他们是游牧民族，住在蒙古包和帐篷里，需要离开时可以快速收拾行李。</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.description>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.fixedName>大可汗</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.ideoDescription>大汗们的生活准则是力量、独立和对部落的忠诚。他们拒绝“文明”社会的规则和限制，宁愿各取所需，自由自在地生活。强者生存，弱者灭亡，部落的生存高于一切。</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.label>大可汗</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.label>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.leaderTitle>汗爸爸</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnSingular>汗</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnsPlural>可汗</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.description>The New California Republic is a faction based out of Shady Sands in the former state of California. It is a federal parliamentary republic, similar to the pre-war USA before it descended into authoritarianism. They represent the 老旧 world and its values. Roads, taxes, prisons, elections, and other phenomena long forgotten made a comeback with the NCR’s rise to power. It is seen by its citizens to be the sole haven of civilisation, democracy, and freedom in the wasteland. While there certainly is truth to that notion, the NCR also suffers from widespread corruption and oligarchic tendencies, for much power is held by exceedingly rich ranchers and farm owners. Furthermore, it uses its vast military, well supplied by their industrial centres, to aggressively expand their territory and claim the resources of neighbouring regions to sate the ever-growing hunger of its population.</FCP_Faction_NCR.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.fixedName>新加州共和国</FCP_Faction_NCR.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.ideoDescription>共和国以自由原则为基础，多年来一直将这些原则付诸实践。最重要的成就是在国家首都区地区禁止奴隶制，这要归功于有影响力的政治家和游骑兵队的共同努力。</FCP_Faction_NCR.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.label>新加州共和国</FCP_Faction_NCR.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>总统</FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>新加州人</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>新加州人</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.royalFavorLabel>服务点</FCP_Faction_NCR.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>A rogue faction of former NCR s老旧iers and officers who have deserted the Republic. Disillusioned with the NCR's leadership, they now operate as a hostile paramilitary group, surviving through raids and mercenary work. Their organization is loose, but they are led by a cunning Rogue Colonel.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.fixedName>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.ideoDescription>Once loyal to the Republic, these deserters have turned away from its broken promises and endless wars. Disillusioned by corruption and failed leadership, they now value survival, freedom, and loyalty to their own above all else. Their ideals are forged in hardship, camaraderie, and a deep distrust of authority. They do what it takes to endure in the wasteland, bound together by necessity and shared experience rather than 老旧 world dogma.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>流氓上校</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>新加州共和国是一个建立在法律、秩序和进步原则基础上的民主联邦。作为 NCR，你领导着一个殖民地，努力恢复文明并扩大其在荒原上的影响力。</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>NCR 玩家殖民地</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>州长</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>公民</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>公民</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.description>中华人民共和国建立在集体主义、和谐和技术进步的理想之上，是一个拥有繁华城市、丰富文化遗产和强烈社区意识的国家。然而，在表面之下，日益加强的审查制度、国家控制和军事扩张正在影响着日常生活。尽管国际冲突的幽灵日益逼近，但公民仍享受着快速的现代化、充满活力的传统和民族自豪感。</FCP_Faction_PRC.description>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.fixedName>中华人民共和国</FCP_Faction_PRC.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.ideoDescription>龙年意识形态重视民族团结、集体努力和技术进步。它鼓励对国家的忠诚、对传统的尊重以及对文化遗产的自豪感。广大人民群众要齐心协力，为国家谋福利，维护社会和谐，勇于创新，相信团结一致就能繁荣富强。</FCP_Faction_PRC.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.label>中华人民共和国</FCP_Faction_PRC.label>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.leaderTitle>最高领袖</FCP_Faction_PRC.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnSingular>中国人</FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnsPlural>中国人</FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.royalFavorLabel>社会信用</FCP_Faction_PRC.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.description>The Raider Gangs are a loose confederation of bandit groups operating in the wasteland. They are known for their brutal tactics, scavenging, and raiding of settlements. While they often fight among themselves, they can unite against common foes. The Raiders reject the 老旧 world values and instead embrace a survival-of-the-fittest mentality. They are feared and despised by many, but also h老旧 a certain allure for those seeking freedom from the constraints of civilization.</FCP_Faction_Raider.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.fixedName>掠夺者帮派</FCP_Faction_Raider.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.ideoDescription>Founded on principles of survival and strength, the Raider Gangs believe in taking what they need by force. They reject the 老旧 world's values and embrace a brutal code of conduct where only the strong survive.</FCP_Faction_Raider.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.label>掠夺者帮派</FCP_Faction_Raider.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.leaderTitle>掠夺者老大</FCP_Faction_Raider.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnSingular>袭击者</FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnsPlural>攻略</FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.royalFavorLabel>奖杯</FCP_Faction_Raider.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.description>美国建立在自由、繁荣和技术进步的理想之上，是一个拥有闪闪发光的城市、舒适的郊区和无限乐观的国家。然而，在表面之下，日益增长的偏执、企业影响力和军事升级改变了日常生活。尽管核战争的阴影日益逼近，公民仍享受着先进的便利、丰富多彩的流行文化和爱国自豪感。</FCP_Faction_USA.description>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.fixedName>美国</FCP_Faction_USA.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.ideoDescription>美国梦相信任何人，无论其背景如何，都可以通过努力工作和决心实现成功和繁荣。它体现了美国立国之本的自由、平等和机会的理想。</FCP_Faction_USA.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.label>美国</FCP_Faction_USA.label>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.leaderTitle>总统</FCP_Faction_USA.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.pawnSingular>美国人</FCP_Faction_USA.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.pawnsPlural>美国人</FCP_Faction_USA.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.royalFavorLabel>服务点</FCP_Faction_USA.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.description>S商场 communities of wastelanders who have banded together to survive in the harsh post-war world. These settlers live in ramshackle towns, trading scrap and salvaged goods while trying to maintain some semblance of civilization. They're cautious but not hostile, willing to trade with strangers but always wary of raiders and other threats. Most are just trying to scrape by, growing mutated crops, herding brahmin, and defending what little they have.</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.fixedName>Wasteland Settlements</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.label>Wasteland Settlers</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.leaderTitle>Mayor</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnSingular>settler</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnsPlural>settlers</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.fixedName>Wasteland Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.label>Wastelander Techprint Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnSingular>Wasteland Trader</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnsPlural>Wasteland Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.fixedName>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.label>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnSingular>Wastelander</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnsPlural>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>
