<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Crashlanded.description>Your airship tore itself apart over the wasteland and three of you barely made it down alive. The wreck scattered supplies across the desert, and now you have one chance to turn an airship crash site into a home.</Crashlanded.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.summary>Three survivors, a crashed airship, and one shot at settling the wasteland.</Crashlanded.scenario.summary>
  <LostTribe.description>Your tribe was burned out by steel war machines and only five of you escaped with what you could carry. Now you must keep the old ways alive long enough to raise a new home from dust, bone, and scrap.

Note: You begin poor, hungry, and far behind the technology of the wastes. This is a difficult scenario.</LostTribe.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.summary>Five survivors from a ruined tribe try to rebuild with little more than tradition and grit. Difficult.</LostTribe.scenario.summary>
  <NakedBrutality.description>Someone stripped you, robbed you, and dumped you naked in the wasteland to die. No gear, no food, no allies, not even a knife. If you live through this, it will be because you refused to become carrion.

Warning: This scenario is brutally unfair. Death can come fast and for stupid reasons.</NakedBrutality.description>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>One naked wastelander left for dead with absolutely nothing. Extremely difficult and unfair.</NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>
  <TheRichExplorer.description>You were born behind a vault door, surrounded by safety, soft beds, and old-world lies. Instead of staying buried, you took your best gear and went looking for the real wasteland. Now your pod has dropped you far from any friendly road, alone with vault supplies and no one coming to save you.

Note: Strong gear cannot cover every weakness. This is an especially difficult early game scenario.</TheRichExplorer.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>One well-equipped vault dweller chasing the real wasteland instead of stories. Extra difficult.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>
  <TheGravship.description>Your Helixen, a pre-War REPCONN aircraft, sits docked at the orbital relay. As your crew begins salvaging its systems, you realize this is no ordinary pre-War cache - it is a robot beacon. The relay crackles to life and broadcasts a war alert to a distant robot command hub. They are hunting you now, and they will eventually find you wherever you go.

Note: This is a difficult scenario and is not recommended for new players.</TheGravship.description>
  <TheGravship.label>the helixen</TheGravship.label>
  <TheGravship.scenario.summary>A crew of three hunted by robots aboard the Helixen.</TheGravship.scenario.summary>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>This start has been disabled by Sunset.</VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>disabled new kingdom</VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>
  <VFES_Bandits.description>This Settlers scenario has been disabled by Sunset.</VFES_Bandits.description>
  <VFES_Bandits.label>disabled bandits</VFES_Bandits.label>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.description>A wandering band of super mutants has broken from the chaos of the wasteland, bringing with them a cache of refined FEV doses, and just enough salvaged knowledge to attempt recreating the transformation process.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.label>forced evolution</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.label>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.summary>One first-generation super mutant, two second-generation super mutants, and some FEV.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.summary>
  <Sanguophage.description>The old stories called creatures like you Wendigos: starving things that outlived the people they once were. However it happened, you carry that curse now. Hunted, half-feral, and never truly full, you fled into the wastes before the wrong people could pin you down.

Note: Wendigos have unique strengths and brutal weaknesses, making this a difficult scenario.</Sanguophage.description>
  <Sanguophage.label>the wendigo</Sanguophage.label>
  <Sanguophage.scenario.summary>One hunted Wendigo, one human companion, and a hunger that never sleeps.</Sanguophage.scenario.summary>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.description>Your Brotherhood expeditionary group has stumbled upon an old bunker, a potential haven. But with the valuable intel you carry, the Whitespring Enclave's visibility on you is alarmingly high. Vertibots patrol the skies, and Whitespring raiding parties are closing in. Use the intel to unlock powerful tech and Brotherhood expeditionary services, aiding your ultimate mission: to assassinate key Whitespring officials. Survive the initial onslaught and lay low; over time, the Whitespring Enclave's relentless search will wane. The choice is yours: fortify, adapt, or perish.\n\nNote: Since you start with high visibility, this is a difficult scenario.</VFED_NewSafehaven.description>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.label>Brotherhood of Steel expedition</VFED_NewSafehaven.label>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.description>It was supposed to be another quiet night for your Whitespring splinter cell, tucked away in a secluded estate far from the main administrative halls. You do not know whether the blackout was caused by Brotherhood sabotage, a compromised security officer, or a simple systems failure, but when the perimeter defenses died at midnight your Enclave cell was left blind and exposed. By the time the gates opened, there was no time to organize a proper response - only to hide and survive.
You heard your officers, researchers, and support staff being cut down as the Brotherhood expeditionary strike team swept through the compound. Whatever remained of your old command structure died with them. Now your splinter cell is shattered, your safehouse is burning, and revenge will mean nothing unless you escape this raid alive. You can wait the assault out, use permits to call for reinforcements, or try running for the hills - the choice is yours.
Note: Since you start during a raid in progress, this is a difficult scenario.</VFEE_NewFamily.description>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.label>new splinter cell</VFEE_NewFamily.label>
</LanguageData>
