<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <!--Slanter-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>Donaustahl_Mutant_Slanter</defName>
    <label>Gentile Slanter Tribe</label>
    <description>The Slanter Tribe traces its roots to survivors who turned back to the old ways when the world fell apart. They live close to the land, guided by oral tradition, ancestor worship, and a deep respect for the cycles of nature. Though primitive by modern standards, they are skilled hunters, gatherers, and healers who blend salvaged pre-war tools with tribal craftsmanship. They defend their territory fiercely but trade fairly with outsiders — if they prove worthy of trust.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter MayRequire="Feil.WestTek">1</WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Numen-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>Donaustahl_Mutant_Numen</defName>
    <label>Gentile Numen Tribe</label>
    <description>The Numen Tribe traces its roots to survivors who turned back to the old ways when the world fell apart. They live close to the land, guided by oral tradition, ancestor worship, and a deep respect for the cycles of nature. Though primitive by modern standards, they are skilled hunters, gatherers, and healers who blend salvaged pre-war tools with tribal craftsmanship. They defend their territory fiercely but trade fairly with outsiders — if they prove worthy of trust.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Numen MayRequire="Feil.WestTek">1</WestTek_Xenotype_Numen>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Critter-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>Donaustahl_Mutant_Critter</defName>
    <label>Gentile Mutant Tribe</label>
    <description>The Mutant Tribe traces its roots to survivors who turned back to the old ways when the world fell apart. They live close to the land, guided by oral tradition, ancestor worship, and a deep respect for the cycles of nature. Though primitive by modern standards, they are skilled hunters, gatherers, and healers who blend salvaged pre-war tools with tribal craftsmanship. They defend their territory fiercely but trade fairly with outsiders — if they prove worthy of trust.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Numen MayRequire="Feil.WestTek">0.5</WestTek_Xenotype_Numen>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter MayRequire="Feil.WestTek">0.5</WestTek_Xenotype_SLanter>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
  </FactionDef>

</Defs>