<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <!--Civil-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="Donaustahl_Settler_Democratic">
    <defName>Donaustahl_NuevoTexico_Civil</defName>
    <label>Civil Nuevo Texico Settlement</label>
    <description>The Civil Nuevo Texico Settlement is a faction of survivors and settlers who have banded
      together to rebuild society in the aftermath of a devastating conflict. They are known for
      their resourcefulness, resilience, and commitment to community values. The CCS emphasizes
      cooperation and mutual aid among its members, striving to create a safe and prosperous
      environment despite the challenges they face in the post-apocalyptic world.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.8</WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.2</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
      <points>
        <li>(17.9,  0.00001)</li>
        <li>(18,    1)</li>
        <li>(24,    1)</li>
      </points>
    </minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Rough-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="Donaustahl_Settler_Despotic">
    <defName>Donaustahl_NuevoTexico_Rough</defName>
    <label>Rough Nuevo Texico Settlement</label>
    <description>The Rough Nuevo Texico Settlement is a loose collection of survivors hardened by the
      wasteland’s brutality. They value grit over grace, and survival over civility. Life here is
      harsh — trade is bartered through intimidation, disputes are settled with fists or gunfire,
      and law depends on who’s standing last. Despite their rough edges, they’ve carved out a
      functioning, if volatile, society where toughness earns respect and weakness finds no quarter.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.8</WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.2</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
      <points>
        <li>(17.9,  0.00001)</li>
        <li>(18,    1)</li>
        <li>(24,    1)</li>
      </points>
    </minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Raider-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="Donaustahl_Raider">
    <defName>Donaustahl_NuevoTexico_Raider</defName>
    <label>Texico Raider</label>
    <description>The Nuevo Texico Raider Gang thrives on chaos and plunder. Forged in the ashes of
      civilization, they scavenge, raid, and rule through fear. Their members are scarred, loud, and
      proud of their savagery, painting their armor with the symbols of past kills. They move in
      convoys of patched-together vehicles, hitting trade routes and settlements for supplies,
      slaves, or sport. To them, the wasteland isn’t a tragedy — it’s freedom without rules.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.8</WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.2</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
      <points>
        <li>(17.9,  0.00001)</li>
        <li>(18,    1)</li>
        <li>(24,    1)</li>
      </points>
    </minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
  </FactionDef>

  <!--Tribal-->
  <FactionDef ParentName="FalloutTribalClan">
    <defName>Donaustahl_NuevoTexico_Tribal</defName>
    <label>Texico Tribe</label>
    <description>The Nuevo Texico Tribe traces its roots to survivors who turned back to the old ways when
      the world fell apart. They live close to the land, guided by oral tradition, ancestor worship,
      and a deep respect for the cycles of nature. Though primitive by modern standards, they are
      skilled hunters, gatherers, and healers who blend salvaged pre-war tools with tribal
      craftsmanship. They defend their territory fiercely but trade fairly with outsiders — if they
      prove worthy of trust.</description>
    <xenotypeSet>
      <xenotypeChances>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.8</WestTek_Xenotype_NuevoTexico>
        <WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul MayRequire="FIP.WestTek">0.2</WestTek_Xenotype_Ghoul>
      </xenotypeChances>
    </xenotypeSet>
    <minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
      <points>
        <li>(17.9,  0.00001)</li>
        <li>(18,    1)</li>
        <li>(24,    1)</li>
      </points>
    </minSettlementTemperatureChanceCurve>
  </FactionDef>

</Defs>