<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.description>A soft beret worn by Brotherhood detachments in Appalachia. Embroidered with the Brotherhood crest, it is used for identification and ceremonial duties by officers and specialized units.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.label>BoS Appalachia Beret</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Beret.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.description>Standard-issue Brotherhood of Steel fatigues. Made from a robust and durable material, these fatigues are worn by members of the Brotherhood during their daily operations in Appalachia.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.label>BoS Appalachia Fatigues</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Fatigues.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.description>Standard-issue hood used by Brotherhood infantry for concealment and basic protection from the elements during patrols and tactical operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.label>BoS Appalachia Infantry Hood</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.description>A pristine military dress uniform worn by Brotherhood infantry during formal occasions. The uniform bears the insignia of the Brotherhood of Steel and represents the discipline and order of the organization.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.label>BoS Appalachia Infantry Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_Infantry_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>Advanced T-60 power armor bearing the distinctive colors and insignia of the Appalachian Brotherhood of Steel. This battle-tested armor provides exceptional protection while maintaining mobility, representing the pinnacle of pre-war American military engineering adapted for wasteland operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS Appalachia T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>Advanced T-60 power armor helmet featuring integrated HUD systems and environmental sensors. The distinctive Appalachian Brotherhood insignia marks this as belonging to the faction that emerged from Vault 76 to reclaim the wasteland and preserve humanity's technological heritage.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>BoS Appalachia T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Appalachia_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.description>A vacuum-sealed asbestos jumpsuit covering the entire body. Its purpose is twofold: it allows the user to actually operate the armor and protect soft tissue from moving parts inside the suit and heat. Unlike the BOS uniform, the Recon Armor provides decent protection on its own and is often used by Brotherhood agents on scouting missions or other situations where the clunky and loud power armor would draw too much attention.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.label>BoS B35C Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.description>A reinforced combat helmet issued to Brotherhood ground troops. Built to resist shrapnel and small-arms fire, commonly paired with infantry armor on patrols and engagements.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.label>BoS B35C Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_B35C_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.description>A sturdy military coat worn by Brotherhood officers. The coat features the Brotherhood's insignia and is designed to withstand the rigors of combat while maintaining a professional appearance.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.label>BoS Battle Coat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Battle_Coat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.description>A leather flight jacket worn by Brotherhood pilots and Vertibird crew members. The jacket features the Brotherhood's gear and sword emblem and provides protection during flight operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.label>BoS Bomber Jacket</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Bomber_Jacket.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.description>Standard-issue field uniform of the Brotherhood of Steel. These durable fatigues are worn by enlisted personnel and junior officers during daily operations and provide basic protection against environmental hazards.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.label>BoS Brotherhood Fatigues</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Fatigues.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.description>Specialized medical uniform worn by Brotherhood field medics. The fatigues feature additional pockets for medical supplies and are designed to resist contamination during treatment of wounded personnel.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.label>BoS Brotherhood Field Medic Fatigues</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Brotherhood_Field_Medic_Fatigues.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.description>Enhanced combat armor upgraded with Brotherhood of Steel technology. This armor retains the design of the original while incorporating improved protection and environmental sealing systems.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.label>BoS Reinforced Combat Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Classic_Combat_Armor_Reinforced.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.description>Ceremonial robes worn by Brotherhood Elders. These robes symbolize the authority and responsibility that comes with leading the Brotherhood of Steel in their sacred mission to preserve technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.label>BoS Elder Robes</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Elder_Robes.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.description>Field uniform worn by Brotherhood Scribes assigned to research missions outside the safety of Brotherhood facilities. The uniform combines scholarly tradition with practical field requirements.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.label>BoS Field Scribe Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.description>Field hat worn by Brotherhood scribes and researchers on expeditions. It offers sun and light-weather protection while marking the wearer as part of the research and recovery cadre.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.label>BoS Science Field Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Field_Scribe_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.description>Pilot helmet used by Brotherhood aircrews and vertibird crews, fitted with padding and basic communications gear to protect crew during flight and rotor operations.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.label>BoS Flight Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Flight_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.description>A jumpsuit designed from the ground up for use in conjunction with the West Tek power armor frame. It is a form-fitting suit designed for maximum comfort and utility while operating the armor. Although it is not a requirement for operating the armor, it makes long-term use more comfortable and reduces chafing.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.label>BoS Jumpsuit</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Jumpsuit.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.description>A peaked cap worn by officers of lancer units to denote rank and authority within the Brotherhood during inspections and official duties.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.label>BoS Lancer's Captain Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.description>A formal dress uniform worn by Lancer Captains of the Brotherhood of Steel. The uniform features gold braiding and ceremonial shoulder boards, marking the wearer as an officer of the Brotherhood's air fleet.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.label>BoS Lancer Captain Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lancer_Captain_Uniform.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor in the classic colors of the original Brotherhood chapter from Lost Hills. This armor represents the foundation of Brotherhood traditions and the original mission to preserve and control pre-war technology for the betterment of humanity.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lost Hills T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Lost_Hills_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>The distinctive power armor of the Midwestern Brotherhood of Steel, featuring a unique horned helmet design that has become their signature on the battlefield. This armor represents the Midwest chapter's adaptive nature - maintaining Brotherhood standards while developing their own identity separate from Lost Hills. The intimidating silhouette strikes fear into raiders and mutants alike across the wastes of the former American Midwest.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>Midwestern Brotherhood Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>The iconic horned helmet of the Midwestern Brotherhood of Steel. This distinctive headgear has become synonymous with the Midwest chapter's pragmatic but formidable approach to wasteland warfare. The intimidating horned design serves both as a symbol of their independence from Lost Hills and as a psychological weapon against their enemies.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>Midwestern Brotherhood Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Midwestern_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.description>Specialized reconnaissance armor worn by Brotherhood Outcast scouts and advance teams. This armor has been modified with enhanced mobility systems and stealth enhancements, featuring the distinctive Outcast markings and tactical modifications that reflect their more aggressive operational doctrine.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.label>BoS Outcast Recon Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.description>A tactical hood worn by Brotherhood Outcast reconnaissance specialists. This hood features enhanced optics integration, communication equipment, and environmental protection systems modified to Outcast specifications for extended field operations behind enemy lines.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.label>BoS Outcast Recon Hood</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Recon_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.description>Functional robes worn by Brotherhood Outcast specialists and technical personnel. These robes feature the distinctive Outcast coloring and insignia, modified for field operations where scholars and engineers work alongside warriors in the pursuit of technological supremacy.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.label>BoS Outcast Scribe Robes</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Outcast_Scribe_Robes.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.description>Lightweight tactical armor used by Brotherhood reconnaissance units. The Recon Armor provides solid protection while maintaining mobility and stealth capabilities, making it ideal for scouting missions and situations where full power armor would be impractical. Features advanced composite materials and integrated sensor systems.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.label>BoS Recon Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.description>Lightweight hood favored by recon teams. Woven for low visibility and reduced glare to aid scouting, observation, and stealthy movement.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.label>BoS Recon Hood</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Recon_Hood.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.description>Laboratory attire worn by Science Scribes of the Brotherhood of Steel. The clean, white coat is designed for work with dangerous pre-war technology and experimental equipment.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.label>BoS Science Scribe Outfit</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.description>Cap worn by science scribes to identify members of the Brotherhood's research corps. Scribes focus on study, salvage, and the preservation of prewar technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.label>BoS Science Scribe Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Science_Scribe_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.description>Hooded robes worn by Brotherhood Scribes during formal ceremonies. These robes represent the scholarly traditions of the Scribe order and their dedication to preserving technological knowledge.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.label>BoS Scribe Robes</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Scribe_Robes.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.description>Training uniform worn by Brotherhood Squires. This practical outfit is designed for combat training and education while marking the wearer's junior status within the Brotherhood hierarchy.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.label>BoS Squire Uniform</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.description>A simple cap issued to squires and trainees. Squires are apprentices attached to knights and paladins, learning fieldcraft and Brotherhood traditions.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.label>BoS Squire Hat</FCP_Apparel_BoS_Squire_Hat.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>T-45 power armor bearing the distinctive markings of Elder Lyons' progressive Brotherhood. This armor represents a departure from traditional Brotherhood doctrine, used by soldiers who prioritized protecting the innocent over hoarding technology, marking a controversial but heroic chapter in Brotherhood history.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>BoS Lyons T-45 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>T-45 power armor helmet worn by soldiers loyal to Elder Lyons' humanitarian mission. This helmet symbolizes a Brotherhood more concerned with protecting the innocent than hoarding technology, representing hope and compassion in the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>BoS Lyons T-45 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Lyons_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>T-45 power armor worn by Brotherhood Outcasts, painted in their characteristic black and red colors. These hardline traditionalists broke away from Elder Lyons' compassionate policies, believing the Brotherhood should focus solely on acquiring technology rather than helping wastelanders.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>BoS Outcast T-45 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>T-45 power armor helmet painted in the black and red colors of the Brotherhood Outcasts. This helmet represents unwavering dedication to the traditional Brotherhood mission of technology acquisition above all else, worn by those who refused to compromise their principles.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>BoS Outcast T-45 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T45_Outcast_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>T-51 power armor customized for the harsh Appalachian environment. This variant features enhanced environmental sealing and radiation shielding, adapted for the unique challenges faced by the Brotherhood's Appalachian chapter in their mission to reclaim and protect technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>BoS Appalachia T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>T-51 power armor helmet modified for the unique challenges of Appalachian operations. Enhanced with improved radiation detection systems and environmental filtering, essential for surviving the irradiated mountains and forests of post-war Appalachia.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>BoS Appalachia T-51  Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Appalachia_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>The venerable T-51 power armor, a mainstay of Brotherhood forces. While older than the T-60 series, this armor has proven its reliability through decades of wasteland combat. Its tried-and-true design offers excellent protection and has been extensively field-tested by Brotherhood knights and paladins.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-51 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>Time-tested T-51 power armor helmet that has protected Brotherhood soldiers for generations. While lacking some of the advanced features of newer models, its proven reliability and rugged construction make it a trusted companion in the wasteland.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>BoS T-51 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T51_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>Standard issue T-60 power armor worn by Brotherhood of Steel soldiers. Built for maximum protection and battlefield durability, this armor represents the apex of pre-war power armor technology, enhanced with post-war modifications and field improvements developed by Brotherhood engineers.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>BoS T-60 Power Armor</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor.label>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>Standard issue T-60 power armor helmet worn by Brotherhood knights and paladins. Features advanced targeting systems, environmental protection, and the iconic red optical sensors that strike fear into the hearts of those who would misuse technology.</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.description>
  <FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>BoS T-60 Power Armor Helmet</FCP_Apparel_BoS_T60_Power_Armor_Helmet.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Vertibird.label>BoS lyons pride vertibird</FCP_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Vertibird.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_VertibirdIncoming.label>BoS lyons pride vertibird (incoming)</FCP_BoS_Lyons_VertibirdIncoming.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_VertibirdLeaving.label>BoS lyons pride vertibird (leaving)</FCP_BoS_Lyons_VertibirdLeaving.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_Vertibird.label>BoS outcast vertibird</FCP_BoS_Outcast_Vertibird.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_VertibirdIncoming.label>BoS outcast vertibird (incoming)</FCP_BoS_Outcast_VertibirdIncoming.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_VertibirdLeaving.label>BoS outcast vertibird (leaving)</FCP_BoS_Outcast_VertibirdLeaving.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Vertibird.label>BoS vertibird</FCP_BoS_Vertibird.label>
  <FCP_BoS_VertibirdIncoming.label>BoS vertibird (incoming)</FCP_BoS_VertibirdIncoming.label>
  <FCP_BoS_VertibirdLeaving.label>BoS vertibird (leaving)</FCP_BoS_VertibirdLeaving.label>
  <FCP_Currency_BoS_Scrip.description>An official paper currency issued by the Brotherhood of Steel. These notes are backed by the Brotherhood's vast technological resources and can be exchanged for advanced equipment, supplies, and services within Brotherhood controlled territories. More valuable than standard bottle caps due to the organization's strict resource management and reputation for honoring debts.</FCP_Currency_BoS_Scrip.description>
  <FCP_Currency_BoS_Scrip.label>Brotherhood Scrip</FCP_Currency_BoS_Scrip.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.description>A precision-engineered 10mm pistol manufactured by the Brotherhood of Steel. The Crusader represents the Brotherhood's philosophy of combining proven ballistic technology with modern manufacturing techniques. Featuring a reinforced frame, enhanced rifling, and superior materials, this sidearm offers exceptional reliability and accuracy compared to standard wasteland pistols. Brotherhood knights and paladins carry these as secondary weapons, trusting in their consistent performance when every shot counts.</FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.description>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.label>BoS 10mm Crusader Pistol</FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.tools.0.label>grip</FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_BoS_Crusader_Pistol.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.description>A refined plasma rifle developed and manufactured by the Brotherhood of Steel's West Coast chapters. The M-94 represents decades of Brotherhood weapons research, featuring improved magnetic confinement, enhanced cooling systems, and superior durability compared to standard plasma rifles. Each weapon is carefully crafted by Brotherhood scribes and tested to rigorous military standards. The Brotherhood's trademark attention to detail and technological excellence make this one of the most reliable plasma weapons in the wasteland.</FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.label>BoS M-94 Plasma Rifle</FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_BoS_M94_Plasma_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.description>A cutting-edge energy weapon developed by the Brotherhood of Steel using ultracite, a rare crystalline material with exceptional energy-conducting properties. This experimental rifle fires rapid bursts of ultracite-charged plasma that penetrates armor more effectively than standard plasma weapons while maintaining a higher rate of fire. The weapon's advanced cooling system and compact design make it a favorite among Brotherhood field operatives who need to engage heavily armored targets quickly. Each rifle is painstakingly assembled in Brotherhood workshops from carefully refined ultracite cores.</FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.description>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.label>BoS Ultracite Rifle</FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.tools.0.label>stock</FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.tools.1.label>barrel</FCP_Gun_BoS_Ultracite_Rifle.tools.1.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.description>A Brotherhood of Steel ration crate containing preserved military meals, purified water, and nutritional supplements. Designed to sustain soldiers during extended operations in the harsh wasteland environment.</FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.label>Brotherhood Food Supply Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Food_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.description>A specialized Brotherhood of Steel uniform crate containing the distinctive gear worn by Elder Lyons' reformed Brotherhood. These uniforms represent the faction's humanitarian mission and their commitment to protecting the innocent.</FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.label>Lyons Pride Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.description>A Brotherhood Outcast supply crate containing the distinctive red and black uniforms worn by the purist faction. These uniforms symbolize their unwavering dedication to the original Codex and their mission to reclaim pre-war technology at any cost.</FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.label>Outcast Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Outcast_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.description>A sealed Brotherhood of Steel supply crate containing essential technological components, spare parts, and advanced materials. These resources are crucial for maintaining and upgrading their sophisticated equipment and installations.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.label>Brotherhood Tech Resource Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Tech_Resource_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>A Brotherhood of Steel supply crate containing standard-issue uniforms, fatigues, and protective gear worn by regular Brotherhood personnel. Each piece bears the distinctive colors and insignia of the faction.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>Brotherhood Standard Uniform Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Uniform_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>A sealed Brotherhood of Steel weapon crate containing high-quality firearms and energy weapons used by their forces. The distinctive red and metallic finish bears the Brotherhood's emblematic cogwheel.</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.description>
  <FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>Brotherhood of Steel Weapon Crate</FCP_Item_BoS_Standard_Weapon_Crate.label>
  <FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.description>A Brotherhood of Steel manufactured super sledgehammer, built to their exacting specifications. This legendary weapon combines a reinforced durasteel head with advanced kinetic energy storage technology. Upon impact, the stored energy releases in a devastating shockwave, multiplying the force of each blow. Brotherhood paladins favor this weapon for breaching fortifications and engaging heavily armored targets in close combat. The BoS insignia stamped on the handle marks this as official Brotherhood equipment, built to last through countless battles.</FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.description>
  <FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.label>BoS Super Sledge</FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.label>
  <FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.tools.0.label>handle</FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.tools.0.label>
  <FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.tools.1.label>kinetic head</FCP_Melee_BoS_Super_Sledge.tools.1.label>
</LanguageData>