<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFES_Bandits.description>After the last job, which was meant to be the last, you and other members of your gang were forced to run without looking back. The only thing you have with you, are the things you managed to steal, extort or find along the way. Your savage ways have granted you a bad reputation, and mending relations with other factions will take a long time.\n\nNote: Since you start without any supplies and with every other faction hostile, this is a difficult scenario.</VFES_Bandits.description>
  <VFES_Bandits.label>bandits</VFES_Bandits.label>
  <VFES_Bandits.scenario.description>After the last job, which was meant to be the last, you and other members of your gang were forced to run without looking back. The only thing you have with you, are the things you managed to steal, extort or find along the way. Your savage ways have granted you a bad reputation, and mending relations with other factions will take a long time.

Note: Since you start with high wealth every other faction hostile, this is a very difficult scenario.</VFES_Bandits.scenario.description>
  <VFES_Bandits.scenario.name>Bandits</VFES_Bandits.scenario.name>
  <VFES_Bandits.scenario.parts.3.text>After the last job, which was meant to be the last, you and other members of your gang were forced to run without looking back. The only thing you have with you, are the things you managed to steal, extort or find along the way. Your savage ways have granted you a bad reputation, and mending relations with other factions will take a long time.</VFES_Bandits.scenario.parts.3.text>
  <VFES_Bandits.scenario.summary>A group of bandits trying to make a name for themselves. Very Difficult.</VFES_Bandits.scenario.summary>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.description>It was a long and quiet night when your entire life turned on its head. You are not sure if it was a deliberate sabotage by one of the family servants, a simple system malfunction or a well executed deserter strategy, but the mansion defense systems turned off as the clock struck midnight. When the gates swung wide, there was no time to call for aid - best you could do was hide.
You heard the screams of your family and mansion workers as they were being slaughtered by the deserter strike team. You vowed to have your revenge, but until you make it out of this particular situation alive, your vows are all for nothing. You can either wait the raid out, use permits to call for reinforcements, or try running for the hills - the choice is yours. 
Note: Since you start during a raid in progress, this is a difficult scenario.</VFEE_NewFamily.description>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.label>new family</VFEE_NewFamily.label>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.scenario.parts.14.text>It was a long and quiet night when your entire life turned on its head. You are not sure if it was a deliberate sabotage by one of the family servants, a simple system malfunction or a well executed deserter strategy, but the mansion defense systems turned off as the clock struck midnight. When the gates swung wide, there was no time to call for aid - best you could do was hide.
You heard the screams of your family and mansion workers as they were being slaughtered by the deserter strike team. You vowed to have your revenge, but until you make it out of this particular situation alive, your vows are all for nothing. You can either wait the raid out, use permits to call for reinforcements, or try running for the hills - the choice is yours.</VFEE_NewFamily.scenario.parts.14.text>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.scenario.summary>An imperial family in dire need of help. A classic VFE - Empire experience.</VFEE_NewFamily.scenario.summary>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.description>Your deserter group has stumbled upon an old bunker, a potential haven. But with the valuable intel you carry, the Empire's visibility on you is alarmingly high. Aerodrones patrol the skies, and Imperial raiding parties are closing in. Use the intel to unlock powerful tech and deserter services, aiding your ultimate mission: to assassinate key Imperial nobility. Survive the initial onslaught and lay low; over time, the Empire's relentless search will wane. The choice is yours: fortify, adapt, or perish.\n\nNote: Since you start with high visibility, this is a difficult scenario.</VFED_NewSafehaven.description>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.label>new safehaven</VFED_NewSafehaven.label>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.scenario.parts.13.text>Your deserter group has stumbled upon an old bunker, a potential haven. But with the valuable intel you carry, the Empire's visibility on you is alarmingly high. Aerodrones patrol the skies, and Imperial raiding parties are closing in. Use the intel to unlock powerful tech and deserter services, aiding your ultimate mission: to assassinate key Imperial nobility. Survive the initial onslaught and lay low; over time, the Empire's relentless search will wane. The choice is yours: fortify, adapt, or perish.</VFED_NewSafehaven.scenario.parts.13.text>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.scenario.summary>A deserter cell, laying low. A classic VFE - Deserters experience.</VFED_NewSafehaven.scenario.summary>
  <VFET_WildMen.description>Your small group has discovered fire, a stepping stone towards forming a tribe. Fire offers warmth, safety, and a chance to develop further. Yet, dangers abound in the wild, unknown world around you. You will have to learn how to perform basic tasks - from hunting and sowing, to doctoring and research. Work your way towards forming a tribe that can stand the test of time.\n\nWarning: You start without the ability to do basic tasks, such as sowing, doctoring and hunting - it is extremely difficult and anything can end your run.</VFET_WildMen.description>
  <VFET_WildMen.label>wild men</VFET_WildMen.label>
  <VFET_WildMen.scenario.parts.6.text>The world was tough and scary. Surviving each day was hard. But a small group of wild people decided to face it together, rather than alone.

They spent their days looking for food and shelter, and their nights fighting off the cold and danger.

Now, they are starting to form a simple group, helping each other to face the tough world ahead. They are taking their first steps towards becoming a tribe, trying to make life a little less hard for each other.</VFET_WildMen.scenario.parts.6.text>
  <VFET_WildMen.scenario.summary>A group of wild people trying to form a tribe. A classic VFE - Tribal experience.</VFET_WildMen.scenario.summary>
  <AM_SafeHouse.description>You've wandered this rimworld, living off the spoils of ancient ruins. You traverse the desolate ruins of cities, devoid of any signs of life. On the outskirts of town, you discover an abandoned ancient underground shelter. Though its resources won't last long...\n\nNote: You have no operable colonists and lack essential survival resources. Scavengers start off starving, making this a challenging scenario.</AM_SafeHouse.description>
  <AM_SafeHouse.label>safe house</AM_SafeHouse.label>
  <AM_SafeHouse.scenario.parts.8.text>You have discovered an ancient, abandoned small underground facility that could potentially serve as a shelter.</AM_SafeHouse.scenario.parts.8.text>
  <AM_SafeHouse.scenario.summary>A lone scavenger discovers an old underground bunker. Particularly challenging.</AM_SafeHouse.scenario.summary>
  <AM_ScavengerGroup.description>In your earlier explorations, the regions nearer to the settlement were thoroughly examined. You've been left with no option but to venture into uncharted territories. On this day, you have discovered an entrance to an unknown underground facility. You have decided to settle here, but the strange odor and faint, incessant sounds seem to hint that this place is not as safe as you once imagined....</AM_ScavengerGroup.description>
  <AM_ScavengerGroup.label>scavenger group</AM_ScavengerGroup.label>
  <AM_ScavengerGroup.scenario.parts.8.text>You have discovered an ancient underground parking lot that could serve as your stronghold, but there seems to be a strange noise underground....</AM_ScavengerGroup.scenario.parts.8.text>
  <AM_ScavengerGroup.scenario.summary>A group of three scavengers wandering between the ruins of a city. Particularly challenging.</AM_ScavengerGroup.scenario.summary>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>Oppression breeds defiance. For years, your village toiled under the weight of crushing taxes and hunger while the lord’s knights took everything: grain, livestock, even your last scraps of dignity. When they seized your final stores of food, desperation turned to rage.

Armed with nothing but fury, you march upon the castle where the lord and his knights hide behind stone walls. You are weak, but sheer numbers and resolve may turn the tide. Should you triumph, the castle’s wealth and security could be yours.

But not all believe in victory. Some whisper of escape, of slipping away before the slaughter begins. Beyond the walls lies an uncertain world, one that promises danger but also the chance for a new life. Will you fight to take the castle, or flee and forge your own path?
Note: Since you start around an enemy castle, this is a difficult scenario.</VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>new kingdom</VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.scenario.parts.8.text>Oppression breeds defiance. For years, your village toiled under the weight of crushing taxes and hunger while the lord’s knights took everything: grain, livestock, even your last scraps of dignity. When they seized your final stores of food, desperation turned to rage.</VFEM2_NewKingdom.scenario.parts.8.text>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.scenario.summary>A group of peasants, rebelling against oppressing knights. A classic VFE - Medieval 2 experience.</VFEM2_NewKingdom.scenario.summary>
  <VQEA_CargoCult.description>It was a fortuitous find: The tribe's foragers were out gathering berries when they spotted a strange metal building half-sunken into the earth, its walls threaded with coiling tubes like the veins of some sleeping giant. Was it crafted by ancient hands, or shaped by the gods themselves? We soon learned it must be divine. Offerings placed within the "pneumatic nexus" vanished with a holy whoosh, only to return later as transformed gifts.\n\nNote: You'll start poor and lack technology, but having the pneumatic nexus means this start is easier than a standard tribal one.</VQEA_CargoCult.description>
  <VQEA_CargoCult.label>cargo cult</VQEA_CargoCult.label>
  <VQEA_CargoCult.scenario.parts.11.text>It was a fortuitous find: The tribe's foragers were out gathering berries when they spotted a strange metal building half-sunken into the earth, its walls threaded with coiling tubes like the veins of some sleeping giant. Was it crafted by ancient hands, or shaped by the gods themselves? We soon learned it must be divine. Offerings placed within the "pneumatic nexus" vanished with a holy whoosh, only to return later as transformed gifts.</VQEA_CargoCult.scenario.parts.11.text>
  <VQEA_CargoCult.scenario.summary>Five lost tribespeople stumble upon a pneumatic nexus and start revering it. Moderate-High difficulty.</VQEA_CargoCult.scenario.summary>
  <VQE_NewVault.description>A memory drifts into your fractured mind as you stumble into a rusted chamber. An experiment, a group of doctors wearing abstract masks, and a flash of golden yellow light enveloping your body. You feel something deeply unnatural pulsing in your chest, you have been modified somehow and have been sleeping for a very long time. Your legs shake as you remember what this place is, a near impenetrable fortress capable of keeping rescue out and captives in. The vault contains an underground section guarded by a sealed door. After so many years, your captives appear long gone. The cold realization thuds onto your chest, what unknown force may have placed you back here?</VQE_NewVault.description>
  <VQE_NewVault.label>sealed vault</VQE_NewVault.label>
  <VQE_NewVault.scenario.parts.9.text>A memory drifts into your fractured mind as you stumble into a rusted chamber. An experiment, a group of doctors wearing abstract masks, and a flash of golden yellow light enveloping your body. You feel something deeply unnatural pulsing in your chest, you have been modified somehow and have been sleeping for a very long time. Your legs shake as you remember what this place is, a near impenetrable fortress capable of keeping rescue out and captives in. The vault contains an underground section guarded by a sealed door. After so many years, your captives appear long gone. The cold realization thuds onto your chest, what unknown force may have placed you back here?</VQE_NewVault.scenario.parts.9.text>
  <VQE_NewVault.scenario.summary>A long forgotten supersoldier guarding their post. A classic VQE - Ancients experience.</VQE_NewVault.scenario.summary>
</LanguageData>
