<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VOE_AmbushedRaid.description>An ongoing ambush battle.</VOE_AmbushedRaid.description>
  <VOE_AmbushedRaid.label>ambush</VOE_AmbushedRaid.label>
  <VOE_TravellingArtilleryStrike.description>Artillery strike in flight.</VOE_TravellingArtilleryStrike.description>
  <VOE_TravellingArtilleryStrike.label>artillery strike</VOE_TravellingArtilleryStrike.label>
  <Outpost_Factory.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led factory that specializes in production and fabrication of goods using machines based on mechanoid technology. As with the machines normally, a wide variety of goods can be produced. Once an ample amount is produced, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Factory.description>
  <Outpost_Factory.label>factory outpost</Outpost_Factory.label>
  <Outpost_Fishing.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in the catching of fish from nearby coasts and rivers. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Fishing.description>
  <Outpost_Fishing.label>fishing outpost</Outpost_Fishing.label>
  <Outpost_Artillery.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in providing point defense to nearby settlements via artillery strikes. Each pawn will be tasked with the maintenance and usage of a mortar. After a barrage has been expended one day will be required to prepare a new one.</Outpost_Artillery.description>
  <Outpost_Artillery.label>artillery outpost</Outpost_Artillery.label>
  <Outpost_Defensive.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in intercepting and ambushing incoming enemy raids on the main colony. Winning a small skirmish at an outpost can significantly diminish the size of an enemy raid on the main colony. Furthermore, defensive outposts can be tasked to send drop pods to the main colony for short-notice defense.</Outpost_Defensive.description>
  <Outpost_Defensive.label>defensive outpost</Outpost_Defensive.label>
  <Outpost_Drilling.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in locating and tapping underground chemfuel reservoirs. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Drilling.description>
  <Outpost_Drilling.label>drilling outpost</Outpost_Drilling.label>
  <Outpost_Encampment.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that serves as a resting point for caravans. While camping all pawns will regain food and rest, and allow time for injuries to heal.</Outpost_Encampment.description>
  <Outpost_Encampment.label>encampment</Outpost_Encampment.label>
  <Outpost_Farming.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in sowing and harvesting easily-grown vegetation, cannot be placed on deserts. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Farming.description>
  <Outpost_Farming.label>farming outpost</Outpost_Farming.label>
  <Outpost_Hunting.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in hunting and butchering wildlife. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Hunting.description>
  <Outpost_Hunting.label>hunting outpost</Outpost_Hunting.label>
  <Outpost_Logging.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in collecting wood from trees in the areas, cannot be placed on deserts. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Logging.description>
  <Outpost_Logging.label>logging outpost</Outpost_Logging.label>
  <Outpost_Mining.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in collecting and processing stone or metal, can only be placed on hills or mountains. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Mining.description>
  <Outpost_Mining.label>mining outpost</Outpost_Mining.label>
  <Outpost_Production.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in manufacturing and fabrication of mechanical and electronic components. Once an ample amount is produced, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Production.description>
  <Outpost_Production.label>production outpost</Outpost_Production.label>
  <Outpost_Scavenging.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in scouting for nearby unmarked settlements and the loot contained within them. Once something notable is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Scavenging.description>
  <Outpost_Scavenging.label>scavenging outpost</Outpost_Scavenging.label>
  <Outpost_Science.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in research and analysis. Any information gained will be shared with the faction as a whole.</Outpost_Science.description>
  <Outpost_Science.label>science outpost</Outpost_Science.label>
  <Outpost_Town.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led town that is designed to provide hospitality to travelers and traders alike. Should a visitor find their lodging amicable they will be invited to join the town as a resident permanently. A town can only be erected if 3 pre-existing settlements are located within 10 hexes.</Outpost_Town.description>
  <Outpost_Town.label>town</Outpost_Town.label>
  <Outpost_Trading.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in selling and bartering with wanderers, caravans, and natives alike in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Trading.description>
  <Outpost_Trading.label>trading outpost</Outpost_Trading.label>
  <Outpost_Border_Post.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in patroling faction's border, searching for illegal trespassers and smugglers. Once the violator is caught, he is fined or imprisoned. After which a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Border_Post.description>
  <Outpost_Border_Post.label>border post</Outpost_Border_Post.label>
  <Outpost_Circus.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in organizing artistic and recreational events for wanderers, caravans and natives in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Circus.description>
  <Outpost_Circus.label>wandering circus</Outpost_Circus.label>
  <Outpost_Construction_Site.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in providing construction workers for temporary employment to other factions in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Construction_Site.description>
  <Outpost_Construction_Site.label>construction workers outpost</Outpost_Construction_Site.label>
  <Outpost_Embassy.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in negotiating with other factions. Once the negotiations are successful, goodwill of that faction will increase.</Outpost_Embassy.description>
  <Outpost_Embassy.label>embassy</Outpost_Embassy.label>
  <Outpost_Field_Hospital.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in producing medical supplies for colony. Alternatively can sell them and provide medical help to wanderers, caravans and natives in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Field_Hospital.description>
  <Outpost_Field_Hospital.label>field hospital</Outpost_Field_Hospital.label>
  <Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in providing mercenary services in exchange for silver. Once mission is over reward will be delivered at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.description>
  <Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.label>mercenary camp</Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.label>
  <Outpost_Prison.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in keeping prisoners and their rehabilitation. Get payment with silver for holding prisoners from other factions. Can force to work, recruit or enslave colony prisoners. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Prison.description>
  <Outpost_Prison.label>prison</Outpost_Prison.label>
  <Outpost_Ranch.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in livestock handling and gathering their products. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Ranch.description>
  <Outpost_Ranch.label>ranch</Outpost_Ranch.label>
  <Outpost_Restaurant.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in producing meals supplies for colony. Alternatively can sell meals to wanderers, caravans and natives in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Restaurant.description>
  <Outpost_Restaurant.label>restaurant</Outpost_Restaurant.label>
  <Outpost_Educational_Center.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in student education. Requires teachers of different specialties.</Outpost_Educational_Center.description>
  <Outpost_Educational_Center.label>educational center</Outpost_Educational_Center.label>
  <Outpost_Church.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in spreading ideology. Get donations with silver from visitors. Can convert people to faction's ideology. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Church.description>
  <Outpost_Church.label>church</Outpost_Church.label>
  <OutpostAO_Fishing.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in the catching of fish from nearby coasts and rivers. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</OutpostAO_Fishing.description>
  <OutpostAO_Fishing.label>fishing outpost</OutpostAO_Fishing.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with chemfuel powered generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.label>chemfuel powered generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with geothermal generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.label>geothermal generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with nuclear reactor. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.label>nuclear reactor power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with power cells. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.label>power cell grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with solar generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.label>solar generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with tidal generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.label>tidal generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with watermill generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.label>watermill generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with wind turbine. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.label>wind turbine power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with wood-fired generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.label>wood-fired generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.label>
  <AerialVehicle.description>An aerial vehicle capable of flight on the world map.</AerialVehicle.description>
  <AerialVehicle.label>aerial vehicle</AerialVehicle.label>
  <CrashedShipSite.description>A recently downed aerial vehicle with possible survivors.</CrashedShipSite.description>
  <CrashedShipSite.label>crash site</CrashedShipSite.label>
  <DebugSettlement.description>Debug</DebugSettlement.description>
  <DebugSettlement.label>original location</DebugSettlement.label>
  <StashedVehicle.description>Stashed vehicles.</StashedVehicle.description>
  <StashedVehicle.label>stashed vehicle</StashedVehicle.label>
  <VehicleCaravan.description>A group of traveling people with vehicles.</VehicleCaravan.description>
  <VehicleCaravan.label>vehicle caravan</VehicleCaravan.label>
  <FT_BaseInvasion.label>base invasion</FT_BaseInvasion.label>
  <FT_SettlementConstruction.label>settlement construction</FT_SettlementConstruction.label>
  <FT_VassalOutpost.label>vassal outpost</FT_VassalOutpost.label>
</LanguageData>
