<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEM2_CastleWall.description>An incredibly resistant impassable wall made out of oversized stone blocks. Very slow to build. Capable of halting a roof. If castle wall sustains enough damage, it becomes a chest-high passable cover that when repaired, turns into an impassable wall again.</VFEM2_CastleWall.description>
  <VFEM2_CastleWall.label>castle wall</VFEM2_CastleWall.label>
  <VFEM2_ClothWall.description>An impassable wall made out of thick overlapping strips of fabric or leather stitched together. Quick to build, but extremely flammable. When deconstructed, returns all of the cloth used.</VFEM2_ClothWall.description>
  <VFEM2_ClothWall.label>cloth wall</VFEM2_ClothWall.label>
  <VFEM2_DamagedCastleWall.description>An incredibly resistant impassable wall made out of oversized stone blocks. Very slow to build. Capable of halting a roof. If castle wall sustains enough damage, it becomes a chest-high passable cover that when repaired, turns into an impassable wall again.</VFEM2_DamagedCastleWall.description>
  <VFEM2_DamagedCastleWall.label>damaged castle wall</VFEM2_DamagedCastleWall.label>
  <VFEM2_DamagedLowCastleWall.description>An incredibly resistant chest-high wall made out of oversized stone blocks. Very slow to build. Incapable of halting a roof. If low castle wall sustains enough damage, it becomes a very low but  standable cover that when repaired, turns into the chest-high wall again.</VFEM2_DamagedLowCastleWall.description>
  <VFEM2_DamagedLowCastleWall.label>damaged low castle wall</VFEM2_DamagedLowCastleWall.label>
  <VFEM2_LowCastleWall.description>An incredibly resistant chest-high wall made out of oversized stone blocks. Very slow to build. Incapable of halting a roof. If low castle wall sustains enough damage, it becomes a very low but  standable cover that when repaired, turns into the chest-high wall again.</VFEM2_LowCastleWall.description>
  <VFEM2_LowCastleWall.label>low castle wall</VFEM2_LowCastleWall.label>
  <VFEM2_Palisade.description>An impassable fence made out of vertically-standing wooden stakes. Slow to build but requires little resources. Incapable of halting a roof.</VFEM2_Palisade.description>
  <VFEM2_Palisade.label>palisade</VFEM2_Palisade.label>
  <VFEM2_TimberedWall.description>An impassable wall made out of stone blocks and heavy, carefully fitted timbers forming a box frame. Slow to build but much more resistant to damage. Flammable, but less so than ordinary wooden walls. Capable of halting a roof.</VFEM2_TimberedWall.description>
  <VFEM2_TimberedWall.label>timbered wall</VFEM2_TimberedWall.label>
</LanguageData>
