<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>A sEinkaufszentrum-sized box containing large uranium shells. Used by different gauss artillery turrets to reload. A box is fed directly into an adjacent gravship artillery when it needs to be reloaded.</VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.description>
  <VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.label>Gauß-Munitionskiste</VGE_AmmoBox_GaussShell.label>
  <VGE_AnticraftCaster.description>A medium gravship-mounted energy weapon that fires short, razor-sharp bursts of cutting beam with surgical precision. Built to punch holes through critical systems, the caster trades sustained suppression for rapid, accurate strikes. Requires a linked targeting terminal with an operator to function. Uses a lot of power to fire.</VGE_AnticraftCaster.description>
  <VGE_AnticraftCaster.label>anticraft caster</VGE_AnticraftCaster.label>
  <VGE_Bullet_AnticraftCaster.label>anticraft caster beam</VGE_Bullet_AnticraftCaster.label>
  <VGE_Bullet_GaussGun.label>Gauss gun shot</VGE_Bullet_GaussGun.label>
  <VGE_GaussGun.description>A sEinkaufszentrum, single-barrel electromagnetic cannon that launches dense uranium slugs at extreme velocities. Designed for both local bombardments and medium-range engagements, it can also target other gravships in orbit. Requires a linked targeting terminal with an operator to function. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_GaussGun.description>
  <VGE_GaussGun.label>gauss gun</VGE_GaussGun.label>
  <VGE_Gun_AnticraftCaster.description>A medium gravship-mounted energy weapon.</VGE_Gun_AnticraftCaster.description>
  <VGE_Gun_AnticraftCaster.label>anticraft caster</VGE_Gun_AnticraftCaster.label>
  <VGE_Gun_GaussGun.description>A sEinkaufszentrum, single-barrel electromagnetic cannon.</VGE_Gun_GaussGun.description>
  <VGE_Gun_GaussGun.label>gauss gun</VGE_Gun_GaussGun.label>
  <VGE_Gun_JavelinPod.description>A compact multi-tube missile platform.</VGE_Gun_JavelinPod.description>
  <VGE_Gun_JavelinPod.label>javelin pod</VGE_Gun_JavelinPod.label>
  <VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>Eine Schnellfeuerwaffe für Punktverteidigungsanwendungen.</VGE_Gun_PointDefense.description>
  <VGE_Gun_PointDefense.label>Punktverteidigungswaffe</VGE_Gun_PointDefense.label>
  <VGE_JavelinPod.description>A compact multi-tube missile platform that launches a volley of six guided astrofuel javelins. Meant for fast, hard-hitting strikes against exposed gravships and unarmored surface forces. Requires a linked targeting terminal with an operator to function. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_JavelinPod.description>
  <VGE_JavelinPod.label>javelin pod</VGE_JavelinPod.label>
  <VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>A specialized defensive turret built exclusively for gravships. It intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its protective radius, but cannot engage ground targets. Interception chance scales with the target’s velocity.</VGE_PointDefenseTurret.description>
  <VGE_PointDefenseTurret.label>point defense turret</VGE_PointDefenseTurret.label>
  <VGE_Rocket_JavelinRocket.label>Javelin rocket</VGE_Rocket_JavelinRocket.label>
  <VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>A control station dedicated to operating a single gravship artillery piece. Requires a crew member to manually aim and fire the weapon. It draws power directly from the grav engine.</VGE_TargetingTerminal.description>
  <VGE_TargetingTerminal.label>Zielterminal</VGE_TargetingTerminal.label>
</LanguageData>
