<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AtmosphericHeater.description>A Poseidon home reactor powered by scavenged dark archotechnology. It burns bioferrite to agitate atmospheric gases, raising the outdoor temperature while flooding the area with waste heat.</AtmosphericHeater.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.label>Poseidon home reactor</AtmosphericHeater.label>
  <Battery.description>A Poseidon reserve battery for holding excess electricity. Charged units remain dangerous when exposed to rain or fire, regardless of what the brochure claims.</Battery.description>
  <BioferriteGenerator.description>An experimental generator that works by pressurizing and igniting bioferrite, then harvesting energy from the resulting heat. The fuel remains bioferrite, but the chassis and control layout read like a harsh Poseidon prototype.</BioferriteGenerator.description>
  <BioferriteShaper.description>A specialized shaping bench that uses heat and electromagnetic stimulation to temporarily coax bioferrite into a pliable state. The material remains bioferrite, but the surrounding hardware fits cleanly into a Fallout-style industrial workshop.</BioferriteShaper.description>
  <BiofuelRefinery.description>A Poseidon refinery that converts biological matter into oil for generators, burners, and industrial storage systems.</BiofuelRefinery.description>
  <BiofuelRefinery.label>oil refinery</BiofuelRefinery.label>
  <Chemfuel.description>A refined liquid fuel suitable for generators, burners, and industrial feed systems. In a saner age Poseidon would have sold it through a smiling subsidiary with a patriotic slogan.</Chemfuel.description>
  <Chemfuel.label>oil</Chemfuel.label>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>Produces power by consuming oil. It must be periodically refueled by hand unless your settlement has the industrial habits of an actual Poseidon facility.</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.description>
  <ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>oil generator</ChemfuelPoweredGenerator.label>
  <CommsConsole.description>A Wattz communications console for contacting other factions and orbital traders. Big, expensive, and full of humming pre-War electronics.</CommsConsole.description>
  <Cooler.description>An Appalachia Freeze cooling unit that pushes cold air to one side and hot exhaust to the other. It can preserve food or simply make summer tolerable if the rest of the grid holds.</Cooler.description>
  <DeepDrill.description>A Corvega deep-crust drilling rig for extracting minerals from far below the surface. Use a ground-penetrating scanner to detect the best seams.</DeepDrill.description>
  <DrugLab.description>A powered industrial chem lab with containers, heaters, and measurement devices for efficient batch processing of drugs and compounds.</DrugLab.description>
  <ElectricCrematorium.description>A heavy industrial crematorium that vaporizes corpses at extreme temperatures. It is efficient, impersonal, and unmistakably pre-War in temperament.</ElectricCrematorium.description>
  <ElectricSmelter.description>A Corvega reclamation smelter that extracts usable metal from slag and mixed scrap. It consumes a lot of power and throws off serious industrial heat.</ElectricSmelter.description>
  <ElectricSmelter.label>Corvega reclamation smelter</ElectricSmelter.label>
  <FabricationBench.description>A Corvega fabrication bench equipped with advanced tools for producing sophisticated machines and components from simpler materials.</FabricationBench.description>
  <Facility_IVDrip.description>A Med-Tek intravenous drip stand for rapidly delivering lost fluids to a patient, helping immunity gain and blood loss recovery when placed directly adjacent to a hospital bed or surgical table. Only works for hospital beds or surgical tables; normal beds will not benefit. Attaching more than one stand to the same bed has no effect.</Facility_IVDrip.description>
  <Facility_IVDrip.label>Med-Tek IV stand</Facility_IVDrip.label>
  <Facility_VitalsCentre.description>A large Med-Tek centre for monitoring the vitals of several patients at once, improving tend quality, surgery success, and immunity gain when linked to hospital beds or surgical suites.</Facility_VitalsCentre.description>
  <Facility_VitalsCentre.label>Med-Tek vitals centre</Facility_VitalsCentre.label>
  <FirefoamPopper.description>A Wattz safety device that sprays fire-retardant foam when it detects a blaze. Exactly the kind of sensible utility hardware that survives long after the corporation that sold it is gone.</FirefoamPopper.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>A Radiation King flatscreen television with crystal-clear image and rich color. Trust the king for all your TV and radio needs.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <GeothermalGenerator.description>A Poseidon geothermal plant that taps deep heat for steady, high-output power. It is exactly the kind of hulking civic infrastructure Poseidon loved to dominate a skyline with.</GeothermalGenerator.description>
  <GeothermalGenerator.label>geothermal plant</GeothermalGenerator.label>
  <Heater.description>A Wattz Electronics heating unit that converts electricity into controlled room heat. It automatically cycles to reach a target temperature.</Heater.description>
  <HiTechResearchBench.description>A Wattz high-tech research bench with computers and electronic measurement equipment. It enables rapid research and more advanced technical projects.</HiTechResearchBench.description>
  <HospitalBed.description>A Med-Tek hospital bed specially designed for clinical care. Adjustable support geometry and integrated instruments improve patient outcomes over ordinary beds.</HospitalBed.description>
  <MegascreenTelevision.description>A huge Radiation King television for settlements that want their entertainment loud, bright, and impossible to ignore.</MegascreenTelevision.description>
  <NutrientPasteDispenser.description>An industrial dispenser that synthesizes edible nutrient paste from feedstocks placed in adjacent hoppers. Efficient, joyless, and exactly the sort of machine a large contractor would call progress.</NutrientPasteDispenser.description>
  <OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>A Wattz orbital trade beacon used to mark goods for exchange with orbital merchants. Dependable, compact, and built for practical frontier commerce.</OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>
  <PowerConduit.description>A bundle of utility cables for moving power around a settlement. It can be placed under walls and other structures as part of a proper pre-War grid.</PowerConduit.description>
  <PS_ChemfuelTank.description>An industrial storage tank meant for oil delivered through the pipe network. Tanks can be siphoned for usable fuel as needed, but even light damage can turn leaking vapors into a violent fireball.</PS_ChemfuelTank.description>
  <PS_ChemfuelTank.label>oil tank</PS_ChemfuelTank.label>
  <RB_FloorLamp.description>A floor-mounted Wattz lamp that lights an area using electricity. It is less powerful than a standing lamp, but it looks right at home in a retro-futurist sitting room.</RB_FloorLamp.description>
  <SerumCentrifuge.description>A Med-Tek serum lab that uses scavenged archotechnology to create single-use injectable serums. Clean, expensive, and morally questionable in exactly the right pre-War way.</SerumCentrifuge.description>
  <SerumCentrifuge.label>Med-Tek serum lab</SerumCentrifuge.label>
  <SolarGenerator.description>A Poseidon Civilian Helios Two solar panel array for settlement-scale power generation. It delivers its best output under full daylight and clear skies.</SolarGenerator.description>
  <SolarGenerator.label>Civilian Helios Two</SolarGenerator.label>
  <Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>An outdoor utility lamp with an integrated Poseidon solar collector. It charges by day and provides dependable lighting after dark.</Spacer_OutdoorLamp.description>
  <TubeTelevision.description>A Radiation King tube television built around bulky old display hardware and a distinctly pre-War sense of domestic prestige.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <UnstablePowerCell.label>unstable fusion battery</UnstablePowerCell.label>
  <VanometricPowerCell.description>A compact power cell that generates free energy forever without conventional fuel. Even by pre-War standards it feels less like engineering and more like a secret Poseidon program nobody was meant to understand.</VanometricPowerCell.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.description>A basin meant to feed stored oil into the network and fill connected tanks.</VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.label>oil drain</VCHE_ChemfuelDrain.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.description>Steel pipes designed to move usable oil from deepchem refineries to oil tanks for storage or to oil-fed structures for automatic refilling.</VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.label>oil pipe</VCHE_ChemfuelPipe.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelTap.description>A basin meant to hold dispensed oil from storage tanks for later use.</VCHE_ChemfuelTap.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelTap.label>oil tap</VCHE_ChemfuelTap.label>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelValve.description>Switches oil flow on or off.</VCHE_ChemfuelValve.description>
  <VCHE_ChemfuelValve.label>oil valve</VCHE_ChemfuelValve.label>
  <VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.description>Buried steel pipes designed to move usable oil from deepchem refineries to oil tanks for storage or to oil-fed structures for automatic refilling.</VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.description>
  <VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.label>subterranean oil pipe</VCHE_UndergroundChemfuelPipe.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedBattery.description>A sealed Poseidon battery unit with far better efficiency than common storage cells. These pre-War housings are rainproof and less prone to catastrophic discharge.</VFE_AdvancedBattery.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.description>A high-efficiency Poseidon solar array marketed as the Industrial Helios Two, built to pull significantly more charge from direct sunlight than ordinary civilian panels.</VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.label>Industrial Helios Two</VFE_AdvancedSolarGenerator.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.description>A Poseidon hydro unit designed to draw industrial power from moving water. Crowded installations create turbulence and reduce output.</VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.label>industrial hydro turbine</VFE_AdvancedWatermillGenerator.label>
  <VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.description>A pre-War Poseidon utility turbine built for industrial output. It needs broad clear approaches to keep airflow stable and advertises the sort of oversized confidence Poseidon loved to stamp on its public works.</VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.label>industrial wind turbine</VFE_AdvancedWindTurbine.label>
  <VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.description>A powered Corvega assembly bench fitted for turning raw stock into industrial and spacer-grade components.</VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.description>
  <VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.label>Corvega assembly bench</VFE_ComponentFabricationBench.label>
  <VFE_FueledSmelter.description>A fuel-fed foundry station for recovering usable metal from slag and scrap items.</VFE_FueledSmelter.description>
  <VFE_FueledSmelter.label>fueled foundry</VFE_FueledSmelter.label>
  <VFE_LargeAdvancedBattery.description>A large sealed Poseidon battery bank built for dependable utility storage. Unlike older packs, these housings withstand rain without exploding.</VFE_LargeAdvancedBattery.description>
  <VFE_LargeBattery.description>A large Poseidon battery bank meant to hold reserve power for later demand. Fully charged units are dangerous when exposed to rain or fire.</VFE_LargeBattery.description>
  <VFE_SmallBattery.description>A compact reserve battery for local circuits and small industrial loads. Charged units can still blow when exposed to rain or fire.</VFE_SmallBattery.description>
  <VFE_TableButcherElectric.description>A motorized butcher line with a rotary saw for fast, precise carcass breakdown. It consumes a heavy amount of power.</VFE_TableButcherElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableButcherElectric.label>industrial butcher line</VFE_TableButcherElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.description>A powered Corvega chem lab with heaters, vessels, and gauges for efficient batch processing of compounds and drugs.</VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.label>industrial chem lab</VFE_TableDrugLabElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableMachiningLarge.description>A large Corvega machining platform with advanced tooling and floor space for rapid fabrication of technical equipment. It consumes power.</VFE_TableMachiningLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableMachiningLarge.label>Corvega machining platform</VFE_TableMachiningLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableSmithyLarge.description>A powered Corvega forge station for weapons, tools, and heavy benchwork. It draws a substantial load from the grid.</VFE_TableSmithyLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableSmithyLarge.label>Corvega forge station</VFE_TableSmithyLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.description>An industrial masonry saw with powered cutters for turning chunks into building blocks at assembly-line speed.</VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.description>
  <VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.label>industrial masonry saw</VFE_TableStonecutterElectric.label>
  <VFE_TableStoveLarge.description>A large industrial cooking line with multiple ovens and burners for rapid meal production under heavy settlement demand.</VFE_TableStoveLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableStoveLarge.label>industrial galley range</VFE_TableStoveLarge.label>
  <VFE_TableTailorLarge.description>A large industrial tailoring bench with powered sewing equipment for rapid clothing output. It can still limp along without power at reduced speed.</VFE_TableTailorLarge.description>
  <VFE_TableTailorLarge.label>industrial tailoring bench</VFE_TableTailorLarge.label>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>A large Corvega field machine that handles sowing and harvest cycles across a designated crop zone, then pushes the yield into attached works hoppers.</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.description>
  <VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>agri-industrial harvester</VFEFactory_Autofarmer.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>An automated Corvega refinery that converts wood and other organic feedstock into oil. It requires a factory floor, works hoppers, and can be overclocked for higher output at higher heat and power cost.</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>Corvega oil refinery</VFEFactory_AutomatedBiofuelRefinery.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>An automated Corvega deep extraction rig for pulling stone and buried metals up from the crust. Works machinery needs hoppers for intake and output, throws off serious heat, and can be overclocked at the cost of even greater draw and temperature.</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>Corvega drill platform</VFEFactory_AutomatedDrillPlatform.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>A Corvega masonry line for turning stone chunks into consistent construction blocks. It needs hoppers, throws heat, and responds well to overclocking if your grid can support it.</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.description>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>automated masonry line</VFEFactory_AutomatedMasonrySaw.label>
  <VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>A heavy Corvega smelter for recovering metal from slag, scrap gear, stone, and mechanoid remains. It belongs on a factory floor and can be overclocked for harsher but faster reclamation.</VFEFactory_AutomatedSmelter.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>A basic industrial conveyor for moving materials between work cells with minimal labor handling.</VFEFactory_Conveyor.description>
  <VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>industrial conveyor</VFEFactory_Conveyor.label>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>Stores feedstock and finished goods for automated Corvega works machinery.</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.description>
  <VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>works hopper</VFEFactory_FactoryHopper.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>A buried intake point that lets an industrial conveyor run beneath short stretches of ground before resurfacing.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>buried conveyor intake</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorEntrance.label>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>A buried discharge point that brings an underground conveyor back to the surface near the next work cell.</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.description>
  <VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>buried conveyor discharge</VFEFactory_UndergroundConveyorExit.label>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.description>A compact Wattz Electronics air scrubber that filters smoke, dust, and hazardous particulates while improving room cleanliness and indoor air quality.</VFES_AirPurifier.description>
  <VFES_AirPurifier.label>Wattz air scrubber</VFES_AirPurifier.label>
  <VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>A large ultratech shield projector with the unmistakable feel of a Poseidon black-budget installation. It consumes enormous power while active and can set the surrounding area ablaze if it absorbs too much punishment too quickly.</VFES_LargeRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>A compact ultratech shield projector that reads like one of Poseidon's more secretive defense contracts. It throws up a potent energy field when a threat is present and idles at far lower draw the rest of the time.</VFES_SmallRepulsor.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>A specialized Corvega anti-air turret that intercepts explosive projectiles and incoming drop pods within its defensive radius. It cannot engage ground targets, but it looks every bit like a pre-War perimeter solution.</VFES_Turret_AntiAir.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>An armored portable turret with Corvega targeting electronics and reinforced plating. Extra armor helps it survive incoming fire, but the control package remains just dumb enough to be dangerous around friendlies.</VFES_Turret_ArmoredTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>A twin-barreled autocannon turret with Corvega fire-control electronics. It trades finesse for volume of fire and remains a power-hungry, violently practical defensive platform.</VFES_Turret_AutocannonDouble.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Flame.description>A portable flamer turret with Corvega control electronics and a brutally simple fuel system. It can engulf enemies and terrain in fire, and it remains as unsafe as any honest pre-War weapon platform should be.</VFES_Turret_Flame.description>
  <VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>A refined automated turret with Corvega targeting hardware, military-grade stabilization, and hardened casing. Its dumb AI brain still cannot be directly controlled, so beware of friendly fire.</VFES_Turret_MilitaryTurret.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>A heavy automatic turret whose multi-barrel mechanism unleashes sustained fire at high speed. Corvega control systems keep it cycling, but they do not make it subtle.</VFES_Turret_Minigun.description>
  <VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>A Corvega searchlight combining an intensely bright lamp with a mirrored reflector, useful for illuminating and dazzling targets across a defensive perimeter.</VFES_Turret_Searchlight.description>
  <VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>A compact automatic turret fitted with a semi-automatic shotgun and Corvega targeting electronics. Short-ranged, nasty, and still not smart enough to trust completely.</VFES_Turret_ShotgunTurret.description>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>A tall propane floodlight that illuminates a massive area. It is not bright enough for crop growth, but it provides dependable yard lighting when connected to the propane network.</VHGE_GasFloodlight.description>
  <VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>propane floodlight</VHGE_GasFloodlight.label>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.description>A propane-fed standing lamp for utility lighting. It must be connected to the propane network and can be placed safely outdoors.</VHGE_GasLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasLamp.label>propane lamp</VHGE_GasLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>An industrial lamp bright enough for crop growth, but it burns a steady supply of propane. It shuts itself off at night.</VHGE_GasSunLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>propane sun lamp</VHGE_GasSunLamp.label>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>A propane-fed wall light for utility corridors and work rooms. It must be connected to the propane network and can be placed safely outdoors.</VHGE_GasWallLamp.description>
  <VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>propane wall lamp</VHGE_GasWallLamp.label>
  <VHGE_Helixien.description>Propane gas.</VHGE_Helixien.description>
  <VHGE_Helixien.label>propane</VHGE_Helixien.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>A Med-Tek patient telemetry unit that improves tend quality, surgery success, and recovery when mounted directly beside a hospital bed.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>A bedside Med-Tek feeding device that delivers nutrient paste directly to bedridden patients when linked to a nutrient vat. Practical, clinical, and just unsettling enough to feel authentic.</VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>A compact Corvega feeder that outputs nutrient paste from the pipe network for routine worker consumption.</VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>A Corvega nutrient grinder that reduces organic feedstocks into pipeline-ready paste stock. Efficient, impersonal, and very much in the spirit of industrial pre-War food engineering.</VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>A Corvega paste tap that dispenses prepared nutrient meals from the vat network. It is the kind of practical cafeteria hardware a large contractor would install by the hundred.</VNPE_NutrientPasteTap.description>
  <VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>A Corvega storage vat for holding large volumes of processed nutrient paste. Destroying one makes exactly the kind of industrial mess you would expect.</VNPE_NutrientPasteVat.description>
  <VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.description>A large Poseidon groundwater reclamation pump that gradually strips pollution from broad terrain and condenses the recovered waste into haulable toxic packs.</VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.description>
  <VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.label>Poseidon reclamation pump</VRecyclingE_LargePollutionPump.label>
  <VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.description>A compact high-draw reclamation pump that clears polluted terrain quickly by burning a heavy amount of grid power and packing the recovered contaminants into toxic wastepacks.</VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.description>
  <VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.label>high-draw reclamation pump</VRecyclingE_PollutionFastPump.label>
  <VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.description>A sealed industrial locker for holding toxic waste products and reclaimed hazardous packs without letting them leak into the local environment.</VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.description>
  <VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.label>sealed waste locker</VRecyclingE_WasteCrate.label>
  <VTE_IndustrialCooler.description>A large Appalachia Freeze wall cooler for serious refrigeration and industrial climate control. Cold air exits one side while hot exhaust is dumped out the other.</VTE_IndustrialCooler.description>
  <VTE_IndustrialHeater.description>A large Wattz industrial heater that fits into a wall and pushes serious utility heat. It can automatically cycle to a target temperature.</VTE_IndustrialHeater.description>
  <VTE_LargeCeilingFan.description>A large Wattz ceiling fan for workshops, warehouses, and other rooms that need stronger air circulation.</VTE_LargeCeilingFan.description>
  <VTE_SmallCeilingFan.description>A Wattz ceiling fan for slow, steady air circulation in smaller rooms.</VTE_SmallCeilingFan.description>
  <VTE_StandingCooler.description>A freestanding Appalachia Freeze cooling unit for open rooms that need relief from summer heat without full freezer performance.</VTE_StandingCooler.description>
  <VTE_WallHeater.description>A Wattz wall heater that fits into a wall and keeps rooms warm without wasting floor space.</VTE_WallHeater.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedCooler.description>An Appalachia Freeze wall-mounted cooler for compact freezer rooms and tight utility spaces.</VTE_WallMountedCooler.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedHeater.description>A compact Wattz wall-mounted heater for utility corridors, workshops, and smaller rooms that still need dependable automatic temperature control.</VTE_WallMountedHeater.description>
  <VTE_WallMountedVent.description>A simple Wattz wall vent for equalizing temperatures between adjacent rooms without opening a passageway.</VTE_WallMountedVent.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>A Poseidon hydro unit designed to draw steady power from moving water. Crowded placements create turbulence and reduce output.</WatermillGenerator.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.label>hydro turbine</WatermillGenerator.label>
  <WindTurbine.description>A utility-grade wind turbine for civilian settlements. It needs a broad, clear approach to keep airflow stable.</WindTurbine.description>
  <WindTurbine.label>civilian wind turbine</WindTurbine.label>
</LanguageData>