<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Food_Black_Blood_Sausage.description>A dark, rich sausage made from the blood and meat of various wasteland creatures. While nutritious and filling, the questionable ingredients and preparation methods can lead to minor toxic buildup. A favorite among raiders and desperate survivors.</FCP_Food_Black_Blood_Sausage.description>
  <FCP_Food_Black_Blood_Sausage.label>black blood sausage</FCP_Food_Black_Blood_Sausage.label>
  <FCP_Food_Brahmin_Pot_Pie.description>A hearty pot pie filled with tender brahmin meat, tatos, and razorgrain. This comfort food from the wasteland provides a satisfying meal that reminds settlers of better times. The rich brahmin meat provides a temporary boost to work speed.</FCP_Food_Brahmin_Pot_Pie.description>
  <FCP_Food_Brahmin_Pot_Pie.label>brahmin pot pie</FCP_Food_Brahmin_Pot_Pie.label>
  <FCP_Food_Bug_Mush.description>A paste made from various insects ground into a protein-rich but unappetizing mush. It's filling and surprisingly nutritious, though the taste leaves much to be desired. The questionable hygiene can cause minor toxic buildup.</FCP_Food_Bug_Mush.description>
  <FCP_Food_Bug_Mush.label>bug mush</FCP_Food_Bug_Mush.label>
  <FCP_Food_Chicken_Noodle_Cup.description>A simple but comforting cup of noodles with chunks of rad chicken meat. Quick to prepare and easy on the stomach, this meal reminds people of simpler times. The warm broth provides a small mood boost.</FCP_Food_Chicken_Noodle_Cup.description>
  <FCP_Food_Chicken_Noodle_Cup.label>chicken noodle cup</FCP_Food_Chicken_Noodle_Cup.label>
  <FCP_Food_Cook_Cooks_Fiend_Stew.description>A spicy, aggressive stew made with whatever meat is available, heavily seasoned with jalapeños and wasteland spices. Named after the infamous Fiend cook, this meal gives a temporary boost to melee damage and pain tolerance, but the toxic ingredients cause buildup.</FCP_Food_Cook_Cooks_Fiend_Stew.description>
  <FCP_Food_Cook_Cooks_Fiend_Stew.label>cook-cook's fiend stew</FCP_Food_Cook_Cooks_Fiend_Stew.label>
  <FCP_Food_Crispy_Wings.description>Deep-fried rad chicken wings with a crispy golden coating. A popular snack in wasteland settlements, these wings are fried in vegetable oil until perfectly crispy. The indulgent meal provides a mood boost.</FCP_Food_Crispy_Wings.description>
  <FCP_Food_Crispy_Wings.label>crispy wings</FCP_Food_Crispy_Wings.label>
  <FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Eggs.description>A premium meal of grilled deathclaw steak served with fresh eggs. Deathclaw meat is incredibly rare and prized for its flavor and nutritional value. This meal provides significant stat boosts including increased movement speed and melee damage for a time.</FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Eggs.description>
  <FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Eggs.label>deathclaw steak and eggs</FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Eggs.label>
  <FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Razorgrain.description>Tender deathclaw steak served alongside razorgrain. The combination of premium meat and hearty grain creates a satisfying and nutritious meal that boosts work efficiency and provides stamina.</FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Razorgrain.description>
  <FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Razorgrain.label>deathclaw steak and razorgrain</FCP_Food_Deathclaw_Steak_And_Razorgrain.label>
  <FCP_Food_Flea_Soup.description>A thin broth made from small wasteland creatures and scraps. While barely palatable and nearly flavorless, it prevents starvation. The questionable ingredients can cause minor toxic buildup.</FCP_Food_Flea_Soup.description>
  <FCP_Food_Flea_Soup.label>flea soup</FCP_Food_Flea_Soup.label>
  <FCP_Food_Meat_On_A_Stick.description>Simple grilled meat skewered on a stick. Quick to prepare and easy to eat on the go, this basic meal is a staple of wasteland traders and travelers.</FCP_Food_Meat_On_A_Stick.description>
  <FCP_Food_Meat_On_A_Stick.label>meat on a stick</FCP_Food_Meat_On_A_Stick.label>
  <FCP_Food_Noodle_Cup.description>A basic cup of noodles made from razorgrain flour. While bland and unremarkable, it's cheap, filling, and quick to prepare. A wasteland staple.</FCP_Food_Noodle_Cup.description>
  <FCP_Food_Noodle_Cup.label>noodle cup</FCP_Food_Noodle_Cup.label>
  <FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak.description>A well-prepared steak from prime wasteland beast meat. Properly cooked and seasoned, this meal is a treat in the harsh wasteland. The high-quality protein provides a temporary boost to consciousness and blood pumping.</FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak.description>
  <FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak.label>prime meat steak</FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak.label>
  <FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak_With_Corn_And_Tatos.description>A lavish meal featuring premium steak served with grilled maize and roasted tatos. This well-balanced meal combines the best ingredients the wasteland has to offer. Provides significant stat boosts and mood improvement.</FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak_With_Corn_And_Tatos.description>
  <FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak_With_Corn_And_Tatos.label>prime meat steak with corn and tatos</FCP_Food_Prime_Meat_Steak_With_Corn_And_Tatos.label>
  <FCP_Food_Sausages.description>Simple grilled sausages made from ground wasteland meat and spices. A straightforward, filling meal that's easy to prepare and transport. Popular among caravans.</FCP_Food_Sausages.description>
  <FCP_Food_Sausages.label>sausages</FCP_Food_Sausages.label>
</LanguageData>