<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VCE_AgaveNectar.description>Create agave nectar from agave. Agave nectar is a thin and semi-sweet nectar, known for its healing and anti-inflammatory properties.</VCE_AgaveNectar.description>
  <VCE_AgaveNectar.label>make agave nectar</VCE_AgaveNectar.label>
  <VCE_CanAlienFish.description>Safely store alien fish in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely.</VCE_CanAlienFish.description>
  <VCE_CanAlienFish.label>can alien fish x20</VCE_CanAlienFish.label>
  <VCE_CanEggs.description>Safely store boiled eggs in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely.</VCE_CanEggs.description>
  <VCE_CanEggs.label>can eggs x20</VCE_CanEggs.label>
  <VCE_CanFish.description>Safely store fish in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely.</VCE_CanFish.description>
  <VCE_CanFish.label>can fish x20</VCE_CanFish.label>
  <VCE_CanFruit.description>Safely store fruit in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely.\n\nPreserved fruit can be used in the production of desserts.</VCE_CanFruit.description>
  <VCE_CanFruit.label>can fruit x20</VCE_CanFruit.label>
  <VCE_CanMeats.description>Safely store meat chunks in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely.</VCE_CanMeats.description>
  <VCE_CanMeats.label>can meats x20</VCE_CanMeats.label>
  <VCE_CanProduce.description>Safely store vegetables in a steel can. Canning food extends its shelf life almost indefinitely.</VCE_CanProduce.description>
  <VCE_CanProduce.label>can produce x20</VCE_CanProduce.label>
  <VCE_ChocolateSyrup.description>Create chocolate syrup from genetically modified chocolate. While still not good for you, chocolate syrup is not quite as bad as straight sugar.</VCE_ChocolateSyrup.description>
  <VCE_ChocolateSyrup.label>make chocolate syrup</VCE_ChocolateSyrup.label>
  <VCE_ChopCondiments.description>Mix a batch of different condiments into a barely edible organic mass that can be fed to animals. Still better than supermarket pet food.</VCE_ChopCondiments.description>
  <VCE_ChopCondiments.label>mix condiments into kibble</VCE_ChopCondiments.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeFine.description>Cook two complex bakes assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients and flour.</VCE_CookBakeFine.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeFine.label>cook fine bake x2</VCE_CookBakeFine.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeFineBulk.description>Cook 8 complex bakes assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients and flour.</VCE_CookBakeFineBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeFineBulk.label>cook fine bake x8</VCE_CookBakeFineBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeGourmet.description>Cook two culinary works of art, characterized by refined, even elaborate preparation and presentation of an aesthetically balanced, albeit low quantity bake.\n\nThis recipe does not allow mixed ingredients.</VCE_CookBakeGourmet.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeGourmet.label>cook gourmet bake x2</VCE_CookBakeGourmet.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeLavish.description>Cook two masterpieces of the culinary arts, these bakes nourish the body, mind, and soul.</VCE_CookBakeLavish.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeLavish.label>cook lavish bake x2</VCE_CookBakeLavish.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeLavishBulk.description>Cook 8 masterpieces of the culinary arts, these bakes nourish the body, mind, and soul.</VCE_CookBakeLavishBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeLavishBulk.label>cook lavish bake x8</VCE_CookBakeLavishBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeSimple.description>Cook two simple bakes quickly cooked from flour.</VCE_CookBakeSimple.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeSimple.label>cook simple bake x2</VCE_CookBakeSimple.label>
  <VCE_CookBakeSimpleBulk.description>Cook 8 simple bakes quickly cooked from flour.</VCE_CookBakeSimpleBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookBakeSimpleBulk.label>cook simple bake x8</VCE_CookBakeSimpleBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertFine.description>Cook a complex dessert assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients.\n\nNote that because Chocolate has 0.10 nutrition per unit, some of it will be wasted while cooking this recipe. Consider using the bulk (x4) version of this recipe instead to avoid wastage.</VCE_CookDessertFine.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertFine.label>cook fine dessert</VCE_CookDessertFine.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertFineBulk.description>Cook 4 complex desserts assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients.</VCE_CookDessertFineBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertFineBulk.label>cook fine dessert x4</VCE_CookDessertFineBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertGourmet.description>Cook a culinary work of art, characterized by refined, even elaborate preparation and presentation of an aesthetically balanced, albeit low quantity dessert.</VCE_CookDessertGourmet.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertGourmet.label>cook gourmet dessert</VCE_CookDessertGourmet.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertLavish.description>Cook a masterpiece of the culinary arts, this dessert nourishes the body, mind, and soul.\n\nNote that because Chocolate has 0.10 nutrition per unit, some of it will be wasted while cooking this recipe. Consider using the bulk (x4) version of this recipe instead to avoid wastage.</VCE_CookDessertLavish.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertLavish.label>cook lavish dessert</VCE_CookDessertLavish.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertLavishBulk.description>Cook 4 masterpieces of the culinary arts, this dessert nourishes the body, mind, and soul.</VCE_CookDessertLavishBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertLavishBulk.label>cook lavish dessert x4</VCE_CookDessertLavishBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertSimple.description>Cook a simple dessert quickly made from a few fruits and other ingredients.</VCE_CookDessertSimple.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertSimple.label>cook simple dessert</VCE_CookDessertSimple.label>
  <VCE_CookDessertSimpleBulk.description>Cook 4 simple desserts quickly made from a few fruits and other ingredients.</VCE_CookDessertSimpleBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookDessertSimpleBulk.label>cook simple dessert x4</VCE_CookDessertSimpleBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillFine.description>Cook a complex grill assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients.</VCE_CookGrillFine.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillFine.label>cook fine grill</VCE_CookGrillFine.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillFineBulk.description>Cook 4 complex grills assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients.</VCE_CookGrillFineBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillFineBulk.label>cook fine grill x4</VCE_CookGrillFineBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillGourmet.description>Cook a culinary works of art, characterized by refined, even elaborate preparation and presentation of an aesthetically balanced, albeit low quantity grill.</VCE_CookGrillGourmet.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillGourmet.label>cook gourmet grill</VCE_CookGrillGourmet.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillLavish.description>Cook a masterpiece of the culinary arts, this grill nourishes the body, mind, and soul.</VCE_CookGrillLavish.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillLavish.label>cook lavish grill</VCE_CookGrillLavish.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillLavishhBulk.description>Cook 4 masterpieces of the culinary arts, these grills nourish the body, mind, and soul.</VCE_CookGrillLavishhBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillLavishhBulk.label>cook lavish grill x4</VCE_CookGrillLavishhBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillSimple.description>Cook two simple grills quickly cooked from a few meat ingredients.</VCE_CookGrillSimple.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillSimple.label>cook simple grill</VCE_CookGrillSimple.label>
  <VCE_CookGrillSimpleBulk.description>Cook 4 simple grills quickly cooked from a few meat ingredients.</VCE_CookGrillSimpleBulk.description>
  <VCE_CookGrillSimpleBulk.label>cook simple grill x4</VCE_CookGrillSimpleBulk.label>
  <VCE_CookMealGourmet.description>Cook a culinary work of art, characterized by refined, even elaborate preparation and presentation of an aesthetically balanced, albeit low quantity meal.</VCE_CookMealGourmet.description>
  <VCE_CookMealGourmet.label>cook gourmet meal</VCE_CookMealGourmet.label>
  <VCE_CookSoupFine.description>Prepare a fine uncooked soup assembled with care from a wide selection of ingredients.</VCE_CookSoupFine.description>
  <VCE_CookSoupFine.label>prepare fine soup</VCE_CookSoupFine.label>
  <VCE_CookSoupGourmet.description>Prepare a gourmet uncooked soup. A culinary work of art, characterized by refined, even elaborate preparation and presentation of an aesthetically balanced, albeit low quantity soup.\n\nThis recipe does not allow mixed ingredients, and takes a long time to make.</VCE_CookSoupGourmet.description>
  <VCE_CookSoupGourmet.label>prepare gourmet soup</VCE_CookSoupGourmet.label>
  <VCE_CookSoupLavish.description>Prepare a lavish uncooked soup. A masterpiece of the culinary arts, this soup nourishes the body, mind, and soul.</VCE_CookSoupLavish.description>
  <VCE_CookSoupLavish.label>prepare lavish soup</VCE_CookSoupLavish.label>
  <VCE_CookSoupSimple.description>Prepare a simple uncooked soup quickly made from a few ingredients.</VCE_CookSoupSimple.description>
  <VCE_CookSoupSimple.label>prepare simple soup</VCE_CookSoupSimple.label>
  <VCE_DeepFryAlienFish.description>Deep fry alien fish. Deep fried food is very tasty, but not very good for your health.</VCE_DeepFryAlienFish.description>
  <VCE_DeepFryAlienFish.label>deep fry alien fish x20</VCE_DeepFryAlienFish.label>
  <VCE_DeepFryFish.description>Deep fry fish. Deep fried food is very tasty, but not very good for your health.</VCE_DeepFryFish.description>
  <VCE_DeepFryFish.label>deep fry fish x20</VCE_DeepFryFish.label>
  <VCE_DeepFryMeats.description>Deep fry large meat chunks. Deep fried food is very tasty, but not very good for your health.</VCE_DeepFryMeats.description>
  <VCE_DeepFryMeats.label>deep fry meats x20</VCE_DeepFryMeats.label>
  <VCE_DeepFryVegetables.description>Deep fry vegetables. Deep fried food is very tasty, but not very good for your health.</VCE_DeepFryVegetables.description>
  <VCE_DeepFryVegetables.label>deep fry vegetables x20</VCE_DeepFryVegetables.label>
  <VCE_HotSauce.description>Create hot sauce from peppers. A potent, spicy sauce made from blending and simmering chilis and other spices. While particularly strong hot sauces hurt at first, they are known to numb pain and work up a warm sweat shortly after consumption.</VCE_HotSauce.description>
  <VCE_HotSauce.label>make hot sauce</VCE_HotSauce.label>
  <VCE_InsectJellyPreserves.description>Create insect jelly preserves from insect jelly. Very rich and sweet, while being surprisingly healthy.</VCE_InsectJellyPreserves.description>
  <VCE_InsectJellyPreserves.label>make insect jelly preserves</VCE_InsectJellyPreserves.label>
  <VCE_Ketchup.description>Create ketchup from tomatoes. A thick sauce made from stewing tomatoes, both salty and tangy in tandem with a sweet aftertaste. Perfect for meaty meals or fried foods.</VCE_Ketchup.description>
  <VCE_Ketchup.label>make ketchup</VCE_Ketchup.label>
  <VCE_MakeSalt.description>Grind and process natural stone to extract edible salts from within stone chunks.\n\nUses the Cooking skill.</VCE_MakeSalt.description>
  <VCE_MakeSalt.label>make salt</VCE_MakeSalt.label>
  <VCE_MakeSaltfromBlocks.description>Grind and process natural stone to extract edible salts from within stone blocks.\n\nUses the Cooking skill.</VCE_MakeSaltfromBlocks.description>
  <VCE_MakeSaltfromBlocks.label>make salt (blocks)</VCE_MakeSaltfromBlocks.label>
  <VCE_Mayo.description>Create mayo from eggs. A thick emulsion of egg, oil, and other herbs. Mayonnaise, while terrible for you, adds a pleasing tang and is very calorically dense.</VCE_Mayo.description>
  <VCE_Mayo.label>make mayo</VCE_Mayo.label>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>Create smokeleaf butter from smokeleaf and milk. A thickened, fatty substance made by churning milk into very thick cream, combining with smokeleaf oil and allowing it to set. Very unhealthy and hits quite a bit harder than a joint.</VCE_SmokeleafButter.description>
  <VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>make smokeleaf butter</VCE_SmokeleafButter.label>
</LanguageData>