<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Addiction_Buffout.description>A chemical addiction to Buffout. Long-term presence of Buffout has caused neurological and physiological adaptations, so the body can no longer function properly without the drug. Without regular doses of Buffout, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the body to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_Buffout.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_Buffout.label>Buffout addiction</FCP_Addiction_Buffout.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Buffout.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_Buffout.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_DaddyO.description>A chemical addiction to Daddy-O. Long-term presence of Daddy-O has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.\n\nWithout regular doses of Daddy-O, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_DaddyO.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_DaddyO.label>Daddy-O addiction</FCP_Addiction_DaddyO.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_DaddyO.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_DaddyO.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_DayTripper.description>A chemical addiction to Day Tripper. Long-term presence of Day Tripper has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.\n\nWithout regular doses of Day Tripper, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_DayTripper.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_DayTripper.label>Day Tripper addiction</FCP_Addiction_DayTripper.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_DayTripper.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_DayTripper.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Jet.description>A chemical addiction to Jet. Long-term presence of Jet has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug. Without regular doses of Jet, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_Jet.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_Jet.label>Jet addiction</FCP_Addiction_Jet.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Jet.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_Jet.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Mentats.description>A psychological addiction to Mentats. The brain has become dependent on the cognitive enhancement, and withdrawal causes severe mental fog and confusion.Without regular doses of Mentats, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will allow the brain to recover its natural function, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_Mentats.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_Mentats.label>Mentats addiction</FCP_Addiction_Mentats.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Mentats.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_Mentats.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Psycho.description>A chemical addiction to Psycho. Long-term presence of Psycho has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug. Without regular doses of Psycho, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_Psycho.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_Psycho.label>Psycho addiction</FCP_Addiction_Psycho.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Psycho.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_Psycho.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Slasher.description>A chemical addiction to Slasher. Long-term presence of Slasher has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug. Without regular doses of Slasher, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_Slasher.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_Slasher.label>Slasher addiction</FCP_Addiction_Slasher.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Slasher.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_Slasher.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Ultrajet.description>A chemical addiction to Ultrajet. Long-term presence of Ultrajet has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.\n\nWithout regular doses of Ultrajet, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_Addiction_Ultrajet.description>
  <FCP_Addiction_Ultrajet.label>Ultrajet addiction</FCP_Addiction_Ultrajet.label>
  <FCP_Addiction_Ultrajet.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_Addiction_Ultrajet.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_AddictolRecovery.description>Undergoing addiction treatment from Addictol. Feeling exhausted but addictions are being purged.</FCP_Hediff_AddictolRecovery.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_AddictolRecovery.label>Addictol treatment</FCP_Hediff_AddictolRecovery.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_Auto_Stimpak.description>An automated delivery system that dispenses a standard stimpak dose when injuries are detected.</FCP_Hediff_Auto_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_Auto_Stimpak.label>auto-stimpak</FCP_Hediff_Auto_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_Auto_Super_Stimpak.description>An automated delivery system loaded with super stimpak formula for rapid emergency healing.</FCP_Hediff_Auto_Super_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_Auto_Super_Stimpak.label>auto-super stimpak</FCP_Hediff_Auto_Super_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_BerryMentatsHigh.description>Enhanced charisma and social skills from Berry Mentats.</FCP_Hediff_BerryMentatsHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_BerryMentatsHigh.label>high on Berry Mentats</FCP_Hediff_BerryMentatsHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_BloodPackHigh.description>Fresh blood is restoring blood volume and promoting healing. The transfusion helps stabilize the patient.</FCP_Hediff_BloodPackHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_BloodPackHigh.label>blood transfusion</FCP_Hediff_BloodPackHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_BuffoutHigh.description>Enhanced by Buffout. Strength, carrying capacity, and melee damage significantly increased.</FCP_Hediff_BuffoutHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_BuffoutHigh.label>high on Buffout</FCP_Hediff_BuffoutHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_BuffoutTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Buffout. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Buffout it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_BuffoutTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_BuffoutTolerance.label>Buffout tolerance</FCP_Hediff_BuffoutTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_CateyeHigh.description>Enhanced by Cateye. Vision significantly improved, especially in low light conditions.</FCP_Hediff_CateyeHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_CateyeHigh.label>cateye vision</FCP_Hediff_CateyeHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_DaddyOHigh.description>Enhanced intelligence and perception but reduced social skills from Daddy-O.</FCP_Hediff_DaddyOHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_DaddyOHigh.label>high on Daddy-O</FCP_Hediff_DaddyOHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_DaddyOTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Daddy-O. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Daddy-O it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_DaddyOTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_DaddyOTolerance.label>Daddy-O tolerance</FCP_Hediff_DaddyOTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_DayTripperHigh.description>Enhanced mood and charisma from Day Tripper.</FCP_Hediff_DayTripperHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_DayTripperHigh.label>high on Day Tripper</FCP_Hediff_DayTripperHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_DayTripperTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Day Tripper. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Day Tripper it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_DayTripperTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_DayTripperTolerance.label>Day Tripper tolerance</FCP_Hediff_DayTripperTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_Diluted_Stimpak.description>A watered-down stimulation pack that provides minor healing over time. The chemicals cause mild discomfort during healing.</FCP_Hediff_Diluted_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_Diluted_Stimpak.label>diluted stimpak</FCP_Hediff_Diluted_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_DixonsJetHigh.description>Under the effects of Dixon's Jet, a premium refined variant. The purer formula provides stronger and longer-lasting speed enhancement with reduced side effects.</FCP_Hediff_DixonsJetHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_DixonsJetHigh.label>Dixon's Jet high</FCP_Hediff_DixonsJetHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_DoctorsBagHigh.description>Comprehensive medical treatment is repairing injuries and crippled limbs. The extensive field surgery provides substantial healing over time.</FCP_Hediff_DoctorsBagHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_DoctorsBagHigh.label>field surgery</FCP_Hediff_DoctorsBagHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_FixerRecovery.description>Undergoing addiction treatment from Fixer. Feeling fatigued but withdrawal symptoms are reduced.</FCP_Hediff_FixerRecovery.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_FixerRecovery.label>Fixer treatment</FCP_Hediff_FixerRecovery.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_GrapeMentatsHigh.description>Balanced enhancement of intelligence and charisma from Grape Mentats.</FCP_Hediff_GrapeMentatsHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_GrapeMentatsHigh.label>high on Grape Mentats</FCP_Hediff_GrapeMentatsHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_HealingPowderHigh.description>Traditional wasteland medicine is providing gradual healing. The mixture of broc flower and xander root promotes natural tissue regeneration.</FCP_Hediff_HealingPowderHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_HealingPowderHigh.label>healing powder</FCP_Hediff_HealingPowderHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_HydraHigh.description>Hydra is rapidly regenerating damaged tissue and healing crippled limbs. The process is intense and causes disorientation.</FCP_Hediff_HydraHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_HydraHigh.label>Hydra</FCP_Hediff_HydraHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_JetHigh.description>Enhanced by Jet. Movement speed and work speed dramatically increased.</FCP_Hediff_JetHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_JetHigh.label>high on Jet</FCP_Hediff_JetHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_JetTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Jet. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Jet it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_JetTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_JetTolerance.label>Jet tolerance</FCP_Hediff_JetTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_MedXHigh.description>Med-X is blocking pain signals and providing damage resistance. The powerful analgesic effect makes injuries less debilitating.</FCP_Hediff_MedXHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_MedXHigh.label>Med-X</FCP_Hediff_MedXHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_MentatsHigh.description>Enhanced by Mentats. Intelligence, perception, and mental acuity significantly improved.</FCP_Hediff_MentatsHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_MentatsHigh.label>high on Mentats</FCP_Hediff_MentatsHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_MentatsTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Mentats. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Mentats it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_MentatsTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_MentatsTolerance.label>Mentats tolerance</FCP_Hediff_MentatsTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_OrangeMentatsHigh.description>Enhanced perception and accuracy from Orange Mentats.</FCP_Hediff_OrangeMentatsHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_OrangeMentatsHigh.label>high on Orange Mentats</FCP_Hediff_OrangeMentatsHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_PartyTimeMentatsHigh.description>Pleasant social enhancement from Party Time Mentats.</FCP_Hediff_PartyTimeMentatsHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_PartyTimeMentatsHigh.label>high on Party Time Mentats</FCP_Hediff_PartyTimeMentatsHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_PsychoHigh.description>Enraged by Psycho. Damage output and resistance dramatically increased, but mental functions suppressed.</FCP_Hediff_PsychoHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_PsychoHigh.label>high on Psycho</FCP_Hediff_PsychoHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_PsychoTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Psycho. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Psycho it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_PsychoTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_PsychoTolerance.label>Psycho tolerance</FCP_Hediff_PsychoTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_RadawayHigh.description>Rad-Away is actively purging radiation from the bloodstream. While effective, the process is exhausting.</FCP_Hediff_RadawayHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_RadawayHigh.label>Rad-Away</FCP_Hediff_RadawayHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_RadXHigh.description>Rad-X is providing protection against radiation and toxic contamination by altering cellular structure. Side effects include minor disorientation and reduced reflexes.</FCP_Hediff_RadXHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_RadXHigh.label>Rad-X</FCP_Hediff_RadXHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_ReboundRecovery.description>Undergoing anti-addiction therapy with Rebound. This medication helps reduce withdrawal symptoms and combat chemical dependencies, though less powerfully than Addictol.</FCP_Hediff_ReboundRecovery.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_ReboundRecovery.label>Rebound recovery</FCP_Hediff_ReboundRecovery.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_RocketHigh.description>Enhanced speed and stamina from Rocket's unique stimulant combination.</FCP_Hediff_RocketHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_RocketHigh.label>high on Rocket</FCP_Hediff_RocketHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_SlasherHigh.description>Enhanced by Slasher. Melee damage dramatically increased, pain reduced.</FCP_Hediff_SlasherHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_SlasherHigh.label>high on Slasher</FCP_Hediff_SlasherHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_SlasherTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Slasher. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Slasher it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_SlasherTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_SlasherTolerance.label>Slasher tolerance</FCP_Hediff_SlasherTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_SteadyHigh.description>Stabilized by Steady. Shooting accuracy and manipulation significantly improved.</FCP_Hediff_SteadyHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_SteadyHigh.label>steadied</FCP_Hediff_SteadyHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_Stimpak.description>A standard stimulation delivery system for healing injuries. The most common medical item in the wasteland. The rapid cellular regeneration causes discomfort and mild disorientation.</FCP_Hediff_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_Stimpak.label>stimpak</FCP_Hediff_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_Super_Stimpak.description>A potent military-grade stimulation pack that provides rapid and extensive healing. The powerful chemicals cause considerable pain and grogginess.</FCP_Hediff_Super_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_Super_Stimpak.label>super stimpak</FCP_Hediff_Super_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_TurboHigh.description>Supercharged by Turbo. Perception and reflexes dramatically enhanced, movement and shooting significantly improved.</FCP_Hediff_TurboHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_TurboHigh.label>high on Turbo</FCP_Hediff_TurboHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_Ultra_Stimpak.description>The pinnacle of pre-war medical technology. Provides extremely rapid and extensive healing, even mending old injuries. The intense cellular regeneration causes significant pain and exhaustion.</FCP_Hediff_Ultra_Stimpak.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_Ultra_Stimpak.label>ultra stimpak</FCP_Hediff_Ultra_Stimpak.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_UltrajetHigh.description>Extreme combat enhancement from combined Jet and Psycho effects. Speed and damage greatly increased, but with severe after-effects.</FCP_Hediff_UltrajetHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_UltrajetHigh.label>high on Ultrajet</FCP_Hediff_UltrajetHigh.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_UltrajetTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Ultrajet. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Ultrajet it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_Hediff_UltrajetTolerance.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_UltrajetTolerance.label>Ultrajet tolerance</FCP_Hediff_UltrajetTolerance.label>
  <FCP_Hediff_XCellHigh.description>Comprehensive enhancement of all capabilities from X-Cell.</FCP_Hediff_XCellHigh.description>
  <FCP_Hediff_XCellHigh.label>high on X-Cell</FCP_Hediff_XCellHigh.label>
  <FCP_MedXAddiction.description>A chemical addiction to Med-X. Long-term presence of Med-X has caused neurological adaptations at the cellular level, so the brain can no longer function properly without the drug.Without regular doses of Med-X, withdrawal symptoms will begin. However, extended abstinence will force the brain to adapt back to its normal state, resolving the addiction.</FCP_MedXAddiction.description>
  <FCP_MedXAddiction.label>Med-X addiction</FCP_MedXAddiction.label>
  <FCP_MedXAddiction.stages.1.label>withdrawal</FCP_MedXAddiction.stages.1.label>
  <FCP_MedXTolerance.description>A built-up tolerance to Med-X. The more severe this tolerance is, the more Med-X it takes to get the same effect.</FCP_MedXTolerance.description>
  <FCP_MedXTolerance.label>Med-X tolerance</FCP_MedXTolerance.label>
</LanguageData>