<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.description>你是兄弟会阿巴拉契亚远征队的一员，被派去追踪流氓成员并保护该地区丰富的战前军事设施。当焦土瘟疫摧毁了你的部队时，任务出现了偏差。\n\n现在你是一个失败章节的幸存者，承受着从艰难的道路上吸取的教训。你已经看到了当兄弟会过于分散、意识形态与生存发生冲突时会发生什么。是时候重新开始、聪明地构建，也许这次会采取不同的做法。</FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.description>
  <FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.label>阿巴拉契亚分会</FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.scenario.parts.14.text>阿巴拉契亚给你上了惨痛的教训。你看着兄弟姐妹们陷入辐射、疾病和那些只应该存在于噩梦中的生物。你看到了当兄弟会的势力范围超出其控制范围时会发生什么。\n\n但你活了下来。你学到了。你适应了。\n\n现在你远离了那些受辐射的山丘，但教训仍然存在。建立一个足够强大、足够聪明、足够灵活、足以应对这个世界向你抛出的任何问题的战团。\n\n兄弟会不断发展，否则就会消亡。是时候证明你是哪一类人了。</FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.scenario.parts.14.text>
  <FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.scenario.summary>五名阿巴拉契亚退伍军人一开始就拥有不同的技能，但过去的失败一直困扰着他们。要么适应，要么灭亡。</FCP_BoS_Appalachia_Chapter.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.description>你们是里昂长老改革后的兄弟会的最后幸存者 - 他们相信保护人民，而不仅仅是囤积技术。在统一并回归正统教义后，你因“浪费”的同情心而被排斥。 \n\n逃离首都荒原，你寻求建立一个尊重里昂愿景的新篇章：一个为人类服务而不仅仅是保留过去的兄弟会。你携带的装备比标准的兄弟会部署要少，但你的理想依然坚定不移。</FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.label>里昂的骄傲遗迹</FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.scenario.parts.10.text>莱昂斯长老告诉你，如果技术不能为人民服务，那么技术就毫无意义。他的女儿莎拉带领你参战，不是为了神器，而是为了生命。\n\n现在，正统兄弟会已经收复了首都废土，他们的队伍中没有“里昂的感伤主义者”的容身之地。你带着他的教诲和太多艰难选择的伤痕逃往东方。\n\n谱写新的篇章。证明兄弟会可以成为希望的灯塔，而不仅仅是过去的避难所。</FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.scenario.parts.10.text>
  <FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.scenario.summary>三名里昂骄傲老兵一开始就怀有人道主义理想，但兄弟会资源有限。证明同情心和技术可以共存。</FCP_BoS_Lyons_Remnants.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.description>Your squad was dispatched from Lost Hills to investigate reports of advanced pre-war technology in this region. The vertibird crashed during a storm, scattering your equipment across the wasteland. As knights and scribes of the 钢铁兄弟会, your mission is clear: secure the technology, establish a forward operating base, and bring order to the chaos.\n\nThe Brotherhood's tenets guide you - preserve technology, maintain discipline, and never forget the mistakes of the past.</FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.description>
  <FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.label>钢铁兄弟会</FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.scenario.parts.14.text>The vertibird's warning klaxons are still ringing in your ears as you pull yourself from the wreckage. Your mission to investigate pre-war technology sites has taken an unexpected turn.\n\nYou are 钢铁兄弟会. Knights, scribes, and initiates bound by the Codex. Your duty is clear: secure technology, establish order, and ensure the mistakes of the 老旧 World are never repeated.\n\nSteel be with you, Brothers and Sisters.</FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.scenario.parts.14.text>
  <FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.scenario.summary>Four 钢铁兄弟会 operatives crash-land with minimal supplies. Establish a chapter and fulfill your technological mandate.</FCP_BoS_Main_Chapter.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.description>You are the survivors of the 隐蔽 Valley bunker, the remnants of a once-proud Brotherhood chapter brought low by Elder Elijah's obsession and the NCR's relentless pressure. After years of isolation and dwindling resources, your bunker has finally been compromised. Scattered and desperate, you've emerged into the wasteland with what little equipment you could salvage. The 老旧 Brotherhood doctrine of technological preservation seems like a luxury when survival is uncertain. Can you rebuild the Mojave chapter's strength, or will you fade into the desert like so many others before you?</FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.description>
  <FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.label>Mojave 钢铁兄弟会</FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.scenario.parts.12.text>The 隐蔽 Valley bunker that once sheltered you is now a tomb of metal and failed dreams. Elder Elijah's obsession with the Sierra Madre, the schism with the NCR, years of isolation - it all led to this moment of desperate exodus. You carry what little you could salvage: worn recon armor, a handful of energy weapons, and the bitter knowledge of what the Brotherhood once was. The Mojave sun beats down mercilessly, but it's nothing compared to the weight of rebuilding from ashes. The 老旧 ways failed. Perhaps it's time to forge new ones.</FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.scenario.parts.12.text>
  <FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.scenario.summary>Four Brotherhood survivors emerge from the 废墟ed 隐蔽 Valley bunker with limited supplies and worn equipment. Rebuild from the ashes of Elijah's legacy.</FCP_BoS_Mojave_Chapter.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>你们是被放逐者——当里昂长老软弱时，你们拒绝放弃法典的真正信徒。虽然他浪费了资源来保护废土居民，但你仍然致力于兄弟会的真正使命：获取和保护技术。\n\n经过多年的冲突和最终以不利条件重新统一，你已经开始寻找一个法典仍然是法律的地方。你从先进的设备和技术知识开始，但你的强硬立场使外交......充满挑战。</FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>被遗弃者的残余</FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.scenario.parts.14.text>该法典很明确：技术必须得到保存、控制，并防止被滥用。里昂长老背叛了这项神圣的职责，将兄弟会的生命和资源浪费在毫无价值的废土上。\n\n你们是被遗弃者 - 真正的兄弟会。当其他人妥协时，你坚守阵地。现在你将建立一个记住兄弟会本意的章节。\n\n让技术囤积者认为你无情。历史会证明你是对的。</FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.scenario.parts.14.text>
  <FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.scenario.summary>三名被遗弃的特工，装备先进，但社交技能较差。技术超越一切。</FCP_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_Scenario_Enclave.description>You are operatives of the 英克雷, the shadow government of pre-war America. Armed with advanced technology and an unwavering belief in genetic superiority, you've been tasked with establishing a new outpost to further the 英克雷's vision of a pure America. The wasteland is filled with mutants and degenerates - it is your duty to cleanse it.</FCP_Scenario_Enclave.description>
  <FCP_Scenario_Enclave.label>The 英克雷</FCP_Scenario_Enclave.label>
  <FCP_Scenario_Enclave.scenario.parts.17.text>Your 英克雷 team has landed in this remote area to establish a new outpost. With your advanced technology and pure American genetics, you must civilize this wasteland and eliminate the mutant threats that plague the region.\n\nRemember: America's future depends on genetic purity and technological superiority. The 英克雷 will rise again!</FCP_Scenario_Enclave.scenario.parts.17.text>
  <FCP_Scenario_Enclave.scenario.summary>英克雷 operatives establishing a new outpost with advanced technology.</FCP_Scenario_Enclave.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.description>你的前哨基地遭到未知敌人的袭击。你的小队在深夜被派去增援，但你现在迷路了。你会努力回到 NCR 吗？或者你会留在原地，作为这片荒凉荒原的新公民生存下来？</FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.description>
  <FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.label>迷失小队</FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.label>
  <FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.scenario.parts.9.text>敌人无情。他们在夜色中悄无声息地带着刀刃和长矛而来。他们冲破了前哨站，砍杀士兵，就像他们以杀人为乐一样。\n\n只有你和你的小队逃脱了，被派去收集增援部队。\n\n在荒原上徘徊后，你会找到下一个扎营的地方。你会休息一晚，还是留下来为自己建造一个新家？</FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.scenario.parts.9.text>
  <FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.scenario.summary>Five lost s老旧iers of the New California Republic attempt to start anew.</FCP_Scenario_Lost_Squad.scenario.summary>
  <FCP_Scenario_USA_Lost_Squad.description>Stranded behind enemy lines after a failed operation, your infantry platoon must rely on teamwork and resourcefulness to survive. Cut off from support and surrounded by hostile forces, you must navigate 危险 territory, manage scarce supplies, and find a way to safety.</FCP_Scenario_USA_Lost_Squad.description>
  <FCP_Scenario_USA_Lost_Squad.label>Infantry Platoon</FCP_Scenario_USA_Lost_Squad.label>
  <FCP_Scenario_USA_Lost_Squad.scenario.parts.7.text>Stranded behind enemy lines after a failed operation, your infantry platoon must rely on teamwork and resourcefulness to survive. Cut off from support and surrounded by hostile forces, you must navigate 危险 territory, manage scarce supplies, and find a way to safety.</FCP_Scenario_USA_Lost_Squad.scenario.parts.7.text>
</LanguageData>
