<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEPD_AppleTree.description>A fake tree bearing glossy, red apples, while a myriad of different varieties exist this particular type favors warm summers and mild winters.</VFEPD_AppleTree.description>
  <VFEPD_AppleTree.label>apple tree</VFEPD_AppleTree.label>
  <VFEPD_BananaTree.description>A fake, broad-leafed, tall tropical tree adorned with a cluster of yellow, elongated berries succinctly known as bananas.</VFEPD_BananaTree.description>
  <VFEPD_BananaTree.label>banana tree</VFEPD_BananaTree.label>
  <VFEPD_BearBerryBush.description>A low-lying bush speckled with pink berries that thrives in poor, even sandy soil. This one is fake.</VFEPD_BearBerryBush.description>
  <VFEPD_BearBerryBush.label>bearberry bush</VFEPD_BearBerryBush.label>
  <VFEPD_Beet.description>A fake herb-like vegetable widely cultivated for humans and livestock alike, notably nutritious and historically used in dye making.</VFEPD_Beet.description>
  <VFEPD_Beet.label>beet</VFEPD_Beet.label>
  <VFEPD_Cabbage.description>A fake somewhat hardy, leafy green vegetable, often chopped and then fermented or stewed.</VFEPD_Cabbage.description>
  <VFEPD_Cabbage.label>cabbage</VFEPD_Cabbage.label>
  <VFEPD_CherryTree.description>A fake tree bearing tiny purple-red sweet cherries.</VFEPD_CherryTree.description>
  <VFEPD_CherryTree.label>cherry tree</VFEPD_CherryTree.label>
  <VFEPD_Eggplant.description>A fake bulbous purple fruit of the nightshade family. Eggplant is rarely served as a side, generally filling the role of the main component of the dish.</VFEPD_Eggplant.description>
  <VFEPD_Eggplant.label>eggplant</VFEPD_Eggplant.label>
  <VFEPD_Onion.description>A fake edible bulb of pungent, savory taste and smell with almost as many varieties as cooking applications.</VFEPD_Onion.description>
  <VFEPD_Onion.label>onion</VFEPD_Onion.label>
  <VFEPD_Opuntia.description>More often referred to as the “prickly pear” cactus, this plant is known to be quite bountiful even in hot, dry deserts. This one is fake.</VFEPD_Opuntia.description>
  <VFEPD_Opuntia.label>opuntia</VFEPD_Opuntia.label>
  <VFEPD_OrangeTree.description>A fake, bushy, semi-tropical tree dotted with orange fruits well equipped for growing in humid environments and in wet soil.</VFEPD_OrangeTree.description>
  <VFEPD_OrangeTree.label>orange tree</VFEPD_OrangeTree.label>
  <VFEPD_PeachTree.description>A fake deciduous tree bearing fuzzy, stone fruit known as peaches, peach trees often require full sunlight and warm temperatures.</VFEPD_PeachTree.description>
  <VFEPD_PeachTree.label>peach tree</VFEPD_PeachTree.label>
  <VFEPD_PearTree.description>A fake stout tree bearing crispy green pears, pear trees are notable for requiring high amounts of water and cool weather, and also doing quite well in shade.</VFEPD_PearTree.description>
  <VFEPD_PearTree.label>pear tree</VFEPD_PearTree.label>
  <VFEPD_Peas.description>Fake spherical green seeds tucked safely away in a fleshy pod. Pea plants are known to be quite thirsty, and will benefit greatly from rainfall.</VFEPD_Peas.description>
  <VFEPD_Peas.label>pea</VFEPD_Peas.label>
  <VFEPD_Pepper.description>Fake, tiny, spicy, crimson pods often used in sauces, relishes, or powders.</VFEPD_Pepper.description>
  <VFEPD_Pepper.label>pepper</VFEPD_Pepper.label>
  <VFEPD_PlumTree.description>A fake bushy tree bearing a smooth-skinned purple fruit.</VFEPD_PlumTree.description>
  <VFEPD_PlumTree.label>plum tree</VFEPD_PlumTree.label>
  <VFEPD_Pumpkin.description>Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest. These ones are fake.</VFEPD_Pumpkin.description>
  <VFEPD_Pumpkin.label>pumpkin</VFEPD_Pumpkin.label>
  <VFEPD_Tomato.description>A series of juicy, glossy red fruits attached by vine, used commonly as a vegetable. These ones are fake.</VFEPD_Tomato.description>
  <VFEPD_Tomato.label>tomato</VFEPD_Tomato.label>
</LanguageData>
