<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEPD_Aerodrone.description>Aerodrone is a spacer-tech, unmanned aerial vehicle equipped with advanced sensors and a missile payload. Non-functional.</VFEPD_Aerodrone.description>
  <VFEPD_Aerodrone.label>aerodrone</VFEPD_Aerodrone.label>
  <VFEPD_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>A large, overcharged aerodrone battery. Non-functional.</VFEPD_AerodroneBatteryPack.description>
  <VFEPD_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>aerodrone battery pack</VFEPD_AerodroneBatteryPack.label>
  <VFEPD_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>A large military crate of aerodrone munitions. Upon closer inspection, all the missiles are fake plastic ones.</VFEPD_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.description>
  <VFEPD_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>aerodrone munitions crate</VFEPD_AerodroneMunitionsCrate.label>
  <VFEPD_AmmoBox_Autocannon.description>A small-sized box containing autocannon ammunition. Used by Palintone turrets to reload. Upon closer inspection this box seems to be just filled with plastic slugs.</VFEPD_AmmoBox_Autocannon.description>
  <VFEPD_AmmoBox_Autocannon.label>autocannon ammo box</VFEPD_AmmoBox_Autocannon.label>
  <VFEPD_AmmoBox_Missile.description>A small-sized box containing missiles. Used by Onager turrets to reload. Upon closer inspection this box seems to be just filled with plastic missiles.</VFEPD_AmmoBox_Missile.description>
  <VFEPD_AmmoBox_Missile.label>missile ammo box</VFEPD_AmmoBox_Missile.label>
  <VFEPD_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.description>A small-sized box containing uranium slug ammunition. Used by Kontarion turrets to reload. May explode when damaged. Upon closer inspection this box seems to be just filled with plastic slugs.</VFEPD_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.description>
  <VFEPD_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.label>uranium slug ammo box</VFEPD_AmmoBox_UraniumSlug.label>
  <VFEPD_BiosecuredCrate.description>A small imperial crate containing extremely valuable items. Sealed shut.</VFEPD_BiosecuredCrate.description>
  <VFEPD_BiosecuredCrate.label>biosecured crate</VFEPD_BiosecuredCrate.label>
  <VFEPD_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>A deserter device capable of intercepting imperial communication. Seems to be inactive.</VFEPD_BurnoutIntelScraper.description>
  <VFEPD_BurnoutIntelScraper.label>burnout intel scraper</VFEPD_BurnoutIntelScraper.label>
  <VFEPD_DeserterShuttle.description>A spacer-tech shuttle designed for transit between surface and orbit, or between moons of a planetary system. This one seems to be non-functional.</VFEPD_DeserterShuttle.description>
  <VFEPD_DeserterShuttle.label>deserter shuttle</VFEPD_DeserterShuttle.label>
  <VFEPD_FuelTank.description>A large fuel tank used to refuel Imperial shuttles. Completely empty.</VFEPD_FuelTank.description>
  <VFEPD_FuelTank.label>fuel tank</VFEPD_FuelTank.label>
  <VFEPD_ImperialMaxpack.description>The Imperial maxpack is a formidable armored transport truck, known for its impressive cargo capacity. This one seems to be non-functional.</VFEPD_ImperialMaxpack.description>
  <VFEPD_ImperialMaxpack.label>imperial maxpack</VFEPD_ImperialMaxpack.label>
  <VFEPD_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>An advanced shielding apparatus. Seems to be inactive.</VFEPD_ImperialMegaHighShield.description>
  <VFEPD_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>imperial mega high-shield</VFEPD_ImperialMegaHighShield.label>
  <VFEPD_ImperialUnderfarm.description>An underground hydroponics basic used by the empire to feed their subjects. Upon closer inspection it is disconnected from the water mains and all its plants are made of plastic.</VFEPD_ImperialUnderfarm.description>
  <VFEPD_ImperialUnderfarm.label>imperial underfarm</VFEPD_ImperialUnderfarm.label>
  <VFEPD_SupplyCrate.description>A small imperial crate containing valuables. Sealed shut.</VFEPD_SupplyCrate.description>
  <VFEPD_SupplyCrate.label>supply crate</VFEPD_SupplyCrate.label>
  <VFEPD_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>An imperial computer interface. This one is disconnected from the grid.</VFEPD_SurveillanceDisplayBank.description>
  <VFEPD_SurveillanceDisplayBank.label>surveillance display bank</VFEPD_SurveillanceDisplayBank.label>
  <VFEPD_SurveillancePillar.description>A large pillar with a series of sensors, cameras and motion detectors. Seems to be inactive.</VFEPD_SurveillancePillar.description>
  <VFEPD_SurveillancePillar.label>surveillance pillar</VFEPD_SurveillancePillar.label>
  <VFEPD_SurveillanceStation.description>A large console designed to link to surrounding surveillance pillars. This one is disconnected from the grid.</VFEPD_SurveillanceStation.description>
  <VFEPD_SurveillanceStation.label>surveillance console</VFEPD_SurveillanceStation.label>
  <VFEPD_TechiteDiscStack.description>A compact stack of discs crafted from the enigmatic element known as techite, produced exclusively by the Empire for knowledge transcribing. These are all blank.</VFEPD_TechiteDiscStack.description>
  <VFEPD_TechiteDiscStack.label>techite disc stack</VFEPD_TechiteDiscStack.label>
  <VFEPD_Techprinter.description>The Techprinter is a marvel of technological innovation, designed to capture and preserve the intricate knowledge residing within a techfriar’s mind. This one is disconnected from the grid.</VFEPD_Techprinter.description>
  <VFEPD_Techprinter.label>techprinter</VFEPD_Techprinter.label>
  <VFEPD_WaterMain.description>A large node connecting all the nearby water mains. Upon closer inspection it is disconnected from the water grid.</VFEPD_WaterMain.description>
  <VFEPD_WaterMain.label>water main</VFEPD_WaterMain.label>
  <VFEPD_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.description>A capacitor bank that transforms electricity into raw energy for the Zeus cannon. Seems to be inactive.</VFEPD_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.description>
  <VFEPD_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>zeus cannon capacitor bank</VFEPD_ZeusCannonCapacitorBank.label>
  <VFEPD_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>This terminal serves as the primary interface for operating the Zeus Cannon batteries. Seems to be inactive.</VFEPD_ZeusCannonControlStation.description>
  <VFEPD_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>zeus cannon control station</VFEPD_ZeusCannonControlStation.label>
  <VFEPD_ZeusCannonStatic.description>A relic of ancient Sophiamundan technology, the Zeus Cannon is a closely guarded secret of the Empire. Wait, what is this? It's... made of cardboard!</VFEPD_ZeusCannonStatic.description>
  <VFEPD_ZeusCannonStatic.label>static zeus cannon</VFEPD_ZeusCannonStatic.label>
</LanguageData>
