<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Crashlanded.description>你們的飛艇在荒原上空解體，你們三人勉強生還。殘骸將補給品散落在沙漠各處，現在您有機會將飛艇墜毀地點變成家園。</Crashlanded.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.summary>三名倖存者，一艘墜毀的飛艇，還有一名在荒地上開槍。</Crashlanded.scenario.summary>
  <LostTribe.description>你們的部落被鋼鐵戰爭機器燒毀，只有你們五個人帶著能攜帶的東西逃了出來。現在你必須讓舊的方式保持足夠長的時間，以便用灰塵、骨頭和廢料建造一個新家。

注意：你一開始貧窮、飢餓，並且遠遠落後於廢物的技術。這是一個困難的情況。</LostTribe.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.summary>被毀部落的五名倖存者試圖僅憑傳統和勇氣進行重建。難的。</LostTribe.scenario.summary>
  <NakedBrutality.description>有人剝光你的衣服，搶劫你的衣服，把你赤裸裸地丟在荒地裡等死。沒有裝備，沒有食物，沒有盟友，甚至沒有刀。如果你經歷了這一切，那將是因為你拒絕成為腐肉。

警告：這種情況是極度不公平的。死亡可能來得很快，而且出於愚蠢的原因。</NakedBrutality.description>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>一名赤裸裸的廢土人身無分文地等死。極度困難且不公平。</NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>
  <TheRichExplorer.description>你出生在金庫門後面，周圍都是安全、柔軟的床和舊世界的謊言。你沒有埋在地下，而是帶著最好的裝備去尋找真正的荒地。現在，你的吊艙已經把你扔到了遠離任何友好道路的地方，只剩下避難所補給，沒有人來拯救你。

注意：強大的裝備並不能掩蓋所有的弱點。這是一個特別困難的早期遊戲場景。</TheRichExplorer.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>一名裝備精良的避難所居民追逐的是真正的荒地而不是故事。特難。</TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>
  <TheGravship.description>您的 Helixen 是一架戰前 REPCONN 飛機，停靠在軌道中繼站。當你的船員開始搶救其係統時，你意識到這不是普通的戰前緩存——它是一個機器人信標。中繼器發出劈啪聲，並向遠處的機器人指揮中心廣播戰爭警報。他們現在正在追捕你，無論你走到哪裡，他們最終都會找到你。

注意：這是一個困難的場景，不建議新玩家使用。</TheGravship.description>
  <TheGravship.label>螺旋森</TheGravship.label>
  <TheGravship.scenario.summary>Helixen 號上的三名船員被機器人追捕。</TheGravship.scenario.summary>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>此啟動已被 Sunset 停用。</VFEM2_NewKingdom.description>
  <VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>殘障新王國</VFEM2_NewKingdom.label>
  <VFES_Bandits.description>此定居者場景已被日落禁用。</VFES_Bandits.description>
  <VFES_Bandits.label>殘疾土匪</VFES_Bandits.label>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.description>A wandering band of super mutants has broken from the chaos of the wasteland, bringing with them a cache of refined FEV doses, and just enough salvaged knowledge to attempt recreating the transformation process.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.label>Forced Evolution</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.label>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.customSummary>Start with one first-generation super mutant and two second-generation super mutants.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.customSummary>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.0.description>first-generation super mutant</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.0.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.1.description>second-generation super mutant</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.0.xenotypeCounts.1.description>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.2.text>The facility burned long before you escaped it. What remained were ruined vats, sealed notes, and three living proofs that West Tek got further than anyone should have allowed.

Now the old bunker is gone, the masters are dead, and your little mutie cadre is alone in the wasteland with a little FEV and just enough knowledge to restart the work. Whether that becomes a refuge, an army, or another atrocity is up to you.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.parts.2.text>
  <WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.summary>One first-generation super mutant, two second-generation super mutants, and some FEV.</WestTek_ForcedEvolution.scenario.summary>
  <Sanguophage.description>古老的故事將像你們這樣的生物稱為溫迪戈：飢餓的生物比它們曾經的人類壽命更長。不管發生了什麼，你現在背負著這個詛咒。被獵殺、半野性、從未真正吃飽的你，在錯誤的人抓住你之前逃進了荒野。

注意：溫迪戈擁有獨特的優勢和殘酷的弱點，這使得這個場景變得困難。</Sanguophage.description>
  <Sanguophage.label>溫迪戈</Sanguophage.label>
  <Sanguophage.scenario.summary>一名被獵殺的溫迪戈，一名人類同伴，以及永不休止的飢餓。</Sanguophage.scenario.summary>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.description>Your Brotherhood expeditionary group has stumbled upon an old bunker, a potential haven. But with the valuable intel you carry, the Whitespring Enclave's visibility on you is alarmingly high. Vertibots patrol the skies, and Whitespring raiding parties are closing in. Use the intel to unlock powerful tech and Brotherhood expeditionary services, aiding your ultimate mission: to assassinate key Whitespring officials. Survive the initial onslaught and lay low; over time, the Whitespring Enclave's relentless search will wane. The choice is yours: fortify, adapt, or perish.\n\nNote: Since you start with high visibility, this is a difficult scenario.</VFED_NewSafehaven.description>
  <VFED_NewSafehaven.label>Brotherhood of Steel Expedition</VFED_NewSafehaven.label>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.description>It was supposed to be another quiet night for your Whitespring splinter cell, tucked away in a secluded estate far from the main administrative halls. You do not know whether the blackout was caused by Brotherhood sabotage, a compromised security officer, or a simple systems failure, but when the perimeter defenses died at midnight your enclave cell was left blind and exposed. By the time the gates opened, there was no time to organize a proper response - only to hide and survive.
You heard your officers, researchers, and support staff being cut down as the Brotherhood expeditionary strike team swept through the compound. Whatever remained of your old command structure died with them. Now your splinter cell is shattered, your safehouse is burning, and revenge will mean nothing unless you escape this raid alive. You can wait the assault out, use permits to call for reinforcements, or try running for the hills - the choice is yours.
Note: Since you start during a raid in progress, this is a difficult scenario.</VFEE_NewFamily.description>
  <VFEE_NewFamily.label>New Splinter Cell</VFEE_NewFamily.label>
</LanguageData>
