<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<LanguageData>
  <VQE_Deadlife_AncientSilo.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==True)-&gt;[asker_nameDef], [asker_faction_leaderTitle] of [asker_faction_name], has informed us of the location of a sealed entrance to one of the continuity bunkers left behind by an old U.S. military emergency command network.

These bunkers were designed to remain sealed for generations, storing the resources needed to rebuild after total collapse. Inside, there should be preserved supplies, old war stockpiles, and command records from the final days before the bombs.

But the bunkers are not empty. The halls below are lightless, and reports speak of feral ghouls stalking the corridors. Restoring power and lights will be essential if we intend to survive the descent.

Somewhere inside should also be command desks and strategic maps that can reveal the location of other bunkers, and perhaps even the central command site where the officers who ran this network made their last stand.

Secure a meaningful share of the bunker's stored resources to complete the operation.</VQE_Deadlife_AncientSilo.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <VQE_Deadlife_AncientSilo.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription(askerIsNull==True)-&gt;Recovered military maps have revealed the location of a sealed continuity bunker built by an old U.S. military emergency command network.

These bunkers were designed to remain closed until after total societal collapse, preserving supplies, weapons, and command infrastructure for whatever remained above.

The corridors below are reported to be completely dark, and feral ghouls are said to roam the interior. Restoring power and lights quickly will be critical.

Command tables inside may point us toward other bunkers and, eventually, the central command site that coordinated the network.

Secure a meaningful share of the bunker's stored resources to complete the operation.</VQE_Deadlife_AncientSilo.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <VQE_Deadlife_AncientICBMLaunchSite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;We have intercepted a broadcast at a recently raided underground silo: Operation: Deadlife is now underway. Enough resource bunkers have been breached, and the final launch sequence has begun. The transmission confirms that [General_nameFull] has started final preparations at an ancient ICBM launch site.

Refueling of the missiles is already in progress. These warheads are loaded with deadlife dust payloads and, if fired, they will burst high over the planet and spread a near-permanent pall that raises the dead as feral ghouls. Endless ghoul hordes would then overrun the surface and finish what the war started.

We have traced the signal to the launch facility. We must travel there and stop [General_nameFull] before the countdown is completed. The site is expected to be heavily defended, not only by feral ghouls, but also by restored automated defenses.

From the control room, [General_nameFull] will trigger sealed death pits, release feral ghoul packs from containment kennels, flood the complex with rotstink gas, and wake preserved officers from cryogenic caskets.

Only by reaching and destroying the launch terminal can we stop the missiles from firing. Failure to stop the launch in time, or ignoring the threat entirely, will condemn the planet to a global ghoul apocalypse.

This is our only chance to end Operation: Deadlife once and for all.</VQE_Deadlife_AncientICBMLaunchSite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
</LanguageData>