<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.description>A democratic settlement in the Nuevo Texico wasteland, where Texan frontier culture and Mexican border tradition have been forged together over two centuries of post-war survival. The Brotherhood of Steel has maintained a presence in the region since the Lone Star chapter established operations in former Texas, and many settlements here have a working relationship with the Brotherhood — whether as trading partners, protectorates, or neighbors who keep the peace by staying out of each other's way.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.label>civil Nuevo Texico settlement</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Civil.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.description>A raider gang operating across the wide-open scrubland and flatlands of Nuevo Texico. They hit trade convoys and isolated homesteads, moving fast across terrain that offers little cover for either prey or pursuer. Their style reflects the region — bold, loud, and accustomed to living rough in dry country far from the centers of any real power.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.label>Texico raider</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Raider.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.description>An autocratic settlement in Nuevo Texico, run by a boss, patriarch, or council of hard-minded locals who answer to no outside authority. The culture is a direct hybrid of Texan and northern Mexican traditions: disputes are settled openly, authority is earned and demonstrated, and both the Brotherhood of Steel and any passing raider gang are assessed on the same pragmatic terms.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.label>rough Nuevo Texico settlement</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Rough.label>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.description>A tribal community in Nuevo Texico, with roots in the ranching families, indigenous groups, and border communities that survived the war in the hill country and badlands. They carry a culture shaped by Spanish, Mexican, and Texan heritage, worn into something distinctly their own. The Brotherhood of Steel's regional presence is a practical reality they navigate carefully, trading with some chapters and avoiding others entirely.</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.description>
  <HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.label>Texico tribe</HHTools_NuevoTexico_Tribal.label>
</LanguageData>
