<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.description>The 钢铁兄弟会 operates under the strict tenets of the Codex, a sacred doctrine that demands the preservation and control of advanced technology. Under Elder Maxson, the Brotherhood has united the ideals of both the Outcasts' technological zealotry and Lyons' willingness to engage with outsiders - but on the Brotherhood's terms. Technology must be controlled, mutants and synths are abominations to be destroyed, and only through discipline and hierarchy can humanity be saved from itself. The Brotherhood is both shield and sword - protecting humanity while ensuring 危险 technology never falls into the wrong hands.</FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.description>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.label>法典至上</FCP_Meme_BoS_Codex_Supremacy.label>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.description>Paladins are the Brotherhood's elite warriors, clad in power armor and wielding the most advanced weapons. They are the tip of the spear in any Brotherhood operation, trained to engage the most 危险 threats head-on. A Paladin's duty is to lead from the front, inspire their squadmates, and demonstrate the Brotherhood's martial superiority.</FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.description>
  <FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.label>钢铁圣骑士</FCP_Meme_BoS_Paladins.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.description>Lost Hills represents the original 钢铁兄弟会 - the purest interpretation of the Codex as written by Roger Maxson himself. Technology must be preserved at any cost, outsiders are never to be trusted, and the Brotherhood's bloodlines must remain pure. Isolation is strength. The wasteland may burn, but the Brotherhood will endure, guarding humanity's technological legacy until the world is ready to rebuild - on Brotherhood terms.</FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.label>永恒法典</FCP_Meme_Lost_Hills_Codex_Eternal.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.description>The Shield of the People represents everything the Lyons Pride stands for - warriors who protect the innocent and fight for those who cannot fight for themselves. They combine Brotherhood combat prowess with genuine compassion, serving as both s老旧iers and humanitarian workers.</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.label>人民之盾</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Shield.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.description>莱昂斯长老教导说，如果技术不能为人民服务，那么技术就毫无价值。里昂骄傲队相信兄弟会不仅仅是收藏家和囤积者，他们还必须是保护者和建设者。尽管仍然受到法典技术智慧的约束，但他们拒绝其孤立主义。技术应该被保留，但也应该被用来帮助那些有需要的人。这片荒原不需要另一群技术囤积者；它需要守护者明白，拯救人类意味着真正帮助人类，而不仅仅是保护文物。</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.label>钢铁般的同情心</FCP_Meme_Lyons_Steel_Compassion.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.description>The Midwestern Brotherhood emerged from the wreckage of their crashed airships with a revolutionary understanding: survival demands adaptation. Unlike the isolationists at Lost Hills, the Midwest chapter actively recruits tribals, wastelanders, and even former enemies into their ranks. Technology still matters, but so does building an army capable of h老旧ing territory and protecting the people within it. The Codex is a guide, not a chain. Expansion is not corruption - it is evolution.</FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.label>钢铁先锋</FCP_Meme_Midwest_Steel_Vanguard.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.description>防御者是被遗弃的专家，他们将卓越的技术知识与战斗能力结合起来。他们负责从敌对势力那里获取技术，并确保先进设备不会落入不值得的人手中。他们对使命的奉献是绝对的。</FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.label>法典的捍卫者</FCP_Meme_Outcast_Defenders.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.description>The Outcasts are the Brotherhood's purists - those who refused to compromise the Codex when Elder Lyons went soft. Technology is everything. It's not about helping wastelanders or building communities; it's about preserving humanity's technological legacy before fools destroy it all. The 老旧 World fell because people misused technology - the Brotherhood's sacred duty is to prevent that from happening again by controlling every piece of advanced tech in existence. Outsiders are liabilities at best, threats at worst. Only through absolute dedication to the mission can the Brotherhood fulfill its purpose.</FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.label>真正的法典</FCP_Meme_Outcast_True_Codex.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Legionism.description>我们的人民应该统治其他所有人。</FCP_Meme_Legionism.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Legionism.label>强权即公理</FCP_Meme_Legionism.label>
  <FCP_Meme_EnclaveManifestDestiny.description>The 英克雷 represents the continuation of the United States government, destined to reclaim and restore America. Only pure, untainted humans have the right to rebuild civilization. All others are aberrations to be removed or subjugated.</FCP_Meme_EnclaveManifestDestiny.description>
  <FCP_Meme_EnclaveManifestDestiny.label>英克雷 Manifest Destiny</FCP_Meme_EnclaveManifestDestiny.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Khan_Chemists.description>大可汗完善了化学生产艺术。他们的化学家是部落中受人尊敬的成员，负责制造为可汗的行动提供资金的药物。熟练的化学制造者价值相当于银子，他们的知识代代相传。</FCP_Meme_Khan_Chemists.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Khan_Chemists.label>可汗化学家</FCP_Meme_Khan_Chemists.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Khan_Freedom.description>大汗们拒绝接受“文明”社会的枷锁——没有法律，没有税收，除了他们中最强大的人之外没有统治者。他们重视个人自由高于一切，但随着自由而来的是对部落的责任。强者受到尊重，弱者受到鄙视，对兄弟姐妹的忠诚是神圣的。可汗们不会因为夺取他们所需要的东西而道歉——这片荒地属于那些强大到足以占领它的人。</FCP_Meme_Khan_Freedom.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Khan_Freedom.label>可汗自由</FCP_Meme_Khan_Freedom.label>
  <FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.description>Once loyal to the New California Republic, these individuals have turned their backs on the 老旧 world order. Disillusioned by corruption and endless war, they now value survival, independence, and camaraderie above all else. They are wary of authority, skeptical of grand ideals, and quick to defend their own. Their code is one of mutual aid, hard-earned trust, and doing what it takes to survive in the wasteland.</FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.description>
  <FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.label>NCR 逃兵</FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.label>
  <FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.description>The New California Republic (NCR) is a federal presidential republic founded in New California, comprised of five contiguous states and additional territorial h老旧ings in Nevada and Baja California. The NCR emphasizes and strives to support a myriad of 老旧 world values, such as democracy, personal liberty, and the rule of law. It also aims to restore general order to the wasteland, the improvement and development of infrastructure and economic systems, and overarching peace between people. Similar to institutions of the 老旧 world it seeks to emulate, continued expansion has created challenges with territorial control, loyalty, and corruption that plague the Republic and serve to hinder its goals.</FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.description>
  <FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.label>老旧 World Blues</FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Rangers.description>游骑兵是一支志愿特种部队，因其专业侦察能力、勇敢和战斗能力而闻名，其主要目的是应对共和国常备军无法应对的威胁，以及在 NCR 领土边界周围进行一般维和、侦察已知和潜在威胁以及执行其他特殊任务。他们先进的训练、武器装备以及战前和战后的技术组合常常使他们能够成为共和国冲突中取得胜利的关键，即使在情况下他们可能在数量和武器上处于劣势。</FCP_Meme_Rangers.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Rangers.label>NCR流浪者队</FCP_Meme_Rangers.label>
  <FCP_Meme_YearOfTheDragon.description>龙年意识形态重视民族团结、集体努力和技术进步。它鼓励对国家的忠诚、对传统的尊重以及对文化遗产的自豪感。广大人民群众要齐心协力，为国家谋福利，维护社会和谐，勇于创新，相信团结一致就能繁荣富强。</FCP_Meme_YearOfTheDragon.description>
  <FCP_Meme_YearOfTheDragon.label>龙年</FCP_Meme_YearOfTheDragon.label>
  <FCP_Meme_TheAmericanDream.description>美国梦是繁荣、自由和无限机会的光辉承诺，点燃了全国数百万人的希望。这些年来，人们的愿景是白色尖桩篱笆、两车位车库和原子能驱动的未来。家人聚集在发光的电视旁，相信辛勤工作和爱国主义可以确保他们在一个不断进步的世界中占据一席之地。乐观情绪高涨，梦想作为美国能够实现的目标的灯塔而持久——对更光明明天的坚定信念。然而，在乐观情绪的背后，裂痕已经形成——企业的贪婪、资源短缺和战争的阴影。尽管如此，即使世界在遗忘的边缘摇摇欲坠，梦想仍然存在，成为美国应有的灯塔。</FCP_Meme_TheAmericanDream.description>
  <FCP_Meme_TheAmericanDream.label>美国梦</FCP_Meme_TheAmericanDream.label>
</LanguageData>
