<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Culture_BoS.description>The Brotherhood of Steel maintains strict military discipline and a reverence for pre-war technology. Members follow the Codex, value the chain of command, and see themselves as preservers of knowledge in a barbaric world.</FCP_Culture_BoS.description>
  <FCP_Culture_BoS.label>Brotherhood of Steel chapter</FCP_Culture_BoS.label>
  <FCP_Culture_BoS_Outcasts.description>The Outcasts are purists who rejected Elder Lyons' deviation from the Codex. They are utterly dedicated to acquiring and preserving technology, viewing outsiders as obstacles at best. The mission is everything.</FCP_Culture_BoS_Outcasts.description>
  <FCP_Culture_BoS_Outcasts.label>Brotherhood of Steel Outcasts</FCP_Culture_BoS_Outcasts.label>
  <FCP_Culture_Lyons_BoS.description>Elder Lyons' chapter broke from the Codex to help the people of the Capital Wasteland. His followers combine Brotherhood discipline with compassion, believing that technology should serve humanity, not be hoarded from it.</FCP_Culture_Lyons_BoS.description>
  <FCP_Culture_Lyons_BoS.label>Brotherhood of Steel Lyons</FCP_Culture_Lyons_BoS.label>
  <FCP_Culture_Legion_NeoRoman.description>Description</FCP_Culture_Legion_NeoRoman.description>
  <FCP_Culture_Legion_NeoRoman.label>neo-roman</FCP_Culture_Legion_NeoRoman.label>
  <FCP_Culture_Enclave.description>The Enclave represents the remnants of the pre-war United States government, embodying a culture of technological superiority, strict hierarchy, and unwavering loyalty to their vision of a purified America. Members of the Enclave are deeply committed to their cause, often viewing themselves as the rightful inheritors of the Earth.</FCP_Culture_Enclave.description>
  <FCP_Culture_Enclave.label>Enclave</FCP_Culture_Enclave.label>
  <FCP_Culture_Khan.description>Culture of the Great Khans, a nomadic raider tribe descended from pre-war biker gangs.</FCP_Culture_Khan.description>
  <FCP_Culture_Khan.label>Khan</FCP_Culture_Khan.label>
  <FCP_Culture_NCR_Californian.description>Culture of those in the New California Republic.</FCP_Culture_NCR_Californian.description>
  <FCP_Culture_NCR_Californian.label>New Californian</FCP_Culture_NCR_Californian.label>
  <FCP_Culture_PRC_Chinese.description>Culture of those in the People's Republic of China.</FCP_Culture_PRC_Chinese.description>
  <FCP_Culture_PRC_Chinese.label>Chinese</FCP_Culture_PRC_Chinese.label>
  <FCP_Culture_Raider.description>Culture of those in the Raider Gangs.</FCP_Culture_Raider.description>
  <FCP_Culture_Raider.label>Raider</FCP_Culture_Raider.label>
  <FCP_Culture_USA_American.description>Culture of those in the United States of America.</FCP_Culture_USA_American.description>
  <FCP_Culture_USA_American.label>American</FCP_Culture_USA_American.label>
  <FCP_Culture_Wastelander.description>Survivors of the post-apocalyptic wasteland, scrapers and scavengers trying to rebuild civilization from the ruins.</FCP_Culture_Wastelander.description>
  <FCP_Culture_Wastelander.label>Wastelander</FCP_Culture_Wastelander.label>
</LanguageData>
