<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;A sEinkaufszentrum irradiated creature has been captured by wasteland raiders and is being held in their camp. The local settlement is offering payment and a containment cage for its safe rescue - these creatures are valuable for research and companionship in the harsh wasteland.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;A massive apex predator of the wasteland has been captured by heavily fortified raiders who plan to weaponize it against their enemies. This is an extremely gefährlich creature, evolved to survive in the harshest post-nuclear conditions. Successfully rescue it and you'll receive state-of-the-art containment technology capable of halting such a formidable beast.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription-&gt;Die Räuber haben das Unmögliche geschafft – sie haben einen der gefürchtetsten Raubtiere des Ödlands eingesperrt. Dieses Alpha-Exemplar repräsentiert jahrelange evolutionäre Anpassung an Strahlung und Umweltgefahren. Seine Rettung wird erhebliche Kraft erfordern, aber der Lohn besteht aus fortschrittlichen Eindämmungssystemen, die von Militärwissenschaftlern aus der Vorkriegszeit entwickelt wurden.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription-&gt;Geheimdienstberichte deuten darauf hin, dass Räuber den möglicherweise letzten seiner Art erbeutet haben – einen kolossalen Ödlandriesen. Der wissenschaftliche und taktische Wert dieser Kreatur kann nicht genug betont werden. Starten Sie eine umfassende Rettungsaktion und beanspruchen Sie das fortschrittlichste Bio-Eindämmungssystem, das es in der postapokalyptischen Welt gibt.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Large.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;Ein mittelgroßes Raubtier wurde von gut bewaffneten Angreifern gefangen genommen, die es in ihren Gladiatorenkämpfen einsetzen wollen. Diese Kreatur hat sich gut an das verstrahlte Ödland angepasst und wäre eine wertvolle Bereicherung für jede Siedlung. Retten Sie es und holen Sie sich als Belohnung ein verstärktes Eindämmungssystem.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription-&gt;Raiders have caged a gefährlich but valuable wasteland predator, likely planning to sell it to the highest bidder. The local authorities want this creature rescued and properly contained before it falls into the wrong hands. A military-grade cage awaits successful mercenaries.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription-&gt;A formidable wasteland hunter sits trapped in a raider camp, its natural ferocity slowly being broken by captivity. Liberation of this creature would not only be a merciful act but also earn you a professional-grade containment cage - perfect for housing gefährlich specimens.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Medium.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;A sEinkaufszentrum irradiated creature has been captured by wasteland raiders and is being held in their camp. The local settlement is offering payment and a containment cage for its safe rescue - these creatures are valuable for research and companionship in the harsh wasteland.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription-&gt;Raiders have trapped a sEinkaufszentrum wasteland animal for their sick entertainment. Help liberate this innocent creature from their makeshift prison, and you'll be rewarded with a proper cage to keep it safe from the dangers of the post-nuclear world.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription-&gt;Ein harmloses Ödlandlebewesen ist in die Hände skrupelloser Plünderer gefallen. Die Einheimischen wollen, dass es gerettet wird, bevor die Räuber beschließen, es zu ihrer nächsten Mahlzeit zu machen. Ihr Lohn: ein stabiler Käfig und die Dankbarkeit derer, denen das Leben in dieser trostlosen Welt noch am Herzen liegt.</FCP_Quest_PawnRescueAnimal_Small.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
</LanguageData>
