<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Barkskin.description>A hardy caste of treeminder, the radbarkling is covered in thick, bark-like hide infused with radiation. It excels at absorbing damage in combat, protecting its tree and allies.</Barkskin.description>
  <Barkskin.label>radbarkling</Barkskin.label>
  <Berrymaker.description>A dryad caste specialized in food production, the mutfruitling generates nourishing mutfruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Berrymaker.description>
  <Berrymaker.label>mutfruitling</Berrymaker.label>
  <Carrier.description>A helpful caste of treeminder, the portling is specialized in carrying items. Under human influence, it hauls goods where they need to go, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Carrier.description>
  <Carrier.label>portling</Carrier.label>
  <Clawer.description>A fierce caste of treeminder, the scratchling is bred for aggression and damage-dealing attacks. Its oversized claws can tear through most threats, but it is vulnerable to retaliation.</Clawer.description>
  <Clawer.label>scratchling</Clawer.label>
  <Gaumaker.description>A unique caste of treeminder, the sproutling can produce new Gauranlen pods and help reproduce the treefather. Three sproutlings must slowly merge to complete the process.</Gaumaker.description>
  <Gaumaker.label>sproutling</Gaumaker.label>
  <Medicinemaker.description>A gentle caste of treeminder, the brocflowerling specializes in producing medicinal herbs. It works with its tree to generate healing plants, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Medicinemaker.description>
  <Medicinemaker.label>brocflowerling</Medicinemaker.label>
  <Pungaling.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder which specializes in pungs production. Together with its Gauranlen tree, this dryad can generate punga fruit on an ongoing basis. However, it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Pungaling.description>
  <Pungaling.label>pungaling</Pungaling.label>
  <VDE_Gaubricmaker.description>A treeminder caste specialized in producing a shaggy, leather-like hide. Together with its Treefather, it can be sheared for a soft, insulative material on an ongoing basis, though it is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</VDE_Gaubricmaker.description>
  <VDE_Nectarmaker.description>A curious treeminder caste specialized in producing invigorating sap-fruit. Together with its Treefather, it can generate this stimulant crop on an ongoing basis, but it is completely defenseless and requires careful protection.</VDE_Nectarmaker.description>
  <VDE_Spitter.description>A treeminder caste specialized in territorial defense that can launch corrosive projectiles. Though it can dish out tremendous damage, it remains vulnerable in melee due to its oversized maw.</VDE_Spitter.description>
  <VDE_Stonedigger.description>An extremely easy-going treeminder caste that specializes in dragging up stone chunks. It absorbs minerals from the ground to harden its hide while leaving the oversized pieces aside.</VDE_Stonedigger.description>
  <Woodmaker.description>A slow, bumbling caste of treeminder, the scrapwoodling specializes in producing scrap wood. Together with its Gauranlen tree, it generates wood-like material on an ongoing basis, but is slow and ineffective at work or combat.</Woodmaker.description>
  <Woodmaker.label>scrapwoodling</Woodmaker.label>
</LanguageData>