<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VFED.SurveillancePillarActivated>You have activated a Whitespring surveillance pillar. Your faction's visibility has increased by {1}. It is now {0}.</VFED.SurveillancePillarActivated>
  <VFED.IntelFromTitle>{0} has been stripped of their Whitespring rank of {1}. They have provided you with {2} Intel.</VFED.IntelFromTitle>
  <VFED.ResponseComing>Whitespring response</VFED.ResponseComing>
  <VFED.ResponseComingDesc>A Whitespring {0} is on its way to this location. It will arrive in {1}s.</VFED.ResponseComingDesc>
  <VFED.ResponseMessage>Due to triggering a Whitespring response, your visibility has increased by {0}. It is now {1}. In the future, you can avoid increasing visibility by completing the mission before the response arrives.</VFED.ResponseMessage>
  <VFED.MustHavePsylink>Must have Cryptid Insight</VFED.MustHavePsylink>
  <VFED.ExtractIntel.Desc>Extract intel from the brain of a ranked Whitespring official. They may be alive or downed, but the brain must be present. This will destroy the brain.</VFED.ExtractIntel.Desc>
  <VFED.ImperialPatrol.Desc>{0} has encountered a Whitespring patrol from {1}. They have been spotted. {0} can try to escape, but this will inevitably increase the visibility of {2}. Fighting the patrol may be dangerous, but it will keep {2} safe. The patrol consists of:\n\n{3}</VFED.ImperialPatrol.Desc>
  <VFED.ImperialPatrol.GaveUp>{0} has surrendered {1} to the Whitespring Enclave. It is unlikely you will ever see them again. Whitespring command does not take kindly to saboteurs.</VFED.ImperialPatrol.GaveUp>
  <VFED.AerodroneBombardment>Vertibot bombardment</VFED.AerodroneBombardment>
  <VFED.AerodroneBombardment.Desc>{0} has dispatched a number of Vertibots to your location. They suspect you are harboring Brotherhood expeditionaries with hostile intent toward the Whitespring Enclave.
A Vertibot is an unmanned atmospheric weapons platform designed for military suppression. Controlled from secure Whitespring installations, it is a highly effective tool for eliminating enemies of the Enclave. Equipped with advanced sensors and targeting systems, a Vertibot can detect and track targets from long distances. Once a target has been identified, it unleashes a devastating salvo of precision rockets designed to cause maximum damage and destruction.
The Whitespring Enclave has pinpointed the location of your critical infrastructure and the Vertibots will shortly begin their bombardment. Evacuation is advised.</VFED.AerodroneBombardment.Desc>
  <VFED.DivineInferno.Init>Orbital inferno initiated</VFED.DivineInferno.Init>
  <VFED.DivineInferno.Desc>The orbital beam satellites have finished arranging themselves above your colony. What follows can only be described as total destruction. The beams carve across the ground, creating a web of energy that systematically levels everything in its path. Terrain buckles and heaves as the fire slices through the earth, leaving behind deep crevices and rubble-filled craters. People, vehicles, and buildings are reduced to dust and ash in seconds. The air itself becomes superheated, creating a blast wave that can travel for miles.
There is no escape from the orbital inferno. Those caught in its path are instantly vaporized, leaving behind only charred remnants of what once stood there. Even underground shelters are no match for the destructive power of the beams.
The aftermath of the orbital inferno is a wasteland of ruin. The landscape is unrecognizable, with little more than rubble and ash as far as the eye can see. The air is thick with the smell of burnt flesh and melting metal. The once-thriving colony is now nothing more than a scorched husk.</VFED.DivineInferno.Desc>
  <VFED.GoodwillDropVisibility>Due to Whitespring disinformation, your relations with {0} have dropped by 10.</VFED.GoodwillDropVisibility>
  <VFED.VisibilityIncreases.Desc>Visibility will increase by {0}. This may lead to more and stronger Whitespring responses.</VFED.VisibilityIncreases.Desc>
  <VFED.VisibilityDecreases.Desc>Visibility will decrease by {0}. This may reduce Whitespring responses.</VFED.VisibilityDecreases.Desc>
  <VFED.BiosecuredCrateWarning>Biosecured crates can only be opened by characters with a Whitespring official backstory.</VFED.BiosecuredCrateWarning>
  <VFED.CantOpenBiosecured>requires Whitespring official backstory</VFED.CantOpenBiosecured>
  <VFED.ServiceIncreasedGoodwill>Goodwill with {0} increased by 5 due to positive rumors from Brotherhood expeditionaries.</VFED.ServiceIncreasedGoodwill>
  <VFED.NobleKilledRevenge>{0} from {1} are attempting to avenge the fallen Whitespring official {2}.</VFED.NobleKilledRevenge>
  <VFED.ContrabandArrived>Your prewar tech shipment has arrived.</VFED.ContrabandArrived>
  <VFED.BurnoutWarning>Building a burnout intel scraper will be considered a declaration of war against the Whitespring Enclave.</VFED.BurnoutWarning>
  <VFED.ActivateScraper.Desc>Enable the intel scraper countdown, which will release a pulse every 60 seconds. This gives you a chance to obtain valuable intel, but it may also trigger a Whitespring investigation.</VFED.ActivateScraper.Desc>
  <VFED.BurnoutIntelGained>Burnout intel scraper intercepted Whitespring communication and generated {0} intel.</VFED.BurnoutIntelGained>
  <VFED.BurnoutCriticalIntelGained>Burnout intel scraper intercepted high-value Whitespring communication and generated {0} critical intel.</VFED.BurnoutCriticalIntelGained>
  <VFED.BurnoutVisibilityIncreased>Burnout intel scraper attracted Whitespring attention and increased your visibility by {0}. Current visibility is {1}.</VFED.BurnoutVisibilityIncreased>
  <VFED.BurnoutRaid>Burnout intel scraper was intercepted by a Whitespring patrol nearby. They are moving in to engage.</VFED.BurnoutRaid>

  <VFED.ContactDeserters>Contact Brotherhood Network</VFED.ContactDeserters>
  <VFED.ContrabandRecieveTimeModifier>Time to receive prewar tech: </VFED.ContrabandRecieveTimeModifier>
  <VFED.ImperialResponseTime>Time for Presidential response: </VFED.ImperialResponseTime>
  <VFED.ImperialResponseType>Type of Presidential response: </VFED.ImperialResponseType>
  <VFED.ContrabandRecieveDesc>Items purchased through the prewar tech network do not arrive in your colony by cargo pods. Instead, a dead drop pickup quest becomes available after some time, and it remains active only briefly. This is where you collect the purchased prewar tech.</VFED.ContrabandRecieveDesc>
  <VFED.TimeLimitDesc>Time to receive and time to pick up depend on the amount of items you are purchasing, as well as your current visibility level. After the receive time has elapsed, a dead drop quest becomes available. It remains active only for the duration shown in 'Time to pick up'. If you fail to collect it in time, the items are gone.</VFED.TimeLimitDesc>
  <VFED.DeserterQuestDesc>This is a Brotherhood expeditionary quest. It may provide intel on the Whitespring Enclave, but it may also increase your faction's visibility.</VFED.DeserterQuestDesc>
  <VFED.QuestPurchaseDesc>You can spend intel to obtain quests from the Brotherhood network. However, you will not know what rewards a quest offers until you purchase it.</VFED.QuestPurchaseDesc>
  <VFED.Flagship>Kovac-Muldoon Platform</VFED.Flagship>

  <VFEDeserters>Brotherhood Expeditionaries</VFEDeserters>
  <VFED.VisibilityFromPillar>Visibility gain from Enclave surveillance pillar: {0}</VFED.VisibilityFromPillar>
  <VFED.ResponseTimeMultiplier>Presidential response time multiplier: {0}</VFED.ResponseTimeMultiplier>

  <VFED.EndgameText>The Whitespring Enclave, once a symbol of secrecy, privilege, and oppression, has crumbled. All over the region, Brotherhood cells and allied defectors rose in rebellion, breaking the machinery that kept the Enclave in power. Every child who now wakes to the dawn of freedom will remember the names of the people who dared to challenge the impossible:
{0}
\nHowever, this is not the end, only a transition. With the old government in ruins and the Kovac-Muldoon Platform reduced to a burning wreck in the sky, the time for healing and rebuilding has begun. Former Whitespring officials now scatter, surrender, or vanish into the wasteland. There is no denying the truth: the world has changed forever.
\nAs you stand at the threshold of that new era, you remember this chapter of defiance and sacrifice. The fall of the Whitespring Enclave will remain a testament to your resilience and to the Brotherhood's refusal to bow. You step forward into a future built on hard-won freedom, vigilance, and hope.</VFED.EndgameText>
  <VFED.EndgameWarningText>You are about to initiate the final Brotherhood operation. After the mission is complete, both the Whitespring Enclave and the Brotherhood expeditionary network will be gone. Are you sure you want to initiate the final mission?</VFED.EndgameWarningText>

</LanguageData>