<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <RB_BarriersWall.description>An impassable wall consisting of metal bars that allow water to pass through. Must be constructed in water.</RB_BarriersWall.description>
  <RB_BarriersWall.label>barriers wall</RB_BarriersWall.label>
  <RB_CellWall.description>An impassable wall consisting of metal bars.</RB_CellWall.description>
  <RB_CellWall.label>cell wall</RB_CellWall.label>
  <RB_ClerestoryWall.description>An impassable half-glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof, but more fragile than a normal wall. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_ClerestoryWall.description>
  <RB_ClerestoryWall.label>clerestory wall</RB_ClerestoryWall.label>
  <RB_GlassWall.description>An impassable glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof, but far more fragile than a normal wall. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_GlassWall.description>
  <RB_GlassWall.label>glass wall</RB_GlassWall.label>
  <RB_OrnateWall.description>An intricate and impassable wall, decorated with gold. Capable of holding up a roof, but more fragile than a normal wall. Dignity-focused psycaster will receive a meditation bonus when meditating near them.</RB_OrnateWall.description>
  <RB_OrnateWall.label>ornate wall</RB_OrnateWall.label>
  <RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.description>An impassable half-glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.description>
  <RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.label>reinforced clerestory wall</RB_ReinforcedClerestoryWall.label>
  <RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.description>An impassable reinforced glass wall. Capable of holding up a roof. Does not block light, providing a growing bonus to plants near them. Slowly refills peoples outdoor need.</RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.description>
  <RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.label>reinforced glass wall</RB_ReinforcedGlassWall.label>
  <RB_RusticWall.description>A simplistic, weak and impassable wall. Capable of holding up a roof.</RB_RusticWall.description>
  <RB_RusticWall.label>rustic wall</RB_RusticWall.label>
</LanguageData>
