<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Greenway_BookBurning.description>Certain ideologies promote the censorship and destruction of knowledge deemed dangerous or subversive. Book burning is a symbolic act representing the rejection of ideas that challenge the established order or threaten societal stability. This practice reflects the broader struggle for control over information and the shaping of cultural narratives in a post-apocalyptic world.</Greenway_BookBurning.description>
  <Greenway_BookBurning.label>Book Burning</Greenway_BookBurning.label>
  <Greenway_BrahminBarons.description>Brahmin Barons are individuals or groups who have mastered the art of breeding and raising Brahmin for profit. They control large herds, supplying meat, milk, and other products to settlements and traders across the region. Their influence often extends into local politics and economies, making them powerful figures in the post-apocalyptic society.</Greenway_BrahminBarons.description>
  <Greenway_BrahminBarons.label>Brahmin Barons</Greenway_BrahminBarons.label>
  <Greenway_CannibalistFamilies.description>In the harsh world of Greenway, some families have turned to cannibalism as a means of survival. These families often operate in secret, preying on outsiders or even resorting to ritualistic practices. While viewed with horror by most, cannibalist families see their actions as a necessary adaptation to the brutal realities of their environment.</Greenway_CannibalistFamilies.description>
  <Greenway_CannibalistFamilies.label>Cannibalist Families</Greenway_CannibalistFamilies.label>
  <Greenway_ChemTrade.description>The trade of chems is a significant aspect of the local economy. Various factions and individuals engage in the production, distribution, and sale of chems, often leading to conflicts and power struggles. The popularity of chems among the populace creates a lucrative market, but also contributes to social issues such as addiction and crime.</Greenway_ChemTrade.description>
  <Greenway_ChemTrade.label>Chem Trade</Greenway_ChemTrade.label>
  <Greenway_CloudResidue.description>Those who live in extreme texic entiroments are often weary of consuming traditional food sources, turning instead to food derived fromunderground sources, where they spend most of their time to avoid the toxic atmosphere.</Greenway_CloudResidue.description>
  <Greenway_CloudResidue.label>Cloud Residue</Greenway_CloudResidue.label>
  <Greenway_DesertRanger.description>The Desert Rangers are a respected group of abolitionist law enforcers, known for their strict adherence to justice and their ability to navigate the harsh desert environment. They serve as protectors of the people, maintaining order in a land rife with danger and lawlessness and liberating any slave they can.</Greenway_DesertRanger.description>
  <Greenway_DesertRanger.label>Desert Ranger</Greenway_DesertRanger.label>
  <Greenway_EnclaveScientistsInExile.description>Former scientists of the Enclave often find themselves in exile, working independently or with other factions. These scientists bring valuable knowledge and expertise, contributing to technological advancements and research efforts in the region. However, their association with the Enclave can also lead to mistrust and suspicion among other groups.</Greenway_EnclaveScientistsInExile.description>
  <Greenway_EnclaveScientistsInExile.label>Enclave in Exile</Greenway_EnclaveScientistsInExile.label>
  <Greenway_FollowerSupport.description>Followers of certain ideologies often provide mutual support and assistance to one another. This can include sharing resources, offering protection, and working together to achieve common goals. Such solidarity is crucial in the harsh environment of Greenway, where survival often depends on cooperation and trust among like-minded individuals.</Greenway_FollowerSupport.description>
  <Greenway_FollowerSupport.label>Follower Support</Greenway_FollowerSupport.label>
  <Greenway_Government_Democratic.description>A democratic government inspired by NCR and prewar city-states, with elected councils, traders, and wild west caravans.</Greenway_Government_Democratic.description>
  <Greenway_Government_Democratic.label>Democratic City-State</Greenway_Government_Democratic.label>
  <Greenway_Government_Despotic.description>A government led by mayors, kings, chiefs, or sheriffs, often corrupt or neutral peacekeepers, ruling by force or tradition.</Greenway_Government_Despotic.description>
  <Greenway_Government_Despotic.label>Despotic Rule</Greenway_Government_Despotic.label>
  <Greenway_Government_Raider.description>Survivalist gangs, mercenaries, looters, and warbands who thrive in chaos and conflict.</Greenway_Government_Raider.description>
  <Greenway_Government_Raider.label>Raider Gang</Greenway_Government_Raider.label>
  <Greenway_Government_Tribal.description>Tribal societies ranging from peaceful natives and spiritualists to aggressive nomads and warbands.</Greenway_Government_Tribal.description>
  <Greenway_Government_Tribal.label>Tribal Society</Greenway_Government_Tribal.label>
  <Greenway_Greaser.description>Greaser culture is a prominent subculture, characterized by a love for classic power armor, rock 'n' roll music, and a rebellious attitude agsinst authority. Their motto: "Every Man a King". Greasers often form tight-knit communities, embracing a distinctive style and way of life that sets them apart from mainstream society.</Greenway_Greaser.description>
  <Greenway_Greaser.label>Greaser</Greenway_Greaser.label>
  <Greenway_IndenturedServitude.description>Indentured servitude is a common practice, where individuals enter into contracts to work for a set period in exchange for passage, shelter, or other necessities. While not as severe as outright slavery, it often leads to harsh working conditions and limited freedoms.</Greenway_IndenturedServitude.description>
  <Greenway_IndenturedServitude.label>Indentured Servitude</Greenway_IndenturedServitude.label>
  <Greenway_JetRoad.description>The trade of Jet, a highly addictive drug, is a significant aspect of the local economy. Various factions and individuals engage in the production, distribution, and sale of Jet, often leading to conflicts and power struggles. The drug's popularity among the populace creates a lucrative market, but also contributes to social issues such as addiction and crime.</Greenway_JetRoad.description>
  <Greenway_JetRoad.label>Jet Road</Greenway_JetRoad.label>
  <Greenway_MutantCitizenship.description>The fight for mutant rights is a significant social issue. Mutants often face discrimination and prejudice, leading to movements advocating for their equal treatment and integration into society. These movements seek to challenge societal norms and promote acceptance of mutants as valuable members of the community.</Greenway_MutantCitizenship.description>
  <Greenway_MutantCitizenship.label>Mutant Citizenship</Greenway_MutantCitizenship.label>
  <Greenway_MutantMasters.description>Mutants are seen as rightful rulers of the wastes, stronger than baseline humanity and entitled to command lesser laborers beneath them.</Greenway_MutantMasters.description>
  <Greenway_MutantMasters.label>Mutant Masters</Greenway_MutantMasters.label>
  <Greenway_MutantPurge.description>There are factions that advocate for the eradication of mutants, viewing them as a threat to humanity. These groups often engage in violent actions and campaigns to eliminate mutants from society, leading to widespread fear and tension between mutants and non-mutants.</Greenway_MutantPurge.description>
  <Greenway_MutantPurge.label>Mutant Purge</Greenway_MutantPurge.label>
  <Greenway_MutantSlaves.description>Mutants are often enslaved and used for labor or entertainment. Their unique abilities make them valuable assets, but they are frequently subjected to harsh treatment and discrimination.</Greenway_MutantSlaves.description>
  <Greenway_MutantSlaves.label>Mutant Slaves</Greenway_MutantSlaves.label>
  <Greenway_PurityLaw.description>Why waste crops on feeding animals when you could be making booze? Nukashiners often operate in secret, using makeshift stills and brewing equipment to create their products. Their creations are highly sought after, providing both a source of income and a means of escape from the harsh realities of life in the wasteland.</Greenway_PurityLaw.description>
  <Greenway_PurityLaw.label>Bavarian Purity Law</Greenway_PurityLaw.label>
  <Greenway_Railroad.description>The Railroad is a secretive organization dedicated to the abolition of slavery. They operate covertly, helping slaves escape to freedom and providing safe havens for those in need. Their members are highly skilled and deeply committed to their cause, often risking their lives to fight against the oppressive systems that perpetuate slavery.</Greenway_Railroad.description>
  <Greenway_Railroad.label>Railroad</Greenway_Railroad.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_AbbeyOfTheRoad.description>A protestant-style order built around scripture and the travelling pulpit; it prizes scripture, preaching and humble worship.</Greenway_Religion_AbbeyOfTheRoad.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_AbbeyOfTheRoad.label>Abbey of the Road</Greenway_Religion_AbbeyOfTheRoad.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_CanaaniteChurch.description>A restorationist movement that mixes frontier theocracy and strict social order, inspired by old doctrinal texts.</Greenway_Religion_CanaaniteChurch.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_CanaaniteChurch.label>Canaanite Church</Greenway_Religion_CanaaniteChurch.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfAtom.description>A new cult that treats radiation and atomic remnants as sacred, with ritualised exposure and offerings.</Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfAtom.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfAtom.label>Children of Atom</Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfAtom.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfKrvibi.description>A Lovecraftian cult venerating Ug-Qualtoth and the forerunners; rituals here are strange and alien to most.</Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfKrvibi.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfKrvibi.label>Children of Krvibi</Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfKrvibi.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfTheCathedral.description>A cathedral-centered faith with strong civic influence and ceremonial public worship.</Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfTheCathedral.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfTheCathedral.label>Children of the Cathedral</Greenway_Religion_ChildrenOfTheCathedral.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_FollowerOfTheApocalypse.description>A secular movement born from the Old World's collapse; its followers have sworn to help those in need.</Greenway_Religion_FollowerOfTheApocalypse.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_FollowerOfTheApocalypse.label>Follower of the Apocalypse</Greenway_Religion_FollowerOfTheApocalypse.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_Hubology.description>A technospiritual faith devoted to the alignment of cosmic energies and the pursuit of mental purification through the Hub.</Greenway_Religion_Hubology.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_Hubology.label>Hubology</Greenway_Religion_Hubology.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_Karma.description>An order devoted to the law of Karma - the eternal cycle of cause and consequence. Through mindful action and reflection, followers seek to purify their deeds and restore harmony to the world's moral balance after the collapse of civilisation.</Greenway_Religion_Karma.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_Karma.label>Karma</Greenway_Religion_Karma.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_Native.description>Indigenous faith rooted in ancestral spirits and the land; rituals, totems and seasonal ceremonies hold communities together.</Greenway_Religion_Native.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_Native.label>Native</Greenway_Religion_Native.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_OrderOfOurLadyOfTheWaters.description>A Catholic-style order deeply devoted to Mary and the saints, keeping older sacramental practices alive.</Greenway_Religion_OrderOfOurLadyOfTheWaters.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_OrderOfOurLadyOfTheWaters.label>Waters of Life</Greenway_Religion_OrderOfOurLadyOfTheWaters.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_Shi.description>The Shi follow the Way of the Emperor - a philosophical order born from the fusion of ancient wisdom and new science. Knowledge, discipline, and harmony are sacred principles. They seek balance between machine, mind, and nature, guided by the teachings of the Old World.</Greenway_Religion_Shi.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_Shi.label>Shi</Greenway_Religion_Shi.label>
  <Greenway_Religion_Syncretic.description>A believe mixing elements of Christianity with tribal spirit worship.</Greenway_Religion_Syncretic.description>
  <Greenway_Religion_Syncretic.label>Gentiles</Greenway_Religion_Syncretic.label>
  <Greenway_SecondClassMutants.description>Mutants are tolerated so long as they remain beneath the human social order. They can work, serve, and endure, but they are never treated as true equals.</Greenway_SecondClassMutants.description>
  <Greenway_SecondClassMutants.label>Second Class Mutants</Greenway_SecondClassMutants.label>
  <Greenway_SurvivalistLifestyle.description>The Survivalist Lifestyle meme emphasizes self-reliance, resourcefulness, and preparedness. Followers of this meme prioritize skills such as hunting, foraging, and crafting, believing that these abilities are essential for thriving in the harsh post-apocalyptic environment of Greenway. They often stockpile supplies and maintain a strong focus on personal and community defense.</Greenway_SurvivalistLifestyle.description>
  <Greenway_SurvivalistLifestyle.label>Survivalist Lifestyle</Greenway_SurvivalistLifestyle.label>
  <Greenway_Utobitha.description>A mutant homeland should belong to mutants alone. Their strength, endurance, and altered bodies are treated as proof that the future belongs to them, not to unaltered wastelanders.</Greenway_Utobitha.description>
  <Greenway_Utobitha.label>Utobitha</Greenway_Utobitha.label>
  <Greenway_ViceCity.description>In the harsh world, vice thrives as a means of escape from the daily struggles of survival. Gambling dens, brothels, and illicit trade are common, providing both a source of income and a way to forget the harsh realities of life in this unforgiving land.</Greenway_ViceCity.description>
  <Greenway_ViceCity.label>Vice City</Greenway_ViceCity.label>
  <Greenway_WorkingCamps.description>Labor camps are a common sight, where prisoners and the unemployed are put to work on various projects. While conditions can be harsh, they provide a means of survival and a chance for redemption through hard work.</Greenway_WorkingCamps.description>
  <Greenway_WorkingCamps.label>Working Camps</Greenway_WorkingCamps.label>
  <VME_Astrology.description>We are guided by signs in the heavens, old-world charts, and the omens they cast over the wastes.</VME_Astrology.description>
  <VME_Astrology.label>sky omens</VME_Astrology.label>
  <VME_GodEmperor.description>Our leader must be obeyed as the living embodiment of the cause.</VME_GodEmperor.description>
  <VME_GodEmperor.label>cult of personality</VME_GodEmperor.label>
</LanguageData>