<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GR_AdrenalineRush.description>Causes the creature to move much faster for a while, at the cost of getting tired afterwards for almost half a day.</GR_AdrenalineRush.description>
  <GR_AdrenalineRush.label>adrenaline rush</GR_AdrenalineRush.label>
  <GR_Burrow.description>Sends the creature underground into burrowing mode, making it very resistant to damage for a while.</GR_Burrow.description>
  <GR_Burrow.label>burrow underground</GR_Burrow.label>
  <GR_CatReflexes.description>Makes the creature much more agile, improving its chance to dodge melee attacks even further.</GR_CatReflexes.description>
  <GR_CatReflexes.label>cat reflexes</GR_CatReflexes.label>
  <GR_ChemfuelDischarge.description>Remotely detonate the chemfuel reservoirs of this creature. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_ChemfuelDischarge.description>
  <GR_ChemfuelDischarge.label>chemfuel discharge</GR_ChemfuelDischarge.label>
  <GR_DeathRay.description>Redirects an orbital mechanoid satellite to fire upon a selected location.</GR_DeathRay.description>
  <GR_DeathRay.label>orbital heat ray</GR_DeathRay.label>
  <GR_DetonateAcid.description>Remotely detonate the acidic chemfuel reservoirs of this creature. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_DetonateAcid.description>
  <GR_DetonateAcid.label>detonate acidic chemfuel</GR_DetonateAcid.label>
  <GR_DetonateBomb.description>Remotely detonate the chemfuel reservoirs of this creature. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_DetonateBomb.description>
  <GR_DetonateBomb.label>detonate chemfuel</GR_DetonateBomb.label>
  <GR_DetonateFrost.description>Remotely detonate the cryo chemfuel reservoirs of this creature. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_DetonateFrost.description>
  <GR_DetonateFrost.label>detonate cryo chemfuel</GR_DetonateFrost.label>
  <GR_DetonatePoison.description>Remotely detonate the venomous chemfuel reservoirs of this creature. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_DetonatePoison.description>
  <GR_DetonatePoison.label>detonate venomous chemfuel</GR_DetonatePoison.label>
  <GR_DetonateStun.description>Remotely detonate the stunning chemfuel reservoirs of this creature. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_DetonateStun.description>
  <GR_DetonateStun.label>detonate stunning chemfuel</GR_DetonateStun.label>
  <GR_FragEggs.description>Lay several exploding eggs. The animal will be affected and damaged by the resulting explosion.</GR_FragEggs.description>
  <GR_FragEggs.label>lay frag eggs</GR_FragEggs.label>
  <GR_InsectClouds.description>Spawns a cloud of drones surrounding this animal that will cut apart any creature, excluding all insectoid paragons.</GR_InsectClouds.description>
  <GR_InsectClouds.label>insect clouds</GR_InsectClouds.label>
  <GR_KeenSenses.description>Makes the creature more aware of its surroundings, increasing its melee capacities (affects sight, hit chance and consciousness)</GR_KeenSenses.description>
  <GR_KeenSenses.label>keen senses</GR_KeenSenses.label>
  <GR_PackTactics.description>Collaborate with other nearby muffalowolves to bring down prey.</GR_PackTactics.description>
  <GR_PackTactics.label>pack tactics</GR_PackTactics.label>
  <GR_PoisonousCloud.description>Releases a cloud of poisonous gas from this creature. The animal will NOT be affected and damaged by it.</GR_PoisonousCloud.description>
  <GR_PoisonousCloud.label>release venomous cloud</GR_PoisonousCloud.label>
  <GR_ResearchDrive.description>Offer investigative insights to nearby researches, allowing them to more easily reach a breakthrough.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; &quot;My fellow scientist, have you considered rejecting humanity, and returning to monkey? Food for thought&quot;.</GR_ResearchDrive.description>
  <GR_ResearchDrive.label>research drive</GR_ResearchDrive.label>
  <GR_SetTrap.description>Sets an explosive trap. The Manalope won't trigger it.</GR_SetTrap.description>
  <GR_SetTrap.label>set chemfuel trap</GR_SetTrap.label>
  <GR_StampedeClouds.description>Stampedes, moving faster and creating dust clouds that block line of view for projectile weapons. Gets the creature tired after a while.</GR_StampedeClouds.description>
  <GR_StampedeClouds.label>stampede</GR_StampedeClouds.label>
  <GR_VentHeatedExhaust.description>Vents the heated gasses produced by this mechanoid hybrid's internal processes. This creates a wave of superheated ait that will affect the surrounding tiles. It will not affect the hybrid.</GR_VentHeatedExhaust.description>
  <GR_VentHeatedExhaust.label>vent heated exhaust</GR_VentHeatedExhaust.label>
</LanguageData>
