<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with chemfuel powered generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.label>chemfuel powered generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_ChemfuelPowered_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with geothermal generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.label>geothermal generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Geothermal_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with nuclear reactor. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.label>nuclear reactor power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Nuclear_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with power cells. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.label>power cell grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_PowerCell.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with solar generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.label>solar generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Solar_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with tidal generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.label>tidal generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Tidal_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with watermill generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.label>watermill generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_Watermill_Generator.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with wind turbine. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.label>wind turbine power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_WindTurbine.label>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in generating power with wood-fired generators. Constantly providing it to faction's primary colony.</Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.description>
  <Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.label>wood-fired generators power grid</Outpost_PowerGrid_WoodFired_Generator.label>
</LanguageData>
