<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VFEPD_BangBus.description>A basic passenger transport, the Bangbus is a relatively cheap piece of machinery to construct to transport people across roads of flat terrain. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_BangBus.description>
  <VFEPD_BangBus.label>bang bus</VFEPD_BangBus.label>
  <VFEPD_Bulldog.description>A general main battle tank, the Bulldog is an improved combat vehicle that performs well in any engagement. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Bulldog.description>
  <VFEPD_Bulldog.label>bulldog</VFEPD_Bulldog.label>
  <VFEPD_Bunsen.description>A basic light tank, the Bunsen is a modified armoured vehicle suited for taking on enemy fortifications and exposed infantry. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Bunsen.description>
  <VFEPD_Bunsen.label>bunsen</VFEPD_Bunsen.label>
  <VFEPD_Charley.description>A general motorcycle, the Charley is a very effective single-person vehicle with a small cargo capacity. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Charley.description>
  <VFEPD_Charley.label>charley</VFEPD_Charley.label>
  <VFEPD_Dinghy.description>A very basic motorised boat, the Dingy is an incredibly cheap and discrete method of transportation over water. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Dinghy.description>
  <VFEPD_Dinghy.label>dinghy</VFEPD_Dinghy.label>
  <VFEPD_Dirtbike.description>A basic off-road motorcycle, the Dirtbike is a very cheap vehicle that allows a single user to travel quickly, efficiently and quietly. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Dirtbike.description>
  <VFEPD_Dirtbike.label>dirtbike</VFEPD_Dirtbike.label>
  <VFEPD_Frog.description>A basic reusable transport pod, the Frog is a relatively cheap vehicle that is the first option when it comes to flying without crashing into the ground. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Frog.description>
  <VFEPD_Frog.label>frog</VFEPD_Frog.label>
  <VFEPD_Highwayman.description>A basic infantry fighting vehicle, the Highwayman is the cheapest weaponized option for transporting three people. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Highwayman.description>
  <VFEPD_Highwayman.label>highwayman</VFEPD_Highwayman.label>
  <VFEPD_Mosquito.description>A general-purpose aircraft, the Mosquito is an extremely fast and mobile mode of transportation. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Mosquito.description>
  <VFEPD_Mosquito.label>mosquito</VFEPD_Mosquito.label>
  <VFEPD_Mule.description>A basic cargo transport, the Mule is a relatively cheap vehicle that can carry a large amount of cargo across smooth roads of flat terrain. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Mule.description>
  <VFEPD_Mule.label>mule</VFEPD_Mule.label>
  <VFEPD_Prowler.description>A basic off-road exploration vehicle, the Prowler is relatively cheap to construct and is an effective all-weather option for efficient travel over steep terrain. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Prowler.description>
  <VFEPD_Prowler.label>prowler</VFEPD_Prowler.label>
  <VFEPD_Roadkill.description>A basic medium tank, the Roadkill is a comparatively cheap armoured vehicle suited for short engagements. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Roadkill.description>
  <VFEPD_Roadkill.label>roadkill</VFEPD_Roadkill.label>
  <VFEPD_Roadrunner.description>A general cargo transporter, the Roadrunner is an excellent vehicle for getting a lot of material from one location to another. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Roadrunner.description>
  <VFEPD_Roadrunner.label>roadrunner</VFEPD_Roadrunner.label>
  <VFEPD_Scytheman.description>A juryrigged multiple rocket launcher system, the Scytheman is a repurposed farming vehicle intended to saturate a location with inaccurate volleys of explosives. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Scytheman.description>
  <VFEPD_Scytheman.label>scytheman</VFEPD_Scytheman.label>
  <VFEPD_Smuggler.description>A general-purpose aircraft, the Smuggler is an extremely fast and effective mode of transportation. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Smuggler.description>
  <VFEPD_Smuggler.label>smuggler</VFEPD_Smuggler.label>
  <VFEPD_Snatcher.description>A general passenger transport, the Snatcher is a solid vehicle for transporting people to different locations. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Snatcher.description>
  <VFEPD_Snatcher.label>snatcher</VFEPD_Snatcher.label>
  <VFEPD_Tango.description>A general purpose armoured personnel carrier, the Tango is a slow but hardy troop transport. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Tango.description>
  <VFEPD_Tango.label>tango</VFEPD_Tango.label>
  <VFEPD_Toad.description>A squad and mortar deployment pod, the Toad is a somewhat expensive vehicle to quickly mount a siege on a nearby locale without exposing your gunners to danger. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Toad.description>
  <VFEPD_Toad.label>toad</VFEPD_Toad.label>
  <VFEPD_Traveller.description>A basic road vehicle suited for flat terrain, the Traveller is a relatively cheap and fast option that still performs quite amicably in cold weather and snowy conditions. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Traveller.description>
  <VFEPD_Traveller.label>traveller</VFEPD_Traveller.label>
  <VFEPD_Trawler.description>A general-purpose boat, the Trawler is an effective long distance transportation across open waters. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Trawler.description>
  <VFEPD_Trawler.label>trawler</VFEPD_Trawler.label>
  <VFEPD_Wagon.description>A general all-rounder vehicle, the Wagon performs well in all categories with a good cargo and passenger capacity. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Wagon.description>
  <VFEPD_Wagon.label>wagon</VFEPD_Wagon.label>
  <VFEPD_Warbird.description>A general-purpose fighter plane, the Warbird is an incredibly fast and effective attack craft. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Warbird.description>
  <VFEPD_Warbird.label>warbird</VFEPD_Warbird.label>
  <VFEPD_Wisent.description>A military-grade all-purpose transporter, the Wisent is a powerful truck capable of transporting both plentiful cargo and soldiers into hostile territory. Non-functional: all its internal wiring and its motor have been removed.</VFEPD_Wisent.description>
  <VFEPD_Wisent.label>wisent</VFEPD_Wisent.label>
</LanguageData>
