<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VCE_AppleTree.description>A tree bearing glossy, red apples, while a myriad of different varieties exist this particular type favors warm summers and mild winters. Apples have been used as snacking food, a dessert ingredient, and brewed into cider since early mankind.</VCE_AppleTree.description>
  <VCE_AppleTree.label>apple tree</VCE_AppleTree.label>
  <VCE_BananaTree.description>A broad-leafed, tall tropical tree adorned with a cluster of yellow, elongated berries succinctly known as bananas. Bananas are easily peeled to reveal a deeply sweet, nearly mushy flesh inside and have been a favorite of both humans and other primates across the tropics for millenia. Bananas are easy to harvest, since a whole &quot;hand&quot; can be cut at the same time.</VCE_BananaTree.description>
  <VCE_BananaTree.label>banana tree</VCE_BananaTree.label>
  <VCE_BearBerryBush.description>A low-lying bush speckled with pink berries that thrives in poor, even sandy soil. While raw bearberries possess an acidic and bland taste, after cooking a natural sweetness comes through and the results can be much more palatable. This plant can be grown in pots.</VCE_BearBerryBush.description>
  <VCE_BearBerryBush.label>bearberry bush</VCE_BearBerryBush.label>
  <VCE_CherryTree.description>A tree bearing tiny purple-red sweet cherries. Cherry trees are notable for requiring a brief freezing season, as such their fruit quickly became a favorite among northern occidental civilizations. This particular genus is quite beautiful, speckled with pink blossoms throughout, blooming fully each winter.</VCE_CherryTree.description>
  <VCE_CherryTree.label>cherry tree</VCE_CherryTree.label>
  <VCE_Opuntia.description>More often referred to as the “prickly pear” cactus, this plant is known to be quite bountiful even in hot, dry deserts. The pads of this tall, spiny cactus bloom pink, melon-like edible fruits, used historically for both snacking as well as medicine by desert natives.</VCE_Opuntia.description>
  <VCE_Opuntia.label>opuntia</VCE_Opuntia.label>
  <VCE_OrangeTree.description>A bushy, semi-tropical tree dotted with orange fruits well equipped for growing in humid environments and in wet soil. Spherical and perforated, oranges are notoriously annoying to peel and quite pulpy, but known as one of the absolute juiciest fruits with a bright tang and sour aftertaste.</VCE_OrangeTree.description>
  <VCE_OrangeTree.label>orange tree</VCE_OrangeTree.label>
  <VCE_PeachTree.description>A deciduous tree bearing fuzzy, stone fruit known as peaches, peach trees often require full sunlight and warm temperatures. Ancient oriental cultures cultivated these trees groves at a time, noting its ability to survive in drought conditions.</VCE_PeachTree.description>
  <VCE_PeachTree.label>peach tree</VCE_PeachTree.label>
  <VCE_PearTree.description>A stout tree bearing crispy green pears, pear trees are notable for requiring high amounts of water and cool weather, and also doing quite well in shade. While at first similar to apples, pears are slightly more fibrous and less sweet.</VCE_PearTree.description>
  <VCE_PearTree.label>pear tree</VCE_PearTree.label>
  <VCE_PlumTree.description>A bushy tree bearing a smooth-skinned purple fruit. Plums are particularly tart and produced into a variety of jams, jellies, and ciders. Many cultures also dry-age plums into prunes for long-term preservation.</VCE_PlumTree.description>
  <VCE_PlumTree.label>plum tree</VCE_PlumTree.label>
</LanguageData>
