<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VVE_ArtilleryWreck.description>An ancient, broken self propelled artillery. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into an Udar.</VVE_ArtilleryWreck.description>
  <VVE_ArtilleryWreck.label>artillery wreck</VVE_ArtilleryWreck.label>
  <VVE_BattleTankWreck.description>An ancient, broken battle tank. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Marshal.</VVE_BattleTankWreck.description>
  <VVE_BattleTankWreck.label>battle tank wreck</VVE_BattleTankWreck.label>
  <VVE_CargoHelicopterWreck.description>An ancient, crashed cargo helicopter. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Cherokee.</VVE_CargoHelicopterWreck.description>
  <VVE_CargoHelicopterWreck.label>cargo helicopter wreck</VVE_CargoHelicopterWreck.label>
  <VVE_ClassicCarWreck.description>An ancient, broken classic car. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Springbok.</VVE_ClassicCarWreck.description>
  <VVE_ClassicCarWreck.label>classical car wreck</VVE_ClassicCarWreck.label>
  <VVE_HelicopterWreck.description>An ancient, broken helicopter. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Louie.</VVE_HelicopterWreck.description>
  <VVE_HelicopterWreck.label>helicopter wreck</VVE_HelicopterWreck.label>
  <VVE_InfantryFightingVehicleWreck.description>An ancient, broken infantry fighting vehicle. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Badger.</VVE_InfantryFightingVehicleWreck.description>
  <VVE_InfantryFightingVehicleWreck.label>infantry fighting vehicle wreck</VVE_InfantryFightingVehicleWreck.label>
  <VVE_LightArmoredVehicleWreck.description>An ancient, broken light armored vehicle. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Paladin.</VVE_LightArmoredVehicleWreck.description>
  <VVE_LightArmoredVehicleWreck.label>light armored vehicle wreck</VVE_LightArmoredVehicleWreck.label>
  <VVE_OffroadJeepWreck.description>An ancient, broken offroad jeep. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Nomad.</VVE_OffroadJeepWreck.description>
  <VVE_OffroadJeepWreck.label>offroad jeep wreck</VVE_OffroadJeepWreck.label>
  <VVE_RefrigeratedTruckWreck.description>An ancient, broken refrigerated truck. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Hermano.</VVE_RefrigeratedTruckWreck.description>
  <VVE_RefrigeratedTruckWreck.label>refrigerated truck wreck</VVE_RefrigeratedTruckWreck.label>
  <VVE_RocketArtilleryWreck.description>An ancient, broken rocket artillery truck. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Burya.</VVE_RocketArtilleryWreck.description>
  <VVE_RocketArtilleryWreck.label>rocket artillery wreck</VVE_RocketArtilleryWreck.label>
  <VVE_SiegePodWreck.description>An ancient, destroyed siege pod. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Goliath.</VVE_SiegePodWreck.description>
  <VVE_SiegePodWreck.label>siege pod wreck</VVE_SiegePodWreck.label>
  <VVE_SupercarWreck.description>An ancient, broken supercar. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Lightning.</VVE_SupercarWreck.description>
  <VVE_SupercarWreck.label>supercar wreck</VVE_SupercarWreck.label>
  <VVE_TruckWreck.description>An ancient, broken truck. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago. Given enough resources, it can be restored into a Big Rig.</VVE_TruckWreck.description>
  <VVE_TruckWreck.label>truck wreck</VVE_TruckWreck.label>
</LanguageData>
