<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AM_AncientAirConditioner.description>An ancient air conditioning machine. Its internals were smashed long ago and what wasn't looted has rusted away in the time since.</AM_AncientAirConditioner.description>
  <AM_AncientAirConditioner.label>ancient air conditioner</AM_AncientAirConditioner.label>
  <AM_AncientATM.description>An ancient ATM. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</AM_AncientATM.description>
  <AM_AncientATM.label>ancient ATM</AM_AncientATM.label>
  <AM_AncientBarrel.description>An ancient, broken barrel that looks like it once contained waste of some sort. The only thing it contains now is a smear of dried sludge.</AM_AncientBarrel.description>
  <AM_AncientBarrel.label>ancient barrel</AM_AncientBarrel.label>
  <AM_AncientBed.description>An old, rotted mattress on a rusty frame. Though uncomfortable, it can still be used, but it's too dilapidated to restore.</AM_AncientBed.description>
  <AM_AncientBed.label>ancient bed</AM_AncientBed.label>
  <AM_AncientContainer.description>A shipping container from some ancient freight-carrying vehicle. It has long since deteriorated into uselessness.</AM_AncientContainer.description>
  <AM_AncientContainer.label>ancient container</AM_AncientContainer.label>
  <AM_AncientCrate.description>An ancient, broken crate. Any valuables it once contained have degraded to uselessness.</AM_AncientCrate.description>
  <AM_AncientCrate.label>ancient crate</AM_AncientCrate.label>
  <AM_AncientDisplayBank.description>An ancient computer interface. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</AM_AncientDisplayBank.description>
  <AM_AncientDisplayBank.label>ancient display bank</AM_AncientDisplayBank.label>
  <AM_AncientEquipmentBlocks.description>A collection of ancient equipment blocks of unknown function. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</AM_AncientEquipmentBlocks.description>
  <AM_AncientEquipmentBlocks.label>ancient equipment blocks</AM_AncientEquipmentBlocks.label>
  <AM_AncientFence.description>An ancient fence made of reinforced concrete posts joined by concrete panels.</AM_AncientFence.description>
  <AM_AncientFence.label>ancient fence</AM_AncientFence.label>
  <AM_AncientFuelNode.description>An ancient, unstable fuel node once used to charge machines with fuel. It has become unstable over the years due to lack of maintenance.</AM_AncientFuelNode.description>
  <AM_AncientFuelNode.label>ancient unstable fuel node</AM_AncientFuelNode.label>
  <AM_AncientGenerator.description>An ancient electrical generator. Its usable parts were smashed or looted long ago, and the rest has rusted into uselessness.</AM_AncientGenerator.description>
  <AM_AncientGenerator.label>ancient generator</AM_AncientGenerator.label>
  <AM_AncientHydrant.description>An ancient hydrant. Heavily rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</AM_AncientHydrant.description>
  <AM_AncientHydrant.label>ancient hydrant</AM_AncientHydrant.label>
  <AM_AncientKitchenSink.description>An ancient kitchen sink made of some non-metallic fiber-sheet material. It is badly deteriorated and there's no way to salvage anything from it.\n\nHow it got here must be a long story.</AM_AncientKitchenSink.description>
  <AM_AncientKitchenSink.label>ancient kitchen sink</AM_AncientKitchenSink.label>
  <AM_AncientLockerBank.description>An ancient, rusted bank of lockers. All of the lockers have been forced open with nothing valuable left behind.</AM_AncientLockerBank.description>
  <AM_AncientLockerBank.label>ancient locker bank</AM_AncientLockerBank.label>
  <AM_AncientMachine.description>A large ancient machine case filled with unknown machinery. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</AM_AncientMachine.description>
  <AM_AncientMachine.label>ancient machine</AM_AncientMachine.label>
  <AM_AncientMicrowave.description>An ancient device for heating food. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</AM_AncientMicrowave.description>
  <AM_AncientMicrowave.label>ancient microwave</AM_AncientMicrowave.label>
  <AM_AncientMilitaryCrate.description>An ancient, military-looking crate. It was broken long ago and any valuables it once contained were looted.</AM_AncientMilitaryCrate.description>
  <AM_AncientMilitaryCrate.label>ancient military crate</AM_AncientMilitaryCrate.label>
  <AM_AncientOperatingTable.description>A table once used for surgical operations. It has long since deteriorated into uselessness.</AM_AncientOperatingTable.description>
  <AM_AncientOperatingTable.label>ancient operating table</AM_AncientOperatingTable.label>
  <AM_AncientOven.description>An ancient oven. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</AM_AncientOven.description>
  <AM_AncientOven.label>ancient oven</AM_AncientOven.label>
  <AM_AncientPipelineSection.description>A section from an ancient pipeline. It once carried some valuable fluid over long distances. Now it's been looted and deteriorated to uselessness.</AM_AncientPipelineSection.description>
  <AM_AncientPipelineSection.label>ancient pipeline section</AM_AncientPipelineSection.label>
  <AM_AncientPipes.description>A bunch of rusted old pipes. It is hard to say how these ended up here.</AM_AncientPipes.description>
  <AM_AncientPipes.label>ancient pipes</AM_AncientPipes.label>
  <AM_AncientPodCar.description>An ancient pod car once capable of automated flight. Its valuable parts were looted long ago, and the rest is badly deteriorated.</AM_AncientPodCar.description>
  <AM_AncientPodCar.label>ancient pod car</AM_AncientPodCar.label>
  <AM_AncientRazorWire.description>A piece of ancient razor wire. It has been deteriorating for many years and no longer poses any danger.</AM_AncientRazorWire.description>
  <AM_AncientRazorWire.label>ancient razor wire</AM_AncientRazorWire.label>
  <AM_AncientRefrigerator.description>An ancient refrigerator. It was stripped of interesting parts long ago.</AM_AncientRefrigerator.description>
  <AM_AncientRefrigerator.label>ancient refrigerator</AM_AncientRefrigerator.label>
  <AM_AncientRustedCar.description>An ancient, broken car. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago.</AM_AncientRustedCar.description>
  <AM_AncientRustedCar.label>ancient car</AM_AncientRustedCar.label>
  <AM_AncientRustedCarFrame.description>An ancient, rusted car frame. The body shell has long since rusted away to nothing.</AM_AncientRustedCarFrame.description>
  <AM_AncientRustedCarFrame.label>ancient car frame</AM_AncientRustedCarFrame.label>
  <AM_AncientRustedJeep.description>An ancient, broken troop carrier. Everything that isn't rusted away was looted long ago.</AM_AncientRustedJeep.description>
  <AM_AncientRustedJeep.label>ancient troop carrier</AM_AncientRustedJeep.label>
  <AM_AncientRustedTruck.description>An ancient, broken truck. Everything useful either rusted away or was looted long ago.</AM_AncientRustedTruck.description>
  <AM_AncientRustedTruck.label>ancient truck</AM_AncientRustedTruck.label>
  <AM_AncientSecurityTurret.description>An ancient, broken security turret. The valuable parts have all been looted or smashed.</AM_AncientSecurityTurret.description>
  <AM_AncientSecurityTurret.label>ancient security turret</AM_AncientSecurityTurret.label>
  <AM_AncientShoppingCart.description>An ancient, rusted shopping cart. How exactly it got here is a mystery, but the story is long and probably quite sad.</AM_AncientShoppingCart.description>
  <AM_AncientShoppingCart.label>ancient shopping cart</AM_AncientShoppingCart.label>
  <AM_AncientStove.description>An ancient stove. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</AM_AncientStove.description>
  <AM_AncientStove.label>ancient stove</AM_AncientStove.label>
  <AM_AncientTankTrap.description>An defensive fortification for stopping vehicles. It's been deteriorating for many years.</AM_AncientTankTrap.description>
  <AM_AncientTankTrap.label>ancient tank trap</AM_AncientTankTrap.label>
  <AM_AncientToilet.description>An ancient toilet. Smashed long ago, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</AM_AncientToilet.description>
  <AM_AncientToilet.label>ancient toilet</AM_AncientToilet.label>
  <AM_AncientVendingMachine.description>An ancient vending machine. It was smashed ages ago and generations of looters have taken every conceivably useful part. How it ended up here is a mystery.</AM_AncientVendingMachine.description>
  <AM_AncientVendingMachine.label>ancient vending machine</AM_AncientVendingMachine.label>
  <AM_AncientWheel.description>An ancient wheel from some kind of vehicle. The rubber has deteriorated away and the metal is twisted and rusted.</AM_AncientWheel.description>
  <AM_AncientWheel.label>ancient wheel</AM_AncientWheel.label>
  <AM_MI26_D.description>An ancient giant helicopter that has crashed, with a vague identification number on its body: mi26.</AM_MI26_D.description>
  <AM_MI26_D.label>ancient giant helicopter</AM_MI26_D.label>
</LanguageData>
