<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AM_Budweiser.description>A once popular ancient beer brand, canned for its ancient customers.</AM_Budweiser.description>
  <AM_Budweiser.label>budweiser</AM_Budweiser.label>
  <AM_CannedBraisedPorkbelly.description>An ancient can of braised pork. Its a great source of happiness despite the dust.</AM_CannedBraisedPorkbelly.description>
  <AM_CannedBraisedPorkbelly.label>canned braised pork</AM_CannedBraisedPorkbelly.label>
  <AM_CannedHerring.description>An ancient can of herring. Quite salty, but the freshness is appealing.</AM_CannedHerring.description>
  <AM_CannedHerring.label>canned herring</AM_CannedHerring.label>
  <AM_CannedPeas.description>An ancient can of soft, sweet peas.</AM_CannedPeas.description>
  <AM_CannedPeas.label>canned peas</AM_CannedPeas.label>
  <AM_CannedStewedBeef.description>An ancient can of muffalo meat stewed with potatoes and tomatoes. Very delicious.</AM_CannedStewedBeef.description>
  <AM_CannedStewedBeef.label>canned stewed muffalo</AM_CannedStewedBeef.label>
  <AM_Coca.description>An ancient sparkling beverage with high sugar content. Just a sip could make someone happy for an entire day.</AM_Coca.description>
  <AM_Coca.label>coca-cola</AM_Coca.label>
  <AM_DeliciousCannedBeef.description>An ancient can of pure muffalo meat stew. Has a very strong buttery aroma.</AM_DeliciousCannedBeef.description>
  <AM_DeliciousCannedBeef.label>deluxe canned muffalo</AM_DeliciousCannedBeef.label>
  <AM_Fanta.description>An ancient carbonated orange-flavored soft drink, sweet and delicious.</AM_Fanta.description>
  <AM_Fanta.label>fanta</AM_Fanta.label>
  <AM_MilkBeer.description>An ancient concoction of milk and beer mixed with canned drinks. It can even fill the stomach!</AM_MilkBeer.description>
  <AM_MilkBeer.label>milk beer</AM_MilkBeer.label>
  <AM_MRE.description>A pack of ancient military rations. It's intact and won't spoil, but it doesn't look very appetizing.</AM_MRE.description>
  <AM_MRE.label>military ration</AM_MRE.label>
  <AM_Pepsi.description>An ancient, slightly inferior carbonated soft drink. Seems sweeter than the others.</AM_Pepsi.description>
  <AM_Pepsi.label>pepsi</AM_Pepsi.label>
  <AM_PotatoChipsA.description>An ancient bag of classic thin cut salted potato chips. and packaged with nitrogen gas making it difficult to spoil.</AM_PotatoChipsA.description>
  <AM_PotatoChipsA.label>classic potato chips</AM_PotatoChipsA.label>
  <AM_PotatoChipsB.description>An ancient bag of tomato flavored potato chips. It's sweet and sour, delicious, and packaged with nitrogen gas making it difficult to spoil.</AM_PotatoChipsB.description>
  <AM_PotatoChipsB.label>tomato potato chips</AM_PotatoChipsB.label>
  <AM_PotatoChipsC.description>An ancient bag of potato chips with a unique cucumber flavor，packaged with nitrogen gas making it difficult to spoil.</AM_PotatoChipsC.description>
  <AM_PotatoChipsC.label>cucumber potato chips</AM_PotatoChipsC.label>
  <AM_PotatoChipsD.description>An ancient bag of steak flavored potato chips. Eating them feels like enjoying a feast. Packaged with nitrogen gas making it difficult to spoil.</AM_PotatoChipsD.description>
  <AM_PotatoChipsD.label>steak potato chips</AM_PotatoChipsD.label>
  <AM_PotatoChipsE.description>An ancient bag of lemon flavored potato chips. Bursting with that summer flavor, and packaged with a nitrogen gas, making difficult to spoil.</AM_PotatoChipsE.description>
  <AM_PotatoChipsE.label>lemon potato chips</AM_PotatoChipsE.label>
  <AM_PotatoChipsF.description>An ancient bag of Italian braised potato chips. Its taste is like eating a strong and fragrant tomato minced meat stew. Packaged with a nitrogen gas, making difficult to spoil.</AM_PotatoChipsF.description>
  <AM_PotatoChipsF.label>italian red stew potato chips</AM_PotatoChipsF.label>
  <AM_Sprite.description>An ancient lemon-lime flavored soft drink with a strong sour taste.</AM_Sprite.description>
  <AM_Sprite.label>sprite</AM_Sprite.label>
  <AM_TsingtaoBeer.description>An ancient canned beer with a lovely aftertaste.</AM_TsingtaoBeer.description>
  <AM_TsingtaoBeer.label>tsingtao</AM_TsingtaoBeer.label>
</LanguageData>
