<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.description>Clumps of vines that burst through the soil to bloom into beautiful flowers. Believed to be part of great collective roots that spread deep under the terrain which occasionally breach the surface to pollinate. The attractive qualities of the flowers encourage humans not to remove them.</VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.label>anima bell</VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.description>Thorny, fast-growing vines infused with faint anima energy. Their barbs are humming softly to the touch.</VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.label>anima brambles</VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.description>A short shrub. Does talk, but only when you're not around.</VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.label>anima bush</VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.description>A delicate, softly glowing flower that blooms near anima trees, resonating faintly with psychic energy. Can be harvested to acquire anima pearls.</VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.label>anima heart blossom</VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.description>A withered anima tree whose bark has hardened into a gray, lifeless shell under relentless pollution. Its psychic presence is muted and distorted, yet a stubborn echo of anima still clings to the husk, refusing to fully fade.</VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.label>anima husk</VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.description>Pale, twisting roots shot through with a soft inner glow, drawn from anima-touched soil. Can be harvested for wood.</VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.label>anima root</VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.label>
  <VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.description>An anima-touched tree. It lacks the psychic potency of a true anima tree, but still hums faintly with psychic life.</VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.description>
  <VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.label>anima tree</VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.label>
  <VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.description>A grand anima-touched tree. It lacks the psychic potency of a true anima tree, but still hums faintly with psychic life.</VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.description>
  <VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.label>grand anima tree</VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.label>
  <VEE_Plant_MysticCap.description>A small, vividly colored mushroom with a faintly iridescent cap. Can be harvested for raw fungus.</VEE_Plant_MysticCap.description>
  <VEE_Plant_MysticCap.label>mystic cap</VEE_Plant_MysticCap.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.description>A huge rare tree with warm, skin-smooth bark and long iridescent leaves. Infused with bioluminescent micro-organisms, ancient anima trees develop a unique form of psychic symbiosis with surrounding lifeforms.\n\nIf a person (psycaster or not) meditates near an ancient anima tree, it will grow anima grass around its base. Once enough grass is grown, it becomes possible to carry out a psychic linking ritual with the tree and upgrade a person's psychic powers. Only tribal peoples know the secret of this ritual. Tribal psycasters are also able to draw psyfocus from ancient anima trees while meditating to them.\n\nAncient anima trees' psychic properties are weakened if artificial structures are placed nearby. They refuse to be caged or studied, and must remain part of nature.\n\nMost tribes believe that ancient anima trees are not simply trees, but are rather the physical extremities of a single world spirit.</VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.label>ancient anima tree</VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.label>
  <VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.description>A small anima-touched tree. It lacks the psychic potency of a true anima tree, but still hums faintly with psychic life.</VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.description>
  <VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.label>anima sapling</VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.label>
</LanguageData>
