<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AirconIndoorUnit.description>Indoor Air-con unit for rooms. Connect to outdoor air-con units. Requires 100 cooling units.</AirconIndoorUnit.description>
  <AirconIndoorUnit.label>Air-Con Indoor Unit</AirconIndoorUnit.label>
  <AirConOutdoorUnit.description>Multi-split Air Conditioner unit. Place outdoors and pipe to indoor units or freezer units. Power mode selection with 100-1000 cooling units capacity</AirConOutdoorUnit.description>
  <AirConOutdoorUnit.label>Air-Con Outdoor Unit</AirConOutdoorUnit.label>
  <CeilingFan.description>Cools a room by circulating air. Includes a built in lamp.</CeilingFan.description>
  <CeilingFan.label>Ceiling Fan 2x2</CeilingFan.label>
  <CeilingFanS.description>Cools a room by circulating air. Includes a built in lamp.</CeilingFanS.description>
  <CeilingFanS.label>Ceiling Fan 1x1</CeilingFanS.label>
  <ElectricBoiler.description>Produces a variable amount of heating units for radiators and hot water tanks. Manually controlled power setting. Can be controlled by thermostats.</ElectricBoiler.description>
  <ElectricBoiler.label>Electric Boiler</ElectricBoiler.label>
  <FreezerUnit.description>Freezer unit for creating a walk in freezer. Connect to outdoor air-con units. Requires 300 cooling units.</FreezerUnit.description>
  <FreezerUnit.label>Walk-in freezer unit</FreezerUnit.label>
  <GasBoiler.description>Produces 2000 heating units for radiators and hot water tanks. Requires chemfuel for fuel. Can be controlled by thermostats.</GasBoiler.description>
  <GasBoiler.label>Gas boiler</GasBoiler.label>
  <HotWaterTank.description>Stores hot running water for showers and baths. Connect to any boiler to heat.</HotWaterTank.description>
  <HotWaterTank.label>Hot Water Tank</HotWaterTank.label>
  <LogBoiler.description>Produces 2000 heating units for radiators and hot water tanks. Requires wood logs for fuel.</LogBoiler.description>
  <LogBoiler.label>Log boiler</LogBoiler.label>
  <RadiatorLarge.description>3 times the output of a standard radiator, useful for larger rooms. Requires 300 heating units.</RadiatorLarge.description>
  <RadiatorLarge.label>Large Radiator</RadiatorLarge.label>
  <RadiatorStuffed.label>Radiator</RadiatorStuffed.label>
  <SolarHeater.description>Uses sunlight to heat hot water tanks and radiators. 0-2000 units of heating power depending on light level and ambient temperature.</SolarHeater.description>
  <SolarHeater.label>Solar Heater</SolarHeater.label>
  <Thermostat.description>Used to control electric and gas boilers. More than 1 can be placed. Connects via standard plumbing.</Thermostat.description>
  <Thermostat.label>Thermostat</Thermostat.label>
</LanguageData>
