<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <DeepWaterWellInlet.description>Accesses a large area of ground water which can be pumped by water pumps. Deep wells are unaffected by pollution.</DeepWaterWellInlet.description>
  <DeepWaterWellInlet.label>Deep Water Well</DeepWaterWellInlet.label>
  <ElectricPump.description>Pumps water from wells to water towers. Pumping capacity: 1500 L/day</ElectricPump.description>
  <ElectricPump.label>Electric Pump</ElectricPump.label>
  <PumpingStation.description>Pumps water from wells to water towers. Pumping capacity: 10000 L/day</PumpingStation.description>
  <PumpingStation.label>Pumping Station</PumpingStation.label>
  <SewageOutlet.description>Can be placed anywhere. Sewage will pool and spread on land or disperse in water. Sewage cleans up over time; the presence of trees, water or rain will speed this up.</SewageOutlet.description>
  <SewageOutlet.label>Sewage outlet</SewageOutlet.label>
  <SewageSepticTank.description>Slowly cleans sewage over time. Sewage is directed to septic tanks first. If it reaches full capacity then excess sewage is sent to sewage outlets.</SewageSepticTank.description>
  <SewageSepticTank.label>Septic Tank</SewageSepticTank.label>
  <SewageTreatment.description>Slowly cleans sewage over time. If it reaches full capacity then excess sewage is sent directly to sewage outlets without treatment.</SewageTreatment.description>
  <SewageTreatment.label>Sewage Treatment</SewageTreatment.label>
  <WaterButt.label>Water Butt</WaterButt.label>
  <WaterTowerL.label>Huge Water Tower</WaterTowerL.label>
  <WaterTowerS.label>Water Tower</WaterTowerS.label>
  <WaterTreatment.description>Cleans 99.99% of germs! Filters existing water in storage towers, and any water used by fixtures, eliminating the risk of disease</WaterTreatment.description>
  <WaterTreatment.label>Water Treatment</WaterTreatment.label>
  <WaterWellInlet.description>Accesses ground water which can be pumped by water pumps. The presence of sewage or other pollution will reduce water quality and can cause contamination.</WaterWellInlet.description>
  <WaterWellInlet.label>Water Well</WaterWellInlet.label>
  <WindPump.description>Pumps water from wells to water towers. Pumping capacity: 3000 L/day</WindPump.description>
  <WindPump.label>Wind Pump</WindPump.label>
</LanguageData>
