<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <AirConditioning.description>Build Wattz heaters and Appalachia Freeze coolers to keep rooms livable in any season, or to maintain proper freezer temperatures.</AirConditioning.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.description>Build compact Poseidon home reactors that burn bioferrite and drive enormous amounts of heat into the surrounding air.</AtmosphericHeater.description>
  <AtmosphericHeater.label>Poseidon home reactor</AtmosphericHeater.label>
  <Batteries.description>Develop Poseidon battery banks for storing reserve grid power with the sort of reassuring pre-War safety language that usually meant the opposite.</Batteries.description>
  <BioferriteGenerator.description>Build power generators that burn bioferrite as a fuel. Bioferrite keeps its own identity here, but the hardware around it can still read like a desperate late-era Poseidon project.</BioferriteGenerator.description>
  <BiofuelRefining.description>Build refinery equipment that converts biological feedstock into oil for generators, burners, and industrial systems.</BiofuelRefining.description>
  <DeepDrilling.description>Build Corvega deep drills for extracting resources from underground. You will still need a ground-penetrating scanner to find the best seams.</DeepDrilling.description>
  <FlatscreenTelevision.description>Produce Radiation King flatscreen televisions for greater comfort and entertainment.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>
  <HospitalBed.description>Construct Med-Tek hospital beds that improve medical outcomes and turn a rough frontier ward into something closer to a pre-War clinic.</HospitalBed.description>
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.description>Work with advanced microelectronics, unlocking Wattz utility electronics, Radiation King entertainment systems, and more sophisticated industrial control equipment.</MicroelectronicsBasics.description>
  <NutrientPaste.description>Build industrial food dispensers that turn organic feedstocks into edible paste with efficient, relentlessly impersonal pre-War engineering.</NutrientPaste.description>
  <SolarPanels.description>Build Poseidon Civilian Helios Two solar panels for domestic and settlement-scale electricity generation.</SolarPanels.description>
  <SolarPanels.label>Civilian Helios Two</SolarPanels.label>
  <TubeTelevision.description>Produce Radiation King tube televisions for recreational watching and proper retro-futurist living room culture.</TubeTelevision.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedBatteries.description>Develop pre-War Poseidon battery units capable of storing large amounts of energy with minimal loss.</VFE_AdvancedBatteries.description>
  <VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.description>Recover advanced Poseidon generation hardware, including solar arrays, hydro units, and high-capacity turbine systems.</VFE_AdvancedPowerSources.description>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.description>Construct basic Corvega works, including conveyors, underground transfer points, and factory hoppers for automating routine industrial tasks around the colony.</VFE_BasicFactories.description>
  <VFE_BasicFactories.label>Corvega basic works</VFE_BasicFactories.label>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.description>Construct specialized Corvega factory systems capable of manufacturing components, producing alloy stock, and handling other advanced automated production jobs.</VFE_ComplexFactories.description>
  <VFE_ComplexFactories.label>Corvega advanced works</VFE_ComplexFactories.label>
  <VFE_IndustrialGenerators.description>Develop heavy-duty Poseidon generator systems built to store more fuel and feed more power into the grid.</VFE_IndustrialGenerators.description>
  <VFE_Manufacturing.description>Establish larger Corvega production benches and powered industrial work centers for high-throughput fabrication, assembly, and finishing.</VFE_Manufacturing.description>
  <VFE_Manufacturing.label>Corvega manufacturing</VFE_Manufacturing.label>
  <VFE_NuclearPower.description>Restore the harshest end of the pre-War power ladder: compact reactor systems with enormous output and equally severe failure risks.</VFE_NuclearPower.description>
  <VFE_TidalPower.description>Build Poseidon tidal generators on open water to supply steady industrial power from current and surf.</VFE_TidalPower.description>
  <VHGE_GasExtraction.description>Research propane deposits and the pipe-fed burner systems that let it function as a compact industrial fuel.</VHGE_GasExtraction.description>
  <VHGE_GasExtraction.label>propane extraction</VHGE_GasExtraction.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Develop Med-Tek patient telemetry rigs that improve surgery outcomes and long-term recovery when mounted beside a hospital bed.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.description>Develop basic waste recovery systems for turning toxic refuse into usable industrial feedstock.</VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.description>
  <VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.label>Poseidon waste recovery</VRecyclingE_BasicRecycling.label>
  <VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.description>Expand waste recovery into sealed reclamation lines for alloy, isotope, and compacted refuse products.</VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.description>
  <VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.label>Poseidon advanced reclamation</VRecyclingE_ComplexRecycling.label>
  <VTE_HVAC.description>Build a reliable climate-control system connecting Wattz control hardware to Appalachia Freeze cooling equipment and related ventilation components.</VTE_HVAC.description>
  <WatermillGenerator.description>Build Poseidon hydro generators on rivers to generate a steady supply of power.</WatermillGenerator.description>
</LanguageData>