<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<LanguageData>
  <MechanoidSignal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You've detected a signal from a robot ship in orbit. The ship has malfunctioned and is slowly losing altitude.

By falsely responding to the signal you can make the ship crash-land nearby, letting you salvage prototype Hellion hardware.</MechanoidSignal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <MechanoidSignal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>gravEngineSpawnedLetterLabel-&gt;Hellion reactor</MechanoidSignal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <MechanoidSignal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>gravEngineSpawnedLetterText-&gt;The robot ship has crash-landed nearby.

It contains an intact Hellion reactor. The assembly can lift a heavily armored aircraft or orbital platform while operating near a planet, making it ideal for long-range travel and orbital insertion.

Inspect the reactor to make use of it.</MechanoidSignal.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <GravEngine.questNameRules.rulesStrings.0>questName-&gt;the Hellion</GravEngine.questNameRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <GravEngine.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You've discovered a robot Hellion reactor. You can use it to rebuild the Hellion and rapidly move around the planet.

The reactor includes instrumentation that passively scans for compatible pre-war components. Recovering those components will let you upgrade the Hellion over time.</GravEngine.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_MechanoidRelay.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. It is powering a relay that is part of a huge robot communication network.

      You can disassemble the relay, but the process will take days to complete. The relay itself will be heavily defended by robots.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</Gravcore_MechanoidRelay.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_MechanoidRelay.questContentRules.rulesStrings.1>letterTextMapGenerated-&gt;A robot relay is nearby, powered by a reactor core.

The relay is currently protected by nearby stabilizers. Extract the reactor core by first hacking or destroying all the stabilizers.

Be careful, destroying a stabilizer will prompt a defensive response. Hacking is a slower but safer option.</Gravcore_MechanoidRelay.questContentRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <Gravcore_InsectLair.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The source lies in a cave system deep underground. The entrance is marked on the world map.

Subterranean caves can be extremely dangerous and may take days to explore.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</Gravcore_InsectLair.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_AncientReactor.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The source originates from an ancient decaying reactor. The location is marked on the world map.

Cracks in the reactor's shielding are leaking harmful material, bathing the nearby area in toxic fallout. The reactor itself will be heavily guarded by ancient security systems.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</Gravcore_AncientReactor.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_OrbitalMechanoidPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The source is an orbital robot platform. Scans reveal a heavy defensive presence.

You can travel to orbital platforms using the Hellion, shuttles, or transport pods.

Be careful, orbital locations are extremely dangerous. Equip your colonists with vacsuits. Plan your return trip, as living in orbit for long periods is very difficult.</Gravcore_OrbitalMechanoidPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_AncientStockpile.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The source originates from an ancient underground stockpile. The location is marked on the world map.

Underground stockpiles must be hacked to enter. This process can take days to complete.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</Gravcore_AncientStockpile.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_CrashedMechanoidPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The source is coming from the wreckage of a crashed orbital platform.

Scans reveal a heavy robot presence.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</Gravcore_CrashedMechanoidPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_OrbitalAncientPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The source is coming from an abandoned orbital platform.

You can travel to orbital platforms using the Hellion, shuttles, or transport pods.

Be careful, orbital locations are extremely dangerous. Equip your colonists with vacsuits. Plan your return trip, as living in orbit for long periods is very difficult.</Gravcore_OrbitalAncientPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_FrozenTerraformer.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected the signal of a reactor core. The core is powering a malfunctioning ancient terraformer. Its location is marked on the world map.

The terraformer is cooling the local region to dangerously low temperatures. Be prepared for cold weather and a long stay.

Recover reactor cores and airframe panels to expand your Hellion.</Gravcore_FrozenTerraformer.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <Gravcore_Mechhive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;You have detected a huge Hellion-systems energy spike originating from a robot command hub in orbit. Its location is marked on the world map.

      This robot command hub is the center of robot coordination on this planet. Shutting it down will disable all murderous robots planet-wide. Alternatively, you may be able to use the command hub for your own purposes.

      The robot command hub is defended with anti-ship weapons. Build an ECM suite before approaching it.

      Be warned, robot command hubs are extremely dangerous. Finish exploring other locations first and ensure you're prepared for a long stay in orbit.</Gravcore_Mechhive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <GravshipWreckage.questNameRules.rulesStrings.0>questName-&gt;Hellion wreckage</GravshipWreckage.questNameRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <GravshipWreckage.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription(askerIsNull==true)-&gt;You've intercepted the distress beacon from a crashed Hellion. The wreckage contains valuable pre-war flight hardware. Be careful - it is guarded by hostile robots.</GravshipWreckage.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <GravshipWreckage.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==true)-&gt;[asker_faction_leaderTitle] [asker_nameFull] of [asker_faction_name] has shared with you the location of a crashed Hellion. [asker_pronoun] heard of your study of reactor-core technology and thought you might be interested in scavenging whatever pre-war flight hardware remains. [asker_nameDef] warns you that the crash site is guarded by hostile robots.</GravshipWreckage.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <GravshipWreckage.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription(asker_royalInCurrentFaction==true)-&gt;[asker_nameFull], a [asker_royalTitleInCurrentFaction] of [asker_faction_name], demands that you destroy a number of bothersome robots that are harassing a nearby settlement. The robots are guarding the wreckage of a Hellion. If you destroy them, [asker_nameDef] will let you keep whatever pre-war flight hardware you're able to scavenge.</GravshipWreckage.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <OpportunitySite_Asteroid.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;[discoveryMethod] the location of an asteroid orbiting the planet. It contains significant amounts of [resource], and potentially other resources as well.

Orbital miners steer asteroids into orbit so that they can be mined and the ore sold to orbital traders. You do not detect any signs of life from this asteroid.

You can reach the asteroid with transport pods, shuttles, or the Hellion. Equip your colonists with sufficient orbital apparel before departing.</OpportunitySite_Asteroid.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <OpportunitySite_AbandonedPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;[discoveryMethod] the location of an abandoned orbital platform. You don't detect any signs of life.

You can break in to obtain the loot inside, but the platform probably has defense systems.

You can travel to orbital locations using the Hellion, shuttles, or transport pods.</OpportunitySite_AbandonedPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <OpportunitySite_OrbitalWreck.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;[discoveryMethod] the coordinates of a massive piece of wreckage in orbit. It could contain valuable resources. Orbital debris fields are often occupied by hostile scavengers.

You can travel to orbital locations using the Hellion, shuttles, or transport pods.</OpportunitySite_OrbitalWreck.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <OpportunitySite_MechanoidPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;[discoveryMethod] the location of an orbital platform. You detect high levels of robot activity.

You can scavenge valuables from the platform.

You can travel to orbital locations using the Hellion, shuttles, or transport pods.</OpportunitySite_MechanoidPlatform.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <OpportunitySite_Satellite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription-&gt;[discoveryMethod] the location of an orbital satellite. These satellites are unmanned and often incapable of supporting life. Satellites serve a wide variety of purposes, from power collection to weapons platforms.

You can scavenge valuable technology from the satellites but be warned, satellites are heavily guarded by ancient security systems.

You can travel to orbital locations using the Hellion, shuttles, or transport pods.</OpportunitySite_Satellite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <SurveySite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription(askerIsNull==true)-&gt;An anonymous AI has requested your help defending surveying equipment at a remote site.

The surveying operation will take ten to fifteen days and will require traveling to a remote destination.

In exchange for your services, the AI is offering a valuable Hellion component.</SurveySite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <SurveySite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==true)-&gt;[asker_faction_leaderTitle] [asker_nameFull] of [asker_faction_name] has heard rumors of your Hellion. [asker_pronoun] wants to survey a distant region and asks that you protect [asker_possessive] surveying equipment.

The surveying operation will take ten to fifteen days and will require traveling to a remote destination.

In exchange for your services, [asker_nameDef] is offering a valuable Hellion component.</SurveySite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <SurveySite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription(asker_royalInCurrentFaction==true)-&gt;[asker_nameFull], a [asker_royalTitleInCurrentFaction] of [asker_faction_name], requests that you protect [asker_possessive] surveying operation. If you do so, [asker_pronoun] will reward you handsomely.

The surveying operation will take ten to fifteen days and will require traveling to a remote destination.

In exchange for your services, [asker_nameDef] is offering a valuable Hellion component.</SurveySite.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
  <OrbitalFugitive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>questDescription(askerIsNull==true)-&gt;An anonymous AI has requested your help dealing with an outlaw named [fugitive_nameDef]. The AI claims [fugitive_nameDef] is wanted for [reason_AI].

[fugitive_nameDef] has stolen a transport pod and has fled to an abandoned orbital platform.

Having heard rumors of your Hellion, the AI requests that you travel to the abandoned platform and kill [fugitive_nameDef]. In return, it will reward you with a valuable Hellion component.

The AI warns you that [fugitive_nameDef] may be in the company of hostile orbital pirates.</OrbitalFugitive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.0>
  <OrbitalFugitive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>questDescription(asker_factionLeader==true)-&gt;[asker_faction_leaderTitle] [asker_nameFull] of [asker_faction_name] has sent us a message. A fugitive named [fugitive_nameDef] escaped from [asker_possessive] custody and used a transport pod to flee to an abandoned orbital platform. [fugitive_nameDef] was in custody for [reason].

Having heard rumors of your Hellion, the [asker_faction_leaderTitle] asks that you travel to the abandoned platform and kill [fugitive_nameDef]. If you do so, [asker_nameDef] will reward you with a valuable Hellion component.

[asker_nameDef] warns you that [fugitive_nameDef] may be in the company of hostile orbital pirates.</OrbitalFugitive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.1>
  <OrbitalFugitive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>questDescription(asker_royalInCurrentFaction==true)-&gt;[asker_nameFull], a [asker_royalTitleInCurrentFaction] of [asker_faction_name], requests that you track down and kill a dangerous fugitive known as [fugitive_nameDef]. The fugitive is wanted for [reason_royal].

[fugitive_nameDef] is hiding out on an abandoned orbital platform and may be guarded by orbital pirates. If you kill the fugitive, [asker_nameDef] will reward you with a valuable Hellion component.</OrbitalFugitive.questDescriptionRules.rulesStrings.2>
</LanguageData>