<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationSequence" MayRequire="VanillaExpanded.VNutrientE">
		<success>Always</success>
		<operations>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Mama Dolce nutrient grinder that reduces organic feedstocks into pipeline-ready paste stock. Efficient, impersonal, and very much in the spirit of industrial pre-War food engineering.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteTap"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Mama Dolce paste tap that dispenses prepared nutrient meals from the vat network. It is the kind of practical cafeteria hardware a large contractor would install by the hundred.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A compact Mama Dolce feeder that outputs nutrient paste from the pipe network for routine worker consumption.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A bedside Mama Dolce feeding device that delivers nutrient paste directly to bedridden patients when linked to a nutrient vat. Practical, clinical, and just unsettling enough to feel authentic.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteVat"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Mama Dolce storage vat for holding large volumes of processed nutrient paste. Destroying one makes exactly the kind of industrial mess you would expect.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/*[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteDripper"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A bedside Med-Tek feeding device that delivers nutrient paste directly to bedridden patients when linked to a nutrient vat. Practical, clinical, and just unsettling enough to feel authentic.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/*[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteFeeder"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A compact Corvega feeder that outputs nutrient paste from the pipe network for routine worker consumption.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/*[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteGrinder"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Corvega nutrient grinder that reduces organic feedstocks into pipeline-ready paste stock. Efficient, impersonal, and very much in the spirit of industrial pre-War food engineering.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/*[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteTap"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Corvega paste tap that dispenses prepared nutrient meals from the vat network. It is the kind of practical cafeteria hardware a large contractor would install by the hundred.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/*[defName="VNPE_NutrientPasteVat"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>A Corvega storage vat for holding large volumes of processed nutrient paste. Destroying one makes exactly the kind of industrial mess you would expect.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
		</operations>
	</Operation>
</Patch>