<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <!-- Mechanitor (RobCo) -->
    <LetterLabelMechsFeral>RobCo bot(s) gone rogue</LetterLabelMechsFeral>
    <LetterMechsFeral>Some RobCo bot(s) have linked with ancient RobCo control signals. They have joined {0} and become hostile, trying to escape the area.

Rogue RobCo bots cannot be resurrected at a gestator when destroyed.

These bots are involved:

{1}</LetterMechsFeral>
    <LetterLabelMechlinkInstalled>RobCo Pipboy equipped</LetterLabelMechlinkInstalled>
    <LetterMechlinkInstalled>{PAWN_labelShort} has equipped a RobCo Pipboy! {PAWN_pronoun} is now a RobCo mechanic and can create and control RobCo bots.

Research RobCo technology to get started.

(*SectionTitle)Creating bots:(/SectionTitle) Your mechanic can create bots at a RobCo workbench.

(*SectionTitle)About bandwidth:(/SectionTitle) Mechanitors can control as many bots as their total bandwidth allows. Select {PAWN_labelShort} and look at {PAWN_possessive} 'Bandwidth' readout to see how much bandwidth {PAWN_pronoun} is currently using and how much {PAWN_pronoun} has available. Bandwidth can be increased with certain apparel and by building RobCo band node buildings.

(*SectionTitle)About control groups:(/SectionTitle) Mechanics control bots in groups. Each control group can be set to one of these modes:

- Work
- Escort
- Recharge
- Dormant self-charge

To learn more about what each mode does, select the work mode icon on one of {PAWN_labelShort}'s control groups and hover over the different work orders. The maximum number of control groups can be increased with apparel and holotapes.

(*SectionTitle)About threat calling:(/SectionTitle) Mechanics can signal ancient leader bots to attack in order to obtain rare items from them. You must do this to improve your mechanitor past certain limits, but beware the danger.</LetterMechlinkInstalled>
    <LetterLabelMechanitorCasketOpened>{PAWN_nameDef}'s RobCo Pipboy available</LetterLabelMechanitorCasketOpened>
    <LetterMechanitorCasketOpened>You have found the corpse of an ancient RobCo mechanic!

Extract {PAWN_possessive} RobCo Pipboy by selecting a colonist and right-clicking the corpse.</LetterMechanitorCasketOpened>
</LanguageData>