<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Feral_People.description>Feral people live in harmony with the Treefather, relying on hunting and gathering for survival in the wasteland.</Feral_People.description>
  <Tree_Worshippers.description>Followers revere the Treefather, a mutated tree that produces treeminders and pods, and maintain a sacred bond with nature.</Tree_Worshippers.description>
  <VME_Cosmic_Cultists.description>The lights above and the ruined world below both speak in signs. We read the sky for warnings, promises, and the fate waiting out in the wastes.</VME_Cosmic_Cultists.description>
  <VME_Cosmic_Cultists.label>omen cultists</VME_Cosmic_Cultists.label>
  <VME_Dwarven_Artificers.description>No day is better spent than one in a hot forge. With hammers, kilns, and scrap steel, we turn hidden workshops into the backbone of a hard underground life.</VME_Dwarven_Artificers.description>
  <VME_Dwarven_Artificers.label>forge clans</VME_Dwarven_Artificers.label>
  <VME_Eastern_Revivalists.description>We believe the old world still holds lessons worth reviving. Discipline, ritual, and a sharpened blade keep a people alive when former brothers turn on each other.</VME_Eastern_Revivalists.description>
  <VME_Eastern_Revivalists.label>old-world revivalists</VME_Eastern_Revivalists.label>
  <VME_GodKing_Radicals.description>The iron rule of our supreme leader should never come into question. If those who oppose us will not kneel, we will break them until they do.</VME_GodKing_Radicals.description>
  <VME_GodKing_Radicals.label>cult radicals</VME_GodKing_Radicals.label>
  <VME_Medieval_Monarchists.description>Our forebears survived by following warlords, bosses, and local strongmen, and we see no reason to change now. If neighboring settlements prefer blades and tribute, then tribute is what they will pay.</VME_Medieval_Monarchists.description>
  <VME_Medieval_Monarchists.label>feudal overlords</VME_Medieval_Monarchists.label>
  <VME_Nordic_Matriarchy.description>Through winter storms and broken coastlines, our shield-mothers lead the people. Die with honor or answer to the women who keep the warbands together.</VME_Nordic_Matriarchy.description>
  <VME_Nordic_Matriarchy.label>raider matriarchy</VME_Nordic_Matriarchy.label>
</LanguageData>