<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.description>These grotesque mutated rodents live underground in vast tunnel networks. They breed rapidly and swarm in large numbers when disturbed. Originally simple wasteland vermin, their population has exploded in underground areas where they create extensive burrow systems. They are aggressive, territorial, and attack anything that enters their domain.</FCP_Faction_Molerat.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.fixedName>Mole Rat Colony</FCP_Faction_Molerat.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.label>mole rat colony</FCP_Faction_Molerat.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnSingular>mole rat</FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnsPlural>mole rats</FCP_Faction_Molerat.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.description>The Brotherhood of Steel is one of the oldest still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their small numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.fixedName>Brotherhood of Steel</FCP_Faction_BoS.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.ideoDescription>Under Elder Maxson, the Brotherhood has united discipline with purpose. We preserve technology, we protect humanity from itself, and we destroy the abominations that threaten our future. Steel be with us.</FCP_Faction_BoS.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.label>Brotherhood of Steel</FCP_Faction_BoS.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.leaderTitle>Elder</FCP_Faction_BoS.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS.royalFavorLabel>Honor</FCP_Faction_BoS.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.description>The Lost Hills Chapter is the original Brotherhood of Steel, founded by Roger Maxson in the ruins of the Mariposa Military Base. As the first and founding chapter, Lost Hills represents the purest form of the Brotherhood's ideals - technological preservation, military discipline, and isolationist philosophy. They are the keepers of the original Codex and consider themselves the supreme authority over all Brotherhood chapters. Their fortress in the Lost Hills bunker complex remains one of the most technologically advanced facilities in the wasteland, housing pre-war military hardware and the Brotherhood's most elite soldiers.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.fixedName>Lost Hills Chapter</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.ideoDescription>We are the original Brotherhood of Steel, keepers of the true Codex as written by Roger Maxson. Technology must be preserved by those of pure bloodline. Outsiders cannot be trusted with our secrets or our legacy. We are the shield that protects humanity's technological heritage - isolation is our strength, purity is our path.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.label>Lost Hills Chapter</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.leaderTitle>Elder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.royalFavorLabel>Honor</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lost_Hills.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.description>The Midwestern Brotherhood of Steel broke away from the main order during an airship expedition that crash-landed in the Midwest. Unlike their Western counterparts, the Midwestern chapter has adopted a more pragmatic and expansionist philosophy, actively recruiting tribals and wastelanders into their ranks. They maintain the Brotherhood's devotion to technology and military prowess, but have shed much of the isolationism that defines other chapters. Their territory spans vast stretches of the former American Midwest, making them one of the largest and most diverse Brotherhood chapters, though they remain estranged from Lost Hills' authority.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.fixedName>Midwestern Brotherhood</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.ideoDescription>We are the Brotherhood evolved. When our airships crashed in the Midwest, we learned that survival demands adaptation. We recruit the worthy - tribals, wastelanders, even former enemies - because strength comes from unity, not isolation. The Codex guides us, but does not chain us. We expand, we protect, we endure.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.label>Midwestern Brotherhood</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.leaderTitle>General</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.royalFavorLabel>Honor</FCP_Faction_BoS_Midwest.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>The Appalachia Chapter stands at a crossroads. Cut off from Lost Hills and forced to operate independently, you must decide your chapter's path: will you follow "The Chain That Binds" - the strict Codex doctrine that demands technological preservation above all else? Or will you break from tradition and become protectors of the wasteland's people, proving the Brotherhood can be more than collectors? Your isolation means no oversight, no reinforcements, but complete freedom to define what the Brotherhood truly stands for in these lands.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>Appalachia Chapter</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>Paladin</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Appalachia_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uphold their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>Lyons' Pride Remnants</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>Elder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>The Mojave Chapter of the Brotherhood of Steel is a shadow of its former self, forced out of the Hidden Valley bunker and now struggling to survive in the harsh Mojave wasteland. Once a proud and disciplined force, they have been reduced to a scattered group, clinging to their mission of safeguarding humanity's technological heritage. Despite their diminished state, their mastery of power armor and energy weapons ensures they remain a formidable presence in the region.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>Mojave Chapter</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>Elder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Mojave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the Brotherhood of Steel, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uphold the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>Brotherhood Outcasts</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>Protector</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>Outcast</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>Outcasts</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>The Brotherhood of Steel is one of the oldest still existing factions in the wasteland. It was founded just before and during the great war itself. True to its army origin, the Brotherhood is a militarised society, based on discipline, prowess, and reliability. However, there are a great number of Brotherhood chapters with often strongly deviating philosophies. Some might see themselves as the sole protectors of humanity and act noble and chivalrous, while others might see outsiders as clueless degenerates unfit for the technological marvels they might possess. Among the few things shared by all chapters of the Brotherhood is their obsession with technology (and the safeguarding of it) and their imposing suits of power armour which make them, despite their small numbers, one of the most powerful groups in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>Brotherhood of Steel</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>Elder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.description>The Lyons' Pride remnants are a faction of disciplined and technologically advanced warriors, striving to preserve the ideals of their late leader, Elder Lyons. Once a proud and unified chapter, they now operate as a fragmented yet determined group, clinging to their mission of protecting humanity and safeguarding advanced technology. Though their numbers have dwindled, their resolve remains unshaken, and they continue to uphold their code of honor amidst the chaos of the wasteland. Their advanced weaponry, power armor, and tactical expertise make them a formidable force, whether as allies or adversaries.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.fixedName>Lyons' Pride Remnants</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.ideoDescription>Elder Lyons taught us that technology without compassion is worthless. We are the shield of the people, protectors of the innocent, and proof that the Brotherhood can be more than collectors of artifacts.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.label>Lyons' Pride Remnants</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.leaderTitle>Elder</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnSingular>Brother</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnsPlural>Brothers</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>Pride Honor</FCP_Faction_BoS_Lyons_Pride_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>The Outcast Remnants are a hardened splinter group of the Brotherhood of Steel, formed by those who rejected the Brotherhood's changing ideals and chose to uphold the original mission: the recovery and preservation of advanced technology at any cost. Isolated from their former brothers, the Outcasts are fiercely independent, pragmatic, and often distrustful of outsiders. Their camps are fortified, their patrols relentless, and their loyalty to their cause unwavering. Though their numbers are few, their discipline, technical expertise, and mastery of power armor make them a formidable force in the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.description>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.fixedName>Brotherhood Outcasts</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.ideoDescription>We are the keepers of the true Brotherhood mission. Technology must be preserved at all costs. Outsiders cannot be trusted with the power of the Old World. The Codex is law.</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>Brotherhood Outcasts</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.label>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.leaderTitle>Protector</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnSingular>Outcast</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnsPlural>Outcasts</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>Tech Scrip</FCP_Faction_BoS_Outcast_Remnants.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.0.nameType.name>Caesar</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.0.nameType.name>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.1.nameType.name>Mars</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.deityPresets.1.nameType.name>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.description>Caesar’s Legion is the fearsome group which conquered most of the former states of Arizona, New Mexico, Colorado, and Utah. The Legion styles itself after the ancient roman legionnaires and uses many low-tech weapons such as javelins and crude but effective melee weapons. They are cruel, warlike, and known to frequently commit massacres against civilians, which they view as dissolute and profligate. Caesar, or Edward Sallow as he was once known, leads his slave armies as an iron fisted dictator and pushes them ever forward to claim new territories for their leader, the self-proclaimed son of Mars himself. Before long, the Legion stood at the shores of the Colorado river and set their eyes on the gleaming towers of New Vegas and California beyond them.</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.fixedName>Caesar's Legion</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.ideoDescription>Caesar, the Son of Mars, was ordered by Mars to conquer all of Earth. To facilitate this conquest, Mars cleansed the Earth with fire, bringing humans to their lowest ebb. The Caesar's divine duty is to deliver the wasteland from chaos and barbarism</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.label>Caesar's Legion</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.leaderTitle>Caesar</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnSingular>Legionary</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnsPlural>Legionaries</FCP_Faction_Caesars_Legion.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.description>Ruthless remnants of the old world government, the Enclave believe themselves to be humanity’s rightful rulers. Isolated, technologically advanced, and fiercely nationalistic, they seek to restore civilization under their iron-fisted vision—no matter the cost to outsiders.</FCP_Faction_Enclave.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.fixedName>The Enclave</FCP_Faction_Enclave.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.ideoDescription>The Enclave represents the continuation of the United States government, destined to reclaim and restore America. Only pure, untainted humans have the right to rebuild civilization. All others are aberrations to be removed or subjugated.</FCP_Faction_Enclave.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.label>The Enclave</FCP_Faction_Enclave.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.leaderTitle>President</FCP_Faction_Enclave.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnSingular>Constituent</FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnsPlural>Constituents</FCP_Faction_Enclave.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave.royalFavorLabel>authority</FCP_Faction_Enclave.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.description>You are operatives of the Enclave, the shadow government that considers itself the rightful heir to the United States of America. Armed with advanced pre-war technology and an unwavering belief in your genetic and technological superiority, you seek to restore America to its former glory - by any means necessary. The wasteland is filled with mutants and degenerates who have no place in the new America you will build.</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.label>The Enclave</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.leaderTitle>Colonel</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnSingular>Agent</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnsPlural>Agents</FCP_Faction_Enclave_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.description>The Great Khans are a tribal raider society that traces its roots back to the pre-war biker gangs of California. Once one of the most powerful raider tribes in the wasteland, they have endured numerous conflicts with the NCR and other factions that have decimated their numbers. Despite their setbacks, the Khans remain proud and fiercely independent, refusing to bow to anyone. They have become experts at producing chems, which they trade for weapons and supplies. The Khans value strength, loyalty to the tribe, and the freedom to live as they choose - free from the laws and taxes of "civilized" societies. They are a nomadic people, living in yurts and tents that can be quickly packed up when it's time to move on.</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.description>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.fixedName>Great Khans</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.ideoDescription>The Great Khans live by a code of strength, independence, and loyalty to the tribe. They reject the rules and restrictions of "civilized" society, preferring to take what they need and live free. The strong survive, the weak perish, and the tribe endures above all else.</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.label>Great Khans</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.label>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.leaderTitle>Papa Khan</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnSingular>Khan</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnsPlural>Khans</FCP_Faction_GreatKhans.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.description>The New California Republic is a faction based out of Shady Sands in the former state of California. It is a federal parliamentary republic, similar to the pre-war USA before it descended into authoritarianism. They represent the old world and its values. Roads, taxes, prisons, elections, and other phenomena long forgotten made a comeback with the NCR’s rise to power. It is seen by its citizens to be the sole haven of civilisation, democracy, and freedom in the wasteland. While there certainly is truth to that notion, the NCR also suffers from widespread corruption and oligarchic tendencies, for much power is held by exceedingly rich ranchers and farm owners. Furthermore, it uses its vast military, well supplied by their industrial centres, to aggressively expand their territory and claim the resources of neighbouring regions to sate the ever-growing hunger of its population.</FCP_Faction_NCR.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.fixedName>New California Republic</FCP_Faction_NCR.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.ideoDescription>Founded on principles of freedom and liberty, the Republic has been putting these into practice over the years. The most important achievement was the banning of slavery in NCR territories, thanks to concerted efforts of influential politicians and the Rangers.</FCP_Faction_NCR.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.label>New California Republic</FCP_Faction_NCR.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>President</FCP_Faction_NCR.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>New Californian</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>New Californians</FCP_Faction_NCR.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR.royalFavorLabel>Service Points</FCP_Faction_NCR.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>A rogue faction of former NCR soldiers and officers who have deserted the Republic. Disillusioned with the NCR's leadership, they now operate as a hostile paramilitary group, surviving through raids and mercenary work. Their organization is loose, but they are led by a cunning Rogue Colonel.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.fixedName>NCR Deserters</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.ideoDescription>Once loyal to the Republic, these deserters have turned away from its broken promises and endless wars. Disillusioned by corruption and failed leadership, they now value survival, freedom, and loyalty to their own above all else. Their ideals are forged in hardship, camaraderie, and a deep distrust of authority. They do what it takes to endure in the wasteland, bound together by necessity and shared experience rather than old world dogma.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>NCR Deserters</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>Rogue Colonel</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>NCR Deserter</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>NCR Deserters</FCP_Faction_NCR_Deserters.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>The New California Republic is a democratic federation founded on the principles of law, order, and progress. As the NCR, you lead a colony striving to restore civilization and expand its influence across the wasteland.</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.description>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>NCR Player Colony</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.label>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>Governor</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>Citizen</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>Citizens</FCP_Faction_NCR_Player.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.description>Founded on ideals of collectivism, harmony, and technological advancement, the People's Republic of China is a nation of bustling cities, rich cultural heritage, and a strong sense of community. Beneath the surface, however, growing censorship, state control, and military expansion shape daily life. Citizens enjoy rapid modernization, vibrant traditions, and national pride, even as the specter of international conflict looms ever closer.</FCP_Faction_PRC.description>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.fixedName>People's Republic of China</FCP_Faction_PRC.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.ideoDescription>The Year of the Dragon ideology values national unity, collective effort, and technological progress. It encourages loyalty to the state, respect for tradition, and pride in cultural heritage. Citizens are expected to work together for the good of the nation, maintain social harmony, and embrace innovation, believing that unity and determination will bring prosperity and strength.</FCP_Faction_PRC.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.label>People's Republic of China</FCP_Faction_PRC.label>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.leaderTitle>Supreme Leader</FCP_Faction_PRC.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnSingular>Chinese</FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnsPlural>Chinese</FCP_Faction_PRC.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_PRC.royalFavorLabel>Social Credits</FCP_Faction_PRC.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.description>The Raider Gangs are a loose confederation of bandit groups operating in the wasteland. They are known for their brutal tactics, scavenging, and raiding of settlements. While they often fight among themselves, they can unite against common foes. The Raiders reject the old world values and instead embrace a survival-of-the-fittest mentality. They are feared and despised by many, but also hold a certain allure for those seeking freedom from the constraints of civilization.</FCP_Faction_Raider.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.fixedName>Raider Gangs</FCP_Faction_Raider.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.ideoDescription>Founded on principles of survival and strength, the Raider Gangs believe in taking what they need by force. They reject the old world's values and embrace a brutal code of conduct where only the strong survive.</FCP_Faction_Raider.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.label>Raider Gangs</FCP_Faction_Raider.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.leaderTitle>Raider Boss</FCP_Faction_Raider.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnSingular>Raider</FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnsPlural>Raiders</FCP_Faction_Raider.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Raider.royalFavorLabel>Trophies</FCP_Faction_Raider.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.description>Founded on ideals of freedom, prosperity, and technological progress, America is a nation of gleaming cities, suburban comfort, and boundless optimism. Beneath the surface, however, growing paranoia, corporate influence, and military escalation shaped daily life. Citizens enjoyed advanced conveniences, colorful pop culture, and patriotic pride, even as the shadow of nuclear war looms ever closer.</FCP_Faction_USA.description>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.fixedName>United States of America</FCP_Faction_USA.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.ideoDescription>The American Dream is the belief that anyone, regardless of their background, can achieve success and prosperity through hard work and determination. It embodies the ideals of freedom, equality, and opportunity that the United States was founded upon.</FCP_Faction_USA.ideoDescription>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.label>United States of America</FCP_Faction_USA.label>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.leaderTitle>President</FCP_Faction_USA.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.pawnSingular>American</FCP_Faction_USA.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.pawnsPlural>Americans</FCP_Faction_USA.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_USA.royalFavorLabel>Service Points</FCP_Faction_USA.royalFavorLabel>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.description>Small communities of wastelanders who have banded together to survive in the harsh post-war world. These settlers live in ramshackle towns, trading scrap and salvaged goods while trying to maintain some semblance of civilization. They're cautious but not hostile, willing to trade with strangers but always wary of raiders and other threats. Most are just trying to scrape by, growing mutated crops, herding brahmin, and defending what little they have.</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.description>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.fixedName>Wasteland Settlements</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.label>Wasteland Settlers</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.leaderTitle>Mayor</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.leaderTitle>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnSingular>settler</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnsPlural>settlers</FCP_Faction_Wasteland_Settlers.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.fixedName>Wasteland Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.label>Wastelander Techprint Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnSingular>Wasteland Trader</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnsPlural>Wasteland Traders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelander_Techprint_Traders.pawnsPlural>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.fixedName>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.fixedName>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.label>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.label>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnSingular>Wastelander</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnSingular>
  <FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnsPlural>Wastelanders</FCP_Faction_Hidden_Wastelanders.pawnsPlural>
</LanguageData>
