<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VBE_AbandonedColonist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was selected for a colonization program on a distant rimworld. When [PAWN_possessive] ship was torn apart, [PAWN_nameDef] was not among the select few granted the privilege of an escape pod. But, by some sheer miracle, [PAWN_pronoun] survived, and vowed to find those who had left [PAWN_objective] behind.</VBE_AbandonedColonist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AbandonedColonist.title>Abandoned colonist</VBE_AbandonedColonist.title>
  <VBE_AbandonedColonist.titleShort>Colonist</VBE_AbandonedColonist.titleShort>
  <VBE_AddictedGamer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has an addiction to video games and can often be found gaming late into the morning. [PAWN_pronoun] fits all the negative stereotypes from the messy room to the social awkwardness, but at least [PAWN_pronoun]'s learned a few things about crafting and mining.</VBE_AddictedGamer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AddictedGamer.title>Addicted gamer</VBE_AddictedGamer.title>
  <VBE_AddictedGamer.titleShort>Gamer</VBE_AddictedGamer.titleShort>
  <VBE_AdventurousDreamer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood consuming outlandish fiction in all its forms, dreaming of exploring fantastic worlds and finding treasures of every variety. Though [PAWN_pronoun] settled more into the mundanity of [PAWN_possessive] life as time passed, [PAWN_pronoun] never lost that spark of hope for something more exciting.</VBE_AdventurousDreamer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AdventurousDreamer.title>Adventurous dreamer</VBE_AdventurousDreamer.title>
  <VBE_AdventurousDreamer.titleShort>Dreamer</VBE_AdventurousDreamer.titleShort>
  <VBE_AimlessDilettante.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into privilege but never quite knew what to do with [PAWN_possessive] life. Despite skilled tutors for everything from fencing to horticulture, [PAWN_pronoun] never really excelled at anything.</VBE_AimlessDilettante.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AimlessDilettante.title>Aimless dilettante</VBE_AimlessDilettante.title>
  <VBE_AimlessDilettante.titleShort>Dilettante</VBE_AimlessDilettante.titleShort>
  <VBE_AndroidHunter.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has made quite a handsome living off of hunting the incognito androids, as well as catering to the ultra elite's more exotic and eclectic tastes in blood sports. Completely supported by the enormous wealth, [PAWN_pronoun] is incredibly proficient at hunting and tracking dangerous prey.</VBE_AndroidHunter.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AndroidHunter.title>Android hunter</VBE_AndroidHunter.title>
  <VBE_AndroidHunter.titleShort>Hunter</VBE_AndroidHunter.titleShort>
  <VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a mechanic who specialized in the construction of animatronics. [PAWN_possessive] creations were often used in movie production, restaurants, theme parks and theater productions.</VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.title>Animatronic mechanic</VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.title>
  <VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.titleShort>Mechanic</VBE_AnimatronicMechanic.titleShort>
  <VBE_AnomalousCreatureResearcher.baseDesc>Part of a secret organization dedicated to the capture and study of phenomena deemed "anomalous", [PAWN_nameDef] was part of a department dedicated to the capture and  study of anomalous creatures. After one too many containment breaches, [PAWN_nameDef] was left traumatized, and left the organization.</VBE_AnomalousCreatureResearcher.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AnomalousCreatureResearcher.title>Anomalous creature researcher</VBE_AnomalousCreatureResearcher.title>
  <VBE_AnomalousCreatureResearcher.titleShort>Researcher</VBE_AnomalousCreatureResearcher.titleShort>
  <VBE_Apprentice.baseDesc>Once of age, a young [PAWN_nameDef] took to study under the great masters, learning from the bottom up. [PAWN_pronoun] left family and home to pursue a passion and trade. The work was grueling, but it was all worth to carve out [PAWN_possessive] own path.</VBE_Apprentice.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Apprentice.title>Apprentice</VBE_Apprentice.title>
  <VBE_Apprentice.titleShort>Apprentice</VBE_Apprentice.titleShort>
  <VBE_AquaponicWorker.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] used to work in an aquaponic lab. He was tasked with the production of fish and vegetables for his colony. While [PAWN_possessive] work was important it did leave little time for socializing.</VBE_AquaponicWorker.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AquaponicWorker.title>Aquaponic worker</VBE_AquaponicWorker.title>
  <VBE_AquaponicWorker.titleShort>Fishfarmer</VBE_AquaponicWorker.titleShort>
  <VBE_ArchotechFanatic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] claims that [PAWN_possessive] mind has been visited by an omnipotent entity that manifests itself through advanced archotech objects. While [PAWN_nameDef] shows great affinity towards technology and research, [PAWN_pronoun] harbors equally strong disgust when it comes to plants and animals.</VBE_ArchotechFanatic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ArchotechFanatic.title>Archotech fanatic</VBE_ArchotechFanatic.title>
  <VBE_ArchotechFanatic.titleShort>Archofanatic</VBE_ArchotechFanatic.titleShort>
  <VBE_ArtCritic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has made a name for themselves as one of the most influential critics. [PAWN_possessive] reviews could make or break careers.</VBE_ArtCritic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ArtCritic.title>Art critic</VBE_ArtCritic.title>
  <VBE_ArtCritic.titleShort>Critic</VBE_ArtCritic.titleShort>
  <VBE_AtomicBombardier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was responsible for lining up and releasing nuclear bombs over enemy territory. During [PAWN_possessive] years of service, [PAWN_possessive] aim became very accurate, and [PAWN_possessive]  mind desensitized to death.</VBE_AtomicBombardier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_AtomicBombardier.title>Atomic bombardier</VBE_AtomicBombardier.title>
  <VBE_AtomicBombardier.titleShort>Bombardier</VBE_AtomicBombardier.titleShort>
  <VBE_Barber.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a barber, cutting and styling hair. [PAWN_pronoun] knows [PAWN_possessive] way around a pair of scissors and can keep conversations going with [PAWN_possessive] clients.</VBE_Barber.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Barber.title>Barber</VBE_Barber.title>
  <VBE_Barber.titleShort>Barber</VBE_Barber.titleShort>
  <VBE_Bioweapon.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was created in a lab in an attempt to splice genomes in the search for a better soldier. The experiment was deemed a failure and [PAWN_pronoun] was put down for disposal. The methods used were sloppy and [PAWN_pronoun] survived the ordeal. [PAWN_pronoun] later managed to find [PAWN_possessive] former masters and destroyed the facility.</VBE_Bioweapon.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Bioweapon.title>Bioweapon</VBE_Bioweapon.title>
  <VBE_Bioweapon.titleShort>Bioweapon</VBE_Bioweapon.titleShort>
  <VBE_Blackguard.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] carries with [PAWN_objective] a cloud of misfortune, causing [PAWN_objective] to be chased out of every town [PAWN_pronoun]'s lived in due to people's superstitions. Despite being followed by disaster at every turn, [PAWN_pronoun] has learned to fend for [PAWN_pronoun]self and become self-sufficient.</VBE_Blackguard.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Blackguard.title>Blackguard</VBE_Blackguard.title>
  <VBE_Blackguard.titleShort>Blackguard</VBE_Blackguard.titleShort>
  <VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked under a respected blacksmith as a young apprentice. [PAWN_possessive] daily duties included tending the forge, hauling supplies, and sometimes making smaller and simpler tools.\n\n[PAWN_possessive] favorite thing to make was small daggers and wooden weapons for [PAWN_possessive] fellow children, which made [PAWN_objective] quite popular.</VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.baseDesc>
  <VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.title>Blacksmith apprentice</VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.title>
  <VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.titleShort>Apprentice</VBE_BlacksmithApprentice.titleShort>
  <VBE_BloodKnight.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a Blood Knight of the Empire, earning that title after going through years of rigorous and potentially deadly training. [PAWN_possessive] duty, and sole purpose for the empire was to cut down anyone that would dare to challenge their rule. [PAWN_nameDef] is merciless, and will do anything and everything in [PAWN_possessive] power to make [PAWN_possessive] enemies pass into the afterlife.</VBE_BloodKnight.baseDesc>
  <VBE_BloodKnight.title>Blood knight</VBE_BloodKnight.title>
  <VBE_BloodKnight.titleShort>Bloodletter</VBE_BloodKnight.titleShort>
  <VBE_BloodlineFounder.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a very contested origin, with no one willing to admit their lineage to [PAWN_possessive] bloodline. Somehow though, [PAWN_pronoun] was of noble birth, having been raised by those uncaring of such matters. When [PAWN_possessive] rights to high royalty came to light, suddenly everyone wanted to have a slice of the cake.</VBE_BloodlineFounder.baseDesc>
  <VBE_BloodlineFounder.title>Bloodline founder</VBE_BloodlineFounder.title>
  <VBE_BloodlineFounder.titleShort>Founder</VBE_BloodlineFounder.titleShort>
  <VBE_BountyHunter.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] takes a lot of pride in [PAWN_possessive] to find, capture and deliver individuals who have pissed off the wrong people, primarily if it involves a large cash influx in [PAWN_possessive] direction. It might not be the most glamorous job but it pays for a decent lifestyle and that's all [PAWN_pronoun] has ever really wanted in life. Plus [PAWN_pronoun] gets to shoot people in the face, which can be surprisingly therapeutic.</VBE_BountyHunter.baseDesc>
  <VBE_BountyHunter.title>Bounty hunter</VBE_BountyHunter.title>
  <VBE_BountyHunter.titleShort>Hunter</VBE_BountyHunter.titleShort>
  <VBE_Bullleaper.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a dancer and an acrobat. [PAWN_pronoun] used to dance around and leap over the back of a charging bull to entertain the crowd. All bull leapers have to be very agile, but what made [PAWN_objective] especially good was [PAWN_possessive] deep understanding of the animal's behavior. As bull leaping is a very dangerous activity, [PAWN_nameDef] often had to provide first aid to wounded colleagues.</VBE_Bullleaper.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Bullleaper.title>Bull leaper</VBE_Bullleaper.title>
  <VBE_Bullleaper.titleShort>Acrobat</VBE_Bullleaper.titleShort>
  <VBE_BureaucraticProgrammer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] adult life coding programs to extract data from bureaucratic forms so they could automatically fill out other forms. Of course, since other bureaucrats legally had to double-check [PAWN_possessive] program's results, the actual work savings were marginal at best. [PAWN_pronoun] has spent too much time behind a desk to be much use at manual labor.</VBE_BureaucraticProgrammer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_BureaucraticProgrammer.title>Bureaucratic programmer</VBE_BureaucraticProgrammer.title>
  <VBE_BureaucraticProgrammer.titleShort>bureaucrat</VBE_BureaucraticProgrammer.titleShort>
  <VBE_CannibalisticSurgeon.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a surgeon at a prestigious institution until [PAWN_possessive] tendency to take 'culinary liberties' with the deceased was revealed. Rather than damage [PAWN_possessive] reputation by going public, [PAWN_pronoun] was offered a one way trip to a distant rimworld as a 'retirement package'.</VBE_CannibalisticSurgeon.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CannibalisticSurgeon.title>Cannibalistic surgeon</VBE_CannibalisticSurgeon.title>
  <VBE_CannibalisticSurgeon.titleShort>Surgeon</VBE_CannibalisticSurgeon.titleShort>
  <VBE_Cannonfodder.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] didn't have any opportunities or connections with influential individuals after reaching adulthood. Knowing [PAWN_possessive] only opportunity was to join the military, [PAWN_pronoun] enlisted into the lowest ranks of the army.</VBE_Cannonfodder.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Cannonfodder.title>Cannonfodder</VBE_Cannonfodder.title>
  <VBE_Cannonfodder.titleShort>Cannonfodder</VBE_Cannonfodder.titleShort>
  <VBE_Catastrophe.baseDesc>Misfortune has followed [PAWN_nameDef] wherever [PAWN_pronoun] has stayed for an extended period. Natural disasters, raids, infestations, bombardments, slavers are just some of the events those who associate with [PAWN_objective] have had to live through. However, through the death and devastation, [PAWN_pronoun] has managed to pull through by the skin of [PAWN_possessive] teeth.</VBE_Catastrophe.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Catastrophe.title>Catastrophe</VBE_Catastrophe.title>
  <VBE_Catastrophe.titleShort>Catastrophe</VBE_Catastrophe.titleShort>
  <VBE_CaveinSurvivor.baseDesc>Forced into thralldom after [PAWN_possessive] clan was destroyed, [PAWN_nameDef] was quickly thrown into the mines, digging for precious metals. Due to a lack of safety and care for [PAWN_objective] life from [PAWN_objective] captors, the mine collapsed, leaving [PAWN_nameDef] as the only survivor. To ensure [PAWN_pronoun] never needs to return, [PAWN_pronoun] became an adept artisan, and would at times become violent when pressed towards the mines.</VBE_CaveinSurvivor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CaveinSurvivor.title>Cave-in survivor</VBE_CaveinSurvivor.title>
  <VBE_CaveinSurvivor.titleShort>Survivor</VBE_CaveinSurvivor.titleShort>
  <VBE_CenturionsDeputy.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] served in [PAWN_possessive] government's military with distinction, eventually rewarded with the rank of optio and would succeed in becoming a centurion once [PAWN_possessive] superior was promoted. In general, [PAWN_pronoun] was quite simple with these new responsibilities as the centurion ran a tight crew and rarely had to deal with insubordination, which resulted in [PAWN_nameDef] missing out on some key disciplinarian training.</VBE_CenturionsDeputy.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CenturionsDeputy.title>Centurion's deputy</VBE_CenturionsDeputy.title>
  <VBE_CenturionsDeputy.titleShort>Optio</VBE_CenturionsDeputy.titleShort>
  <VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is an entrepreneur. [PAWN_pronoun] recognized immediately how much money was to be made with chemfuel, a substance so widely used that demand never seems to go down, no matter how much of the stuff you sell. [PAWN_pronoun] first convinced [PAWN_possessive] family to buy a boomalope ranch, then his neighbors to plant chemroot. Soon, the whole town was refining everything they could get their hands on. Since the storm of last summer, [PAWN_pronoun] has been looking for a new town to live in. Anywhere, really: [PAWN_pronoun] has no family to tie him down.</VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.title>Chemfuel farmer</VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.title>
  <VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.titleShort>Farmer</VBE_ChemfuelFarmer.titleShort>
  <VBE_Chemist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has mastered the art of chemistry. It proved to be a quite versatile skill in [PAWN_possessive] life - from volcano for a science fair to homemade bombs, odds are [PAWN_nameDef] knows how to create that.</VBE_Chemist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Chemist.title>Chemist</VBE_Chemist.title>
  <VBE_Chemist.titleShort>Chemist</VBE_Chemist.titleShort>
  <VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born and raised in close proximity to an Anima tree. [PAWN_possessive] village taught [PAWN_objective] about the tree's importance and how to take good care of it. As a result of spending so much time with the tree, [PAWN_pronoun] developed a profound connection to the psychic energies of this world.</VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.title>Child of the anima tree</VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.title>
  <VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.titleShort>Psychic</VBE_ChildofTheAnimaTree.titleShort>
  <VBE_ChildSoldier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was taken in at a very early age and was conditioned to the horrors of war. While being a capable soldier in [PAWN_possessive] own right, [PAWN_pronoun] excelled as a low-profile medic to tend to the wounded as well as a spy to be sent into enemy encampments.</VBE_ChildSoldier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ChildSoldier.title>Child soldier</VBE_ChildSoldier.title>
  <VBE_ChildSoldier.titleShort>Soldier</VBE_ChildSoldier.titleShort>
  <VBE_CivilRightsActivist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] became aware of various societal injustices not long after leaving [PAWN_possessive] family home for higher education, and sought to become a force for positive change. [PAWN_pronoun] organized rallies in front of administrative buildings during semester breaks, designing signs and slogans.</VBE_CivilRightsActivist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CivilRightsActivist.title>Civil rights activist</VBE_CivilRightsActivist.title>
  <VBE_CivilRightsActivist.titleShort>Activist</VBE_CivilRightsActivist.titleShort>
  <VBE_ClonedHeir.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was created to replace the missing heir of a noble house, but did not turn out quite right. Despite the best efforts of [PAWN_possessive] tutors, [PAWN_pronoun] was far more interested in bloodshed than the intricacies of the court.

When the heir turned out to be alive after all, [PAWN_nameDef] was discarded to make room for [PAWN_possessive] genetic source.</VBE_ClonedHeir.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ClonedHeir.title>Cloned heir</VBE_ClonedHeir.title>
  <VBE_ClonedHeir.titleShort>Clone</VBE_ClonedHeir.titleShort>
  <VBE_CoginTheMachine.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a very organized and efficient world. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained from birth to do one very specialized job: to paint one specific screw in a specific shade of gray. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] decided to paint the screws green. The other workers couldn't cope with this unforeseen change and stopped working. The chaos spread, and [PAWN_nameDef] soon had to flee a world plunged in anarchy.</VBE_CoginTheMachine.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CoginTheMachine.title>Cog in the machine</VBE_CoginTheMachine.title>
  <VBE_CoginTheMachine.titleShort>Cog</VBE_CoginTheMachine.titleShort>
  <VBE_Commenter.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] did absolutely nothing with [PAWN_possessive] life other than shamelessly mock more successful people's work. Through internet forums, [PAWN_pronoun] found more of [PAWN_possessive] kind, and collectively bickered, contributing absolutely nothing to glitterworld society. [PAWN_nameDef] knew quite well how to use a thesaurus, though.</VBE_Commenter.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Commenter.title>Commenter</VBE_Commenter.title>
  <VBE_Commenter.titleShort>Commenter</VBE_Commenter.titleShort>
  <VBE_CorporateMascot.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a costumed entertainer for a morally questionable entertainment corporation. [PAWN_pronoun] was forced to dance in a depressing white animal suit in exchange for meager pay.</VBE_CorporateMascot.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CorporateMascot.title>Corporate mascot</VBE_CorporateMascot.title>
  <VBE_CorporateMascot.titleShort>Mascot</VBE_CorporateMascot.titleShort>
  <VBE_CorporateSpy.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] used to conduct industrial espionage for a big corporation. One of [PAWN_possessive] missions required [PAWN_objective] to undergo gender reassignment to seduce the CEO of a rival corporation. [PAWN_nameDef] only managed to accomplish [PAWN_possessive] mission because [PAWN_pronoun] felt more in tune with [PAWN_possessive] new gender than the previous one. This gave [PAWN_objective] a unique perspective and [PAWN_pronoun] began to offer counseling to people feeling overwhelmed by the expectations of others.</VBE_CorporateSpy.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CorporateSpy.title>Corporate spy</VBE_CorporateSpy.title>
  <VBE_CorporateSpy.titleShort>Spy</VBE_CorporateSpy.titleShort>
  <VBE_CorruptPolitician.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a gift for lying and getting away with it, a gift [PAWN_pronoun] used to get elected only to embezzle staggering sums. When [PAWN_possessive] lies finally caught up with [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] shot a peacekeeper and fled the planet.</VBE_CorruptPolitician.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CorruptPolitician.title>Corrupt politician</VBE_CorruptPolitician.title>
  <VBE_CorruptPolitician.titleShort>Politician</VBE_CorruptPolitician.titleShort>
  <VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has a particular joy in cosplaying. While that may sound simple enough, a lot of research goes into getting it just right. One can't just throw anything together, but instead one has to carefully research the material and era- and culture-appropriate pieces that the outfit could be worn in. Particular care is taken into appropriate food, drink and mannerisms. At least, that's what [PAWN_pronoun] says and it's hard to argue with results, although that doesn't stop some people from trying to kill [PAWN_objective] for making other enthusiasts look bad.</VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.title>Cosplay enthusiast</VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.title>
  <VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.titleShort>Cosplayer</VBE_CosplayEnthusiast.titleShort>
  <VBE_CriminalPriest.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] somehow wormed [PAWN_possessive] way into a comfortable position among the clergy in a small outlander town on a rimworld. [PAWN_pronoun] would often exploit this position for personal gain whether it be by blackmailing those who had come to confess, or by directly stealing donations.\n\nDuring this time [PAWN_nameDef] relied heavily on [PAWN_possessive] charisma to avoid conflict.</VBE_CriminalPriest.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CriminalPriest.title>Criminal priest</VBE_CriminalPriest.title>
  <VBE_CriminalPriest.titleShort>Priest</VBE_CriminalPriest.titleShort>
  <VBE_Cryonic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is from a civilization that perished to an ice age that devastated [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [PAWN_possessive] body was preserved in the ice for centuries until [PAWN_pronoun] was recovered by a glitterworld archaeological expedition, and was resuscitated with advanced mechanite serums on their planet. Unwilling to be kept as a research subject, [PAWN_nameDef] escaped with the help of a group of humanitarian activists. This experience made [PAWN_objective] distrustful of strangers, but [PAWN_pronoun] also picked up some knowledge from [PAWN_possessive] time in the laboratory.</VBE_Cryonic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Cryonic.title>Cryonic</VBE_Cryonic.title>
  <VBE_Cryonic.titleShort>Cryonic</VBE_Cryonic.titleShort>
  <VBE_CultLeader.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] held the reigns of a dreaded cult, where [PAWN_pronoun] presided over heinous rituals. [PAWN_pronoun] reveled in the torture and sacrifice of victims, offering them up to appease their merciless deity. All members were made to conceal their identities with frightening masks and ceremonial robes. No one dared leave the cult alive, until now.</VBE_CultLeader.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CultLeader.title>Cult leader</VBE_CultLeader.title>
  <VBE_CultLeader.titleShort>Cultist</VBE_CultLeader.titleShort>
  <VBE_CyberDilettante.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is in love with software and cyberspace, with the potential to connect people across vast distances and enhance their abilities with the speedy precision of mechanized computation. [PAWN_pronoun] has always wanted to be a coder and is full of ideas [PAWN_pronoun]'d love to implement... if [PAWN_pronoun] was any good at coding. Unfortunately, [PAWN_possessive] talents lie elsewhere.</VBE_CyberDilettante.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CyberDilettante.title>Cyber dilettante</VBE_CyberDilettante.title>
  <VBE_CyberDilettante.titleShort>Techie</VBE_CyberDilettante.titleShort>
  <VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.baseDesc>Due to the amount of recent interstellar battles, there are a lot of derelict ships floating in space. It's [PAWN_nameDef]'s job to find these ships and salvage them. [PAWN_nameDef] scraps ships, both in orbit and planetside wrecks, and sells the material and parts. Since the ownership of these ships can come into question, [PAWN_nameDef] sometimes finds [PAWN_objective]self on the wrong side of the law.</VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.title>Deep space scrapper</VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.title>
  <VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.titleShort>Scrapper</VBE_DeepSpaceScrapper.titleShort>
  <VBE_Demoscener.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has always been interested in computers and programming. Specifically the computers which are so old that the line between programming and engineering is blurred. [PAWN_nameDef] has fallen in with a culture that uses these ancient machines to create art, using the full extent of the primitive programming available.</VBE_Demoscener.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Demoscener.title>Demoscener</VBE_Demoscener.title>
  <VBE_Demoscener.titleShort>Demoscener</VBE_Demoscener.titleShort>
  <VBE_DeposedRoyalty.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] founded a region-spanning territory through bloody conflict, refusing to give up [PAWN_possessive] and [PAWN_possessive] people's right to live without oppression for their gender and beliefs. Eventually, multiple factions joined together to wage war against [PAWN_possessive] nation, culminating in [PAWN_possessive] bodyguards forcing [PAWN_objective] to flee. While [PAWN_pronoun] did everything [PAWN_pronoun] could to carve a future for [PAWN_possessive] people, [PAWN_possessive] failure to protect them has been [PAWN_possessive] greatest shame.</VBE_DeposedRoyalty.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DeposedRoyalty.title>Deposed royalty</VBE_DeposedRoyalty.title>
  <VBE_DeposedRoyalty.titleShort>Royalty</VBE_DeposedRoyalty.titleShort>
  <VBE_DesertSurvivor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s sworn enemies left [PAWN_objective] to die on a hostile desert planet. Despite all the odds, [PAWN_pronoun] survived in such an environment and adapted to it. Due to spending a lot of time living in the wastelands, [PAWN_nameDef] has no knowledge about plants.</VBE_DesertSurvivor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DesertSurvivor.title>Desert survivor</VBE_DesertSurvivor.title>
  <VBE_DesertSurvivor.titleShort>Survivor</VBE_DesertSurvivor.titleShort>
  <VBE_Dietetician.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s interest in nutrition led [PAWN_objective] to specialize in treating patients with clinical conditions using personalized nutrition plans. Despite the challenges [PAWN_pronoun] faced, [PAWN_nameDef] remained committed to using [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of food and nutrition to make a positive impact on the lives of those [PAWN_pronoun] treated.</VBE_Dietetician.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Dietetician.title>Dietitian</VBE_Dietetician.title>
  <VBE_Dietetician.titleShort>Dietitian</VBE_Dietetician.titleShort>
  <VBE_DogWalker.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] enjoys being around animals so much, [PAWN_pronoun] volunteered at their local shelter to help walk the dogs and give them some exercise. That lasted until [PAWN_pronoun] realized how lucrative of a business it could be and [PAWN_nameDef] scaled up operations to become a full time dog walker with dozens of clients.</VBE_DogWalker.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DogWalker.title>Dog walker</VBE_DogWalker.title>
  <VBE_DogWalker.titleShort>Walker</VBE_DogWalker.titleShort>
  <VBE_Doomsayer.baseDesc>After the death of a pet that was very dear to [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_nameDef] took to journey outwards and share [PAWN_possessive] pain among those who deserved it. Sometimes this was performed in an oratory manner, proclaiming that sinners will suffer for their actions and all should hail the coming of the destroyer. At other times - much more preferably - it was done with a steel barreled sword of vengeance.</VBE_Doomsayer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Doomsayer.title>Doomsayer</VBE_Doomsayer.title>
  <VBE_Doomsayer.titleShort>Doomsayer</VBE_Doomsayer.titleShort>
  <VBE_DrillOperator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was employed in a crust-penetrating mining operation gone wrong. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of the few survivors, and with the others, [PAWN_pronoun] brought a legal case against the mining company on the basis that they'd covered up the discovery of insectoid infestation to secure more profits. When the company started silencing the survivors, [PAWN_pronoun] stowed away on a starship for safety's sake.</VBE_DrillOperator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DrillOperator.title>Drill operator</VBE_DrillOperator.title>
  <VBE_DrillOperator.titleShort>Driller</VBE_DrillOperator.titleShort>
  <VBE_DroneOperator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was hired to oversee the defensive drones for a large intra-system freighter ship. Intended to help provide a set of human eyes to stop craftier pirates from slipping past the automated systems, [PAWN_possessive] job frequently entailed long stretches of nothing but maintenance and watching empty screens between docks. When the ship was enlisted to transfer to a system, [PAWN_pronoun] thought nothing of it, and continued [PAWN_possessive] routine. [PAWN_pronoun] was dozing soundly when the first breaching pod hit.</VBE_DroneOperator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_DroneOperator.title>Drone operator</VBE_DroneOperator.title>
  <VBE_DroneOperator.titleShort>Controller</VBE_DroneOperator.titleShort>
  <VBE_EldestCaretaker.baseDesc>As the eldest child, it was the job of [PAWN_nameDef] to look after [PAWN_possessive] younger siblings. While the adults were away working, [PAWN_pronoun] got used to being in charge, but didn't have much chance to explore on [PAWN_possessive] own as a child.</VBE_EldestCaretaker.baseDesc>
  <VBE_EldestCaretaker.title>Eldest caretaker</VBE_EldestCaretaker.title>
  <VBE_EldestCaretaker.titleShort>Caretaker</VBE_EldestCaretaker.titleShort>
  <VBE_EnlistedTeen.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] enlisted at a young age with the military by using forged documents, eager to go out into the world and make a difference. That didn't last long, since [PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned that [PAWN_possessive] new comrades were the ones dying and those who instigated conflicts only made greater profits from idealists such as [PAWN_objective]self.</VBE_EnlistedTeen.baseDesc>
  <VBE_EnlistedTeen.title>Enlisted teen</VBE_EnlistedTeen.title>
  <VBE_EnlistedTeen.titleShort>Enlisted</VBE_EnlistedTeen.titleShort>
  <VBE_ExtranetTroll.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days spreading disinformation across the extranet at the behest of [PAWN_possessive] employers. Eventually, [PAWN_pronoun] outlived [PAWN_possessive] usefulness and was fired, and with no marketable skills, [PAWN_pronoun] had to work miserable, dead-end jobs just to feed [PAWN_objective]self.</VBE_ExtranetTroll.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ExtranetTroll.title>Extranet troll</VBE_ExtranetTroll.title>
  <VBE_ExtranetTroll.titleShort>Troll</VBE_ExtranetTroll.titleShort>
  <VBE_FanaticInventor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s love for machinery and engineering is downright fanatic. In [PAWN_possessive] Urbworld home, [PAWN_pronoun] made illegal drones, guns and machines, often being chased by the police. [PAWN_nameDef] doesn't see nature as anything other than a source of materials to be refined into something useful.</VBE_FanaticInventor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_FanaticInventor.title>Fanatic inventor</VBE_FanaticInventor.title>
  <VBE_FanaticInventor.titleShort>Inventor</VBE_FanaticInventor.titleShort>
  <VBE_FashionDesigner.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] always said the world was never ready for [PAWN_possessive] creations, but [PAWN_pronoun] was going to be fabulous anyway. With [PAWN_possessive] trusty sewing machine, [PAWN_nameDef] went from runway to runway trying to make a name for [PAWN_objective]self.</VBE_FashionDesigner.baseDesc>
  <VBE_FashionDesigner.title>Fashion designer</VBE_FashionDesigner.title>
  <VBE_FashionDesigner.titleShort>Seamstress</VBE_FashionDesigner.titleShort>
  <VBE_Florist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a gentle soul with a talent for creating new flower hybrids. [PAWN_pronoun] loved to create new flowers for all kinds of occasions, but was deeply distressed each time someone died. When the plague struck [PAWN_possessive] city, [PAWN_pronoun] was one of the few to survive and went nearly mad with grief as [PAWN_pronoun] saw how many had died. The city had to be abandoned, but a few years later travelers started to tell that it was now entirely covered in flowers, as if one flower sprouted for each and every victim of the plague.</VBE_Florist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Florist.title>Florist</VBE_Florist.title>
  <VBE_Florist.titleShort>Florist</VBE_Florist.titleShort>
  <VBE_FoodCritic.baseDesc>The child of an esteemed culinary genius, [PAWN_nameDef] used the influence of [PAWN_possessive] parent's name to launch a career in critiquing the cuisine of [PAWN_possessive] home system. While many restaurants and chefs feared [PAWN_objective], some sought after [PAWN_nameDef]'s mark of approval.</VBE_FoodCritic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_FoodCritic.title>Food critic</VBE_FoodCritic.title>
  <VBE_FoodCritic.titleShort>Critic</VBE_FoodCritic.titleShort>
  <VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] wasn't always part of the tribes. After getting exiled from [PAWN_possessive] local outlander union due to ruining an entire crop harvest, [PAWN_nameDef] had to live out in the open for years, with only crude tools to aid [PAWN_objective]. This made [PAWN_objective] a jack-of-all-trades, but completely broke [PAWN_possessive] trust of people.</VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.title>Forced primitivist</VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.title>
  <VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.titleShort>Primitivist</VBE_ForcedPrimitivist.titleShort>
  <VBE_Foreman.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a foreman in a mine extracting industrial metals. [PAWN_pronoun] worked alongside the workers to ensure safety and motivate them. Workers under [PAWN_objective] were paid decently well, and liked [PAWN_possessive] leadership.</VBE_Foreman.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Foreman.title>Foreman</VBE_Foreman.title>
  <VBE_Foreman.titleShort>Foreman</VBE_Foreman.titleShort>
  <VBE_ForgottenChild.baseDesc>When [PAWN_nameDef] was young, [PAWN_pronoun] came across a secret door in [PAWN_possessive] grandfather's antique shop. Curious of what may lie beyond it, [PAWN_pronoun] wandered in and tells of a land of endless adventure. There's no way of knowing if that were true, but seeing as [PAWN_nameDef] was found as child, forgotten in cryptosleep nearly a hundred years later, nothing seems impossible.</VBE_ForgottenChild.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ForgottenChild.title>Forgotten child</VBE_ForgottenChild.title>
  <VBE_ForgottenChild.titleShort>Disappeared</VBE_ForgottenChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] used to be employed under one of the largest megacorporations in known space. While [PAWN_pronoun] was extremely successful in bringing [PAWN_possessive] company the highest profit margins they had seen in years, [PAWN_pronoun] was predictably laid off when [PAWN_pronoun] could no longer bring in even higher profits for the shareholders. And since people familiar with company secrets have their silence guaranteed, [PAWN_pronoun] quickly boarded the first flight off of the planet.</VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.title>Chief financial officer</VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.title>
  <VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.titleShort>Ex-CFO</VBE_FormerChiefFinancialOfficer.titleShort>
  <VBE_ForsakenPatriot.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] served [PAWN_possessive] faction with dedication and conviction as a black operative. One particular operation went foul and [PAWN_possessive] death was arranged to ease political tensions. However, [PAWN_possessive] loyalty was rewarded with a fake execution and exiled, on the condition [PAWN_pronoun] never return lest [PAWN_pronoun] jeopardize [PAWN_possessive] faction's machinations.</VBE_ForsakenPatriot.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ForsakenPatriot.title>Forsaken patriot</VBE_ForsakenPatriot.title>
  <VBE_ForsakenPatriot.titleShort>Patriot</VBE_ForsakenPatriot.titleShort>
  <VBE_Freak.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born heavily deformed. [PAWN_pronoun] was sold a space circus and travelled between worlds. There, people paid to watch [PAWN_objective] perform various shows. One day, as the company was travelling to a nearby space station, [PAWN_nameDef] managed to escape.</VBE_Freak.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Freak.title>Freak</VBE_Freak.title>
  <VBE_Freak.titleShort>Freak</VBE_Freak.titleShort>
  <VBE_FringeShitposter.baseDesc>As a young adult, [PAWN_nameDef] became interested in niche, fringe internet forums. Obsessed with the deep culture and intricate in-jokes, [PAWN_nameDef] allowed this to consume [PAWN_possessive] life. Now, on the Rim, [PAWN_nameDef] finds [PAWN_objective]self unprepared for survival, and experiences difficulty communicating without bringing up some ancient, forgotten slang or deeply-layered meme. At least [PAWN_pronoun] picked up some vague, outdated military jargon...</VBE_FringeShitposter.baseDesc>
  <VBE_FringeShitposter.title>Fringe shitposter</VBE_FringeShitposter.title>
  <VBE_FringeShitposter.titleShort>Shitposter</VBE_FringeShitposter.titleShort>
  <VBE_GalleryJanitor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a janitor in a modern art gallery, but never understood the appeal. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] decided to add a few strokes of paint to an asymmetrical artwork worth millions. [PAWN_nameDef] made headlines in the news, and [PAWN_pronoun] was fired and banned from the gallery.</VBE_GalleryJanitor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GalleryJanitor.title>Gallery janitor</VBE_GalleryJanitor.title>
  <VBE_GalleryJanitor.titleShort>Janitor</VBE_GalleryJanitor.titleShort>
  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is the result of some of [PAWN_possessive] home glitterworld's most advanced cosmetic surgery. During [PAWN_possessive] life, [PAWN_pronoun] spent an untold fortune on [PAWN_possessive] looks and didn't have much time for to practice any more practical of skills.</VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.title>Gene-modded beauty</VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.title>
  <VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.titleShort>Beauty</VBE_GeneModdedBeauty.titleShort>
  <VBE_GeneticReincarnation.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was vat-grown as a genetic clone of an ancient philosopher-tyrant. Beheld as a celebrity of cultural revitalization from infanthood, [PAWN_pronoun] was simultaneously doted upon and stifled, everyone demanding [PAWN_objective] to act exactly as [PAWN_pronoun] did in [PAWN_possessive] previous life.</VBE_GeneticReincarnation.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GeneticReincarnation.title>Genetic reincarnation</VBE_GeneticReincarnation.title>
  <VBE_GeneticReincarnation.titleShort>Reincarnation</VBE_GeneticReincarnation.titleShort>
  <VBE_GiftedBurnout.baseDesc>From a young age, [PAWN_nameDef] was heralded as a genius. The constant testing, training, and praise from surrounding adults was good, but the constant pressure, expectation, and eventual failure exacerbated a long list of mental disorders lying dormant within [PAWN_nameDef]'s mind. [PAWN_pronoun] still retains [PAWN_possessive] training, but making use of it will be difficult for the rest of [PAWN_possessive] life.</VBE_GiftedBurnout.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GiftedBurnout.title>Gifted burnout</VBE_GiftedBurnout.title>
  <VBE_GiftedBurnout.titleShort>Gifted</VBE_GiftedBurnout.titleShort>
  <VBE_HostessInTraining.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent plenty of time in [PAWN_possessive] parent's restaurant growing up, eventually getting a job seating patrons. While [PAWN_pronoun] wasn't a cook by trade, [PAWN_pronoun] still picked up a lot of the tastes and preferences of the clientele, along with plenty of gossip. This ended poorly one day after an altercation with an ex-lover, and they've been drifting since.</VBE_HostessInTraining.baseDesc>
  <VBE_HostessInTraining.title>Hostess in training</VBE_HostessInTraining.title>
  <VBE_HostessInTraining.titleShort>Hostess</VBE_HostessInTraining.titleShort>
  <VBE_Housecarl.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a housecarl to a powerful chieftain. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained in a variety of weapons, and was always armed both on and off the field of battle. After a conflict with a more powerful clan left [PAWN_possessive] chieftain and many clan members dead, [PAWN_pronoun] left to find a new house to lend [PAWN_possessive] blade, or simply do something new entirely.</VBE_Housecarl.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Housecarl.title>Housecarl</VBE_Housecarl.title>
  <VBE_Housecarl.titleShort>Housecarl</VBE_Housecarl.titleShort>
  <VBE_HumanFarm.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was made only for one purpose, consumption. Grown out of a spindly set of hormone and development injectors connected to a solution-filled tube, many years of [PAWN_possessive] life was spent peering out into the lab, where butchers and scientists went on with their daily lives. During a freak accident which collapsed the farm, [PAWN_nameDef] escaped.
This gave a basic understanding of human anatomy to [PAWN_nameDef], but scarred [PAWN_objective] for life.</VBE_HumanFarm.baseDesc>
  <VBE_HumanFarm.title>Human farm</VBE_HumanFarm.title>
  <VBE_HumanFarm.titleShort>Meat</VBE_HumanFarm.titleShort>
  <VBE_HumanSupremacist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is fervently against gene-modification and the creation of xenohumans. [PAWN_pronoun] believes that baseline, unmodified humans have superior minds and spirits in comparison. Though prejudiced, [PAWN_possessive] arguments were well-rehearsed and spoken with authority.</VBE_HumanSupremacist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_HumanSupremacist.title>Human supremacist</VBE_HumanSupremacist.title>
  <VBE_HumanSupremacist.titleShort>Supremacist</VBE_HumanSupremacist.titleShort>
  <VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.baseDesc>Though [PAWN_pronoun] is known by [PAWN_possessive] friends as [PAWN_nameDef], throughout the systems [PAWN_pronoun] is known as [PAWN_nameDef] the Amazing. [PAWN_nameDef] has performed theatrics and acrobatic stunts and for the Imperial nobles. [PAWN_pronoun] will often brag about [PAWN_possessive] group of followers that attend [PAWN_possessive] every show. Though, no one really knows how many of [PAWN_possessive] stories are just made up.</VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.title>Imperial circus performer</VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.title>
  <VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.titleShort>Clown</VBE_ImperialCircusPerformer.titleShort>
  <VBE_IncompetentPilot.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a helmsman of a large cargo vessel. An unfortunate series of events, some of which were [PAWN_possessive] fault, resulted in the entirety of [PAWN_possessive] crew being vaporized by the ship's fusion engine in a freak accident. Fearing reprisal, [PAWN_pronoun] hailed a passing pirate ship and managed to smooth talk [PAWN_possessive] way into safe passage to another world to restart [PAWN_possessive] life, and hopefully forget about [PAWN_possessive] past mistakes.</VBE_IncompetentPilot.baseDesc>
  <VBE_IncompetentPilot.title>Incompetent pilot</VBE_IncompetentPilot.title>
  <VBE_IncompetentPilot.titleShort>Incompetent</VBE_IncompetentPilot.titleShort>
  <VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] days meticulously working at [PAWN_possessive] machining table to create firearms. [PAWN_pronoun] spent several hours at the gun range to test out [PAWN_possessive] new designs. However, spending so much time working with firearms has left [PAWN_objective] rather deficient in close range combat.</VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.baseDesc>
  <VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.title>Industrial gunsmith</VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.title>
  <VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.titleShort>Gunsmith</VBE_IndustrialGunsmith.titleShort>
  <VBE_IndustrialSoldier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was recruited into the army of an industrial power on a midworld. When training finally ended, [PAWN_pronoun] was sent to the frontlines, where [PAWN_pronoun] took part in an unbelievably bloody battle. The rest of [PAWN_possessive] platoon was killed in the ensuing battle. This terrible tragedy has left [PAWN_nameDef] a shell of [PAWN_possessive] former self.</VBE_IndustrialSoldier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_IndustrialSoldier.title>Industrial soldier</VBE_IndustrialSoldier.title>
  <VBE_IndustrialSoldier.titleShort>Soldier</VBE_IndustrialSoldier.titleShort>
  <VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.baseDesc>Once finding [PAWN_possessive] passion in the way things work, [PAWN_nameDef] became enthralled with tinkering, building and coding. Taking inspiration from nature and the machines [PAWN_pronoun] disassembled, [PAWN_nameDef] built many useful mechanical and electrical contraptions to improve [PAWN_possessive] everyday life. While exploring and studying nature, [PAWN_pronoun] also learned about basic survival needs, and some basic healing. Due to always being in [PAWN_possessive] mind, [PAWN_nameDef] is not very sociable, and is always high strung.</VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.title>Industrial tinkerer</VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.title>
  <VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.titleShort>Tinkerer</VBE_IndustrialTinkerer.titleShort>
  <VBE_IndustrialWorldCounterterrorist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] served on a counterterrorism unit on a factionalized industrial world. [PAWN_pronoun] understood the reasons why they operated, but stood staunchly against the violent methods they used against the innocent. [PAWN_pronoun] gained considerable skills in rhetoric, negotiation, combat, and emergency first aid. Despite this, [PAWN_possessive] personal life skills were undeveloped as the custodial and cafeteria staff handled most of it.</VBE_IndustrialWorldCounterterrorist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_IndustrialWorldCounterterrorist.title>Industrial world counterterrorist</VBE_IndustrialWorldCounterterrorist.title>
  <VBE_IndustrialWorldCounterterrorist.titleShort>Counterterrorist</VBE_IndustrialWorldCounterterrorist.titleShort>
  <VBE_Informant.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was once in a major criminal organization, but after being caught, [PAWN_pronoun] became an informant for Glitterworld Law Enforcement. As part of the deal, [PAWN_pronoun] would be given a new name and identity and be shipped off to an outer world.</VBE_Informant.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Informant.title>Informant</VBE_Informant.title>
  <VBE_Informant.titleShort>Informant</VBE_Informant.titleShort>
  <VBE_InformationSponge.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up with a thirst for knowledge, be it for science, history, or philosophy. Running off into the wilderness, [PAWN_pronoun] would spend as much time learning from nature and the ruins that [PAWN_pronoun] would find. When younger, many would listen to [PAWN_objective] just to see what [PAWN_pronoun] would say, but over time others stopped listening as [PAWN_possessive] knowledge grew in depth, leaving them behind. Over time, [PAWN_pronoun] became more reclusive, and mainly found solace in [PAWN_possessive] work.</VBE_InformationSponge.baseDesc>
  <VBE_InformationSponge.title>Information sponge</VBE_InformationSponge.title>
  <VBE_InformationSponge.titleShort>Sponge</VBE_InformationSponge.titleShort>
  <VBE_Jeweler.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] inspected, cut, polished, and sold all sorts of gems and exotic minerals. [PAWN_pronoun] could tell you the difference between ten types of quartz by lustre alone.</VBE_Jeweler.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Jeweler.title>Jeweler</VBE_Jeweler.title>
  <VBE_Jeweler.titleShort>Jeweler</VBE_Jeweler.titleShort>
  <VBE_JuniorJeweler.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated by gems and minerals as a child. [PAWN_pronoun] built a collection, learned how to polish and cut stones, and developed an encyclopedic knowledge on mineralogy.</VBE_JuniorJeweler.baseDesc>
  <VBE_JuniorJeweler.title>Junior jeweler</VBE_JuniorJeweler.title>
  <VBE_JuniorJeweler.titleShort>Mineralogist</VBE_JuniorJeweler.titleShort>
  <VBE_LandscapePainter.baseDesc>For as long as [PAWN_nameDef] can remember, capturing breathtaking landscapes has been the focus of [PAWN_possessive] life's work. Despite not receiving much recognition for [PAWN_possessive] creations, [PAWN_nameDef] found solace in the fact that [PAWN_possessive] art helped [PAWN_objective] make ends meet. However, the solitary lifestyle it entailed made [PAWN_objective] somewhat withdrawn from the world.</VBE_LandscapePainter.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LandscapePainter.title>Landscape painter</VBE_LandscapePainter.title>
  <VBE_LandscapePainter.titleShort>Painter</VBE_LandscapePainter.titleShort>
  <VBE_Landsknecht.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was barely scrapping by in [PAWN_possessive] village when the recruiter came. The man told [PAWN_objective] that [PAWN_pronoun] would get [PAWN_possessive] first payment in advance, so [PAWN_nameDef] sold [PAWN_possessive] tools and enlisted. At the beginning, [PAWN_pronoun] only had a pike, but after some time [PAWN_pronoun] was able to buy the extravagant clothing marking [PAWN_objective] as a successful soldier. He never betrayed [PAWN_possessive] principles: don't question the orders of whoever is keeping you fed.</VBE_Landsknecht.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Landsknecht.title>Landsknecht</VBE_Landsknecht.title>
  <VBE_Landsknecht.titleShort>Landsknecht</VBE_Landsknecht.titleShort>
  <VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was formerly employed under a rather demanding clientele who demanded absolute and unwavering commitment. While [PAWN_pronoun] was incapable of disobeying, nevertheless [PAWN_pronoun] resented [PAWN_possessive] situation and indirectly caused [PAWN_possessive] master's fall from grace. Rather than face [PAWN_possessive] fate in being “decommissioned”, [PAWN_pronoun] used any and all methods available to smuggle [PAWN_objective]self off-station.</VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.title>Lifelong personal assistant</VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.title>
  <VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.titleShort>Assistant</VBE_LifelongPersonalAssistant.titleShort>
  <VBE_LighthouseKeeper.baseDesc>A solitary individual, [PAWN_nameDef] has spent a large portion of [PAWN_possessive] life tending to the (mostly) automated lighthouse space stations. Feeding navigational information to ships of many eras, these quiet postings were often considered punishments by those who worked them. [PAWN_nameDef] disagrees, however, and the quiet was wonderful for [PAWN_objective] and [PAWN_possessive] art.</VBE_LighthouseKeeper.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LighthouseKeeper.title>Lighthouse keeper</VBE_LighthouseKeeper.title>
  <VBE_LighthouseKeeper.titleShort>Keeper</VBE_LighthouseKeeper.titleShort>
  <VBE_LightingAssistant.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] helped make the background lighting in films and shows. Working behind the scenes completely undetected, [PAWN_pronoun] was never acknowledged by higher-ups, and just opted to work harder until somebody noticed [PAWN_possessive] talent. All the tinkering with electrical equipment gave [PAWN_nameDef] a distinct knowledge of manufacturing.</VBE_LightingAssistant.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LightingAssistant.title>Lighting assistant</VBE_LightingAssistant.title>
  <VBE_LightingAssistant.titleShort>Lighter</VBE_LightingAssistant.titleShort>
  <VBE_LiteraryCritic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] partook in formal education in Literature, obtaining the highest score in [PAWN_possessive] class and even in the history of that department's founding. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] takes almost sadistic pleasure in critiquing people's work, especially if they are otherwise considered their magnum opus. Many bestselling authors have been reduced to tears by [PAWN_possessive] harsh judgment, which often results in their life's work becoming publicly despised.</VBE_LiteraryCritic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LiteraryCritic.title>Literary critic</VBE_LiteraryCritic.title>
  <VBE_LiteraryCritic.titleShort>Critic</VBE_LiteraryCritic.titleShort>
  <VBE_LivingCure.baseDesc>When [PAWN_nameDef] was going through a checkup after [PAWN_objective] was born, doctors found out [PAWN_objective] was immune to a variety of diseases due to an extremely rare mutation, and that [PAWN_possessive] blood could be used to treat many illnesses first thought to be terminal. This led to [PAWN_nameDef] having to stay in the hospital to work as a living cure, and [PAWN_objective] was not allowed to leave.</VBE_LivingCure.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LivingCure.title>Living cure</VBE_LivingCure.title>
  <VBE_LivingCure.titleShort>Living Cure</VBE_LivingCure.titleShort>
  <VBE_LoneTraveller.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] dedicated [PAWN_possessive] life to travelling all across the world, with no specific destiny or reason. Many joined and leaved [PAWN_nameDef]'s travels throughout the time, and during which [PAWN_pronoun] learned many different skills. Given the nature of [PAWN_possessive] life, [PAWN_nameDef] learned to live life with no great comforts.</VBE_LoneTraveller.baseDesc>
  <VBE_LoneTraveller.title>Lone traveller</VBE_LoneTraveller.title>
  <VBE_LoneTraveller.titleShort>Traveller</VBE_LoneTraveller.titleShort>
  <VBE_Maid.baseDesc>Trim and tidy, this is [PAWN_nameDef]'s moto. [PAWN_pronoun] sees a lot more the seedy side of the world, cleaning up after it in one way or another. But [PAWN_pronoun] knows best when to apply [PAWN_possessive] trade, for there's more to [PAWN_possessive] skill than merely cleaning.</VBE_Maid.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Maid.title>Maid</VBE_Maid.title>
  <VBE_Maid.titleShort>Maid</VBE_Maid.titleShort>
  <VBE_Marauder.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] life as a fighter in a nomadic fleet of space pirates until it dissolved from infighting. [PAWN_pronoun] saw many battles, but never even went close to any books.</VBE_Marauder.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Marauder.title>Marauder</VBE_Marauder.title>
  <VBE_Marauder.titleShort>Marauder</VBE_Marauder.titleShort>
  <VBE_Mariner.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] life on a ship at sea, securing cargo from port to port. [PAWN_pronoun] was well-versed in keeping the ship intact, but rarely spent much time off a ship or outside of a port.</VBE_Mariner.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Mariner.title>Mariner</VBE_Mariner.title>
  <VBE_Mariner.titleShort>Mariner</VBE_Mariner.titleShort>
  <VBE_MarineworldResearcher.baseDesc>Seeing untapped potential in the oceans for feeding colonies and cities alike, [PAWN_nameDef] established [PAWN_objective]self on a world which was almost entirely covered in ocean. While [PAWN_nameDef] was adept in the study of algae and aquatic life, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely took time from work to interact with fellow researchers or hone other skills.</VBE_MarineworldResearcher.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MarineworldResearcher.title>Marineworld researcher</VBE_MarineworldResearcher.title>
  <VBE_MarineworldResearcher.titleShort>Marineworlder</VBE_MarineworldResearcher.titleShort>
  <VBE_Masterofceremonies.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a master of ceremonies. [PAWN_pronoun] trained for decades just to meet the minimal requirements for the job: [PAWN_pronoun] had to memorize the thousands of complicated rituals ruling diplomatic meetings on his world, including the correct way to execute one who makes a mistake. In [PAWN_possessive] culture, war has all but disappeared: nobody has ever managed to get to the end of the ritual required to declare war without making a mistake. [PAWN_pronoun] now hopes to bring the same peace to the Rim, one ritual at a time.</VBE_Masterofceremonies.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Masterofceremonies.title>Master of ceremonies</VBE_Masterofceremonies.title>
  <VBE_Masterofceremonies.titleShort>Arbiter</VBE_Masterofceremonies.titleShort>
  <VBE_MattressTester.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] got paid to take naps on different beds and rate them based on their softness and the quality of sleep they provide. People often remarked that [PAWN_possessive] job is "the best job in the world", since naps are contractually required.</VBE_MattressTester.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MattressTester.title>Mattress tester</VBE_MattressTester.title>
  <VBE_MattressTester.titleShort>Mattress</VBE_MattressTester.titleShort>
  <VBE_MedicineProdigy.baseDesc>Born on an overpopulated urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef] displayed a remarkable aptitude for medicine from an early age. Plucked from the education system and inducted into a special program for the intellectually gifted, [PAWN_pronoun] received the best education money could buy, but little time to develop socially or engage in risky behavior.

To [PAWN_possessive] benefactors, [PAWN_pronoun] was an expensive investment.</VBE_MedicineProdigy.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MedicineProdigy.title>Medical prodigy</VBE_MedicineProdigy.title>
  <VBE_MedicineProdigy.titleShort>Prodigy</VBE_MedicineProdigy.titleShort>
  <VBE_MedievalOrphan.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up the child of a Medieval footsoldier. Early in [PAWN_possessive] adolescence, [PAWN_possessive] father died on campaign, leaving [PAWN_possessive] family to live on a meagre pension, managing with what little income [PAWN_nameDef] could make by selling simple textiles and growing vegetables. The years of barely scraping by left [PAWN_objective] tough and somewhat aloof.</VBE_MedievalOrphan.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MedievalOrphan.title>Medieval orphan</VBE_MedievalOrphan.title>
  <VBE_MedievalOrphan.titleShort>Orphan</VBE_MedievalOrphan.titleShort>
  <VBE_MedievalPage.baseDesc>Serving under a great lord or lady, [PAWN_nameDef] was sworn to their liege. This mostly amounted to a whole lot of hauling, cleaning and busywork, but there was much to be learned in studying under the 'care' of nobility.</VBE_MedievalPage.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MedievalPage.title>Medieval page</VBE_MedievalPage.title>
  <VBE_MedievalPage.titleShort>Page</VBE_MedievalPage.titleShort>
  <VBE_MidworldNomad.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] younger years on a midworld studying variety of both modern and historical subjects including agriculture, engineering and politics. After [PAWN_possessive] transport pod crashed on a Medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef] was heralded as a summoned champion sent by the Gods. In the next few years, [PAWN_pronoun] started to introduce several cultural, technological, and societal reforms that would drastically improve the quality of life on this world.</VBE_MidworldNomad.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MidworldNomad.title>Midworld nomad</VBE_MidworldNomad.title>
  <VBE_MidworldNomad.titleShort>Nomad child</VBE_MidworldNomad.titleShort>
  <VBE_MidworldProgrammer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s dream was to become a programmer and create software that saves lives and enhances people's well-being. Yet, as life often takes unexpected turns, [PAWN_pronoun] found [PAWN_objective]self developing cutting-edge software for the military. The work gave [PAWN_objective] ample opportunity to expand [PAWN_possessive] programming expertise and gain an in-depth understanding of the intricacies of advanced weaponry. Despite the deviation from [PAWN_possessive] original plans, [PAWN_nameDef] embraced the challenge and continued to hone [PAWN_possessive] skills.</VBE_MidworldProgrammer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MidworldProgrammer.title>Midworld programmer</VBE_MidworldProgrammer.title>
  <VBE_MidworldProgrammer.titleShort>Programmer</VBE_MidworldProgrammer.titleShort>
  <VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a firm believer in the right to bear arms and the right to arm bears. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] has an established reputation as one of the most prolific exporters in military surplus hardware. Many complain that [PAWN_pronoun] is perpetuating the ever-increasing scale of conflict between pirates and government military. However, [PAWN_possessive] counter-argument is that it's simply good business practice and the military should properly dispose of their own ordinance instead of relying on people like [PAWN_objective].</VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.title>Military surplus supplier</VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.title>
  <VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.titleShort>Supplier</VBE_MilitarySurplusSupplier.titleShort>
  <VBE_ModelCitizen.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived a criminal life, a very violent one, but was caught. Instead of being executed or sent to prison, [PAWN_pronoun] was sent to try an experimental psychological treatment that would make [PAWN_possessive] a good member of society again. While the nature and morality of the program was questionable, the results were definitive, [PAWN_pronoun] is now a model citizen.</VBE_ModelCitizen.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ModelCitizen.title>Model citizen</VBE_ModelCitizen.title>
  <VBE_ModelCitizen.titleShort>Citizen</VBE_ModelCitizen.titleShort>
  <VBE_NatureLover.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has an inherent disdain for being told what [PAWN_pronoun] can and cannot do, and when [PAWN_pronoun] was a child [PAWN_pronoun] was told that [PAWN_pronoun] couldn't just adopt a random rabbit. With almost righteous indignation, [PAWN_pronoun] took care of [PAWN_possessive] pet rabbit better than [PAWN_possessive] own well-being.</VBE_NatureLover.baseDesc>
  <VBE_NatureLover.title>Nature lover</VBE_NatureLover.title>
  <VBE_NatureLover.titleShort>Naturist</VBE_NatureLover.titleShort>
  <VBE_NoirDetective.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] fills a very particular niche in law enforcement while not being under the direct influence of any police. Even though [PAWN_pronoun] has an office with its own neon sign out front and a secretary that is constantly trying to get a hold of [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] is rarely in as [PAWN_possessive] investigations take [PAWN_objective] all over the place. And since [PAWN_pronoun] has a habit of sticking [PAWN_possessive] nose where others don't want it, trouble has a much easier time finding [PAWN_objective].</VBE_NoirDetective.baseDesc>
  <VBE_NoirDetective.title>Noir detective</VBE_NoirDetective.title>
  <VBE_NoirDetective.titleShort>Detective</VBE_NoirDetective.titleShort>
  <VBE_OldWarSurvivor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has been in one too many conflicts which has taken a toll on [PAWN_possessive] mind, as [PAWN_pronoun] still believes that the war never ended. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] is on a very tight hair-trigger and suffers from intense PTSD. Very few people could go toe-to-toe with [PAWN_objective] and any potential allies would do well to stay out of [PAWN_possessive] way and let [PAWN_objective] do what [PAWN_pronoun] does best: eliminate all threats.</VBE_OldWarSurvivor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_OldWarSurvivor.title>Old war survivor</VBE_OldWarSurvivor.title>
  <VBE_OldWarSurvivor.titleShort>Survivor</VBE_OldWarSurvivor.titleShort>
  <VBE_OliveFarmer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the lucky owner of an olive tree plantation. [PAWN_pronoun] would spend hours tending the saplings, always telling [PAWN_possessive] family when they would laugh about it: never give up your last sapling, whatever happens, you can always start over. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] was found in a refugee group, staring blankly at [PAWN_possessive] last possessions: a bloody picture and a small sapling. When it was time to go, [PAWN_pronoun] left the small olive tree behind.</VBE_OliveFarmer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_OliveFarmer.title>Olive farmer</VBE_OliveFarmer.title>
  <VBE_OliveFarmer.titleShort>Farmer</VBE_OliveFarmer.titleShort>
  <VBE_Oracle.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] wasn't like everyone else, and they all knew it. The strange visions, outbursts and eccentric behavior always kept [PAWN_nameDef] at arm's length from others. [PAWN_pronoun] would have been outcast long before, were it not for [PAWN_possessive] visions so often true.</VBE_Oracle.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Oracle.title>Oracle</VBE_Oracle.title>
  <VBE_Oracle.titleShort>Oracle</VBE_Oracle.titleShort>
  <VBE_OrphanThief.baseDesc>When [PAWN_pronoun] was young, [PAWN_nameDef]'s parents were imprisoned for speaking out against the local government. [PAWN_pronoun] was forced to steal food in order to survive, and soon became a capable thief. The experience left [PAWN_objective] unwilling to rely much on others.

As a hobby, [PAWN_nameDef] began collecting helmets stolen from military police.</VBE_OrphanThief.baseDesc>
  <VBE_OrphanThief.title>Orphan thief</VBE_OrphanThief.title>
  <VBE_OrphanThief.titleShort>Orphan</VBE_OrphanThief.titleShort>
  <VBE_PathologicalLiar.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] loves to make stuff up and just can't help [PAWN_objective]self. Particularly, [PAWN_pronoun] enjoys going to any place that serves alcohol and tells the biggest, boldest stories full of twists, turns and drama while being bought round after round. However, once [PAWN_pronoun] gets bored or has decided that [PAWN_pronoun] has drunk enough, almost every story ends on a completely random note with everyone dying in horrific fashion.</VBE_PathologicalLiar.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PathologicalLiar.title>Pathological liar</VBE_PathologicalLiar.title>
  <VBE_PathologicalLiar.titleShort>Liar</VBE_PathologicalLiar.titleShort>
  <VBE_PirateChef.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the Chef on a pirate ship. Between meals, [PAWN_pronoun] told tall tales that kept the crew's morale high. The crew's loyalty to their chef was great, possibly even greater than to their captain...</VBE_PirateChef.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PirateChef.title>Pirate chef</VBE_PirateChef.title>
  <VBE_PirateChef.titleShort>Chef</VBE_PirateChef.titleShort>
  <VBE_PirateKid.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was kidnapped by pirates at a young age. [PAWN_possessive] small size allowed [PAWN_objective] to fit into tiny maintenance spaces on boarded ships to steal valuable electronic components. Coincidentally,  [PAWN_pronoun] also became quite adept at treating electrical burns.</VBE_PirateKid.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PirateKid.title>Pirate kid</VBE_PirateKid.title>
  <VBE_PirateKid.titleShort>Pirate</VBE_PirateKid.titleShort>
  <VBE_PodChild.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s home planet was rapidly escalating to nuclear war right after [PAWN_pronoun] was born. [PAWN_pronoun] was forced to go into cryptosleep and escaped to relative safety. After cruising for decades in deep sleep, [PAWN_pronoun] was found by an outlander community. [PAWN_nameDef] tries to keep up-beat about life due to the sheer luck that was in play for [PAWN_possessive] survival.</VBE_PodChild.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PodChild.title>Pod child</VBE_PodChild.title>
  <VBE_PodChild.titleShort>Escapee</VBE_PodChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_PondDesigner.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] created extravagant ponds for the wealthy. [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of aquatic flora and fauna and how they interact is unsurpassed. One day, a client introduced a new fish into one of [PAWN_possessive] ponds, destroying the delicate ecosystem. That was the last drop for [PAWN_nameDef], who left everything behind and took the first ship to the Rim, where [PAWN_pronoun] hopes to realize [PAWN_possessive] dream: to design a whole new ecosystem on a planetary scale.</VBE_PondDesigner.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PondDesigner.title>Pond designer</VBE_PondDesigner.title>
  <VBE_PondDesigner.titleShort>Gardener</VBE_PondDesigner.titleShort>
  <VBE_PreservationistRuler.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] ruled over a once prospering civilization that stood as a testament to the arts and human creativity. Unfortunately, [PAWN_pronoun] inherited [PAWN_possessive] family's feud with a rival dynasty which resulted in the glassing of [PAWN_possessive] home world. Rather than move-on, [PAWN_pronoun] oversaw the construction of a vast network of orbital habitats and defense networks to preserve the culture and history of [PAWN_possessive] now-glassworld.</VBE_PreservationistRuler.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PreservationistRuler.title>Preservationist ruler</VBE_PreservationistRuler.title>
  <VBE_PreservationistRuler.titleShort>Preserver</VBE_PreservationistRuler.titleShort>
  <VBE_PrivateContractor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] always works for the highest bidder. [PAWN_possessive] background in the military made [PAWN_objective] a good shot. Due to being present when many shady deals were made, [PAWN_pronoun] also picked up on some negotiation skills.</VBE_PrivateContractor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PrivateContractor.title>Private contractor</VBE_PrivateContractor.title>
  <VBE_PrivateContractor.titleShort>Bought</VBE_PrivateContractor.titleShort>
  <VBE_PrivateerCaptain.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has never really turned away from hard work, especially if that results in reaping greater rewards from other people's labours as well. Thus the pirate life has always called to [PAWN_objective] because if anyone's going to be earning money from the - sometimes literal - sweat from [PAWN_possessive] back, it's going to be [PAWN_objective], damn it. Why work for the Man when you can work for yourself.</VBE_PrivateerCaptain.baseDesc>
  <VBE_PrivateerCaptain.title>Privateer captain</VBE_PrivateerCaptain.title>
  <VBE_PrivateerCaptain.titleShort>Captain</VBE_PrivateerCaptain.titleShort>
  <VBE_Propagandist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] got a job as a reporter, but eventually noticed that [PAWN_possessive] work was often edited before release, with many aspects being omitted or rewritten entirely. When [PAWN_pronoun] brought it up with upper management and was told the choice was truth or success... [PAWN_pronoun] chose the latter. It used to keep [PAWN_objective] up at night, but money is money and fame is fame.</VBE_Propagandist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Propagandist.title>Propagandist</VBE_Propagandist.title>
  <VBE_Propagandist.titleShort>Propagandist</VBE_Propagandist.titleShort>
  <VBE_ProsecutedWarVeteran.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was on the losing side of a bitter civil war. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained in the art of combat and the chaos of urban warfare. But once the guns fell silent, [PAWN_pronoun] had to stand trial for [PAWN_possessive] actions. [PAWN_pronoun] was ultimately stripped of [PAWN_possessive] rank and banished from society. With [PAWN_possessive] skills dulled and [PAWN_possessive] reputation tarnished, [PAWN_nameDef] found it a struggle to adjust to life as a civilian once again.</VBE_ProsecutedWarVeteran.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ProsecutedWarVeteran.title>Prosecuted war veteran</VBE_ProsecutedWarVeteran.title>
  <VBE_ProsecutedWarVeteran.titleShort>Prosecuted Vet</VBE_ProsecutedWarVeteran.titleShort>
  <VBE_Pushover.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a pushover and a severe social outcast. Being constantly bullied, [PAWN_pronoun] gained a distaste towards other people. All the nights being forced to do other people's homework made for great test results, though.</VBE_Pushover.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Pushover.title>Pushover</VBE_Pushover.title>
  <VBE_Pushover.titleShort>Pushover</VBE_Pushover.titleShort>
  <VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] believes [PAWN_pronoun] was once a pious steward of some long, lost religion. Reborn again to live life as [PAWN_pronoun] choose, [PAWN_nameDef] seems to have an unnatural proficiency with cooking and art of craft despite [PAWN_possessive] young age.</VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.title>Reincarnated soul</VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.title>
  <VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.titleShort>Reincarnated</VBE_ReincarnatedSoul.titleShort>
  <VBE_ReluctantCadet.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was recruited into an Imperial youth training program. [PAWN_pronoun] lacked any enthusiasm and accordingly failed most of [PAWN_possessive] classes. However, refusing to participate left [PAWN_objective] with plenty of time to talk to [PAWN_possessive] friends and try out different hobbies.</VBE_ReluctantCadet.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ReluctantCadet.title>Reluctant cadet</VBE_ReluctantCadet.title>
  <VBE_ReluctantCadet.titleShort>Cadet</VBE_ReluctantCadet.titleShort>
  <VBE_ResearchScientist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a scientist and analyst from a prominent Glitterworld research institute. [PAWN_possessive] studies and experimentation may have got [PAWN_objective] no great acclaim, but [PAWN_pronoun] contributed in [PAWN_possessive] own way to the companies larger breakthroughs. [PAWN_possessive] work often took the majority of [PAWN_possessive] free time, so [PAWN_pronoun] does lack some of the emotional intelligence of average citizens.</VBE_ResearchScientist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ResearchScientist.title>Research scientist</VBE_ResearchScientist.title>
  <VBE_ResearchScientist.titleShort>Researcher</VBE_ResearchScientist.titleShort>
  <VBE_Rocker.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] became disillusioned with [PAWN_possessive] government and the controlling influence of megacorporations. So [PAWN_pronoun] decided to start [PAWN_possessive] own kind of protest by producing underground music. Sometimes these events were simply fronts in order to stage an attack on different locations of interest.</VBE_Rocker.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Rocker.title>Rocker</VBE_Rocker.title>
  <VBE_Rocker.titleShort>Rocker</VBE_Rocker.titleShort>
  <VBE_RodentRancher.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent a lot of [PAWN_possessive] time working on a rodent farm in an overpopulated city on one of the urbworlds. Due to limited spacing and mostly processed foods, [PAWN_pronoun] found great success in offering actual meat for those who wanted a break from mediocrity. Granted, [PAWN_pronoun] ended up on the run because [PAWN_possessive] Ratburgers attracted the taxman, but [PAWN_pronoun] found it fun while it lasted.</VBE_RodentRancher.baseDesc>
  <VBE_RodentRancher.title>Rodent rancher</VBE_RodentRancher.title>
  <VBE_RodentRancher.titleShort>Rancher</VBE_RodentRancher.titleShort>
  <VBE_Rudie.baseDesc>Growing up on an industrial world, [PAWN_nameDef] found the world around [PAWN_objective] rapidly being corporatized and gentrified. When [PAWN_possessive] town came under threat, [PAWN_pronoun] joined a local gang of youths who would sabotage corporate efforts and spread culture back onto the streets. After the suspicious, accidental death of the corporation's CEO, [PAWN_nameDef] hung up [PAWN_possessive] skates and spraycan, and left for a safer life.</VBE_Rudie.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Rudie.title>Rudie</VBE_Rudie.title>
  <VBE_Rudie.titleShort>Rudie</VBE_Rudie.titleShort>
  <VBE_ShipSalvager.baseDesc>Quick, crafty, and dirty. That's how [PAWN_nameDef] lives. [PAWN_pronoun] embraced the perilous trade of ship breaking as a means of survival. [PAWN_possessive] expertise grew, as [PAWN_pronoun] excelled at taking apart vessels, but the risk remained high, with near-death experiences on nearly every job.</VBE_ShipSalvager.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ShipSalvager.title>Ship salvager</VBE_ShipSalvager.title>
  <VBE_ShipSalvager.titleShort>Salvager</VBE_ShipSalvager.titleShort>
  <VBE_SiloManager.baseDesc>Urbworlds are filled with massive resource silos, half a kilometer high and several kilometers across, with thousands of barely-paid workers carrying materials like little ants across the vast complex. [PAWN_nameDef] worked as a manager to one of the silos, and didn't even have to stand up from [PAWN_possessive] desk.</VBE_SiloManager.baseDesc>
  <VBE_SiloManager.title>Silo manager</VBE_SiloManager.title>
  <VBE_SiloManager.titleShort>Manager</VBE_SiloManager.titleShort>
  <VBE_Simraised.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a simulated environment composed of augmented reality and virtual reality elements inside a robot-tended, environmentally sealed dome. While safe and idyllic, this placid lifestyle left [PAWN_objective] wanting something more in life.</VBE_Simraised.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Simraised.title>Sim-raised</VBE_Simraised.title>
  <VBE_Simraised.titleShort>Sheltered</VBE_Simraised.titleShort>
  <VBE_SlaveTrader.baseDesc>Realizing the profit bodies bring when warm instead of cold, [PAWN_nameDef] would insist [PAWN_possessive] clan take as many prisoners as possible during a raid, employing nets, bolas, and other items that could be thrown towards those fleeing. When the fighting was over, [PAWN_pronoun] would travel, peddling [PAWN_possessive] wares in various kingdoms. Always having thralls around has made [PAWN_nameDef] adverse to so-called "slave work," and generally less compassionate.</VBE_SlaveTrader.baseDesc>
  <VBE_SlaveTrader.title>Slave trader</VBE_SlaveTrader.title>
  <VBE_SlaveTrader.titleShort>Slaver</VBE_SlaveTrader.titleShort>
  <VBE_Sommelier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an experienced winemaker, growing [PAWN_possessive] own grapes and putting utmost care into [PAWN_possessive] work. [PAWN_pronoun] also is quite fond of cooking meals to pair with [PAWN_possessive] wines.</VBE_Sommelier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Sommelier.title>Sommelier</VBE_Sommelier.title>
  <VBE_Sommelier.titleShort>Sommelier</VBE_Sommelier.titleShort>
  <VBE_Standardbearer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a fearless standard-bearer, entrusted to carry the symbol of [PAWN_possessive] people into conflict. [PAWN_pronoun] was known for [PAWN_possessive] strategic thinking and combat proficiency, able to lead the charge or retreat with the emblem as needed. [PAWN_possessive] contributions earned [PAWN_objective] a privileged position, freeing [PAWN_objective] from tasks like cooking and digging.</VBE_Standardbearer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Standardbearer.title>Standard-bearer</VBE_Standardbearer.title>
  <VBE_Standardbearer.titleShort>Banneret</VBE_Standardbearer.titleShort>
  <VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] served on carrier ships in campaigns across [PAWN_possessive] home system, working to keep the starfighters and transports in fighting shape. While [PAWN_pronoun] knows just about everything there is to know about spacecraft maintenance, [PAWN_possessive] reliance on following repair manuals to the letter has had a negative impact on [PAWN_possessive] lateral thinking.</VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.title>Starfighter maintainer</VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.title>
  <VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.titleShort>Mechanic</VBE_StarfighterMaintainer.titleShort>
  <VBE_StarvingArtist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an relatively well-off art student in an urban world. A financial collapse forced [PAWN_objective] onto the streets, selling paintings for a living. [PAWN_pronoun] didn't make much, and what surplus [PAWN_pronoun] had went into more materials and food for some friendly and loyal stray dogs.</VBE_StarvingArtist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StarvingArtist.title>Starving artist</VBE_StarvingArtist.title>
  <VBE_StarvingArtist.titleShort>Artist</VBE_StarvingArtist.titleShort>
  <VBE_StewCooker.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] marched with long lines of medieval armies, and was in charge of the stew pots in the camps. [PAWN_possessive] know-how about some local plants and fungi allowed people to stretch ration for longer, and saved a life or two when the supplies ran dry.</VBE_StewCooker.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StewCooker.title>Stew cooker</VBE_StewCooker.title>
  <VBE_StewCooker.titleShort>Cook</VBE_StewCooker.titleShort>
  <VBE_StrangeChild.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] enjoyed torturing small animals, and as [PAWN_pronoun] got older, other people. This gave them a unique understanding of the body, but stunted [PAWN_possessive] social skills considerably.</VBE_StrangeChild.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StrangeChild.title>Strange child</VBE_StrangeChild.title>
  <VBE_StrangeChild.titleShort>Psychopath</VBE_StrangeChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_StructuralEngineer.baseDesc>After studying engineering for a few years, [PAWN_nameDef] now designs buildings, bridges, and other structures. [PAWN_pronoun] has a great understanding of how to construct every part of a project. Much of [PAWN_possessive] time goes to coordinating with the architect, contractor, and other engineers.</VBE_StructuralEngineer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StructuralEngineer.title>Structural engineer</VBE_StructuralEngineer.title>
  <VBE_StructuralEngineer.titleShort>Engineer</VBE_StructuralEngineer.titleShort>
  <VBE_TaxCollector.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has been appointed with the duty of collecting taxes and other payments from various merchants of [PAWN_possessive] settlement. Due to nature of [PAWN_possessive] job, [PAWN_pronoun] was one of the most despised people in town, but the cut from the taxes [PAWN_pronoun] took made the job worth it.</VBE_TaxCollector.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TaxCollector.title>Tax collector</VBE_TaxCollector.title>
  <VBE_TaxCollector.titleShort>Collector</VBE_TaxCollector.titleShort>
  <VBE_Thane.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was elevated to a position of thane in [PAWN_possessive] jarl's holding, giving [PAWN_possessive] a large degree of freedom to do as [PAWN_pronoun] pleased as long as it advanced their interests. So far [PAWN_pronoun] has enjoyed an easier life with a few servants while taking up an interest in raising beasts of war and training elite soldiers.</VBE_Thane.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Thane.title>Thane</VBE_Thane.title>
  <VBE_Thane.titleShort>Thane</VBE_Thane.titleShort>
  <VBE_TombMaker.baseDesc>When [PAWN_nameDef] was young, a lethal pox swept through [PAWN_possessive] settlement, killing four out of every five people. Old enough to use a shovel, [PAWN_pronoun] dug graves for many people [PAWN_pronoun] knew and loved, but burial wasn't enough to honor them. [PAWN_pronoun] would routinely return over the years and gradually erect ornamented tombs for the fallen.</VBE_TombMaker.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TombMaker.title>Tomb maker</VBE_TombMaker.title>
  <VBE_TombMaker.titleShort>Sepulcherist</VBE_TombMaker.titleShort>
  <VBE_TrainDriver.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] loves trains. [PAWN_pronoun] used to drive a steam-powered locomotive on a small line in an idyllic landscape. [PAWN_pronoun] would greet the sleepy villages along the line each morning with the cheery sound of the horn. [PAWN_possessive] only worry was to shovel enough coal to keep the locomotive running and to repair the train from time to time. One day, [PAWN_pronoun] had to stop in a village. An enraged and sleep-deprived mob took the opportunity to destroy the train and [PAWN_nameDef] decided to leave before they remembered who was responsible for sounding the horn.</VBE_TrainDriver.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TrainDriver.title>Train driver</VBE_TrainDriver.title>
  <VBE_TrainDriver.titleShort>Engineer</VBE_TrainDriver.titleShort>
  <VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] has received extensive military training to act as the lynchpin for [PAWN_possessive] squad. This includes but is not limited to recovering and treating wounded soldiers or people of interest, as well as acting as second-in-command. While this doesn't detract from the results, [PAWN_pronoun] has an extremely dry, no-nonsense personality and can be difficult to get along with.</VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.title>Trainee combat medic</VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.title>
  <VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.titleShort>Paramedic</VBE_TraineeCombatMedic.titleShort>
  <VBE_Translator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] always loved foreign languages. [PAWN_pronoun] worked from home as a freelance translator. This gave [PAWN_objective] enough time to broaden [PAWN_possessive] knowledge in various areas and to tend to [PAWN_possessive] garden. However, [PAWN_pronoun] would spend weeks without human contact and is still unseasy around strangers to this day.</VBE_Translator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Translator.title>Translator</VBE_Translator.title>
  <VBE_Translator.titleShort>Translator</VBE_Translator.titleShort>
  <VBE_TravelingLocksmith.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] days traveling between jobs in various towns and cities as a locksmith. [PAWN_possessive] work ranged from picking locks and installing doors to fixing intricate mechanisms and safecracking. [PAWN_nameDef] enjoyed spending [PAWN_possessive] leisure time making tools and taking in the scenery of life on the road.</VBE_TravelingLocksmith.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TravelingLocksmith.title>Traveling locksmith</VBE_TravelingLocksmith.title>
  <VBE_TravelingLocksmith.titleShort>Locksmith</VBE_TravelingLocksmith.titleShort>
  <VBE_TroupeChild.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a traveling troupe family, but never fell into the craft. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] relegated [PAWN_objective]self to odd jobs and keeping [PAWN_possessive] head down, which [PAWN_pronoun] thrived at. The nomadic nature of [PAWN_possessive] family, however, made it so [PAWN_pronoun] did not make many friends.</VBE_TroupeChild.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TroupeChild.title>Troupe child</VBE_TroupeChild.title>
  <VBE_TroupeChild.titleShort>Troupe Child</VBE_TroupeChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_TunerPunk.baseDesc>A bit of a loner, [PAWN_nameDef] found belonging and family in the mechanics who'd race modded-out cars. This led to many knife brawls, high-speed chases, and the occasional gunshot wound, but this didn't stop [PAWN_nameDef] from enjoying the competition.</VBE_TunerPunk.baseDesc>
  <VBE_TunerPunk.title>Tuner punk</VBE_TunerPunk.title>
  <VBE_TunerPunk.titleShort>Tuner</VBE_TunerPunk.titleShort>
  <VBE_UrbworldRioter.baseDesc>When peaceful protest was not enough to incite social change, [PAWN_nameDef] would don [PAWN_possessive] makeshift gear and take the fight against authority to the city streets. At a severe disadvantage against those in power, [PAWN_nameDef] had to fashion [PAWN_possessive] own weapons and protection, and tend to [PAWN_possessive] own wounds.</VBE_UrbworldRioter.baseDesc>
  <VBE_UrbworldRioter.title>Urbworld rioter</VBE_UrbworldRioter.title>
  <VBE_UrbworldRioter.titleShort>Rioter</VBE_UrbworldRioter.titleShort>
  <VBE_UrbworldWarStudent.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in fairly plush conditions on a turbulent Urbworld. [PAWN_pronoun] dedicated much of [PAWN_possessive] childhood to formal studies on a planet constantly engulfed in conflict. As a result, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up with an intricate understanding about the machines of war and developed a passion for them.</VBE_UrbworldWarStudent.baseDesc>
  <VBE_UrbworldWarStudent.title>Urbworld war student</VBE_UrbworldWarStudent.title>
  <VBE_UrbworldWarStudent.titleShort>Student</VBE_UrbworldWarStudent.titleShort>
  <VBE_VatgrownColonist.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was grown in a lab as an expendable body on [PAWN_possessive] Glitterworld. [PAWN_pronoun] was raised along with the other standard template children who only knew life under their scientist guides.</VBE_VatgrownColonist.baseDesc>
  <VBE_VatgrownColonist.title>Vatgrown colonist</VBE_VatgrownColonist.title>
  <VBE_VatgrownColonist.titleShort>Colonist</VBE_VatgrownColonist.titleShort>
  <VBE_WalkerEngineer.baseDesc>Always eager for a challenge, [PAWN_nameDef] worked on various military vehicles, including the frightening Warwalkers. A tough and sweaty job with high risk of limb injury, [PAWN_nameDef] adapted quickly to strenuous work cycles. This cost [PAWN_objective] [PAWN_possessive] creativity, however, and left little time for other hobbies.</VBE_WalkerEngineer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_WalkerEngineer.title>Walker engineer</VBE_WalkerEngineer.title>
  <VBE_WalkerEngineer.titleShort>Engineer</VBE_WalkerEngineer.titleShort>
  <VBE_Watchman.baseDesc>Not the strongest fighter, [PAWN_nameDef] was placed on watchtower duty. Watching the comings and goings of those passing through the town's gate made for a very boring life, causing [PAWN_objective] to start cooking in [PAWN_possessive] wooden tower. One day [PAWN_pronoun] accidentally knocked over the cauldron, sending coals everywhere. The tower quickly caught ablaze and burned to ash. [PAWN_pronoun] survived, but was never the same around fire.</VBE_Watchman.baseDesc>
  <VBE_Watchman.title>Watchman</VBE_Watchman.title>
  <VBE_Watchman.titleShort>Watchman</VBE_Watchman.titleShort>
  <VBE_WretchedChild.baseDesc>As a child, [PAWN_nameDef] was cast out by [PAWN_possessive] peers. [PAWN_pronoun] grew uncaring of others and focused on surviving with what [PAWN_pronoun] had near [PAWN_possessive] home.</VBE_WretchedChild.baseDesc>
  <VBE_WretchedChild.title>Wretched child</VBE_WretchedChild.title>
  <VBE_WretchedChild.titleShort>Wretch</VBE_WretchedChild.titleShort>
  <VBE_CargoHandler.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was responsible for managing the cargo bay of a space vessel, ensuring supplies were securely stowed and inventory was accurately tracked. [PAWN_pronoun] was physically strong and highly organized, but [PAWN_pronoun] had little patience for detailed documentation or scholarly pursuits.</VBE_CargoHandler.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CargoHandler.title>Cargo handler</VBE_CargoHandler.title>
  <VBE_CargoHandler.titleShort>Handler</VBE_CargoHandler.titleShort>
  <VBE_ColonyAuditor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] kept the colony's finances in check, ensuring resources were used efficiently and planning for future needs. While [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in numbers and was pivotal in resource allocation, [PAWN_pronoun] found hands-on tasks tedious and lacked the patience for caregiving.</VBE_ColonyAuditor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ColonyAuditor.title>Colony auditor</VBE_ColonyAuditor.title>
  <VBE_ColonyAuditor.titleShort>Auditor</VBE_ColonyAuditor.titleShort>
  <VBE_CommunityDoctor.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] served as the community's primary healthcare provider, treating everything from minor cuts to major diseases. While [PAWN_pronoun] was an expert in medical practices, [PAWN_pronoun] had little patience for negotiating or handling animals, preferring to focus on [PAWN_possessive] patients' well-being.</VBE_CommunityDoctor.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CommunityDoctor.title>Community doctor</VBE_CommunityDoctor.title>
  <VBE_CommunityDoctor.titleShort>Doctor</VBE_CommunityDoctor.titleShort>
  <VBE_CorporateFinancier.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] navigated the complex world of corporate finance, managing investments and financial strategies for a major spacefaring conglomerate. [PAWN_possessive] sharp mind for numbers did not translate well to the physical demands of colony life or the nuances of personal interaction.</VBE_CorporateFinancier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_CorporateFinancier.title>Corporate financier</VBE_CorporateFinancier.title>
  <VBE_CorporateFinancier.titleShort>Financier</VBE_CorporateFinancier.titleShort>
  <VBE_EngineHelper.baseDesc>Even as a child, [PAWN_pronoun] was obsessed with the ship's engine room. Under the watchful eye of the engineers, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to maintain and repair the engines that kept their world alive. This early start gave [PAWN_objective] a good head start in mechanical skills but meant [PAWN_pronoun] was often too busy to make friends or study other subjects.</VBE_EngineHelper.baseDesc>
  <VBE_EngineHelper.title>Engine helper</VBE_EngineHelper.title>
  <VBE_EngineHelper.titleShort>Helper</VBE_EngineHelper.titleShort>
  <VBE_EngineRoomTech.baseDesc>As an engine room technician, [PAWN_nameDef] kept the heart of the spaceship running. [PAWN_pronoun] could fix almost anything with the right tools, but [PAWN_pronoun] lacked finesse in social interactions and avoided any tasks that required a gentle touch.</VBE_EngineRoomTech.baseDesc>
  <VBE_EngineRoomTech.title>Engine room tech</VBE_EngineRoomTech.title>
  <VBE_EngineRoomTech.titleShort>Technician</VBE_EngineRoomTech.titleShort>
  <VBE_FieldTechnician.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a field technician, maintaining and repairing equipment in remote locations. Adept at solving complex technical problems, [PAWN_pronoun] preferred the company of machines over people, leading to [PAWN_possessive] underdeveloped social skills.</VBE_FieldTechnician.baseDesc>
  <VBE_FieldTechnician.title>Field technician</VBE_FieldTechnician.title>
  <VBE_FieldTechnician.titleShort>Technician</VBE_FieldTechnician.titleShort>
  <VBE_GalacticMedic.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] served as the medic on a spaceship, treating everything from space sickness to injuries from asteroid impacts. [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of medicine was unparalleled, but [PAWN_pronoun] had no head for research or complex theories.</VBE_GalacticMedic.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GalacticMedic.title>Galactic medic</VBE_GalacticMedic.title>
  <VBE_GalacticMedic.titleShort>Medic</VBE_GalacticMedic.titleShort>
  <VBE_GalleyChef.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] ran the galley on a mid-sized spacecraft, providing hearty and nutritious meals for the crew. Cooking in zero gravity presented unique challenges, yet [PAWN_pronoun] mastered the art. However, [PAWN_pronoun] never took well to the mechanics of the ship, preferring pans over plasma engines.</VBE_GalleyChef.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GalleyChef.title>Galley chef</VBE_GalleyChef.title>
  <VBE_GalleyChef.titleShort>Chef</VBE_GalleyChef.titleShort>
  <VBE_GardenCurator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] oversaw a large botanical garden, specializing in the cultivation of rare plants and educating the public. [PAWN_possessive] green thumb was unparalleled, yet [PAWN_pronoun] lacked the physical capabilities for demanding labor or combat.</VBE_GardenCurator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_GardenCurator.title>Garden curator</VBE_GardenCurator.title>
  <VBE_GardenCurator.titleShort>Curator</VBE_GardenCurator.titleShort>
  <VBE_HerbalKin.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised by the tribe's herbal healer, learning the properties of each plant and how to use them to cure ailments. This early exposure to natural medicine made [PAWN_pronoun] proficient in healing practices, though [PAWN_pronoun] never took to the more violent aspects of tribal life, such as hunting or defending the tribe.</VBE_HerbalKin.baseDesc>
  <VBE_HerbalKin.title>Herbal kin</VBE_HerbalKin.title>
  <VBE_HerbalKin.titleShort>Kin</VBE_HerbalKin.titleShort>
  <VBE_JungleScout.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a tribe that lived in the dense jungles of their homeworld. From a young age, [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to move silently through the underbrush and identify the myriad of plants and animals. While [PAWN_pronoun] became adept at tracking and foraging, the isolation from advanced technology left [PAWN_pronoun] with little understanding of the outside world.</VBE_JungleScout.baseDesc>
  <VBE_JungleScout.title>Jungle scout</VBE_JungleScout.title>
  <VBE_JungleScout.titleShort>Scout</VBE_JungleScout.titleShort>
  <VBE_MilitiaRecruit.baseDesc>In a land torn by conflict, [PAWN_nameDef] was recruited into a local militia at a young age. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the harsh realities of war, becoming proficient with weapons and tactics. Yet, the focus on survival and combat left [PAWN_pronoun] with gaps in [PAWN_possessive] formal education and a wary attitude towards strangers.</VBE_MilitiaRecruit.baseDesc>
  <VBE_MilitiaRecruit.title>Militia recruit</VBE_MilitiaRecruit.title>
  <VBE_MilitiaRecruit.titleShort>Recruit</VBE_MilitiaRecruit.titleShort>
  <VBE_RefugeeRunner.baseDesc>Escaping from conflict zones was a constant part of [PAWN_nameDef]'s childhood. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to navigate dangerous landscapes and to trust [PAWN_possessive] instincts above all. These harrowing experiences honed [PAWN_possessive] survival skills but left little room for education or social niceties.</VBE_RefugeeRunner.baseDesc>
  <VBE_RefugeeRunner.title>Refugee runner</VBE_RefugeeRunner.title>
  <VBE_RefugeeRunner.titleShort>Runner</VBE_RefugeeRunner.titleShort>
  <VBE_RetiredSoldier.baseDesc>After years of military service, [PAWN_nameDef] retired to the colony seeking peace. Despite [PAWN_possessive] efforts to integrate, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with non-violent tasks, finding solace only in routine and physical labor. [PAWN_possessive] experience made [PAWN_objective] a valuable asset during conflicts, but [PAWN_pronoun] never quite adapted to civilian life.</VBE_RetiredSoldier.baseDesc>
  <VBE_RetiredSoldier.title>Retired soldier</VBE_RetiredSoldier.title>
  <VBE_RetiredSoldier.titleShort>Soldier</VBE_RetiredSoldier.titleShort>
  <VBE_ShipsNavigator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] charted the stars as the primary navigator aboard a spacefaring vessel. [PAWN_pronoun] had an uncanny ability to find the safest and quickest routes through the cosmos, though [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with mechanical tasks and often left those to others.</VBE_ShipsNavigator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_ShipsNavigator.title>Ship's navigator</VBE_ShipsNavigator.title>
  <VBE_ShipsNavigator.titleShort>Navigator</VBE_ShipsNavigator.titleShort>
  <VBE_StarshipScamp.baseDesc>As a child born aboard the interstellar vessel 'Endeavor', [PAWN_nameDef] grew up navigating the narrow corridors and vast cargo holds of the ship. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to fix small mechanical issues from watching the crew, but [PAWN_possessive] education in other areas was patchy at best, relying on shipboard terminals and any data slates [PAWN_pronoun] could get [PAWN_possessive] hands on.</VBE_StarshipScamp.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StarshipScamp.title>Starship scamp</VBE_StarshipScamp.title>
  <VBE_StarshipScamp.titleShort>Scamp</VBE_StarshipScamp.titleShort>
  <VBE_StorytellersKin.baseDesc>As the kin to the tribe's storyteller, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the ancient tales and legends by heart, understanding the moral and lessons within each story. [PAWN_pronoun] could captivate any audience with [PAWN_possessive] words, but [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with the practical skills of hunting and crafting, finding more comfort in tales than tools.</VBE_StorytellersKin.baseDesc>
  <VBE_StorytellersKin.title>Storyteller's kin</VBE_StorytellersKin.title>
  <VBE_StorytellersKin.titleShort>Kin</VBE_StorytellersKin.titleShort>
  <VBE_SupplyCoordinator.baseDesc>[PAWN_nameDef] was essential in managing the colony's logistics and supply chains, ensuring the efficient flow of goods and materials. Highly organized but not particularly hands-on, [PAWN_pronoun] steered clear of direct care roles and skilled manual work.</VBE_SupplyCoordinator.baseDesc>
  <VBE_SupplyCoordinator.title>Supply coordinator</VBE_SupplyCoordinator.title>
  <VBE_SupplyCoordinator.titleShort>Coordinator</VBE_SupplyCoordinator.titleShort>
  <VBE_WarOrphan.baseDesc>War took everything from [PAWN_nameDef]: family, home, and innocence. In the aftermath, [PAWN_pronoun] found solace in the pages of books, learning about the world from the safety of a refugee camp's library. While [PAWN_pronoun] developed a keen intellect, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with physical tasks and social interaction.</VBE_WarOrphan.baseDesc>
  <VBE_WarOrphan.title>War orphan</VBE_WarOrphan.title>
  <VBE_WarOrphan.titleShort>Orphan</VBE_WarOrphan.titleShort>
  <VBE_YoungAstronomer.baseDesc>[PAWN_pronoun] was fascinated by the stars from a very young age. Living on a spacecraft gave [PAWN_objective] a unique perspective on the cosmos. [PAWN_pronoun] spent nights charting star maps and dreaming of distant galaxies. However, this obsession left little room for practical skills or socializing.</VBE_YoungAstronomer.baseDesc>
  <VBE_YoungAstronomer.title>Young astronomer</VBE_YoungAstronomer.title>
  <VBE_YoungAstronomer.titleShort>Astronomer</VBE_YoungAstronomer.titleShort>
  <Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.description>A natural pilot, [PAWN_nameDef] has flown shuttles and other craft through the most perilous conditions imaginable. [PAWN_pronoun] is unflappable, has been around the block, and is always ready to throw down in a bar brawl - or socialize with roughnecks and glitterati alike.</Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.description>
  <Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.title>Shuttle pilot</Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.title>
  <Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.titleShort>Pilot</Spaceports_ShuttlePilot.titleShort>
  <AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is an intern at a chemical plant, tasked with handling certain chemical agents and learning to operate the factory equipment. [PAWN_pronoun] learns rapidly and occasionally assists workers in treating injuries sustained while on the job.[PAWN_pronoun] also enjoys drawing in his spare time.</AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.description>
  <AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.title>chemical plant intern</AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.title>
  <AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.titleFemale>chemical plant intern</AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.titleFemale>
  <AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.titleShort>intern</AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.titleShort>
  <AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.titleShortFemale>intern</AM_ChemicalPlantIntern.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_DisasterOrphans.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lost [PAWN_possessive] parents in the insect infestation and lived alone in an underground network of caves.  [PAWN_pronoun] often went hungry until one day [PAWN_pronoun] discovered the back door of a secret laboratory warehouse. [PAWN_pronoun] broke in and stole the food inside, but was caught on [PAWN_possessive] second attempt.</AM_DisasterOrphans.description>
  <AM_DisasterOrphans.title>disaster orphans</AM_DisasterOrphans.title>
  <AM_DisasterOrphans.titleFemale>disaster orphans</AM_DisasterOrphans.titleFemale>
  <AM_DisasterOrphans.titleShort>orphans</AM_DisasterOrphans.titleShort>
  <AM_DisasterOrphans.titleShortFemale>orphans</AM_DisasterOrphans.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_FailedExperimentalSubjects.description>[PAWN_nameDef] inhaled a large amount of toxic gas during a chemical plant accident .[PAWN_possessive] twin brother sent [PAWN_pronoun] to the hospital affiliated with the chemical plant to save [PAWN_pronoun], but the hospital did not treat [PAWN_nameDef]. Instead, they lied to [PAWN_possessive] family that [PAWN_pronoun] had died and used [PAWN_nameDef] as an experimental subject in a parasite experiment. This failed experiment destroyed [PAWN_possessive] mind.</AM_FailedExperimentalSubjects.description>
  <AM_FailedExperimentalSubjects.title>failed subjects</AM_FailedExperimentalSubjects.title>
  <AM_FailedExperimentalSubjects.titleShort>failed subjects</AM_FailedExperimentalSubjects.titleShort>
  <AM_FashionGuy.description>After being injured,[PAWN_nameDef] was no longer able to continue [PAWN_pronoun] career as an athlete. Disappointed, [PAWN_pronoun] was hired as a security guard by a shopping mall. This fashionable guy liked to patrol the mall at night in his classic black striped sportswear and use a machine gun to knock out every sneaky thief.</AM_FashionGuy.description>
  <AM_FashionGuy.title>fashion guy</AM_FashionGuy.title>
  <AM_FashionGuy.titleShort>fashion guy</AM_FashionGuy.titleShort>
  <AM_FormerAthlete.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a former athlete. [PAWN_pronoun] had won multiple sports championships before injury.[PAWN_pronoun] had a twin brother who started working in a chemical factory during his youth, but has never heard from him since.</AM_FormerAthlete.description>
  <AM_FormerAthlete.title>former athlete</AM_FormerAthlete.title>
  <AM_FormerAthlete.titleFemale>former athlete</AM_FormerAthlete.titleFemale>
  <AM_FormerAthlete.titleShort>athlete</AM_FormerAthlete.titleShort>
  <AM_FormerAthlete.titleShortFemale>athlete</AM_FormerAthlete.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_LaboratoryKid.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was conceived in a test tube in a secret laboratory, where every child underwent military-style education and was frequently administered drugs. There, [PAWN_nameDef] acquired a great deal of knowledge.</AM_LaboratoryKid.description>
  <AM_LaboratoryKid.title>laboratory kid</AM_LaboratoryKid.title>
  <AM_LaboratoryKid.titleFemale>laboratory kid</AM_LaboratoryKid.titleFemale>
  <AM_LaboratoryKid.titleShort>lab kid</AM_LaboratoryKid.titleShort>
  <AM_LaboratoryKid.titleShortFemale>lab kid</AM_LaboratoryKid.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_ResearchersChild.description>[PAWN_nameDef]'s father was a researcher at an ancient laboratory, with an unnatural fondness for experimentation. Consequently, [PAWN_nameDef] was frequently administered unauthorized drugs, inflicting severe pain upon [PAWN_nameDef].</AM_ResearchersChild.description>
  <AM_ResearchersChild.title>researcher's child</AM_ResearchersChild.title>
  <AM_ResearchersChild.titleFemale>researcher's child</AM_ResearchersChild.titleFemale>
  <AM_ResearchersChild.titleShort>researcher's child</AM_ResearchersChild.titleShort>
  <AM_ResearchersChild.titleShortFemale>researcher's child</AM_ResearchersChild.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_RisingStar.description>[PAWN_nameDef] is a rising star in the military academy with excellent physical fitness and combat skills, which led to [PAWN_pronoun] being kidnapped and sent to a secret laboratory, where a clone was sent to [PAWN_possessive] family as a substitute.</AM_RisingStar.description>
  <AM_RisingStar.title>rising star of the military academy</AM_RisingStar.title>
  <AM_RisingStar.titleFemale>rising star of the military academy</AM_RisingStar.titleFemale>
  <AM_RisingStar.titleShort>rising star</AM_RisingStar.titleShort>
  <AM_RisingStar.titleShortFemale>rising star</AM_RisingStar.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_RunawayChild.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was frequently mistreated by [PAWN_possessive] parents, leading [PAWN_pronoun] to leave home in a fit of rage. Tragically, [PAWN_pronoun] was soon kidnapped by individuals and spirited away to a covert laboratory.</AM_RunawayChild.description>
  <AM_RunawayChild.title>runaway child</AM_RunawayChild.title>
  <AM_RunawayChild.titleFemale>runaway child</AM_RunawayChild.titleFemale>
  <AM_RunawayChild.titleShort>runaway child</AM_RunawayChild.titleShort>
  <AM_RunawayChild.titleShortFemale>runaway child</AM_RunawayChild.titleShortFemale>
  <AM_SpecialUnits.description>Following a specialized "consensual" parasite experiment, [PAWN_nameDef] was enhanced and designated as a unique unit, frequently undertaking covert missions.</AM_SpecialUnits.description>
  <AM_SpecialUnits.title>Special units</AM_SpecialUnits.title>
  <AM_SpecialUnits.titleShort>Special units</AM_SpecialUnits.titleShort>
  <VQE_AncientEngineer01.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was part of a team attempting to reverse-engineer ancient ARC components. The mysteries behind the machine’s intricate designs fascinated [PAWN_objective]. Although much of the technology was incomprehensible, [PAWN_pronoun] successfully adapted a few critical parts for modern use.</VQE_AncientEngineer01.description>
  <VQE_AncientEngineer01.title>ancient engineer</VQE_AncientEngineer01.title>
  <VQE_AncientEngineer01.titleShort>engineer</VQE_AncientEngineer01.titleShort>
  <VQE_ControlSystemsEngineer03.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was tasked with modernizing the control systems of ARC reactors. While [PAWN_pronoun] integrated new safety protocols, many of the core functions remained a black box. Even so, [PAWN_pronoun] managed to boost efficiency by adapting the ancient algorithms.</VQE_ControlSystemsEngineer03.description>
  <VQE_ControlSystemsEngineer03.title>control systems engineer</VQE_ControlSystemsEngineer03.title>
  <VQE_ControlSystemsEngineer03.titleShort>controller</VQE_ControlSystemsEngineer03.titleShort>
  <VQE_FieldRepairTech04.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent years repairing damaged ARC units in remote colonies. Despite lacking the original schematics, [PAWN_pronoun] became adept at improvising fixes. It was a dangerous job, but [PAWN_pronoun] always carried a few spare ARC components, just in case.</VQE_FieldRepairTech04.description>
  <VQE_FieldRepairTech04.title>field repair tech</VQE_FieldRepairTech04.title>
  <VQE_FieldRepairTech04.titleShort>repair tech</VQE_FieldRepairTech04.titleShort>
  <VQE_PowerArchitect02.description>[PAWN_nameDef] specialized in optimizing the power flow within ARC systems. By carefully calibrating the fuel rods, [PAWN_pronoun] was able to significantly extend the reactor's operational time. Despite lacking full knowledge of the ancient mechanisms, [PAWN_nameDef]'s adjustments became the industry standard.</VQE_PowerArchitect02.description>
  <VQE_PowerArchitect02.title>power architect</VQE_PowerArchitect02.title>
  <VQE_PowerArchitect02.titleShort>architect</VQE_PowerArchitect02.titleShort>
  <VQE_SafetyInspector05.description>As a safety inspector, [PAWN_nameDef] traveled between colonies, checking the status of ARC reactors. Although [PAWN_pronoun] could only speculate about how the core systems worked, [PAWN_pronoun] was able to identify potential failures and suggest maintenance that extended reactor lifespans.</VQE_SafetyInspector05.description>
  <VQE_SafetyInspector05.title>ARC safety inspector</VQE_SafetyInspector05.title>
  <VQE_SafetyInspector05.titleShort>inspector</VQE_SafetyInspector05.titleShort>
  <VQE_ChildhoodInventorGenetron.description>As a child, [PAWN_nameDef] was never content with toys or simple amusements. [PAWN_pronoun] found joy in taking apart old machines and scraps salvaged from the colony’s scrapyard. While the other children played, [PAWN_nameDef] could be found elbows-deep in a broken generator or defunct mining drone, trying to understand what made it tick. The adults often saw this as a nuisance, especially when [PAWN_pronoun] "borrowed" essential equipment for experiments. But those who looked closer saw a spark of genius.</VQE_ChildhoodInventorGenetron.description>
  <VQE_ChildhoodInventorGenetron.title>curious tinkerer</VQE_ChildhoodInventorGenetron.title>
  <VQE_ChildhoodInventorGenetron.titleShort>tinkerer</VQE_ChildhoodInventorGenetron.titleShort>
  <VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] became a legend among engineers as the inventor of the ARC, a groundbreaking power generator that changed the fate of entire colonies. Driven by a relentless desire to solve the energy shortages crippling the outer rim, [PAWN_pronoun] pushed the boundaries of safe experimentation. The first prototypes were rushed, leading to tragic accidents that claimed many lives. Though these failures weighed heavily on [PAWN_objective], they fueled [PAWN_possessive] determination. After countless trials, [PAWN_nameDef] finally succeeded, cementing [PAWN_possessive] legacy as a hero to some, and a reckless maverick to others.</VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.description>
  <VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.title>inventor of the ARC</VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.title>
  <VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.titleShort>inventor</VQE_InventorGenetronAdulthood.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Archer22.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was trained to fight in the lord’s army as an archer, spending countless hours practicing [PAWN_possessive] aim. [PAWN_pronoun] became an expert at firing arrows accurately and quickly, even under pressure. However, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked experience with close combat, often relying on others to protect [PAWN_objective].</VFEM_Archer22.description>
  <VFEM_Archer22.title>archer</VFEM_Archer22.title>
  <VFEM_Archer22.titleShort>archer</VFEM_Archer22.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Baker14.description>[PAWN_nameDef] rose early each morning to knead dough and bake bread for the village. Over the years, [PAWN_pronoun] developed a knack for crafting perfect loaves and managing a hot oven. However, the repetitive nature of the work left [PAWN_pronoun] uninterested in other trades or studies.</VFEM_Baker14.description>
  <VFEM_Baker14.title>baker</VFEM_Baker14.title>
  <VFEM_Baker14.titleShort>baker</VFEM_Baker14.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Bandit48.description>[PAWN_nameDef] roamed the countryside with a band of outlaws, ambushing travelers and raiding villages. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled in both melee combat and intimidation but earned a reputation as a dangerous outlaw. Life on the run hardened [PAWN_pronoun] and left [PAWN_pronoun] distrusting of others.</VFEM_Bandit48.description>
  <VFEM_Bandit48.title>bandit</VFEM_Bandit48.title>
  <VFEM_Bandit48.titleShort>bandit</VFEM_Bandit48.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Beggar31.description>[PAWN_nameDef] survived by begging on the streets, relying on the charity of others for food and shelter. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at reading people’s moods and persuading them to give, but the harsh life left [PAWN_pronoun] weak and unskilled in manual labor.</VFEM_Beggar31.description>
  <VFEM_Beggar31.title>beggar</VFEM_Beggar31.title>
  <VFEM_Beggar31.titleShort>beggar</VFEM_Beggar31.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Blacksmith37.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked in the forge, shaping metal into tools, weapons, and armor. [PAWN_pronoun] earned the admiration of the village for [PAWN_possessive] skill and reliability. The constant heat and heavy labor left [PAWN_pronoun] strong and focused, though not particularly well-read.</VFEM_Blacksmith37.description>
  <VFEM_Blacksmith37.title>blacksmith</VFEM_Blacksmith37.title>
  <VFEM_Blacksmith37.titleShort>blacksmith</VFEM_Blacksmith37.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Brickmaker10.description>[PAWN_nameDef] shaped and fired clay bricks for construction projects in [PAWN_possessive] village. The intense labor strengthened [PAWN_possessive] body and gave [PAWN_pronoun] a keen understanding of construction techniques. Years of working near hot kilns left [PAWN_pronoun] with little stamina for long days of physical labor.</VFEM_Brickmaker10.description>
  <VFEM_Brickmaker10.title>brickmaker</VFEM_Brickmaker10.title>
  <VFEM_Brickmaker10.titleShort>brickmaker</VFEM_Brickmaker10.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Butler45.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served the lord and [PAWN_possessive] family directly, ensuring their needs were met with promptness and discretion. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled in etiquette and managing a household staff. The role gave [PAWN_pronoun] a sharp eye for detail but little patience for physical labor.</VFEM_Butler45.description>
  <VFEM_Butler45.title>butler</VFEM_Butler45.title>
  <VFEM_Butler45.titleShort>butler</VFEM_Butler45.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CampFollower28.description>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled with armies, maintaining the camp and preparing supplies. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled in basic survival and cooking, ensuring the soldiers were fed and ready for battle. Despite living near combat, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely saw direct action and focused on support roles.</VFEM_CampFollower28.description>
  <VFEM_CampFollower28.title>camp follower</VFEM_CampFollower28.title>
  <VFEM_CampFollower28.titleShort>camp follower</VFEM_CampFollower28.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CandleMaker08.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent years crafting candles from tallow and wax, supplying light to the nearby village. The work required patience and precision, which [PAWN_pronoun] excelled at. However, the repetitive nature of the trade left [PAWN_pronoun] uninterested in more creative pursuits.</VFEM_CandleMaker08.description>
  <VFEM_CandleMaker08.title>candle maker</VFEM_CandleMaker08.title>
  <VFEM_CandleMaker08.titleShort>candler</VFEM_CandleMaker08.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Carpenter40.description>[PAWN_nameDef] crafted furniture, tools, and wooden structures for the village. [PAWN_pronoun] earned [PAWN_possessive] living through precision and skill, shaping timber into practical and beautiful creations. Though [PAWN_pronoun] excelled at [PAWN_possessive] trade, [PAWN_pronoun] had little time for intellectual pursuits.</VFEM_Carpenter40.description>
  <VFEM_Carpenter40.title>carpenter</VFEM_Carpenter40.title>
  <VFEM_Carpenter40.titleShort>carpenter</VFEM_Carpenter40.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Chamberlain42.description>[PAWN_nameDef] managed the keep’s living quarters, overseeing servants and ensuring the lord’s chambers were well-kept. [PAWN_pronoun] became adept at organizing and managing resources but often found [PAWN_possessive]self caught in the politics of the household. The role demanded both precision and tact.</VFEM_Chamberlain42.description>
  <VFEM_Chamberlain42.title>chamberlain</VFEM_Chamberlain42.title>
  <VFEM_Chamberlain42.titleShort>chamberlain</VFEM_Chamberlain42.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Cooper15.description>[PAWN_nameDef] crafted barrels and casks for the village, using simple tools to shape and assemble wooden staves. The work required precision and patience, skills that [PAWN_pronoun] mastered over years. Despite [PAWN_possessive] expertise, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely ventured beyond the workshop to socialize or pursue other interests.</VFEM_Cooper15.description>
  <VFEM_Cooper15.title>cooper</VFEM_Cooper15.title>
  <VFEM_Cooper15.titleShort>cooper</VFEM_Cooper15.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Counterfeiter50.description>[PAWN_nameDef] forged coins and documents, deceiving merchants and nobles alike. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at crafting convincing replicas, though [PAWN_pronoun] avoided physical labor whenever possible. The constant risk of exposure forced [PAWN_pronoun] to move frequently, never staying in one place for long.</VFEM_Counterfeiter50.description>
  <VFEM_Counterfeiter50.title>counterfeiter</VFEM_Counterfeiter50.title>
  <VFEM_Counterfeiter50.titleShort>counterfeiter</VFEM_Counterfeiter50.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Fence47.description>[PAWN_nameDef] traded in stolen goods, turning ill-gotten items into coin while avoiding the attention of the authorities. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at bargaining and gauging the value of items but avoided direct involvement in theft. The constant deception made [PAWN_pronoun] adept at reading people’s motives.</VFEM_Fence47.description>
  <VFEM_Fence47.title>fence</VFEM_Fence47.title>
  <VFEM_Fence47.titleShort>fence</VFEM_Fence47.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FieldHand02.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a laborer in the fields from a young age, planting crops and harvesting under the watchful eye of overseers. [PAWN_pronoun] grew strong from hauling sacks of grain and learned the basics of caring for plants. However, the grueling work left little time for other pursuits, and [PAWN_pronoun] never learned to read or write.</VFEM_FieldHand02.description>
  <VFEM_FieldHand02.title>field hand</VFEM_FieldHand02.title>
  <VFEM_FieldHand02.titleShort>field hand</VFEM_FieldHand02.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Fisher04.description>[PAWN_nameDef] made a living catching fish from the rivers and lakes near [PAWN_possessive] village. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to craft simple nets and traps but spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time alone on the water. The repetitive work left [PAWN_pronoun] skilled but uninterested in other tasks.</VFEM_Fisher04.description>
  <VFEM_Fisher04.title>fisher</VFEM_Fisher04.title>
  <VFEM_Fisher04.titleShort>fisher</VFEM_Fisher04.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Footman21.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as a foot soldier in the local lord's army, marching into battle with sword and shield. The brutal skirmishes taught [PAWN_pronoun] the value of endurance and discipline. Years of combat left [PAWN_pronoun] skilled with melee weapons but untrained in ranged combat.</VFEM_Footman21.description>
  <VFEM_Footman21.title>footman</VFEM_Footman21.title>
  <VFEM_Footman21.titleShort>footman</VFEM_Footman21.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Gravedigger13.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] nights digging graves for the dead and maintaining the village cemetery. The work was somber and lonely, but it made [PAWN_pronoun] strong and capable of handling heavy tools. Constant exposure to death left [PAWN_pronoun] emotionally detached from others.</VFEM_Gravedigger13.description>
  <VFEM_Gravedigger13.title>gravedigger</VFEM_Gravedigger13.title>
  <VFEM_Gravedigger13.titleShort>gravedigger</VFEM_Gravedigger13.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Healer39.description>[PAWN_nameDef] tended to the sick and wounded, applying [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of medicine and herbal remedies. [PAWN_pronoun] gained respect for [PAWN_possessive] ability to save lives, though [PAWN_pronoun] often had to face the harsh reality of those [PAWN_pronoun] couldn’t save. The villagers relied on [PAWN_objective] as their primary source of care.</VFEM_Healer39.description>
  <VFEM_Healer39.title>healer</VFEM_Healer39.title>
  <VFEM_Healer39.titleShort>healer</VFEM_Healer39.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Herbalist36.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived near the edge of the forest, gathering plants to craft medicines and salves for the village. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a keen understanding of nature and its uses but often kept to [PAWN_possessive]self to focus on [PAWN_possessive] craft. Villagers respected [PAWN_possessive] knowledge, seeking [PAWN_possessive] help in times of need.</VFEM_Herbalist36.description>
  <VFEM_Herbalist36.title>herbalist</VFEM_Herbalist36.title>
  <VFEM_Herbalist36.titleShort>herbalist</VFEM_Herbalist36.titleShort>
  <VFEM_KitchenServant41.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked long hours in the keep's kitchens, preparing food for the nobles and their guests. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to cook large meals with limited resources, honing [PAWN_possessive] culinary skills. Though the work was exhausting, [PAWN_pronoun] found pride in [PAWN_possessive] ability to feed others.</VFEM_KitchenServant41.description>
  <VFEM_KitchenServant41.title>kitchen servant</VFEM_KitchenServant41.title>
  <VFEM_KitchenServant41.titleShort>kitchen hand</VFEM_KitchenServant41.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Mason38.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a skilled mason, shaping stone into sturdy walls and magnificent buildings. [PAWN_pronoun] earned a good reputation for [PAWN_possessive] precision and creativity in construction. [PAWN_pronoun] rarely participated in farming or hunting, focusing solely on [PAWN_possessive] craft.</VFEM_Mason38.description>
  <VFEM_Mason38.title>mason</VFEM_Mason38.title>
  <VFEM_Mason38.titleShort>mason</VFEM_Mason38.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Mercenary29.description>[PAWN_nameDef] sold [PAWN_possessive] sword to the highest bidder, fighting in skirmishes across the land. Years of battle left [PAWN_pronoun] hardened and skilled in melee combat, but [PAWN_pronoun] never trusted anyone enough to form lasting bonds. [PAWN_pronoun] carried scars from both physical and emotional wounds.</VFEM_Mercenary29.description>
  <VFEM_Mercenary29.title>mercenary</VFEM_Mercenary29.title>
  <VFEM_Mercenary29.titleShort>mercenary</VFEM_Mercenary29.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Miller12.description>[PAWN_nameDef] operated a village mill, grinding grain into flour for the community. The job required an understanding of machinery and a steady hand to keep the mill running smoothly. Years of dusty work left [PAWN_pronoun] prone to coughing fits and other ailments.</VFEM_Miller12.description>
  <VFEM_Miller12.title>miller</VFEM_Miller12.title>
  <VFEM_Miller12.titleShort>miller</VFEM_Miller12.titleShort>
  <VFEM_MudDigger20.description>[PAWN_nameDef] dug clay from riverbanks for pottery and construction projects in the village. The exhausting labor left [PAWN_pronoun] with a strong back and thick arms but little interest in intellectual endeavors. [PAWN_pronoun] rarely interacted with others, spending most days knee-deep in mud.</VFEM_MudDigger20.description>
  <VFEM_MudDigger20.title>mud digger</VFEM_MudDigger20.title>
  <VFEM_MudDigger20.titleShort>mud digger</VFEM_MudDigger20.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Outlaw33.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived outside the law, surviving through theft and violence. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at fighting and evading capture, but [PAWN_pronoun] was shunned by society and relied on [PAWN_possessive] wits to stay alive. The life of an outlaw left [PAWN_pronoun] hardened and distrusting of others.</VFEM_Outlaw33.description>
  <VFEM_Outlaw33.title>outlaw</VFEM_Outlaw33.title>
  <VFEM_Outlaw33.titleShort>outlaw</VFEM_Outlaw33.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Pickpocket46.description>[PAWN_nameDef] survived by slipping through crowded markets, deftly lifting coins and trinkets from unsuspecting villagers. [PAWN_pronoun] developed nimble fingers and a keen sense for spotting opportunities, but [PAWN_pronoun] always lived in fear of being caught. Years of petty theft left [PAWN_pronoun] mistrustful and secretive.</VFEM_Pickpocket46.description>
  <VFEM_Pickpocket46.title>pickpocket</VFEM_Pickpocket46.title>
  <VFEM_Pickpocket46.titleShort>pickpocket</VFEM_Pickpocket46.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Pikeman26.description>[PAWN_nameDef] stood in tightly packed lines, wielding a long pike to defend against charging cavalry. The work was grueling and required coordination with [PAWN_possessive] comrades to form an impenetrable wall of steel. While [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in formation combat, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with tasks requiring individual creativity.</VFEM_Pikeman26.description>
  <VFEM_Pikeman26.title>pikeman</VFEM_Pikeman26.title>
  <VFEM_Pikeman26.titleShort>pikeman</VFEM_Pikeman26.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Poacher32.description>[PAWN_nameDef] hunted illegally in the lord’s forests, risking [PAWN_possessive] life to feed [PAWN_possessive] family. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled with a bow and learned to move silently through the woods, but [PAWN_pronoun] always lived in fear of being caught by the lord’s men.</VFEM_Poacher32.description>
  <VFEM_Poacher32.title>poacher</VFEM_Poacher32.title>
  <VFEM_Poacher32.titleShort>poacher</VFEM_Poacher32.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RatCatcher19.description>[PAWN_nameDef] made a living ridding the village of vermin, setting traps and chasing down rats with [PAWN_possessive] bare hands. The work was dangerous and filthy, but it honed [PAWN_possessive] reflexes and taught [PAWN_pronoun] the ways of small creatures. Years in dark cellars left [PAWN_pronoun] socially awkward.</VFEM_RatCatcher19.description>
  <VFEM_RatCatcher19.title>rat catcher</VFEM_RatCatcher19.title>
  <VFEM_RatCatcher19.titleShort>rat catcher</VFEM_RatCatcher19.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Scavenger34.description>[PAWN_nameDef] survived by scavenging abandoned battlefields and ruined villages, gathering anything of value. [PAWN_pronoun] became adept at spotting useful items and avoiding danger, but the life left [PAWN_pronoun] with little sense of cleanliness or order.</VFEM_Scavenger34.description>
  <VFEM_Scavenger34.title>scavenger</VFEM_Scavenger34.title>
  <VFEM_Scavenger34.titleShort>scavenger</VFEM_Scavenger34.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Scullion43.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days washing dishes and scrubbing pots in the keep’s kitchens. The work was dirty and thankless, but it gave [PAWN_pronoun] a strong work ethic and the ability to endure long hours of labor. [PAWN_pronoun] rarely interacted with anyone outside the kitchen staff.</VFEM_Scullion43.description>
  <VFEM_Scullion43.title>scullion</VFEM_Scullion43.title>
  <VFEM_Scullion43.titleShort>scullion</VFEM_Scullion43.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Shepherd06.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days tending sheep in the hills surrounding [PAWN_possessive] village. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at managing livestock and defending the flock from predators. The quiet life made [PAWN_pronoun] thoughtful but left [PAWN_pronoun] unprepared for more physically demanding work.</VFEM_Shepherd06.description>
  <VFEM_Shepherd06.title>shepherd</VFEM_Shepherd06.title>
  <VFEM_Shepherd06.titleShort>shepherd</VFEM_Shepherd06.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Shieldbearer27.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was tasked with carrying a large shield into battle, protecting [PAWN_possessive] comrades from incoming projectiles. The position required endurance and discipline, as [PAWN_pronoun] stood firm even under heavy fire. The role left [PAWN_pronoun] with little opportunity to practice ranged combat.</VFEM_Shieldbearer27.description>
  <VFEM_Shieldbearer27.title>shieldbearer</VFEM_Shieldbearer27.title>
  <VFEM_Shieldbearer27.titleShort>shieldbearer</VFEM_Shieldbearer27.titleShort>
  <VFEM_SiegeEngineer30.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked with a team to build and operate siege engines during castle assaults. The role demanded ingenuity and strength, as [PAWN_pronoun] helped design, construct, and fire massive weapons. While skilled in engineering, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with close-quarters combat.</VFEM_SiegeEngineer30.description>
  <VFEM_SiegeEngineer30.title>siege engineer</VFEM_SiegeEngineer30.title>
  <VFEM_SiegeEngineer30.titleShort>siege engineer</VFEM_SiegeEngineer30.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Smuggler49.description>[PAWN_nameDef] transported contraband across borders, using [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of hidden paths and bribes to avoid detection. [PAWN_pronoun] became adept at navigating and negotiating under pressure, though the constant risk of capture took a toll on [PAWN_possessive] nerves. The life of secrecy made [PAWN_pronoun] wary of strangers.</VFEM_Smuggler49.description>
  <VFEM_Smuggler49.title>smuggler</VFEM_Smuggler49.title>
  <VFEM_Smuggler49.titleShort>smuggler</VFEM_Smuggler49.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Spearman25.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was trained to hold the front line with a spear, using reach to keep enemies at bay. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to work in formation with others, relying on coordination and timing to fend off cavalry charges. Years of combat hardened [PAWN_pronoun], though [PAWN_pronoun] lacked skill in crafting or more delicate tasks.</VFEM_Spearman25.description>
  <VFEM_Spearman25.title>spearman</VFEM_Spearman25.title>
  <VFEM_Spearman25.titleShort>spearman</VFEM_Spearman25.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Squire23.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as a squire to a local knight, learning the ways of battle and assisting [PAWN_objective] master. [PAWN_pronoun] gained skill with weapons and armor, though most of [PAWN_possessive] duties involved maintenance and carrying supplies. The experience made [PAWN_pronoun] strong and disciplined but left little time for independent thought.</VFEM_Squire23.description>
  <VFEM_Squire23.title>squire</VFEM_Squire23.title>
  <VFEM_Squire23.titleShort>squire</VFEM_Squire23.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Stablehand16.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days mucking stalls and tending to horses in the village stables. Over time, [PAWN_pronoun] developed a deep understanding of animal care and a steady hand for calming even the most skittish creatures. The hard labor left [PAWN_pronoun] with little time for intellectual pursuits.</VFEM_Stablehand16.description>
  <VFEM_Stablehand16.title>stablehand</VFEM_Stablehand16.title>
  <VFEM_Stablehand16.titleShort>stablehand</VFEM_Stablehand16.titleShort>
  <VFEM_StableServant44.description>[PAWN_nameDef] tended to the lord’s horses, feeding and grooming them and cleaning their stalls. [PAWN_pronoun] gained a deep understanding of animal care and built strong muscles from the physical labor. The isolation of the stables left [PAWN_pronoun] with limited social skills.</VFEM_StableServant44.description>
  <VFEM_StableServant44.title>stable servant</VFEM_StableServant44.title>
  <VFEM_StableServant44.titleShort>stable hand</VFEM_StableServant44.titleShort>
  <VFEM_StoneHauler05.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked in a stone quarry, hauling heavy blocks to construction sites. The endless labor left [PAWN_pronoun] with great strength but little patience for intellectual pursuits. The hard life in the quarry also sharpened [PAWN_possessive] instincts for survival.</VFEM_StoneHauler05.description>
  <VFEM_StoneHauler05.title>stone hauler</VFEM_StoneHauler05.title>
  <VFEM_StoneHauler05.titleShort>hauler</VFEM_StoneHauler05.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Tanner07.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked in a tannery, turning raw hides into leather for clothing and armor. The job was messy and unpleasant, but it gave [PAWN_pronoun] an eye for detail and strong hands. Years of exposure to harsh chemicals left [PAWN_pronoun] with poor health.</VFEM_Tanner07.description>
  <VFEM_Tanner07.title>tanner</VFEM_Tanner07.title>
  <VFEM_Tanner07.titleShort>tanner</VFEM_Tanner07.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Thatcher17.description>[PAWN_nameDef] repaired and constructed thatched roofs for the village. The work demanded both skill and endurance, as [PAWN_pronoun] balanced on rooftops for hours. Years of labor made [PAWN_pronoun] strong and precise, but [PAWN_pronoun] rarely pursued creative endeavors.</VFEM_Thatcher17.description>
  <VFEM_Thatcher17.title>thatcher</VFEM_Thatcher17.title>
  <VFEM_Thatcher17.titleShort>thatcher</VFEM_Thatcher17.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Vagabond35.description>[PAWN_nameDef] wandered from village to village, taking odd jobs and sleeping wherever [PAWN_pronoun] could find shelter. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to survive on little and became skilled at adapting to new situations, but [PAWN_pronoun] never stayed in one place long enough to form meaningful relationships.</VFEM_Vagabond35.description>
  <VFEM_Vagabond35.title>vagabond</VFEM_Vagabond35.title>
  <VFEM_Vagabond35.titleShort>vagabond</VFEM_Vagabond35.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageBrewer18.description>[PAWN_nameDef] brewed ale for the village, perfecting recipes passed down through generations. The brewing process taught [PAWN_pronoun] patience and attention to detail, as each batch required careful timing and temperature control. [PAWN_pronoun] spent so much time brewing that [PAWN_pronoun] neglected physical training.</VFEM_VillageBrewer18.description>
  <VFEM_VillageBrewer18.title>village brewer</VFEM_VillageBrewer18.title>
  <VFEM_VillageBrewer18.titleShort>brewer</VFEM_VillageBrewer18.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageCook09.description>[PAWN_nameDef] prepared meals for the local villagers, using simple ingredients to make hearty stews and breads. [PAWN_pronoun] honed [PAWN_possessive] skills over countless fires and learned to stretch resources in times of scarcity. The kitchen, however, left no time for intellectual or artistic pursuits.</VFEM_VillageCook09.description>
  <VFEM_VillageCook09.title>village cook</VFEM_VillageCook09.title>
  <VFEM_VillageCook09.titleShort>cook</VFEM_VillageCook09.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageHunter01.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a small village and spent [PAWN_possessive] days hunting game to provide food for the community. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at tracking and setting traps but rarely interacted with others, preferring the solitude of the forest. Over time, [PAWN_pronoun] gained a reputation as a reliable provider, though [PAWN_possessive] social skills remained underdeveloped.</VFEM_VillageHunter01.description>
  <VFEM_VillageHunter01.title>village hunter</VFEM_VillageHunter01.title>
  <VFEM_VillageHunter01.titleShort>hunter</VFEM_VillageHunter01.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Watchman24.description>[PAWN_nameDef] guarded the village walls and gates, keeping an eye out for bandits and other threats. The job demanded vigilance and a steady hand, which [PAWN_pronoun] developed over long hours of patrol. Though experienced with ranged weapons, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely saw true battle.</VFEM_Watchman24.description>
  <VFEM_Watchman24.title>watchman</VFEM_Watchman24.title>
  <VFEM_Watchman24.titleShort>watchman</VFEM_Watchman24.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Weaver11.description>[PAWN_nameDef] worked at a loom, spinning thread into fabric for the village. The delicate work required focus and dexterity, which [PAWN_pronoun] developed over years of practice. However, the sedentary nature of weaving left [PAWN_pronoun] with little physical strength.</VFEM_Weaver11.description>
  <VFEM_Weaver11.title>weaver</VFEM_Weaver11.title>
  <VFEM_Weaver11.titleShort>weaver</VFEM_Weaver11.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Woodcutter03.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] life in the forests, cutting down trees to supply timber for the local village. The work was grueling, but it made [PAWN_pronoun] strong and skilled with tools. Though the solitude of the woods suited [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] never learned much about socializing or the finer arts of crafting.</VFEM_Woodcutter03.description>
  <VFEM_Woodcutter03.title>woodcutter</VFEM_Woodcutter03.title>
  <VFEM_Woodcutter03.titleShort>woodcutter</VFEM_Woodcutter03.titleShort>
  <VFEM_AlleySneak128.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] childhood slipping through alleys and shadows, avoiding the attention of adults and bullies. The streets taught [PAWN_pronoun] how to move silently and blend into crowds. While stealthy and clever, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked trust in others and avoided forming connections.</VFEM_AlleySneak128.description>
  <VFEM_AlleySneak128.title>alley sneak</VFEM_AlleySneak128.title>
  <VFEM_AlleySneak128.titleShort>sneak</VFEM_AlleySneak128.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BakersChild109.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood kneading dough and tending ovens in the family bakery. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a keen sense of timing and a knack for crafting simple but satisfying meals. The early mornings and long hours left [PAWN_pronoun] with a strong work ethic but little free time.</VFEM_BakersChild109.description>
  <VFEM_BakersChild109.title>baker's child</VFEM_BakersChild109.title>
  <VFEM_BakersChild109.titleShort>baker</VFEM_BakersChild109.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BeggarChild126.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] early years sitting in muddy streets, pleading for coins or scraps of food. The life taught [PAWN_pronoun] how to read people’s emotions and appeal to their sympathies, but it also made [PAWN_pronoun] deeply wary of rejection. Begging for survival left [PAWN_pronoun] resourceful but mistrusted.</VFEM_BeggarChild126.description>
  <VFEM_BeggarChild126.title>beggar child</VFEM_BeggarChild126.title>
  <VFEM_BeggarChild126.titleShort>beggar</VFEM_BeggarChild126.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BlacksmithsApprentice103.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] early years in a smoky forge, assisting [PAWN_possessive] family with small tasks like pumping bellows and carrying coal. The heat and noise became a constant part of [PAWN_possessive] life, and [PAWN_pronoun] began to understand the basics of crafting and hard work. Though the work was tiring, it sparked an appreciation for precision and skill.</VFEM_BlacksmithsApprentice103.description>
  <VFEM_BlacksmithsApprentice103.title>blacksmith's apprentice</VFEM_BlacksmithsApprentice103.title>
  <VFEM_BlacksmithsApprentice103.titleShort>apprentice</VFEM_BlacksmithsApprentice103.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ClanStoryteller140.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up learning the sagas and legends of [PAWN_possessive] ancestors, memorizing the stories that bound the clan together. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a gift for storytelling and inspiring others with words. Though not a warrior, [PAWN_pronoun] played an important role in preserving [PAWN_possessive] people’s history and culture.</VFEM_ClanStoryteller140.description>
  <VFEM_ClanStoryteller140.title>clan storyteller</VFEM_ClanStoryteller140.title>
  <VFEM_ClanStoryteller140.titleShort>storyteller</VFEM_ClanStoryteller140.titleShort>
  <VFEM_EarlyLaborer115.description>[PAWN_nameDef] started working in the fields as soon as [PAWN_pronoun] could carry a tool, spending long days planting and harvesting. The grueling work made [PAWN_pronoun] strong and resilient but left little time for play or education. Despite the hardships, [PAWN_pronoun] grew to appreciate the rewards of hard work.</VFEM_EarlyLaborer115.description>
  <VFEM_EarlyLaborer115.title>early laborer</VFEM_EarlyLaborer115.title>
  <VFEM_EarlyLaborer115.titleShort>laborer</VFEM_EarlyLaborer115.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FarmersChild104.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up working the fields with [PAWN_possessive] family, planting crops and tending to livestock. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at using simple tools and understanding the rhythms of the seasons. The hard labor instilled a strong work ethic but left little time for formal learning.</VFEM_FarmersChild104.description>
  <VFEM_FarmersChild104.title>farmer's child</VFEM_FarmersChild104.title>
  <VFEM_FarmersChild104.titleShort>farmhand</VFEM_FarmersChild104.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FarmsteadHand138.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a Viking farmstead, helping tend to livestock and till the soil during the short growing seasons. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the cycles of planting and harvest while preparing for the colder months. Life on the farm taught [PAWN_pronoun] hard work and how to endure nature’s challenges.</VFEM_FarmsteadHand138.description>
  <VFEM_FarmsteadHand138.title>farmstead hand</VFEM_FarmsteadHand138.title>
  <VFEM_FarmsteadHand138.titleShort>farmhand</VFEM_FarmsteadHand138.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FieldWatcher117.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent hours sitting by the fields, keeping an eye out for crows, rabbits, or anything else that might harm the crops. [PAWN_pronoun] learned patience and vigilance, but the solitary work left [PAWN_pronoun] starved for human interaction. [PAWN_pronoun] grew resourceful, using simple tools to ward off pests and predators.</VFEM_FieldWatcher117.description>
  <VFEM_FieldWatcher117.title>field watcher</VFEM_FieldWatcher117.title>
  <VFEM_FieldWatcher117.titleShort>watcher</VFEM_FieldWatcher117.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FieldWorker131.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] early years helping in the fields, learning to plant and harvest crops. The work was repetitive but rewarding, teaching [PAWN_pronoun] the value of patience and effort. [PAWN_pronoun] grew up strong and practical, with a deep appreciation for the land.</VFEM_FieldWorker131.description>
  <VFEM_FieldWorker131.title>field worker</VFEM_FieldWorker131.title>
  <VFEM_FieldWorker131.titleShort>worker</VFEM_FieldWorker131.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FishermansChild105.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] youth casting nets and hauling in fish alongside [PAWN_possessive] family. The smell of salt and the sound of water became second nature to [PAWN_objective], as did a knack for patience and a steady hand. Life on the water left [PAWN_pronoun] with a practical mindset and the ability to adapt to challenges.</VFEM_FishermansChild105.description>
  <VFEM_FishermansChild105.title>fisherman’s child</VFEM_FishermansChild105.title>
  <VFEM_FishermansChild105.titleShort>fisher</VFEM_FishermansChild105.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FjordFisher136.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood fishing along the rocky fjords, learning to handle nets and row longboats in icy waters. The life taught [PAWN_pronoun] resilience and respect for the sea’s power. Though the work was cold and grueling, [PAWN_pronoun] grew up strong and capable in harsh conditions.</VFEM_FjordFisher136.description>
  <VFEM_FjordFisher136.title>fjord fisher</VFEM_FjordFisher136.title>
  <VFEM_FjordFisher136.titleShort>fisher</VFEM_FjordFisher136.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ForestForager111.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood scouring the woods for berries, herbs, and mushrooms to help feed the village. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to identify edible plants and navigate dense forests with ease. Though [PAWN_pronoun] rarely interacted with others, [PAWN_pronoun] became deeply attuned to nature.</VFEM_ForestForager111.description>
  <VFEM_ForestForager111.title>forest forager</VFEM_ForestForager111.title>
  <VFEM_ForestForager111.titleShort>forager</VFEM_ForestForager111.titleShort>
  <VFEM_HearthKeeper134.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up tending the hearth and helping prepare meals for the family. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the basics of cooking and the importance of keeping the fire burning through the night. Though the work was simple, it taught [PAWN_pronoun] the value of care and consistency.</VFEM_HearthKeeper134.description>
  <VFEM_HearthKeeper134.title>hearth keeper</VFEM_HearthKeeper134.title>
  <VFEM_HearthKeeper134.titleShort>keeper</VFEM_HearthKeeper134.titleShort>
  <VFEM_HuntersChild108.description>[PAWN_nameDef] followed [PAWN_possessive] family through the forests, learning to track animals and use a bow. [PAWN_pronoun] grew up attuned to the wilderness, with sharp instincts and steady hands. While skilled at survival, [PAWN_pronoun] spent little time with other children and was often solitary.</VFEM_HuntersChild108.description>
  <VFEM_HuntersChild108.title>hunter's child</VFEM_HuntersChild108.title>
  <VFEM_HuntersChild108.titleShort>hunter</VFEM_HuntersChild108.titleShort>
  <VFEM_LongboatPaddler139.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised on tales of far-off lands and spent [PAWN_possessive] youth rowing Viking longboats. [PAWN_pronoun] gained strength and endurance from the endless paddling while learning the rhythms of the sea. Though not yet a raider, [PAWN_pronoun] was well-prepared for a life of exploration and adventure.</VFEM_LongboatPaddler139.description>
  <VFEM_LongboatPaddler139.title>longboat paddler</VFEM_LongboatPaddler139.title>
  <VFEM_LongboatPaddler139.titleShort>paddler</VFEM_LongboatPaddler139.titleShort>
  <VFEM_MarketHelper118.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood helping traders set up their stalls, haul goods, and haggle with customers. The bustling marketplace taught [PAWN_pronoun] how to read people and bargain effectively. Though quick-witted, [PAWN_pronoun] had little time for physical labor outside the market.</VFEM_MarketHelper118.description>
  <VFEM_MarketHelper118.title>market helper</VFEM_MarketHelper118.title>
  <VFEM_MarketHelper118.titleShort>helper</VFEM_MarketHelper118.titleShort>
  <VFEM_MillersChild107.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up around the constant hum of the mill, helping [PAWN_possessive] family grind grain into flour. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the importance of precision and efficiency, keeping the machinery running smoothly. [PAWN_pronoun] also gained a knack for basic problem-solving when repairs were needed.</VFEM_MillersChild107.description>
  <VFEM_MillersChild107.title>miller's child</VFEM_MillersChild107.title>
  <VFEM_MillersChild107.titleShort>miller</VFEM_MillersChild107.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Outcast122.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was shunned by the other children in [PAWN_possessive] village for reasons [PAWN_pronoun] never fully understood. Forced to fend for [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] days alone in the wilderness or on the village outskirts. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a deep sense of independence and distrust of others.</VFEM_Outcast122.description>
  <VFEM_Outcast122.title>outcast</VFEM_Outcast122.title>
  <VFEM_Outcast122.titleShort>outcast</VFEM_Outcast122.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Pickpocket123.description>[PAWN_nameDef] turned to petty theft as a way to survive in a world that had little use for [PAWN_objective]. [PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned to move unseen and snatch valuables without getting caught. While skilled at stealing, [PAWN_pronoun] earned a reputation for dishonesty and was never trusted by others.</VFEM_Pickpocket123.description>
  <VFEM_Pickpocket123.title>pickpocket</VFEM_Pickpocket123.title>
  <VFEM_Pickpocket123.titleShort>thief</VFEM_Pickpocket123.titleShort>
  <VFEM_PlayfulExplorer133.description>[PAWN_nameDef] loved wandering the woods and hills near the village, discovering hidden streams and climbing trees. [PAWN_pronoun] often returned with scratched knees and pockets full of interesting stones or berries. Though more playful than productive, [PAWN_pronoun] grew up with a keen sense of adventure and a connection to nature.</VFEM_PlayfulExplorer133.description>
  <VFEM_PlayfulExplorer133.title>playful explorer</VFEM_PlayfulExplorer133.title>
  <VFEM_PlayfulExplorer133.titleShort>explorer</VFEM_PlayfulExplorer133.titleShort>
  <VFEM_QuietObserver114.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood watching the world from the edges, unnoticed but always attentive. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to listen, read emotions, and predict behavior, skills that [PAWN_pronoun] used to avoid trouble and gain favor. While [PAWN_pronoun] excelled at understanding others, [PAWN_pronoun] avoided physical labor whenever possible.</VFEM_QuietObserver114.description>
  <VFEM_QuietObserver114.title>quiet observer</VFEM_QuietObserver114.title>
  <VFEM_QuietObserver114.titleShort>observer</VFEM_QuietObserver114.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RatCatcher124.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was tasked with clearing vermin from food stores and homes, often wading into the dirtiest corners of the village. [PAWN_pronoun] developed quick reflexes and an uncanny knack for traps, but the work left [PAWN_pronoun] isolated and avoided by others. The smell of [PAWN_possessive] trade lingered wherever [PAWN_pronoun] went.</VFEM_RatCatcher124.description>
  <VFEM_RatCatcher124.title>rat catcher</VFEM_RatCatcher124.title>
  <VFEM_RatCatcher124.titleShort>rat catcher</VFEM_RatCatcher124.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RiverWader112.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent endless hours by the river, catching fish with traps and nets. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at spotting fish and understanding the flow of water, skills that kept [PAWN_objective] well-fed even in lean times. Life by the river gave [PAWN_pronoun] a practical outlook but limited [PAWN_possessive] social skills.</VFEM_RiverWader112.description>
  <VFEM_RiverWader112.title>river wader</VFEM_RiverWader112.title>
  <VFEM_RiverWader112.titleShort>river wader</VFEM_RiverWader112.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RuntOfThePack130.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was the smallest and weakest of [PAWN_possessive] peers, often picked on by others. To survive, [PAWN_pronoun] learned to think fast and avoid direct conflicts, relying on cunning to outsmart [PAWN_possessive] tormentors. Though quick and clever, [PAWN_pronoun] grew up mistrustful and fiercely independent.</VFEM_RuntOfThePack130.description>
  <VFEM_RuntOfThePack130.title>runt of the pack</VFEM_RuntOfThePack130.title>
  <VFEM_RuntOfThePack130.titleShort>runt</VFEM_RuntOfThePack130.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ScrapHoarder127.description>[PAWN_nameDef] collected broken tools, discarded wood, and other castoffs, turning them into makeshift toys or tools. Though often teased for [PAWN_possessive] peculiar habits, [PAWN_pronoun] became adept at finding value in things others overlooked. [PAWN_pronoun] gained practical skills but struggled to connect with others.</VFEM_ScrapHoarder127.description>
  <VFEM_ScrapHoarder127.title>scrap hoarder</VFEM_ScrapHoarder127.title>
  <VFEM_ScrapHoarder127.titleShort>hoarder</VFEM_ScrapHoarder127.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ShepherdsChild102.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood helping [PAWN_possessive] family tend sheep on the hillsides near the village. [PAWN_pronoun] learned patience, vigilance, and a deep understanding of animal behavior. The quiet life also gave [PAWN_pronoun] plenty of time to dream and observe the world around [PAWN_objective].</VFEM_ShepherdsChild102.description>
  <VFEM_ShepherdsChild102.title>shepherd's child</VFEM_ShepherdsChild102.title>
  <VFEM_ShepherdsChild102.titleShort>shepherd</VFEM_ShepherdsChild102.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ShieldBearer137.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was trained from a young age to carry shields and assist warriors during raids and battles. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to endure heavy loads and follow commands, watching closely as the older fighters honed their skills. The experience prepared [PAWN_pronoun] for a life of conflict and loyalty to [PAWN_possessive] clan.</VFEM_ShieldBearer137.description>
  <VFEM_ShieldBearer137.title>shield bearer</VFEM_ShieldBearer137.title>
  <VFEM_ShieldBearer137.titleShort>shield bearer</VFEM_ShieldBearer137.titleShort>
  <VFEM_StablehandsChild110.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in the stables, helping care for horses and keeping the stalls clean. [PAWN_pronoun] learned the basics of animal care and the value of steady, dependable work. While comfortable around animals, [PAWN_pronoun] often struggled to relate to [PAWN_possessive] peers.</VFEM_StablehandsChild110.description>
  <VFEM_StablehandsChild110.title>stablehand's child</VFEM_StablehandsChild110.title>
  <VFEM_StablehandsChild110.titleShort>stablehand</VFEM_StablehandsChild110.titleShort>
  <VFEM_StreetEntertainer120.description>[PAWN_nameDef] performed in the village square as a juggler, singer, or storyteller, hoping to earn coins or scraps of food. [PAWN_pronoun] learned how to capture an audience’s attention and bring joy to others, even when times were tough. While talented in performance, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with practical skills outside the arts.</VFEM_StreetEntertainer120.description>
  <VFEM_StreetEntertainer120.title>street entertainer</VFEM_StreetEntertainer120.title>
  <VFEM_StreetEntertainer120.titleShort>entertainer</VFEM_StreetEntertainer120.titleShort>
  <VFEM_StreetScavenger121.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up scavenging through garbage and refuse, searching for anything [PAWN_pronoun] could eat or sell. The harsh life taught [PAWN_pronoun] how to survive with very little but left [PAWN_pronoun] mistrusting of others. [PAWN_pronoun] became quick on [PAWN_possessive] feet to avoid confrontations over scraps.</VFEM_StreetScavenger121.description>
  <VFEM_StreetScavenger121.title>street scavenger</VFEM_StreetScavenger121.title>
  <VFEM_StreetScavenger121.titleShort>scavenger</VFEM_StreetScavenger121.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Troublemaker125.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was known for causing mischief and stirring up chaos, often at the expense of others. [PAWN_pronoun] enjoyed playing pranks, picking fights, and pushing boundaries wherever possible. Though disliked by adults and peers alike, [PAWN_pronoun] developed sharp wits and quick reflexes to avoid punishment.</VFEM_Troublemaker125.description>
  <VFEM_Troublemaker125.title>troublemaker</VFEM_Troublemaker125.title>
  <VFEM_Troublemaker125.titleShort>troublemaker</VFEM_Troublemaker125.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageGatherer135.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent much of [PAWN_possessive] childhood collecting firewood, herbs, and other necessities for the village. The long days outdoors gave [PAWN_pronoun] an eye for useful plants and a steady hand for simple tools. [PAWN_pronoun] grew up practical and capable, well-suited to life in the countryside.</VFEM_VillageGatherer135.description>
  <VFEM_VillageGatherer135.title>village gatherer</VFEM_VillageGatherer135.title>
  <VFEM_VillageGatherer135.titleShort>gatherer</VFEM_VillageGatherer135.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageHelper132.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood running errands and helping with small tasks around the village. Whether delivering goods, fetching water, or mending fences, [PAWN_pronoun] was always willing to lend a hand. These simple chores instilled [PAWN_pronoun] with a strong work ethic and practical skills.</VFEM_VillageHelper132.description>
  <VFEM_VillageHelper132.title>village helper</VFEM_VillageHelper132.title>
  <VFEM_VillageHelper132.titleShort>helper</VFEM_VillageHelper132.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageRunner116.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was often tasked with delivering messages and small packages between villagers. [PAWN_pronoun] spent countless hours running along dirt paths, learning the fastest routes and how to avoid danger. The constant movement made [PAWN_pronoun] quick and agile but left little time for rest or study.</VFEM_VillageRunner116.description>
  <VFEM_VillageRunner116.title>village runner</VFEM_VillageRunner116.title>
  <VFEM_VillageRunner116.titleShort>runner</VFEM_VillageRunner116.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageScapegoat129.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was blamed for every broken tool, missing coin, or spoiled crop in the village, often regardless of [PAWN_possessive] involvement. The constant accusations taught [PAWN_pronoun] how to endure hardship and avoid confrontations. [PAWN_pronoun] grew to be resourceful but deeply mistrustful of authority.</VFEM_VillageScapegoat129.description>
  <VFEM_VillageScapegoat129.title>village scapegoat</VFEM_VillageScapegoat129.title>
  <VFEM_VillageScapegoat129.titleShort>scapegoat</VFEM_VillageScapegoat129.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageUrchin101.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as a street child in a small village, surviving by stealing scraps and begging from passersby. [PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned to navigate crowded markets and avoid the watchful eyes of the guards. Though [PAWN_pronoun] lacked formal education, [PAWN_pronoun] became clever and resourceful.</VFEM_VillageUrchin101.description>
  <VFEM_VillageUrchin101.title>village urchin</VFEM_VillageUrchin101.title>
  <VFEM_VillageUrchin101.titleShort>urchin</VFEM_VillageUrchin101.titleShort>
  <VFEM_WanderingHelper113.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up lending a hand wherever [PAWN_pronoun] could, moving from farm to farm doing odd jobs. From tending crops to mending fences, [PAWN_pronoun] learned a little bit of everything but mastered none. Constantly on the move, [PAWN_pronoun] never formed close friendships but gained practical skills.</VFEM_WanderingHelper113.description>
  <VFEM_WanderingHelper113.title>wandering helper</VFEM_WanderingHelper113.title>
  <VFEM_WanderingHelper113.titleShort>helper</VFEM_WanderingHelper113.titleShort>
  <VFEM_WellTender119.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was responsible for keeping the village well clean and drawing water for the community. [PAWN_pronoun] grew strong from hauling heavy buckets and learned to maintain the mechanisms that made the work easier. The repetitive work left [PAWN_pronoun] with little variety but a dependable skill set.</VFEM_WellTender119.description>
  <VFEM_WellTender119.title>well tender</VFEM_WellTender119.title>
  <VFEM_WellTender119.titleShort>well tender</VFEM_WellTender119.titleShort>
  <VFEM_WoodcuttersChild106.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up helping [PAWN_possessive] family cut trees and haul logs from the nearby forest. [PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned to handle axes and saws, developing both strength and skill. Though accustomed to hard labor, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely had time for anything beyond work and rest.</VFEM_WoodcuttersChild106.description>
  <VFEM_WoodcuttersChild106.title>woodcutter's child</VFEM_WoodcuttersChild106.title>
  <VFEM_WoodcuttersChild106.titleShort>woodcutter</VFEM_WoodcuttersChild106.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Armorer57.description>[PAWN_nameDef] crafted fine weapons and armor for knights and nobles, perfecting [PAWN_possessive] trade in the forge. [PAWN_pronoun] developed an unmatched skill in shaping steel into works of art and tools of war. Though a master artisan, [PAWN_pronoun] often neglected other aspects of life, focusing solely on [PAWN_possessive] craft.</VFEM_Armorer57.description>
  <VFEM_Armorer57.title>armorer</VFEM_Armorer57.title>
  <VFEM_Armorer57.titleShort>armorer</VFEM_Armorer57.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Baron67.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was granted the title of baron and ruled over a small region in [PAWN_possessive] lord's service. [PAWN_pronoun] managed taxes, enforced laws, and led the local militia when needed. Though [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in leadership, [PAWN_pronoun] saw manual labor as the work of peasants.</VFEM_Baron67.description>
  <VFEM_Baron67.title>baron</VFEM_Baron67.title>
  <VFEM_Baron67.titleShort>baron</VFEM_Baron67.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BaronOfTheWoodlands91.description>[PAWN_nameDef] presided over a vast forested estate, managing timber, game, and the people who lived beneath the canopy. [PAWN_pronoun] was skilled at balancing resource exploitation with conservation, ensuring the lordship’s wealth for generations. While [PAWN_pronoun] understood the land and its uses, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely participated in court politics.</VFEM_BaronOfTheWoodlands91.description>
  <VFEM_BaronOfTheWoodlands91.title>baron of the woodlands</VFEM_BaronOfTheWoodlands91.title>
  <VFEM_BaronOfTheWoodlands91.titleShort>woodland baron</VFEM_BaronOfTheWoodlands91.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BeastTamer78.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was known for [PAWN_possessive] ability to tame and train even the wildest of animals. [PAWN_pronoun] was often called upon to handle dangerous beasts, a skill that earned both admiration and fear. Years spent with creatures left [PAWN_pronoun] more at ease with animals than people.</VFEM_BeastTamer78.description>
  <VFEM_BeastTamer78.title>beast tamer</VFEM_BeastTamer78.title>
  <VFEM_BeastTamer78.titleShort>beast tamer</VFEM_BeastTamer78.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Castellan56.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was entrusted with the management of a noble's castle, ensuring its defenses were maintained and its residents well-cared for. [PAWN_pronoun] became an expert in logistics and leadership, coordinating repairs and overseeing the garrison. While skilled in administration and strategy, [PAWN_pronoun] left manual tasks to the servants.</VFEM_Castellan56.description>
  <VFEM_Castellan56.title>castellan</VFEM_Castellan56.title>
  <VFEM_Castellan56.titleShort>castellan</VFEM_Castellan56.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CastellanOfArms62.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was entrusted with the armory of a great castle, overseeing the maintenance and distribution of weapons and armor. [PAWN_pronoun] became an expert in the design and upkeep of equipment, ensuring the garrison was always ready for battle. Though skilled in [PAWN_possessive] craft, [PAWN_pronoun] left combat to the knights [PAWN_pronoun] served.</VFEM_CastellanOfArms62.description>
  <VFEM_CastellanOfArms62.title>castellan of arms</VFEM_CastellanOfArms62.title>
  <VFEM_CastellanOfArms62.titleShort>armorer</VFEM_CastellanOfArms62.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CommanderOfTheWatch73.description>[PAWN_nameDef] led a band of sworn warriors tasked with guarding the borderlands from threats beyond. [PAWN_pronoun] was skilled in tactics, inspiring loyalty in [PAWN_possessive] men while maintaining discipline in harsh conditions. Though [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in combat and leadership, [PAWN_pronoun] remained isolated from the intrigues of court life.</VFEM_CommanderOfTheWatch73.description>
  <VFEM_CommanderOfTheWatch73.title>commander of the watch</VFEM_CommanderOfTheWatch73.title>
  <VFEM_CommanderOfTheWatch73.titleShort>commander</VFEM_CommanderOfTheWatch73.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CourtBard54.description>[PAWN_nameDef] entertained the courts of lords and kings with poetic tales, music, and sharp wit. [PAWN_pronoun] became a master of performance and an expert in reading the social dynamics of the nobility. Though praised for [PAWN_possessive] artistic brilliance, [PAWN_pronoun] avoided manual labor and relied on [PAWN_possessive] charm to navigate life.</VFEM_CourtBard54.description>
  <VFEM_CourtBard54.title>court bard</VFEM_CourtBard54.title>
  <VFEM_CourtBard54.titleShort>bard</VFEM_CourtBard54.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CourtPhysician60.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served in the noble court, tending to the illnesses and injuries of the ruling family. [PAWN_pronoun] gained expertise in medicine and herbal remedies, becoming a trusted advisor in matters of health. Though valued for [PAWN_possessive] skills, [PAWN_pronoun] had little patience for physical labor.</VFEM_CourtPhysician60.description>
  <VFEM_CourtPhysician60.title>court physician</VFEM_CourtPhysician60.title>
  <VFEM_CourtPhysician60.titleShort>physician</VFEM_CourtPhysician60.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CourtSchemer74.description>[PAWN_nameDef] thrived in the cutthroat world of the royal court, manipulating allies and enemies alike to advance [PAWN_possessive] ambitions. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled in deception, politics, and reading people’s motives. While [PAWN_pronoun] rarely took to the battlefield, [PAWN_pronoun] wielded words as effectively as others wielded swords.</VFEM_CourtSchemer74.description>
  <VFEM_CourtSchemer74.title>court schemer</VFEM_CourtSchemer74.title>
  <VFEM_CourtSchemer74.titleShort>schemer</VFEM_CourtSchemer74.titleShort>
  <VFEM_DebauchedAristocrat83.description>[PAWN_nameDef] squandered [PAWN_possessive] family’s wealth on lavish parties and indulgent pursuits, earning the ire of [PAWN_possessive] peers. Though well-versed in etiquette and manipulation, [PAWN_pronoun] alienated allies and left [PAWN_possessive] family struggling to maintain their status. [PAWN_pronoun] remains charming but untrustworthy.</VFEM_DebauchedAristocrat83.description>
  <VFEM_DebauchedAristocrat83.title>debauched aristocrat</VFEM_DebauchedAristocrat83.title>
  <VFEM_DebauchedAristocrat83.titleShort>debauched</VFEM_DebauchedAristocrat83.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Diplomat58.description>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled between courts, negotiating treaties and mediating disputes between noble houses. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in persuasion and understanding the intricacies of politics, earning a reputation for tact and wisdom. [PAWN_pronoun] left physical tasks to others, relying on [PAWN_possessive] intellect and charm to succeed.</VFEM_Diplomat58.description>
  <VFEM_Diplomat58.title>diplomat</VFEM_Diplomat58.title>
  <VFEM_Diplomat58.titleShort>diplomat</VFEM_Diplomat58.titleShort>
  <VFEM_DisgracedHeir81.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was once poised to inherit a noble title, but a scandal stripped [PAWN_objective] of [PAWN_possessive] birthright. Cast out from [PAWN_possessive] family, [PAWN_pronoun] became a shadow of [PAWN_possessive] former self, surviving through cunning and scraps of [PAWN_possessive] once-great wealth. Though [PAWN_pronoun] retained the manners of a noble, [PAWN_pronoun] was shunned by high society.</VFEM_DisgracedHeir81.description>
  <VFEM_DisgracedHeir81.title>disgraced heir</VFEM_DisgracedHeir81.title>
  <VFEM_DisgracedHeir81.titleShort>disgraced</VFEM_DisgracedHeir81.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ExiledNoble82.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was banished from [PAWN_possessive] homeland after losing a power struggle within [PAWN_possessive] family. Forced to flee, [PAWN_pronoun] lived in obscurity, using [PAWN_possessive] charm and wit to survive in foreign lands. While [PAWN_pronoun] retained noble airs, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled to regain the privileges of [PAWN_possessive] birth.</VFEM_ExiledNoble82.description>
  <VFEM_ExiledNoble82.title>exiled noble</VFEM_ExiledNoble82.title>
  <VFEM_ExiledNoble82.titleShort>exiled</VFEM_ExiledNoble82.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Falconer76.description>[PAWN_nameDef] trained and cared for hunting birds, guiding them to track prey for [PAWN_possessive] lord. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a deep understanding of animal behavior and earned respect for [PAWN_possessive] skill in falconry. While skilled with animals, [PAWN_pronoun] had little experience with tasks unrelated to [PAWN_possessive] craft.</VFEM_Falconer76.description>
  <VFEM_Falconer76.title>falconer</VFEM_Falconer76.title>
  <VFEM_Falconer76.titleShort>falconer</VFEM_Falconer76.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FallenKnight85.description>[PAWN_nameDef] once swore an oath of loyalty as a knight but broke [PAWN_possessive] vows in pursuit of personal gain. Disgraced and stripped of [PAWN_possessive] title, [PAWN_pronoun] now wanders as a sell-sword, haunted by [PAWN_possessive] dishonor. Though [PAWN_pronoun] retains [PAWN_possessive] combat skills, [PAWN_pronoun] struggles to regain the respect [PAWN_pronoun] once commanded.</VFEM_FallenKnight85.description>
  <VFEM_FallenKnight85.title>fallen knight</VFEM_FallenKnight85.title>
  <VFEM_FallenKnight85.titleShort>fallen knight</VFEM_FallenKnight85.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Guildmaster59.description>[PAWN_nameDef] led a prosperous guild, coordinating the efforts of skilled artisans and merchants. [PAWN_pronoun] became a shrewd leader and negotiator, balancing trade and politics to secure the guild's interests. While brilliant in leadership, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely engaged in the craft [PAWN_pronoun] oversaw.</VFEM_Guildmaster59.description>
  <VFEM_Guildmaster59.title>guildmaster</VFEM_Guildmaster59.title>
  <VFEM_Guildmaster59.titleShort>guildmaster</VFEM_Guildmaster59.titleShort>
  <VFEM_HighNoble68.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into one of the most powerful noble families in the land, growing up surrounded by luxury and political intrigue. [PAWN_pronoun] mastered the art of diplomacy and the subtleties of court politics, earning a reputation as a skilled negotiator. While proficient in social and intellectual pursuits, [PAWN_pronoun] relied entirely on servants for physical tasks.</VFEM_HighNoble68.description>
  <VFEM_HighNoble68.title>high noble</VFEM_HighNoble68.title>
  <VFEM_HighNoble68.titleShort>noble</VFEM_HighNoble68.titleShort>
  <VFEM_HighPriest96.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as the spiritual leader of an influential ideology, presiding over rituals and interpreting sacred texts. [PAWN_pronoun] became a master of oratory and philosophy, guiding [PAWN_possessive] followers through times of prosperity and hardship. Though revered for [PAWN_possessive] wisdom, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely engaged in physical labor.</VFEM_HighPriest96.description>
  <VFEM_HighPriest96.title>high priest</VFEM_HighPriest96.title>
  <VFEM_HighPriest96.titleShort>priest</VFEM_HighPriest96.titleShort>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalCrusader99.description>[PAWN_nameDef] fought to spread [PAWN_possessive] ideology by force, leading armies in its name. [PAWN_pronoun] was a fearsome warrior and an inspiring leader, rallying others to [PAWN_possessive] cause with [PAWN_possessive] fervor. While skilled in combat and persuasion, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked the patience for intellectual pursuits.</VFEM_IdeologicalCrusader99.description>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalCrusader99.title>ideological crusader</VFEM_IdeologicalCrusader99.title>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalCrusader99.titleShort>crusader</VFEM_IdeologicalCrusader99.titleShort>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalOrator100.description>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled from village to village, delivering sermons and spreading the tenets of [PAWN_possessive] ideology. [PAWN_pronoun] was a charismatic speaker, capable of inspiring devotion or stirring up rebellion. Though skilled at rallying others, [PAWN_pronoun] had little experience with physical labor or practical skills.</VFEM_IdeologicalOrator100.description>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalOrator100.title>ideological orator</VFEM_IdeologicalOrator100.title>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalOrator100.titleShort>orator</VFEM_IdeologicalOrator100.titleShort>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalScholar97.description>[PAWN_nameDef] devoted [PAWN_possessive] life to studying the tenets of [PAWN_possessive] ideology, crafting treatises and debating its principles with others. [PAWN_pronoun] became highly respected for [PAWN_possessive] intellect and insight, often advising leaders on spiritual and ethical matters. While brilliant in [PAWN_possessive] field, [PAWN_pronoun] avoided manual or practical work.</VFEM_IdeologicalScholar97.description>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalScholar97.title>ideological scholar</VFEM_IdeologicalScholar97.title>
  <VFEM_IdeologicalScholar97.titleShort>scholar</VFEM_IdeologicalScholar97.titleShort>
  <VFEM_KeeperOfRelics98.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was entrusted with safeguarding the sacred artifacts of [PAWN_possessive] ideology, protecting them from harm and ensuring they were used in rituals. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a meticulous attention to detail and a deep reverence for [PAWN_possessive] duties. However, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked skills outside the preservation of relics and ceremonies.</VFEM_KeeperOfRelics98.description>
  <VFEM_KeeperOfRelics98.title>keeper of relics</VFEM_KeeperOfRelics98.title>
  <VFEM_KeeperOfRelics98.titleShort>keeper</VFEM_KeeperOfRelics98.titleShort>
  <VFEM_KeeperOfTheHerds93.description>[PAWN_nameDef] managed vast flocks of sheep and herds of cattle for [PAWN_possessive] noble family, ensuring the animals thrived year-round. [PAWN_pronoun] developed an unmatched understanding of animal care and breeding while overseeing the laborers who worked under [PAWN_objective]. Though well-respected in [PAWN_possessive] rural domain, [PAWN_pronoun] had little experience with urban or military life.</VFEM_KeeperOfTheHerds93.description>
  <VFEM_KeeperOfTheHerds93.title>keeper of the herds</VFEM_KeeperOfTheHerds93.title>
  <VFEM_KeeperOfTheHerds93.titleShort>herd keeper</VFEM_KeeperOfTheHerds93.titleShort>
  <VFEM_KennelMaster77.description>[PAWN_nameDef] cared for the lord’s hunting dogs, training them for the chase and keeping them healthy. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at managing animals and handling their temperaments, earning trust as an expert handler. [PAWN_pronoun] often spent more time with dogs than people, leaving [PAWN_pronoun] socially awkward.</VFEM_KennelMaster77.description>
  <VFEM_KennelMaster77.title>kennel master</VFEM_KennelMaster77.title>
  <VFEM_KennelMaster77.titleShort>kennel master</VFEM_KennelMaster77.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Knight51.description>[PAWN_nameDef] rose from the ranks of squires to earn [PAWN_possessive] title as a knight through courage and dedication. [PAWN_pronoun] became a master of swordplay and horseback combat, leading troops and protecting the realm with honor. While skilled in warfare, [PAWN_pronoun] considered manual labor beneath [PAWN_objective] and rarely engaged in menial tasks.</VFEM_Knight51.description>
  <VFEM_Knight51.title>knight</VFEM_Knight51.title>
  <VFEM_Knight51.titleShort>knight</VFEM_Knight51.titleShort>
  <VFEM_KnightCommander61.description>[PAWN_nameDef] led a company of knights into battle, earning [PAWN_possessive] title through years of skill and strategy. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled at coordinating troops, inspiring loyalty among [PAWN_possessive] men, and devising battle plans. While unmatched in leadership and combat, [PAWN_pronoun] considered manual labor beneath [PAWN_objective].</VFEM_KnightCommander61.description>
  <VFEM_KnightCommander61.title>knight commander</VFEM_KnightCommander61.title>
  <VFEM_KnightCommander61.titleShort>commander</VFEM_KnightCommander61.titleShort>
  <VFEM_KnightErrant63.description>[PAWN_nameDef] wandered the land as a knight errant, seeking to prove [PAWN_possessive] valor through combat and acts of chivalry. [PAWN_pronoun] mastered swordsmanship and gained a reputation for [PAWN_possessive] fearless bravery. While skilled in combat and diplomacy, [PAWN_pronoun] neglected practical skills during [PAWN_possessive] travels.</VFEM_KnightErrant63.description>
  <VFEM_KnightErrant63.title>knight errant</VFEM_KnightErrant63.title>
  <VFEM_KnightErrant63.titleShort>errant</VFEM_KnightErrant63.titleShort>
  <VFEM_LandedKnight87.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was granted a small estate in reward for [PAWN_possessive] service in battle. [PAWN_pronoun] balanced managing the land and protecting the local peasants, maintaining [PAWN_possessive] fighting skills while overseeing daily operations. Though a capable warrior and leader, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked the refinement of courtly life.</VFEM_LandedKnight87.description>
  <VFEM_LandedKnight87.title>landed knight</VFEM_LandedKnight87.title>
  <VFEM_LandedKnight87.titleShort>knight</VFEM_LandedKnight87.titleShort>
  <VFEM_LordsHeir66.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born as the eldest child of a noble family, destined to inherit the estate and title. [PAWN_pronoun] received the finest education in governance, diplomacy, and warfare. While skilled in leadership and strategy, [PAWN_pronoun] avoided physical labor, seeing it as beneath [PAWN_objective].</VFEM_LordsHeir66.description>
  <VFEM_LordsHeir66.title>lord's heir</VFEM_LordsHeir66.title>
  <VFEM_LordsHeir66.titleShort>heir</VFEM_LordsHeir66.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ManorLord86.description>[PAWN_nameDef] ruled over a countryside manor, overseeing the labor of serfs and ensuring the productivity of [PAWN_possessive] lands. [PAWN_pronoun] was skilled in managing people and resources, often mediating disputes and collecting taxes. Though respected locally, [PAWN_pronoun] had little exposure to the broader politics of noble society.</VFEM_ManorLord86.description>
  <VFEM_ManorLord86.title>manor lord</VFEM_ManorLord86.title>
  <VFEM_ManorLord86.titleShort>lord</VFEM_ManorLord86.titleShort>
  <VFEM_MasterOfWhispers72.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as the spymaster for a great lord, gathering intelligence through a network of informants and spies. [PAWN_pronoun] became an expert in intrigue, manipulation, and uncovering secrets, often wielding information as a weapon. While skilled in subterfuge, [PAWN_pronoun] avoided physical confrontations, preferring to work behind the scenes.</VFEM_MasterOfWhispers72.description>
  <VFEM_MasterOfWhispers72.title>master of whispers</VFEM_MasterOfWhispers72.title>
  <VFEM_MasterOfWhispers72.titleShort>spymaster</VFEM_MasterOfWhispers72.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Merchant52.description>[PAWN_nameDef] built [PAWN_possessive] wealth through savvy trade, traveling across regions to barter exotic goods and secure lucrative deals. [PAWN_pronoun] became highly skilled in negotiation and logistics, ensuring the success of [PAWN_possessive] ventures. Though financially successful, [PAWN_pronoun] relied on others for physical labor and practical skills.</VFEM_Merchant52.description>
  <VFEM_Merchant52.title>merchant</VFEM_Merchant52.title>
  <VFEM_Merchant52.titleShort>merchant</VFEM_Merchant52.titleShort>
  <VFEM_NobleDiplomat69.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was sent to foreign courts as a representative of [PAWN_possessive] family, brokering alliances and treaties. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled in diplomacy and negotiation, earning admiration for [PAWN_possessive] eloquence and charm. However, [PAWN_pronoun] relied on servants for physical labor and rarely engaged in manual tasks.</VFEM_NobleDiplomat69.description>
  <VFEM_NobleDiplomat69.title>noble diplomat</VFEM_NobleDiplomat69.title>
  <VFEM_NobleDiplomat69.titleShort>diplomat</VFEM_NobleDiplomat69.titleShort>
  <VFEM_NobleHeir53.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up surrounded by wealth and privilege, trained from a young age to govern lands and lead people. [PAWN_pronoun] mastered the art of diplomacy and honed [PAWN_possessive] skills in archery and strategy to prepare for [PAWN_possessive] future responsibilities. However, [PAWN_pronoun] considered manual work beneath [PAWN_objective] and delegated such tasks to servants.</VFEM_NobleHeir53.description>
  <VFEM_NobleHeir53.title>noble heir</VFEM_NobleHeir53.title>
  <VFEM_NobleHeir53.titleShort>noble</VFEM_NobleHeir53.titleShort>
  <VFEM_PastoralGuardian90.description>[PAWN_nameDef] protected the countryside estates and nearby villages from bandits and wild beasts. [PAWN_pronoun] served as a bridge between the nobility and common folk, maintaining order through diplomacy and strength. Though skilled in combat and negotiation, [PAWN_pronoun] remained rooted in the simplicity of rural life.</VFEM_PastoralGuardian90.description>
  <VFEM_PastoralGuardian90.title>pastoral guardian</VFEM_PastoralGuardian90.title>
  <VFEM_PastoralGuardian90.titleShort>guardian</VFEM_PastoralGuardian90.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RiverWarden94.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was responsible for patrolling and protecting the rivers flowing through [PAWN_possessive] family’s lands. [PAWN_pronoun] ensured trade and fishing were conducted lawfully, earning respect as a fair and capable overseer. Though [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in maintaining order, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked skills in diplomacy beyond [PAWN_possessive] domain.</VFEM_RiverWarden94.description>
  <VFEM_RiverWarden94.title>river warden</VFEM_RiverWarden94.title>
  <VFEM_RiverWarden94.titleShort>warden</VFEM_RiverWarden94.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RoyalGuard64.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as one of the elite guards sworn to protect the king and [PAWN_possessive] family. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained in both melee and ranged combat, becoming highly skilled in personal defense and loyalty. The prestigious position left [PAWN_pronoun] unaccustomed to menial tasks, focusing solely on [PAWN_possessive] duty.</VFEM_RoyalGuard64.description>
  <VFEM_RoyalGuard64.title>royal guard</VFEM_RoyalGuard64.title>
  <VFEM_RoyalGuard64.titleShort>guard</VFEM_RoyalGuard64.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RoyalKnight70.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was trained from a young age to serve the king directly as a member of [PAWN_possessive] personal guard. [PAWN_pronoun] became a master of both mounted and melee combat, earning the respect of peers and commanders alike. While [PAWN_pronoun] excelled on the battlefield, [PAWN_pronoun] avoided menial tasks, considering them unworthy of [PAWN_possessive] status.</VFEM_RoyalKnight70.description>
  <VFEM_RoyalKnight70.title>royal knight</VFEM_RoyalKnight70.title>
  <VFEM_RoyalKnight70.titleShort>royal knight</VFEM_RoyalKnight70.titleShort>
  <VFEM_RuralCastellan92.description>[PAWN_nameDef] oversaw a remote fortress, serving as the noble family’s representative in the countryside. [PAWN_pronoun] maintained the keep, organized the defense of local villages, and managed disputes among the serfs. [PAWN_pronoun] was skilled in construction and leadership but lacked the sophistication of high court life.</VFEM_RuralCastellan92.description>
  <VFEM_RuralCastellan92.title>rural castellan</VFEM_RuralCastellan92.title>
  <VFEM_RuralCastellan92.titleShort>castellan</VFEM_RuralCastellan92.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Shepherd79.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days guiding flocks of sheep across pastures, protecting them from predators and ensuring their well-being. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to live off the land and gained a natural affinity for animals. Though adept at caring for livestock, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked interest in pursuits beyond [PAWN_possessive] work.</VFEM_Shepherd79.description>
  <VFEM_Shepherd79.title>shepherd of the flock</VFEM_Shepherd79.title>
  <VFEM_Shepherd79.titleShort>shepherd</VFEM_Shepherd79.titleShort>
  <VFEM_SouthernLord75.description>[PAWN_nameDef] ruled over a warm and fertile region, maintaining order and wealth through agriculture and trade. [PAWN_pronoun] developed strong diplomatic skills to navigate the alliances and rivalries of neighboring houses. Though adept at politics, [PAWN_pronoun] relied on others for matters of warfare and manual labor.</VFEM_SouthernLord75.description>
  <VFEM_SouthernLord75.title>southern lord</VFEM_SouthernLord75.title>
  <VFEM_SouthernLord75.titleShort>lord</VFEM_SouthernLord75.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Steward55.description>[PAWN_nameDef] managed the estates of a noble, overseeing finances, organizing events, and ensuring the smooth operation of the household. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in administration and diplomacy, becoming indispensable to the lord [PAWN_pronoun] served. Though proficient in intellectual and social skills, [PAWN_pronoun] saw physical labor as beneath [PAWN_objective].</VFEM_Steward55.description>
  <VFEM_Steward55.title>steward</VFEM_Steward55.title>
  <VFEM_Steward55.titleShort>steward</VFEM_Steward55.titleShort>
  <VFEM_StewardOfTheFields89.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was responsible for managing the agricultural production of a large estate, ensuring the fields were worked and the harvests collected. [PAWN_pronoun] developed a deep understanding of farming and organization, balancing the needs of the land with the demands of [PAWN_possessive] lord. Though skilled in rural management, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked military and courtly training.</VFEM_StewardOfTheFields89.description>
  <VFEM_StewardOfTheFields89.title>steward of the fields</VFEM_StewardOfTheFields89.title>
  <VFEM_StewardOfTheFields89.titleShort>steward</VFEM_StewardOfTheFields89.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Strategist65.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a master tactician, advising lords and generals on the best paths to victory. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled at reading the battlefield, coordinating troops, and anticipating enemy moves. Though [PAWN_pronoun] rarely fought directly, [PAWN_pronoun] commanded respect for [PAWN_possessive] brilliant mind and sharp tongue.</VFEM_Strategist65.description>
  <VFEM_Strategist65.title>strategist</VFEM_Strategist65.title>
  <VFEM_Strategist65.titleShort>strategist</VFEM_Strategist65.titleShort>
  <VFEM_UsurpersKin84.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a family that seized power through treachery, earning the scorn of noble society. [PAWN_pronoun] grew up isolated and mistrusted, forced to rely on guile and intelligence to navigate the court. Though skilled in intrigue, [PAWN_pronoun] lacked the respect and alliances of legitimate noble houses.</VFEM_UsurpersKin84.description>
  <VFEM_UsurpersKin84.title>usurper's kin</VFEM_UsurpersKin84.title>
  <VFEM_UsurpersKin84.titleShort>disgraced kin</VFEM_UsurpersKin84.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageElder88.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a respected figure in a rural community, resolving disputes and guiding decisions for the benefit of the village. [PAWN_pronoun] developed wisdom through years of leadership and experience, earning the trust of those under [PAWN_possessive] care. While [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in diplomacy, [PAWN_pronoun] left physical tasks to the younger villagers.</VFEM_VillageElder88.description>
  <VFEM_VillageElder88.title>village elder</VFEM_VillageElder88.title>
  <VFEM_VillageElder88.titleShort>elder</VFEM_VillageElder88.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillagePatron95.description>[PAWN_nameDef] served as a benefactor to a local village, funding improvements to infrastructure and ensuring the well-being of [PAWN_possessive] tenants. [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at balancing generosity with practicality, ensuring the village prospered without excessive costs. Though respected by the villagers, [PAWN_pronoun] had little experience with warfare or courtly intrigue.</VFEM_VillagePatron95.description>
  <VFEM_VillagePatron95.title>village patron</VFEM_VillagePatron95.title>
  <VFEM_VillagePatron95.titleShort>patron</VFEM_VillagePatron95.titleShort>
  <VFEM_WarBeastTrainer80.description>[PAWN_nameDef] trained war dogs and other beasts to fight alongside soldiers in battle. [PAWN_pronoun] specialized in teaching animals to obey commands even in the chaos of combat. Though skilled in working with animals, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with the finer points of diplomacy and negotiation.</VFEM_WarBeastTrainer80.description>
  <VFEM_WarBeastTrainer80.title>war beast trainer</VFEM_WarBeastTrainer80.title>
  <VFEM_WarBeastTrainer80.titleShort>trainer</VFEM_WarBeastTrainer80.titleShort>
  <VFEM_WardenOfTheNorth71.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was charged with the defense of a vast and frigid northern realm, managing both its people and its armies. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in leadership, strategy, and building alliances to keep the lands united under [PAWN_possessive] banner. The harsh conditions forged [PAWN_pronoun] into a hardened and resolute figure.</VFEM_WardenOfTheNorth71.description>
  <VFEM_WardenOfTheNorth71.title>warden of the north</VFEM_WardenOfTheNorth71.title>
  <VFEM_WardenOfTheNorth71.titleShort>warden</VFEM_WardenOfTheNorth71.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ArcherTrainee155.description>[PAWN_nameDef] began training with a bow from a young age, aiming for skill and precision as required of noble warriors. [PAWN_pronoun] spent hours drawing targets in the courtyard and practicing long-distance shots. The training honed [PAWN_possessive] focus and gave [PAWN_pronoun] an edge in ranged combat.</VFEM_ArcherTrainee155.description>
  <VFEM_ArcherTrainee155.title>archer trainee</VFEM_ArcherTrainee155.title>
  <VFEM_ArcherTrainee155.titleShort>archer</VFEM_ArcherTrainee155.titleShort>
  <VFEM_AspiringDiplomat150.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was groomed for a future in diplomacy, studying languages, geography, and the customs of foreign courts. [PAWN_pronoun] practiced making speeches and mediating minor disputes among peers. Though still young, [PAWN_pronoun] showed promise as a skilled negotiator and tactician.</VFEM_AspiringDiplomat150.description>
  <VFEM_AspiringDiplomat150.title>aspiring diplomat</VFEM_AspiringDiplomat150.title>
  <VFEM_AspiringDiplomat150.titleShort>diplomat</VFEM_AspiringDiplomat150.titleShort>
  <VFEM_AspiringKnight145.description>[PAWN_nameDef] trained from an early age in the art of combat, preparing for the day [PAWN_pronoun] could earn [PAWN_possessive] place among the knights of [PAWN_possessive] house. [PAWN_pronoun] practiced with wooden swords and sparred with instructors, learning discipline and honor. While young, [PAWN_pronoun] already showed promise as a warrior.</VFEM_AspiringKnight145.description>
  <VFEM_AspiringKnight145.title>aspiring knight</VFEM_AspiringKnight145.title>
  <VFEM_AspiringKnight145.titleShort>knight</VFEM_AspiringKnight145.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BannerBearer154.description>[PAWN_nameDef] carried the family banner into drills and parades, learning to represent [PAWN_possessive] house with pride. [PAWN_pronoun] spent hours practicing marching formations and staying composed under scrutiny. Though not a frontline fighter, [PAWN_pronoun] gained valuable lessons in discipline and leadership.</VFEM_BannerBearer154.description>
  <VFEM_BannerBearer154.title>banner bearer</VFEM_BannerBearer154.title>
  <VFEM_BannerBearer154.titleShort>banner bearer</VFEM_BannerBearer154.titleShort>
  <VFEM_BuddingPoet170.description>[PAWN_nameDef] composed an epic poem at a young age that spread throughout the region, earning [PAWN_pronoun] fame and admiration. Nobles and commoners alike recited [PAWN_possessive] verses, praising their vivid imagery and emotional depth. The success brought invitations to courts across the land.</VFEM_BuddingPoet170.description>
  <VFEM_BuddingPoet170.title>budding poet</VFEM_BuddingPoet170.title>
  <VFEM_BuddingPoet170.titleShort>poet</VFEM_BuddingPoet170.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CastleDefender153.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in a fortified castle and spent [PAWN_possessive] days training with guards and learning the basics of siege defense. [PAWN_pronoun] practiced with bows on the battlements and drilled with spears in the courtyard. The life gave [PAWN_pronoun] a strong sense of duty and early combat experience.</VFEM_CastleDefender153.description>
  <VFEM_CastleDefender153.title>castle defender</VFEM_CastleDefender153.title>
  <VFEM_CastleDefender153.titleShort>defender</VFEM_CastleDefender153.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CastlePlaymate144.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood running through the halls and courtyards of a castle, playing games with other noble children. The carefree years gave [PAWN_pronoun] a strong sense of camaraderie and a basic understanding of courtly manners. However, the sheltered life left [PAWN_pronoun] naive about the struggles of common folk.</VFEM_CastlePlaymate144.description>
  <VFEM_CastlePlaymate144.title>castle playmate</VFEM_CastlePlaymate144.title>
  <VFEM_CastlePlaymate144.titleShort>playmate</VFEM_CastlePlaymate144.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ChildOfTheEclipse162.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born under an ominous eclipse, a sign that filled the villagers with dread. [PAWN_pronoun] grew up under the weight of grim superstition, with some believing [PAWN_pronoun] brought bad luck or worse. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to navigate the fear of others, growing cunning and detached to survive.</VFEM_ChildOfTheEclipse162.description>
  <VFEM_ChildOfTheEclipse162.title>child of the eclipse</VFEM_ChildOfTheEclipse162.title>
  <VFEM_ChildOfTheEclipse162.titleShort>eclipse-born</VFEM_ChildOfTheEclipse162.titleShort>
  <VFEM_CourtAttendant148.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up serving as a junior attendant in a royal court, learning the nuances of etiquette and the art of flattery. [PAWN_pronoun] observed the dealings of nobles and practiced [PAWN_possessive] own skills in negotiation and charm. Though immersed in the intrigue of the court, [PAWN_pronoun] rarely ventured beyond its walls.</VFEM_CourtAttendant148.description>
  <VFEM_CourtAttendant148.title>court attendant</VFEM_CourtAttendant148.title>
  <VFEM_CourtAttendant148.titleShort>attendant</VFEM_CourtAttendant148.titleShort>
  <VFEM_EstateHeir157.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised on a sprawling estate, learning to oversee the household and manage the laborers who worked the land. [PAWN_pronoun] received lessons in stewardship and basic leadership, preparing [PAWN_objective] for a life of privilege. Though competent, [PAWN_pronoun] had little understanding of life beyond [PAWN_possessive] family’s wealth.</VFEM_EstateHeir157.description>
  <VFEM_EstateHeir157.title>estate heir</VFEM_EstateHeir157.title>
  <VFEM_EstateHeir157.titleShort>heir</VFEM_EstateHeir157.titleShort>
  <VFEM_FalconryStudent149.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] youth learning the noble pastime of falconry, training birds to hunt and obey commands. [PAWN_pronoun] developed patience and a keen understanding of animal behavior. Though the skill impressed others, [PAWN_pronoun] had little time for practical tasks outside the sport.</VFEM_FalconryStudent149.description>
  <VFEM_FalconryStudent149.title>falconry student</VFEM_FalconryStudent149.title>
  <VFEM_FalconryStudent149.titleShort>falconer</VFEM_FalconryStudent149.titleShort>
  <VFEM_GraveyardWanderer163.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] days among the headstones, speaking to the dead as though they were alive. [PAWN_pronoun] was drawn to the quiet stillness and the stories carved into weathered stone. The villagers whispered of [PAWN_possessive] odd habits, and [PAWN_pronoun] learned to keep [PAWN_possessive] thoughts hidden from prying eyes.</VFEM_GraveyardWanderer163.description>
  <VFEM_GraveyardWanderer163.title>graveyard wanderer</VFEM_GraveyardWanderer163.title>
  <VFEM_GraveyardWanderer163.titleShort>wanderer</VFEM_GraveyardWanderer163.titleShort>
  <VFEM_HeirToTheEstate146.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised to inherit the family estate, receiving lessons in administration and diplomacy from a young age. [PAWN_pronoun] was taught to manage resources, oversee servants, and maintain order among the household. The structured upbringing prepared [PAWN_pronoun] for leadership but left little time for play.</VFEM_HeirToTheEstate146.description>
  <VFEM_HeirToTheEstate146.title>heir to the estate</VFEM_HeirToTheEstate146.title>
  <VFEM_HeirToTheEstate146.titleShort>heir</VFEM_HeirToTheEstate146.titleShort>
  <VFEM_LavishUpbringing158.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was surrounded by luxury from birth, never knowing hunger or hardship. [PAWN_pronoun] was taught courtly manners and spent [PAWN_possessive] days enjoying music, fine food, and leisure. While refined and confident, [PAWN_pronoun] struggled with practical tasks that required hard labor.</VFEM_LavishUpbringing158.description>
  <VFEM_LavishUpbringing158.title>lavish upbringing</VFEM_LavishUpbringing158.title>
  <VFEM_LavishUpbringing158.titleShort>lavish</VFEM_LavishUpbringing158.titleShort>
  <VFEM_MerchantsProdigy156.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up surrounded by the bustling trade of [PAWN_possessive] family’s business, watching deals unfold and goods change hands. [PAWN_pronoun] was taught the art of negotiation and the importance of wealth. Though well-versed in trade, [PAWN_pronoun] had little exposure to the struggles of common life.</VFEM_MerchantsProdigy156.description>
  <VFEM_MerchantsProdigy156.title>merchant's prodigy</VFEM_MerchantsProdigy156.title>
  <VFEM_MerchantsProdigy156.titleShort>prodigy</VFEM_MerchantsProdigy156.titleShort>
  <VFEM_NobleWard141.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was sent to another noble’s court to be raised and educated in the ways of governance and etiquette. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to navigate the complexities of noble relationships and gained a basic understanding of leadership. Though surrounded by luxury, [PAWN_pronoun] spent much of [PAWN_possessive] time under watchful eyes.</VFEM_NobleWard141.description>
  <VFEM_NobleWard141.title>noble ward</VFEM_NobleWard141.title>
  <VFEM_NobleWard141.titleShort>ward</VFEM_NobleWard141.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Page142.description>[PAWN_nameDef] began [PAWN_possessive] training in a noble household, learning the fundamentals of serving and knightly duties. [PAWN_pronoun] spent hours cleaning armor, carrying messages, and studying basic combat techniques. The experience gave [PAWN_pronoun] an early introduction to the discipline and loyalty expected of nobility.</VFEM_Page142.description>
  <VFEM_Page142.title>page</VFEM_Page142.title>
  <VFEM_Page142.titleShort>page</VFEM_Page142.titleShort>
  <VFEM_PatronOfTheArts159.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was encouraged to pursue and support the arts, attending performances and commissioning works from talented craftsmen. [PAWN_pronoun] developed an appreciation for beauty and creativity, as well as a talent for recognizing skill in others. Though cultured, [PAWN_pronoun] was sheltered from the harsher realities of life.</VFEM_PatronOfTheArts159.description>
  <VFEM_PatronOfTheArts159.title>patron of the arts</VFEM_PatronOfTheArts159.title>
  <VFEM_PatronOfTheArts159.titleShort>patron</VFEM_PatronOfTheArts159.titleShort>
  <VFEM_PrivilegedScholar160.description>[PAWN_nameDef] had access to the finest tutors, studying history, philosophy, and the sciences from a young age. [PAWN_pronoun] showed promise in academic pursuits, impressing [PAWN_possessive] family with [PAWN_possessive] keen intellect. However, [PAWN_pronoun] had little understanding of the struggles faced by those less fortunate.</VFEM_PrivilegedScholar160.description>
  <VFEM_PrivilegedScholar160.title>privileged scholar</VFEM_PrivilegedScholar160.title>
  <VFEM_PrivilegedScholar160.titleShort>scholar</VFEM_PrivilegedScholar160.titleShort>
  <VFEM_PrizeArcher169.description>[PAWN_nameDef] won a prestigious archery competition at the age of thirteen, besting older and more experienced opponents. [PAWN_pronoun] was praised for [PAWN_possessive] precision and composure under pressure. The victory brought honor to [PAWN_possessive] family and set [PAWN_objective] on a path of future acclaim.</VFEM_PrizeArcher169.description>
  <VFEM_PrizeArcher169.title>prize archer</VFEM_PrizeArcher169.title>
  <VFEM_PrizeArcher169.titleShort>archer</VFEM_PrizeArcher169.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ProdigiousTactician167.description>[PAWN_nameDef] demonstrated a gift for strategy by organizing and winning a mock battle between the castle’s squires. [PAWN_pronoun] anticipated [PAWN_possessive] opponents’ moves and used the terrain to [PAWN_possessive] advantage, earning the admiration of seasoned knights. The event marked [PAWN_objective] as a promising future commander.</VFEM_ProdigiousTactician167.description>
  <VFEM_ProdigiousTactician167.title>prodigious tactician</VFEM_ProdigiousTactician167.title>
  <VFEM_ProdigiousTactician167.titleShort>tactician</VFEM_ProdigiousTactician167.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ScribeInTraining147.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent long hours learning to read and write under the guidance of a family-appointed tutor. [PAWN_pronoun] practiced copying texts and recording transactions, developing a keen eye for detail. While skilled in intellectual pursuits, [PAWN_pronoun] had little exposure to physical labor or combat training.</VFEM_ScribeInTraining147.description>
  <VFEM_ScribeInTraining147.title>scribe in training</VFEM_ScribeInTraining147.title>
  <VFEM_ScribeInTraining147.titleShort>scribe</VFEM_ScribeInTraining147.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ShadowedOutcast161.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was feared by the villagers for reasons whispered but never explained. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] childhood in the shadows, avoiding those who glared or crossed themselves at [PAWN_possessive] presence. The isolation hardened [PAWN_objective], leaving [PAWN_pronoun] mistrustful and quiet, always watching from the dark corners.</VFEM_ShadowedOutcast161.description>
  <VFEM_ShadowedOutcast161.title>shadowed outcast</VFEM_ShadowedOutcast161.title>
  <VFEM_ShadowedOutcast161.titleShort>outcast</VFEM_ShadowedOutcast161.titleShort>
  <VFEM_ShieldCarrier152.description>[PAWN_nameDef] trained alongside warriors, serving as a shield carrier during skirmishes and drills. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to endure long marches and protect [PAWN_possessive] mentors in the heat of battle. Though young, [PAWN_pronoun] displayed courage and determination beyond [PAWN_possessive] years.</VFEM_ShieldCarrier152.description>
  <VFEM_ShieldCarrier152.title>shield carrier</VFEM_ShieldCarrier152.title>
  <VFEM_ShieldCarrier152.titleShort>carrier</VFEM_ShieldCarrier152.titleShort>
  <VFEM_Squire151.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was apprenticed to a knight, tasked with maintaining armor, tending horses, and learning the code of chivalry. [PAWN_pronoun] spent countless hours observing battles and practicing with training weapons. The rigorous training instilled discipline and a desire to prove [PAWN_possessive] worth on the battlefield.</VFEM_Squire151.description>
  <VFEM_Squire151.title>squire</VFEM_Squire151.title>
  <VFEM_Squire151.titleShort>squire</VFEM_Squire151.titleShort>
  <VFEM_VillageCurseBearer164.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was believed to be cursed, blamed for every ill fortune that befell the village. Crops failed, livestock died, and villagers fell ill, all under [PAWN_possessive] dark shadow. [PAWN_pronoun] grew to expect rejection, developing a cold resilience to survive in a world that feared [PAWN_objective].</VFEM_VillageCurseBearer164.description>
  <VFEM_VillageCurseBearer164.title>village curse-bearer</VFEM_VillageCurseBearer164.title>
  <VFEM_VillageCurseBearer164.titleShort>cursed</VFEM_VillageCurseBearer164.titleShort>
  <VFEM_WhisperedFoundling165.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was discovered as an infant at the edge of the woods, wrapped in tattered cloth and left in the rain. The villagers took [PAWN_objective] in reluctantly, always murmuring of unnatural origins. [PAWN_pronoun] grew up in the shadow of suspicion, learning to remain unseen and unheard.</VFEM_WhisperedFoundling165.description>
  <VFEM_WhisperedFoundling165.title>whispered foundling</VFEM_WhisperedFoundling165.title>
  <VFEM_WhisperedFoundling165.titleShort>foundling</VFEM_WhisperedFoundling165.titleShort>
  <VFEM_YoungArchitect168.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed an innovative irrigation system for the family estate at just ten years old, greatly increasing crop yields. [PAWN_pronoun] impressed both the stewards and laborers with [PAWN_possessive] ingenuity. The success ensured [PAWN_pronoun] would be taken seriously, even at such a young age.</VFEM_YoungArchitect168.description>
  <VFEM_YoungArchitect168.title>young architect</VFEM_YoungArchitect168.title>
  <VFEM_YoungArchitect168.titleShort>architect</VFEM_YoungArchitect168.titleShort>
  <VFEM_YoungDiplomat166.description>[PAWN_nameDef] surprised [PAWN_possessive] elders by brokering a truce between feuding noble families at just twelve years old. [PAWN_pronoun] used charm and logic to persuade both sides, earning respect far beyond [PAWN_possessive] years. The experience cemented [PAWN_possessive] place as a rising star in courtly politics.</VFEM_YoungDiplomat166.description>
  <VFEM_YoungDiplomat166.title>young diplomat</VFEM_YoungDiplomat166.title>
  <VFEM_YoungDiplomat166.titleShort>diplomat</VFEM_YoungDiplomat166.titleShort>
  <VFEM_YoungScholar143.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was tutored in history, philosophy, and mathematics from an early age, as was expected of highborn children. [PAWN_pronoun] showed a natural curiosity and an aptitude for learning, earning praise from [PAWN_possessive] tutors. Though well-read, [PAWN_pronoun] had little experience with manual or practical work.</VFEM_YoungScholar143.description>
  <VFEM_YoungScholar143.title>young scholar</VFEM_YoungScholar143.title>
  <VFEM_YoungScholar143.titleShort>scholar</VFEM_YoungScholar143.titleShort>
  <VQE_ChildhoodLegendaryBlacksmith.description>Born beneath the towering chimneys of the Grand Forge, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up with fire and steel as [PAWN_possessive] only companions. While others played, [PAWN_pronoun] watched the master smiths shape metal into weapons of legend. By the time [PAWN_pronoun] could walk, [PAWN_pronoun] had learned the weight of a hammer. By the time [PAWN_pronoun] could read, [PAWN_pronoun] had memorized the blueprints of masterwork armor. Elders whispered that [PAWN_nameDef] was destined to craft wonders beyond imagination, a future shaped by the ringing of steel on anvil.</VQE_ChildhoodLegendaryBlacksmith.description>
  <VQE_ChildhoodLegendaryBlacksmith.title>child of the forge</VQE_ChildhoodLegendaryBlacksmith.title>
  <VQE_ChildhoodLegendaryBlacksmith.titleShort>forgeborn</VQE_ChildhoodLegendaryBlacksmith.titleShort>
  <VQE_LegendaryBlacksmithAdulthood.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was the last of [PAWN_possessive] kind, the final master of an art lost to time. In a world where steel had become obsolete, [PAWN_pronoun] forged weapons that could cut through plasteel and armor that could withstand railgun fire. Every strike of [PAWN_possessive] hammer wrote history in tempered alloys, cryptofused plating, and weapons that defied physics itself. But when [PAWN_possessive] ship fell, the forges cooled and the secrets of the craft faded into legend. Now, wandering among the ruins of [PAWN_possessive] past, [PAWN_pronoun] carries the weight of a lost age, the guilt of being the last one.</VQE_LegendaryBlacksmithAdulthood.description>
  <VQE_LegendaryBlacksmithAdulthood.title>legendary blacksmith</VQE_LegendaryBlacksmithAdulthood.title>
  <VQE_LegendaryBlacksmithAdulthood.titleShort>legendary smith</VQE_LegendaryBlacksmithAdulthood.titleShort>
  <VQE_AshStrategist40.description>[PAWN_nameDef] formulated long-term battle plans relying on the deployment of expendable, undead battalions into irradiated and cursed zones. [PAWN_pronoun] viewed humans as inefficient vessels, preferring dust-born constructs who didn’t sleep or retreat. [PAWN_pronoun] once approved a maneuver where only the dead returned and called it a flawless victory.</VQE_AshStrategist40.description>
  <VQE_AshStrategist40.title>ash strategist</VQE_AshStrategist40.title>
  <VQE_AshStrategist40.titleShort>strategist</VQE_AshStrategist40.titleShort>
  <VQE_AshTranslator15.description>[PAWN_nameDef] analyzed the patterns left in deadlife dust as it settled, fractals of intent, echoing through silence. [PAWN_pronoun] claimed the dust was speaking, and spent hours tracing messages only [PAWN_pronoun] could see. The others stopped questioning it when [PAWN_pronoun] predicted a breach twelve hours before it happened.</VQE_AshTranslator15.description>
  <VQE_AshTranslator15.title>ash translator</VQE_AshTranslator15.title>
  <VQE_AshTranslator15.titleShort>translator</VQE_AshTranslator15.titleShort>
  <VQE_BreachVolunteer46.description>[PAWN_nameDef] stepped forward during the first breach trials, signing a form titled "Consent to Dissolution." [PAWN_pronoun] was marched into the dust storm without armor, carrying only a black flag. Days later, the flag returned, stitched into [PAWN_possessive] new uniform.</VQE_BreachVolunteer46.description>
  <VQE_BreachVolunteer46.title>breach volunteer</VQE_BreachVolunteer46.title>
  <VQE_BreachVolunteer46.titleShort>volunteer</VQE_BreachVolunteer46.titleShort>
  <VQE_ComplianceAuditor30.description>[PAWN_nameDef] reviewed personnel logs, behavioral reports, and incident transcripts, flagging deviations for reconditioning. [PAWN_pronoun] never met the people [PAWN_pronoun] condemned. Only once did [PAWN_pronoun] hesitate - when the file bore [PAWN_possessive] own name.</VQE_ComplianceAuditor30.description>
  <VQE_ComplianceAuditor30.title>compliance auditor</VQE_ComplianceAuditor30.title>
  <VQE_ComplianceAuditor30.titleShort>auditor</VQE_ComplianceAuditor30.titleShort>
  <VQE_CompliantHusk10.description>[PAWN_nameDef] volunteered for cognitive stripping, which included the removal of memory, name, and will. What remained was a body that obeyed. [PAWN_pronoun] stood in formation while storms raged and flesh fell from bone, waiting only for the next command pulse from the central stack.</VQE_CompliantHusk10.description>
  <VQE_CompliantHusk10.title>compliant husk</VQE_CompliantHusk10.title>
  <VQE_CompliantHusk10.titleShort>husk</VQE_CompliantHusk10.titleShort>
  <VQE_CorridorWatch25.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was posted in a hallway that no one walked down, outside a door that no one opened. [PAWN_pronoun] was told to stand still, never speak, and never blink too long. On the seventh year, [PAWN_pronoun] started to hear footsteps behind the wall.</VQE_CorridorWatch25.description>
  <VQE_CorridorWatch25.title>corridor watch</VQE_CorridorWatch25.title>
  <VQE_CorridorWatch25.titleShort>watch</VQE_CorridorWatch25.titleShort>
  <VQE_CrateNotator32.description>[PAWN_nameDef] scrawled codes onto crates, noting date, contents, and threat tier. Many containers arrived unmarked, but [PAWN_pronoun] learned quickly: if it rattled, it was best to skip the contents line. Sometimes the ink bled upward, off the label, and into [PAWN_possessive] sleeve.</VQE_CrateNotator32.description>
  <VQE_CrateNotator32.title>crate notator</VQE_CrateNotator32.title>
  <VQE_CrateNotator32.titleShort>notator</VQE_CrateNotator32.titleShort>
  <VQE_DockGunner19.description>[PAWN_nameDef] manned the auto-cannons near the dust transfer docks, defending against "anomalous discharge movement", whatever that meant. Nothing ever approached the dock, but [PAWN_pronoun] fired anyway. Better that than let the dust think [PAWN_pronoun] hesitated.</VQE_DockGunner19.description>
  <VQE_DockGunner19.title>dock gunner</VQE_DockGunner19.title>
  <VQE_DockGunner19.titleShort>gunner</VQE_DockGunner19.titleShort>
  <VQE_DoctrineScribe27.description>[PAWN_nameDef] transcribed the daily decrees of the central authority, etching them onto rusted tablets distributed throughout the facility. [PAWN_pronoun] wrote in total silence, copying phrases [PAWN_pronoun] did not understand. One phrase, however, appeared in every order: "Decay is compliance."</VQE_DoctrineScribe27.description>
  <VQE_DoctrineScribe27.title>doctrine scribe</VQE_DoctrineScribe27.title>
  <VQE_DoctrineScribe27.titleShort>scribe</VQE_DoctrineScribe27.titleShort>
  <VQE_DoorTechnician14.description>[PAWN_nameDef] operated the containment pylons and extraction rigs around the Death Door. [PAWN_pronoun] calibrated siphons by eye and rebalanced psychic insulators mid-flow. The margin for error was one breath, and [PAWN_pronoun] hasn’t taken a full one since.</VQE_DoorTechnician14.description>
  <VQE_DoorTechnician14.title>door technician</VQE_DoorTechnician14.title>
  <VQE_DoorTechnician14.titleShort>technician</VQE_DoorTechnician14.titleShort>
  <VQE_DustCourier12.description>[PAWN_nameDef] ferried containers of deadlife dust from the extraction chamber to cold-vault containment zones. Escorts were forbidden, as too much movement stirred the dust. [PAWN_pronoun] walked in silence, clutching steel boxes that sometimes wept from within.</VQE_DustCourier12.description>
  <VQE_DustCourier12.title>dust courier</VQE_DustCourier12.title>
  <VQE_DustCourier12.titleShort>courier</VQE_DustCourier12.titleShort>
  <VQE_DustDoctrineArchitect36.description>[PAWN_nameDef] authored the central philosophy behind the use of deadlife dust, an ideology blending utility, inevitability, and transcendence through decay. [PAWN_pronoun] designed the program not to conquer death, but to industrialize it. Those who dissented were reassigned to dust-harvesting duties until compliant.</VQE_DustDoctrineArchitect36.description>
  <VQE_DustDoctrineArchitect36.title>dust doctrine architect</VQE_DustDoctrineArchitect36.title>
  <VQE_DustDoctrineArchitect36.titleShort>architect</VQE_DustDoctrineArchitect36.titleShort>
  <VQE_DustLoader16.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was responsible for loading raw deadlife dust into containment drums, working under flashing hazard lights and sealed hoods. The powder stuck to gloves and skin no matter how thick the gear. [PAWN_pronoun] was told it couldn't penetrate bone, but [PAWN_pronoun] isn’t sure anymore.</VQE_DustLoader16.description>
  <VQE_DustLoader16.title>dust loader</VQE_DustLoader16.title>
  <VQE_DustLoader16.titleShort>loader</VQE_DustLoader16.titleShort>
  <VQE_DustRegistrar26.description>[PAWN_nameDef] catalogued every gram of deadlife dust processed through the sector, logging each shipment’s origin and intended experiment. [PAWN_pronoun] never asked what the dust did, just that the weights matched and the signatures were clean. Some days, the logbook filled itself.</VQE_DustRegistrar26.description>
  <VQE_DustRegistrar26.title>dust registrar</VQE_DustRegistrar26.title>
  <VQE_DustRegistrar26.titleShort>registrar</VQE_DustRegistrar26.titleShort>
  <VQE_EchoRepeater45.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was exposed to the Death Door during a containment breach and hasn't spoken [PAWN_possessive] own thoughts since. Everything [PAWN_pronoun] says is a repetition of something someone else is about to say. [PAWN_pronoun] knows things that haven’t happened yet. The facility keeps [PAWN_objective] alive... just in case.</VQE_EchoRepeater45.description>
  <VQE_EchoRepeater45.title>echo repeater</VQE_EchoRepeater45.title>
  <VQE_EchoRepeater45.titleShort>repeater</VQE_EchoRepeater45.titleShort>
  <VQE_EternalLogisticsOfficer38.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed the warehouse and storage rotation protocol meant to function without human oversight for over a thousand years. [PAWN_pronoun] believed a perfect system outlived its masters, and had [PAWN_possessive] own heart replaced with a synthetic failsafe. [PAWN_pronoun] has not aged since activation.</VQE_EternalLogisticsOfficer38.description>
  <VQE_EternalLogisticsOfficer38.title>eternal logistics officer</VQE_EternalLogisticsOfficer38.title>
  <VQE_EternalLogisticsOfficer38.titleShort>officer</VQE_EternalLogisticsOfficer38.titleShort>
  <VQE_FilterMechanic20.description>[PAWN_nameDef] maintained the dust filtration systems that kept the air breathable and the death sealed. The filters clogged fast, screaming if left too long. [PAWN_pronoun] replaced them by hand, gloved, double-suited, and breathing recycled air laced with static.</VQE_FilterMechanic20.description>
  <VQE_FilterMechanic20.title>filter mechanic</VQE_FilterMechanic20.title>
  <VQE_FilterMechanic20.titleShort>mechanic</VQE_FilterMechanic20.titleShort>
  <VQE_FoglineObserver8.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was deployed alone into chemically saturated deadzones, tasked with recording troop decay rates and atmospheric effects. [PAWN_pronoun] watched comrades dissolve, regenerate, and march again, then noted the results with unblinking precision. [PAWN_pronoun] didn’t speak for years afterward, and no one asked [PAWN_objective] to.</VQE_FoglineObserver8.description>
  <VQE_FoglineObserver8.title>fogline observer</VQE_FoglineObserver8.title>
  <VQE_FoglineObserver8.titleShort>observer</VQE_FoglineObserver8.titleShort>
  <VQE_GatewaySentinel13.description>[PAWN_nameDef] guarded the perimeter of the Death Door facility, tasked with eliminating anything that emerged or tried to return. [PAWN_pronoun] saw shapes that didn’t reflect light, and heard commands that weren’t broadcast. The dust drifted past the line sometimes, and [PAWN_pronoun] learned not to breathe too deep.</VQE_GatewaySentinel13.description>
  <VQE_GatewaySentinel13.title>gateway sentinel</VQE_GatewaySentinel13.title>
  <VQE_GatewaySentinel13.titleShort>sentinel</VQE_GatewaySentinel13.titleShort>
  <VQE_IndoctrinatedRevenant5.description>[PAWN_nameDef] died in the field and was immediately reanimated under Directive Pale Flame: an experimental loop-binding protocol to override memory, identity, and morality. [PAWN_pronoun] still wears the scars of [PAWN_possessive] first death, though they’ve long ceased to matter. Now, [PAWN_pronoun] kills with the calm of someone who’s already passed judgment.</VQE_IndoctrinatedRevenant5.description>
  <VQE_IndoctrinatedRevenant5.title>indoctrinated revenant</VQE_IndoctrinatedRevenant5.title>
  <VQE_IndoctrinatedRevenant5.titleShort>revenant</VQE_IndoctrinatedRevenant5.titleShort>
  <VQE_IntakeMonitor18.description>[PAWN_nameDef] watched the flow of deadlife dust into containment silos, reporting clogs and pressure drops with precise timing. [PAWN_pronoun] wasn’t allowed to speak to other staff as too many went missing between shifts. The job required focus and silence, which [PAWN_pronoun] delivered perfectly.</VQE_IntakeMonitor18.description>
  <VQE_IntakeMonitor18.title>intake monitor</VQE_IntakeMonitor18.title>
  <VQE_IntakeMonitor18.titleShort>monitor</VQE_IntakeMonitor18.titleShort>
  <VQE_LabelOverseer34.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was in charge of verifying label integrity across the sealed vault grid. [PAWN_pronoun] spent entire shifts reading faded text under flickering lights, checking against catalogs no longer maintained. Some crates had no labels, just symbols that [PAWN_pronoun] could swear [PAWN_pronoun] remembered from dreams.</VQE_LabelOverseer34.description>
  <VQE_LabelOverseer34.title>label overseer</VQE_LabelOverseer34.title>
  <VQE_LabelOverseer34.titleShort>overseer</VQE_LabelOverseer34.titleShort>
  <VQE_MealDistributor24.description>[PAWN_nameDef] handed out ration packs to workers exiting the sealed extraction halls. The meals were identical, grey, tasteless, pre-labeled. Sometimes one would whisper when opened. [PAWN_pronoun] never took one for [PAWN_objective]self, just in case.</VQE_MealDistributor24.description>
  <VQE_MealDistributor24.title>meal distributor</VQE_MealDistributor24.title>
  <VQE_MealDistributor24.titleShort>distributor</VQE_MealDistributor24.titleShort>
  <VQE_Necroengineer3.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was both soldier and scientist, one of the few entrusted to maintain the resurrection architecture embedded in elite corpses. [PAWN_pronoun] spliced code into spinal columns and rewrote death like it was faulty circuitry. Despite the grotesque procedures, [PAWN_pronoun] never hesitated, as progress demanded flesh.</VQE_Necroengineer3.description>
  <VQE_Necroengineer3.title>necroengineer</VQE_Necroengineer3.title>
  <VQE_Necroengineer3.titleShort>engineer</VQE_Necroengineer3.titleShort>
  <VQE_NullInfantry7.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was among the first inducted into the Null Corps: frontline troops chemically lobotomized to erase fear and memory. [PAWN_pronoun] received orders through skull-implanted transceivers, moving silently and without question. [PAWN_pronoun] does not remember pain, or why [PAWN_pronoun] enlisted. Only the rifle in [PAWN_possessive] hands.</VQE_NullInfantry7.description>
  <VQE_NullInfantry7.title>null infantry</VQE_NullInfantry7.title>
  <VQE_NullInfantry7.titleShort>null</VQE_NullInfantry7.titleShort>
  <VQE_NullWitness44.description>No records exist for [PAWN_nameDef] prior to Vault Cycle 18. [PAWN_pronoun] was found kneeling at the Death Door, eyes closed, hands outstretched, murmuring patterns that canceled sound in a six-meter radius. [PAWN_pronoun] now works in Inventory. The lights dim when [PAWN_pronoun] passes.</VQE_NullWitness44.description>
  <VQE_NullWitness44.title>null witness</VQE_NullWitness44.title>
  <VQE_NullWitness44.titleShort>witness</VQE_NullWitness44.titleShort>
  <VQE_NutritionSynthesist29.description>[PAWN_nameDef] formulated nutrient slurries for long-term storage in deep dormancy wings. [PAWN_pronoun] was told not to question the smell, or why some vats emptied without record. [PAWN_pronoun] just stirred, sealed, and labeled each batch: “For Contingency Use Only.”</VQE_NutritionSynthesist29.description>
  <VQE_NutritionSynthesist29.title>nutrition synthesist</VQE_NutritionSynthesist29.title>
  <VQE_NutritionSynthesist29.titleShort>synthesist</VQE_NutritionSynthesist29.titleShort>
  <VQE_ObediencePledge48.description>[PAWN_nameDef] signed the Oath of Obedience in blood, requesting permanent reassignment to non-cognitive labor. [PAWN_pronoun] underwent cerebral smoothing, then was sent to carry crates too heavy for the living. [PAWN_pronoun] does not stop until ordered to, even if bones crack.</VQE_ObediencePledge48.description>
  <VQE_ObediencePledge48.title>obedience pledge</VQE_ObediencePledge48.title>
  <VQE_ObediencePledge48.titleShort>pledged</VQE_ObediencePledge48.titleShort>
  <VQE_OssuaryGuard9.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was stationed in the ossuaries: vast chambers where failed soldiers were stacked and catalogued for parts. [PAWN_pronoun] patrolled in silence, rifle in hand, surrounded by the rattling echoes of half-living experiments. No one spoke in the ossuaries. No one had mouths.</VQE_OssuaryGuard9.description>
  <VQE_OssuaryGuard9.title>ossuary guard</VQE_OssuaryGuard9.title>
  <VQE_OssuaryGuard9.titleShort>guard</VQE_OssuaryGuard9.titleShort>
  <VQE_PaleWitness43.description>[PAWN_nameDef] stood guard outside the inner chamber for 900 days, never entering, never relieved. Then, on day 901, the door opened just a slit. [PAWN_pronoun] looked inside for exactly three seconds. Since then, [PAWN_pronoun] has not blinked once.</VQE_PaleWitness43.description>
  <VQE_PaleWitness43.title>pale witness</VQE_PaleWitness43.title>
  <VQE_PaleWitness43.titleShort>witness</VQE_PaleWitness43.titleShort>
  <VQE_PreservedCommander4.description>[PAWN_nameDef] rose to command a death battalion before being sealed in cryostorage with [PAWN_possessive] mind uploaded to carbon-thin neural plates. Decades passed in blackout stasis, dreaming only of tactical formations and absolute obedience. When awakened, [PAWN_pronoun] resumed command as if the war had never paused.</VQE_PreservedCommander4.description>
  <VQE_PreservedCommander4.title>preserved commander</VQE_PreservedCommander4.title>
  <VQE_PreservedCommander4.titleShort>commander</VQE_PreservedCommander4.titleShort>
  <VQE_ProcessedSentinel50.description>[PAWN_nameDef] requested the “watcher’s gift” - a surgical splice of deadlife dust into the optic nerves and frontal cortex. [PAWN_pronoun] stands motionless for days, monitoring movement where none exists. [PAWN_pronoun] hasn’t reported an intrusion, but occasionally whispers that one is "already inside."</VQE_ProcessedSentinel50.description>
  <VQE_ProcessedSentinel50.title>processed sentinel</VQE_ProcessedSentinel50.title>
  <VQE_ProcessedSentinel50.titleShort>sentinel</VQE_ProcessedSentinel50.titleShort>
  <VQE_PrototypeSubject1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] volunteered for the first wave of transhuman necrosis trials, offering [PAWN_possessive] body to a military doctrine that worshipped permanence through decay. [PAWN_pronoun] endured months in a sealed vat as bone, tissue, and cognition were rewired by machine and fluid alike. What emerged was no longer fully alive, but unshakably loyal.</VQE_PrototypeSubject1.description>
  <VQE_PrototypeSubject1.title>prototype subject</VQE_PrototypeSubject1.title>
  <VQE_PrototypeSubject1.titleShort>subject</VQE_PrototypeSubject1.titleShort>
  <VQE_ReanimationWarden39.description>[PAWN_nameDef] oversaw the barracks of the reanimated units, managing deployment cycles and overseeing mental degradation thresholds. [PAWN_pronoun] insisted the undead required no names, only barcodes. When one subject regained a memory and spoke, [PAWN_pronoun] personally incinerated it.</VQE_ReanimationWarden39.description>
  <VQE_ReanimationWarden39.title>reanimation warden</VQE_ReanimationWarden39.title>
  <VQE_ReanimationWarden39.titleShort>warden</VQE_ReanimationWarden39.titleShort>
  <VQE_ReturnedObserver42.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was sent through the Death Door for a three-minute reconnaissance. The cameras failed instantly. [PAWN_pronoun] returned eighteen hours later, unharmed but altered, with skin colder, voice slower, eyes not entirely [PAWN_possessive]. No one asked what [PAWN_pronoun] saw. No one does now.</VQE_ReturnedObserver42.description>
  <VQE_ReturnedObserver42.title>returned observer</VQE_ReturnedObserver42.title>
  <VQE_ReturnedObserver42.titleShort>returned</VQE_ReturnedObserver42.titleShort>
  <VQE_RitualSubject47.description>[PAWN_nameDef] knelt willingly in the circle, surrounded by augurs and dark machines, and did not scream when the dust was poured into [PAWN_possessive] lungs. [PAWN_pronoun] was declared clinically dead, then reassigned to frontline duty two hours later. [PAWN_pronoun] no longer blinks. Nor stops.</VQE_RitualSubject47.description>
  <VQE_RitualSubject47.title>ritual subject</VQE_RitualSubject47.title>
  <VQE_RitualSubject47.titleShort>subject</VQE_RitualSubject47.titleShort>
  <VQE_ShiftRecorder23.description>[PAWN_nameDef] logged every shift rotation, personnel movement, and anomaly ping near the Death Door. [PAWN_pronoun] noticed strange patterns in the logs: repeating names, people clocking in after confirmed deaths, whole hours missing. [PAWN_pronoun] kept recording anyway.</VQE_ShiftRecorder23.description>
  <VQE_ShiftRecorder23.title>shift recorder</VQE_ShiftRecorder23.title>
  <VQE_ShiftRecorder23.titleShort>recorder</VQE_ShiftRecorder23.titleShort>
  <VQE_SilenceOfficer21.description>[PAWN_nameDef] enforced silence protocol within the dust-processing halls, where sound was said to attract unwanted responses. [PAWN_pronoun] walked the catwalks with a shock-rod and a clicker, punishing speech, coughs and even breath, if too loud. [PAWN_pronoun] hasn’t spoken in years, even off duty.</VQE_SilenceOfficer21.description>
  <VQE_SilenceOfficer21.title>silence officer</VQE_SilenceOfficer21.title>
  <VQE_SilenceOfficer21.titleShort>officer</VQE_SilenceOfficer21.titleShort>
  <VQE_SilentConversion49.description>[PAWN_nameDef] walked into the conversion chamber, sealed the door behind [PAWN_objective], and waited. The machine inside removed [PAWN_possessive] speech, hunger, and memory. What emerged walked straight to duty assignment without waiting for instruction.</VQE_SilentConversion49.description>
  <VQE_SilentConversion49.title>silent conversion</VQE_SilentConversion49.title>
  <VQE_SilentConversion49.titleShort>converted</VQE_SilentConversion49.titleShort>
  <VQE_SpecimenHandler28.description>[PAWN_nameDef] moved biological containers between crypto-labs, some twitching, some whispering. [PAWN_pronoun] never opened a crate, but sometimes the shadows inside moved with familiarity. [PAWN_pronoun] didn’t log what didn’t stop moving.</VQE_SpecimenHandler28.description>
  <VQE_SpecimenHandler28.title>specimen handler</VQE_SpecimenHandler28.title>
  <VQE_SpecimenHandler28.titleShort>handler</VQE_SpecimenHandler28.titleShort>
  <VQE_StockpileRotator33.description>[PAWN_nameDef] moved ancient supplies through decaying aisles, rotating materials to slow entropy. Many of the items had no known purpose, some no discernible shape. [PAWN_pronoun] once touched something warm that shouldn’t have been. It didn’t cool down afterward.</VQE_StockpileRotator33.description>
  <VQE_StockpileRotator33.title>stockpile rotator</VQE_StockpileRotator33.title>
  <VQE_StockpileRotator33.titleShort>rotator</VQE_StockpileRotator33.titleShort>
  <VQE_ThresholdHarvester11.description>[PAWN_nameDef] stood closest to the Death Door, siphoning dust from its breathless aperture into sealed black vials. The dust hissed, shimmered, and whispered, burning the air and minds alike. [PAWN_pronoun] wore triple-layered filtration gear, but still wakes to coughing shadows.</VQE_ThresholdHarvester11.description>
  <VQE_ThresholdHarvester11.title>threshold harvester</VQE_ThresholdHarvester11.title>
  <VQE_ThresholdHarvester11.titleShort>harvester</VQE_ThresholdHarvester11.titleShort>
  <VQE_TrenchAwakener6.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was assigned to burial patrols, recovering fallen comrades and tagging them for reanimation. [PAWN_pronoun] slept among corpses, carried bone-thin bodies back to processing, and watched them twitch to life again. The stench never faded, but neither did [PAWN_possessive] unwavering obedience.</VQE_TrenchAwakener6.description>
  <VQE_TrenchAwakener6.title>trench awakener</VQE_TrenchAwakener6.title>
  <VQE_TrenchAwakener6.titleShort>awakener</VQE_TrenchAwakener6.titleShort>
  <VQE_UniformInspector22.description>[PAWN_nameDef] checked for dust contamination in uniforms and skin before workers left the core sectors. [PAWN_pronoun] scrubbed patches that pulsed, burned fabric that moved, and blacklisted anything that remembered touch. [PAWN_pronoun] stopped questioning why some suits came back... without the wearers.</VQE_UniformInspector22.description>
  <VQE_UniformInspector22.title>uniform inspector</VQE_UniformInspector22.title>
  <VQE_UniformInspector22.titleShort>inspector</VQE_UniformInspector22.titleShort>
  <VQE_VaultArchivist31.description>[PAWN_nameDef] maintained ledgers of inventory buried deep in the sub-storage vaults. [PAWN_pronoun] documented sealed containers with unreadable glyphs and crates that hummed faintly when touched. One morning, an entry appeared in [PAWN_possessive] own handwriting, describing a box [PAWN_pronoun] hadn’t logged yet.</VQE_VaultArchivist31.description>
  <VQE_VaultArchivist31.title>vault archivist</VQE_VaultArchivist31.title>
  <VQE_VaultArchivist31.titleShort>archivist</VQE_VaultArchivist31.titleShort>
  <VQE_VaultCommissar37.description>[PAWN_nameDef] ensured ideological purity among vault personnel, conducting loyalty evaluations and sanctioning disciplinary corrections. [PAWN_pronoun] maintained that those exposed to the Death Door too long became unreliable. [PAWN_pronoun] had many of them sealed behind the vaults, alive or not was irrelevant.</VQE_VaultCommissar37.description>
  <VQE_VaultCommissar37.title>vault commissar</VQE_VaultCommissar37.title>
  <VQE_VaultCommissar37.titleShort>commissar</VQE_VaultCommissar37.titleShort>
  <VQE_VaultEnforcer2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was stationed deep beneath the surface, tasked with protecting the bio-vaults that housed experimental regeneration tanks and failed prototypes. When containment alarms sounded, [PAWN_pronoun] didn’t flinch. The only thing [PAWN_pronoun] feared was failure, and fear had been surgically removed years ago.</VQE_VaultEnforcer2.description>
  <VQE_VaultEnforcer2.title>vault enforcer</VQE_VaultEnforcer2.title>
  <VQE_VaultEnforcer2.titleShort>enforcer</VQE_VaultEnforcer2.titleShort>
  <VQE_VaultEntryClerk35.description>[PAWN_nameDef] verified access credentials for vault entrants and logged removals from sealed shelves. [PAWN_pronoun] noticed that names on the log began to repeat: dead soldiers requesting supplies long after they’d been archived. [PAWN_pronoun] flagged it once. Nothing changed.</VQE_VaultEntryClerk35.description>
  <VQE_VaultEntryClerk35.title>vault entry clerk</VQE_VaultEntryClerk35.title>
  <VQE_VaultEntryClerk35.titleShort>clerk</VQE_VaultEntryClerk35.titleShort>
  <VQE_VaultScrubber17.description>[PAWN_nameDef] cleaned the insides of sealed dust vaults after they were purged. The walls were never truly clean, they were always humming, always whispering. [PAWN_pronoun] stopped using [PAWN_possessive] name after the third cycle. No one corrected [PAWN_objective].</VQE_VaultScrubber17.description>
  <VQE_VaultScrubber17.title>vault scrubber</VQE_VaultScrubber17.title>
  <VQE_VaultScrubber17.titleShort>scrubber</VQE_VaultScrubber17.titleShort>
  <VQE_WhisperHost41.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was assigned to monitor the auditory pulses emitted by the Death Door during lunar shifts. [PAWN_pronoun] began transcribing messages in no known language, yet perfectly understood. After the seventh day, [PAWN_pronoun] no longer required equipment to hear them.</VQE_WhisperHost41.description>
  <VQE_WhisperHost41.title>whisper host</VQE_WhisperHost41.title>
  <VQE_WhisperHost41.titleShort>host</VQE_WhisperHost41.titleShort>
  <VQE_Childhood_OfficersShadow.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up behind reinforced glass, just beyond the war room where [PAWN_possessive] parent issued silent commands to a dying world. The halls were sterile, the uniforms always grey, and [PAWN_pronoun] quickly learned which doors never opened and which ones never closed. [PAWN_pronoun] was told the flickering silhouettes beyond the viewing screens were simulations, until one of them looked back. No one mentioned it afterward, and neither did [PAWN_pronoun].</VQE_Childhood_OfficersShadow.description>
  <VQE_Childhood_OfficersShadow.title>officer’s shadow</VQE_Childhood_OfficersShadow.title>
  <VQE_Childhood_OfficersShadow.titleShort>shadow</VQE_Childhood_OfficersShadow.titleShort>
  <VQE_TheGeneral.description>[PAWN_nameDef] designed Operation: Deadlife from the first blueprint to the last breath, believing death could be structured, harnessed, and weaponized. When the Death Door was first opened, [PAWN_pronoun] stepped through without hesitation, alone, unarmed, and smiling. [PAWN_pronoun] returned days later, silent and burned from within, wrapped in binding cloth and sealed inside a containment sarcophagus that no one claimed to understand. The war ended. The door remained open. [PAWN_pronoun] sleeps still - but the seals are growing warm.</VQE_TheGeneral.description>
  <VQE_TheGeneral.title>the general</VQE_TheGeneral.title>
  <VQE_TheGeneral.titleShort>general</VQE_TheGeneral.titleShort>
  <VQE_ArchiteVolunteer1.description>[PAWN_nameDef] enlisted in a secret military program that promised glory and strength. The experiments left [PAWN_objective] tougher than most, but the treatments damaged [PAWN_possessive] fine motor skills and stability.</VQE_ArchiteVolunteer1.description>
  <VQE_ArchiteVolunteer1.title>archite volunteer</VQE_ArchiteVolunteer1.title>
  <VQE_ArchiteVolunteer1.titleShort>volunteer</VQE_ArchiteVolunteer1.titleShort>
  <VQE_BetrayalStudy21.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was forced into experiments where subjects were paired as close companions, only to be tricked into betraying one another for survival. The cruelty broke [PAWN_possessive] ability to trust, but sharpened [PAWN_possessive] instincts for danger.</VQE_BetrayalStudy21.description>
  <VQE_BetrayalStudy21.title>betrayal study</VQE_BetrayalStudy21.title>
  <VQE_BetrayalStudy21.titleShort>betrayed</VQE_BetrayalStudy21.titleShort>
  <VQE_BoneReforged6.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was subjected to a brutal trial where every bone in [PAWN_possessive] body was shattered, replaced, and rebuilt with reinforced grafts. The process left [PAWN_objective] nearly unbreakable, but the constant agony scarred [PAWN_possessive] mind forever.</VQE_BoneReforged6.description>
  <VQE_BoneReforged6.title>bone reforged</VQE_BoneReforged6.title>
  <VQE_BoneReforged6.titleShort>reforged</VQE_BoneReforged6.titleShort>
  <VQE_BrainProbed8.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was part of a horrific program where archite nodes were drilled directly into [PAWN_possessive] brain. The procedures heightened reflexes and memory recall, but frequent blackouts and haunting visions still plague [PAWN_objective].</VQE_BrainProbed8.description>
  <VQE_BrainProbed8.title>brain probed</VQE_BrainProbed8.title>
  <VQE_BrainProbed8.titleShort>probed</VQE_BrainProbed8.titleShort>
  <VQE_CombatDrills15.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was forced through punishing combat drills meant to test the breaking point of soldiers under fire. The brutal regimen honed [PAWN_possessive] instincts, but left [PAWN_objective] with lingering injuries and a deep mistrust of authority.</VQE_CombatDrills15.description>
  <VQE_CombatDrills15.title>combat drill subject</VQE_CombatDrills15.title>
  <VQE_CombatDrills15.titleShort>drilled</VQE_CombatDrills15.titleShort>
  <VQE_CompassionPunished24.description>[PAWN_nameDef] lived through trials where showing kindness meant punishment, while cruelty was rewarded. Over time, [PAWN_pronoun] learned to hide compassion behind a mask of cold obedience, though the instinct to care never fully left.</VQE_CompassionPunished24.description>
  <VQE_CompassionPunished24.title>compassion punished</VQE_CompassionPunished24.title>
  <VQE_CompassionPunished24.titleShort>hardened</VQE_CompassionPunished24.titleShort>
  <VQE_DeceptionStudy16.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was placed in a program that rewarded lying and punished honesty. Over time, [PAWN_pronoun] became skilled at reading people, but found it difficult to form genuine connections.</VQE_DeceptionStudy16.description>
  <VQE_DeceptionStudy16.title>deception study</VQE_DeceptionStudy16.title>
  <VQE_DeceptionStudy16.titleShort>deceiver</VQE_DeceptionStudy16.titleShort>
  <VQE_EnhancedSoldier5.description>[PAWN_nameDef] became part of a military program to create supersoldiers through archite injections. The procedures hardened [PAWN_objective] for combat, but the constant modifications dulled [PAWN_possessive] sense of self and left [PAWN_objective] detached from ordinary life.</VQE_EnhancedSoldier5.description>
  <VQE_EnhancedSoldier5.title>enhanced soldier</VQE_EnhancedSoldier5.title>
  <VQE_EnhancedSoldier5.titleShort>soldier</VQE_EnhancedSoldier5.titleShort>
  <VQE_EyeReplaced10.description>[PAWN_nameDef] had both eyes removed and replaced with unstable experimental augments, meant to track targets in darkness. The implants improved [PAWN_possessive] aim, but left [PAWN_objective] sensitive to light and forever reliant on strange visual overlays.</VQE_EyeReplaced10.description>
  <VQE_EyeReplaced10.title>eye replaced</VQE_EyeReplaced10.title>
  <VQE_EyeReplaced10.titleShort>augmented</VQE_EyeReplaced10.titleShort>
  <VQE_FalseFamily22.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was placed into simulated households with strangers acting as kin, only to have them vanish without explanation. This cycle repeated until [PAWN_pronoun] stopped forming bonds at all, surviving instead through cold detachment.</VQE_FalseFamily22.description>
  <VQE_FalseFamily22.title>false family</VQE_FalseFamily22.title>
  <VQE_FalseFamily22.titleShort>orphaned</VQE_FalseFamily22.titleShort>
  <VQE_GeneFighter3.description>Chosen for a military experiment, [PAWN_nameDef] underwent forced genetic alterations meant to create stronger soldiers. The project gave [PAWN_objective] an edge in battle, but the constant tests left little time for education or civilian skills.</VQE_GeneFighter3.description>
  <VQE_GeneFighter3.title>gene fighter</VQE_GeneFighter3.title>
  <VQE_GeneFighter3.titleShort>fighter</VQE_GeneFighter3.titleShort>
  <VQE_GroupConflict17.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was locked in rooms with other subjects while researchers manipulated resources to force conflict. The constant fighting sharpened [PAWN_possessive] survival instincts, but trust became impossible.</VQE_GroupConflict17.description>
  <VQE_GroupConflict17.title>conflict subject</VQE_GroupConflict17.title>
  <VQE_GroupConflict17.titleShort>conflicted</VQE_GroupConflict17.titleShort>
  <VQE_IsolationChamber14.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was kept alone in a silent, lightless cell for months while researchers studied the effects of sensory deprivation. The ordeal left [PAWN_objective] distant and withdrawn, but strangely focused when working alone.</VQE_IsolationChamber14.description>
  <VQE_IsolationChamber14.title>isolation chamber</VQE_IsolationChamber14.title>
  <VQE_IsolationChamber14.titleShort>isolated</VQE_IsolationChamber14.titleShort>
  <VQE_IsolationTest19.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was forced into false social situations where allies would suddenly vanish or betray them. The shifting rules left [PAWN_objective] paranoid, but keenly aware of small details others overlook.</VQE_IsolationTest19.description>
  <VQE_IsolationTest19.title>isolation test</VQE_IsolationTest19.title>
  <VQE_IsolationTest19.titleShort>isolated</VQE_IsolationTest19.titleShort>
  <VQE_LossExperiment20.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was made to form bonds with fellow subjects, only to watch them be taken away again and again. The grief left scars, but also gave [PAWN_objective] an unusual resilience to despair.</VQE_LossExperiment20.description>
  <VQE_LossExperiment20.title>loss experiment</VQE_LossExperiment20.title>
  <VQE_LossExperiment20.titleShort>bereaved</VQE_LossExperiment20.titleShort>
  <VQE_MilitaryExperiment4.description>[PAWN_nameDef] volunteered for classified experiments, believing it was [PAWN_possessive] duty. Enhanced reflexes and stronger muscles were the results — but at the cost of chronic pain and a short temper.</VQE_MilitaryExperiment4.description>
  <VQE_MilitaryExperiment4.title>military experiment</VQE_MilitaryExperiment4.title>
  <VQE_MilitaryExperiment4.titleShort>experiment</VQE_MilitaryExperiment4.titleShort>
  <VQE_MuscleStitched9.description>[PAWN_nameDef] endured endless cycles of muscle excision and forced regrowth, each time restitched into denser configurations. The outcome was immense strength, but [PAWN_possessive] body remains grotesquely uneven and constantly aches from the strain.</VQE_MuscleStitched9.description>
  <VQE_MuscleStitched9.title>muscle stitched</VQE_MuscleStitched9.title>
  <VQE_MuscleStitched9.titleShort>stitched</VQE_MuscleStitched9.titleShort>
  <VQE_ObedienceTrial18.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent years in a program designed to test the limits of obedience to authority. Following orders became second nature, but [PAWN_objective] never learned to make decisions for [PAWN_objective]self.</VQE_ObedienceTrial18.description>
  <VQE_ObedienceTrial18.title>obedience trial</VQE_ObedienceTrial18.title>
  <VQE_ObedienceTrial18.titleShort>obedient</VQE_ObedienceTrial18.titleShort>
  <VQE_PainTolerance13.description>[PAWN_nameDef] endured endless procedures designed to push the limits of human pain tolerance. Though the agony left [PAWN_objective] hardened, [PAWN_pronoun] never truly recovered [PAWN_possessive] sense of trust in others.</VQE_PainTolerance13.description>
  <VQE_PainTolerance13.title>pain tolerance trial</VQE_PainTolerance13.title>
  <VQE_PainTolerance13.titleShort>trialed</VQE_PainTolerance13.titleShort>
  <VQE_SilenceStudy25.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in enforced silence, punished for speaking or even making noise. The isolation left [PAWN_objective] almost mute in groups, but gave [PAWN_possessive] an uncanny focus when working alone.</VQE_SilenceStudy25.description>
  <VQE_SilenceStudy25.title>silence study</VQE_SilenceStudy25.title>
  <VQE_SilenceStudy25.titleShort>silent</VQE_SilenceStudy25.titleShort>
  <VQE_SkinGrafted7.description>[PAWN_nameDef] underwent repeated skin-flaying and regenerative grafting, designed to test rapid healing serums. The experiments made [PAWN_objective] resistant to injury, but also dulled [PAWN_possessive] sense of touch and left [PAWN_possessive] body covered in scars.</VQE_SkinGrafted7.description>
  <VQE_SkinGrafted7.title>skin grafted</VQE_SkinGrafted7.title>
  <VQE_SkinGrafted7.titleShort>grafted</VQE_SkinGrafted7.titleShort>
  <VQE_StarvationTrial23.description>[PAWN_nameDef] endured experiments where food was withheld and rations were deliberately uneven, forcing subjects to beg or fight for scraps. Hunger carved deep scars into [PAWN_possessive] mind, leaving [PAWN_objective] restless and distrustful of generosity.</VQE_StarvationTrial23.description>
  <VQE_StarvationTrial23.title>starvation trial</VQE_StarvationTrial23.title>
  <VQE_StarvationTrial23.titleShort>starved</VQE_StarvationTrial23.titleShort>
  <VQE_StressTest11.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was confined for weeks in controlled conditions, deprived of sleep and overloaded with sensory input to measure endurance. The tests broke [PAWN_possessive] nerves, leaving [PAWN_objective] twitchy but strangely resistant to stress.</VQE_StressTest11.description>
  <VQE_StressTest11.title>stress test subject</VQE_StressTest11.title>
  <VQE_StressTest11.titleShort>subject</VQE_StressTest11.titleShort>
  <VQE_ToxicExposure12.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was sealed in chambers filled with toxic vapors as part of a military resilience program. The experience scarred [PAWN_possessive] lungs and burned [PAWN_possessive] skin, but [PAWN_pronoun] learned to push through sickness and pain.</VQE_ToxicExposure12.description>
  <VQE_ToxicExposure12.title>toxic exposure</VQE_ToxicExposure12.title>
  <VQE_ToxicExposure12.titleShort>exposed</VQE_ToxicExposure12.titleShort>
  <VQE_TrialSubject2.description>[PAWN_nameDef] signed away [PAWN_possessive] rights for a chance to join an experimental unit. Endless injections and training made [PAWN_objective] resilient, but constant observation and confinement left [PAWN_objective] anxious and withdrawn.</VQE_TrialSubject2.description>
  <VQE_TrialSubject2.title>trial subject</VQE_TrialSubject2.title>
  <VQE_TrialSubject2.titleShort>subject</VQE_TrialSubject2.titleShort>
  <VQE_IdealPatient.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was chosen for countless experimental procedures with archite technology. For reasons unknown, [PAWN_pronoun] never rejected an implant, making [PAWN_objective] the perfect subject for radical genetic experiments. The treatments left [PAWN_objective] frail in body, but adapted to pain and unusually tolerant of hardship. Sadly, one of the treatments has resulted in a slowly progressing terminal illness.</VQE_IdealPatient.description>
  <VQE_IdealPatient.title>ideal patient</VQE_IdealPatient.title>
  <VQE_IdealPatient.titleShort>patient</VQE_IdealPatient.titleShort>
  <VQE_KidnappedChild.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was abducted at a young age and raised in captivity. Deprived of proper schooling, [PAWN_pronoun] survived by learning to listen, to obey, and to read the moods of [PAWN_possessive] captors. The experience left [PAWN_objective] wary of others and untrained in most practical skills, but unusually sensitive to people’s intentions.</VQE_KidnappedChild.description>
  <VQE_KidnappedChild.title>kidnapped child</VQE_KidnappedChild.title>
  <VQE_KidnappedChild.titleShort>kidnapped</VQE_KidnappedChild.titleShort>
</LanguageData>
