<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.description>Once loyal to the New California Republic, these individuals have turned their backs on the old world order. Disillusioned by corruption and endless war, they now value survival, independence, and camaraderie above all else. They are wary of authority, skeptical of grand ideals, and quick to defend their own. Their code is one of mutual aid, hard-earned trust, and doing what it takes to survive in the wasteland.</FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.description>
  <FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.label>NCR Deserters</FCP_Meme_NCRDeserters.label>
  <FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.description>The New California Republic (NCR) is a federal presidential republic founded in New California, comprised of five contiguous states and additional territorial holdings in Nevada and Baja California. The NCR emphasizes and strives to support a myriad of old world values, such as democracy, personal liberty, and the rule of law. It also aims to restore general order to the wasteland, the improvement and development of infrastructure and economic systems, and overarching peace between people. Similar to institutions of the old world it seeks to emulate, continued expansion has created challenges with territorial control, loyalty, and corruption that plague the Republic and serve to hinder its goals.</FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.description>
  <FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.label>Old World Blues</FCP_Meme_OldWorldBlues.label>
  <FCP_Meme_Rangers.description>A volunteer special forces renowned as much for their expert reconnaissance capabilities as their bravery and combat prowess, the Rangers' primary purpose is dealing with threats the forces of the republic's standing Army cannot handle, as well as general peacekeeping around the borders of NCR territory, scouting out known and potential threats, and other special assignments. Their cutting-edge training, weaponry and assortment of both pre- and post-War technology often allows them to serve as lynchpins for victory in the republic's conflicts even when a situation may see them outnumbered and outgunned.</FCP_Meme_Rangers.description>
  <FCP_Meme_Rangers.label>NCR Rangers</FCP_Meme_Rangers.label>
</LanguageData>