<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <Apparel_CultistMask.description>A ritual mask worn by those devoted to the Holy Mothman.</Apparel_CultistMask.description>
  <Apparel_CeremonialCultistMask.description>A ceremonial hood typically worn by pilgrims devoted to the Holy Mothman.</Apparel_CeremonialCultistMask.description>
  <Bioferrite.label>ultracite</Bioferrite.label>
  <Bioferrite.description>An unusual mineral-organic composite recovered from contaminated tissue and unstable deposits. Ultracite is valued for its heat reactivity, fuel value, and use in specialized industrial and occult equipment.</Bioferrite.description>
  <BioferriteGenerator.label>ultracite generator</BioferriteGenerator.label>
  <BioferriteGenerator.description>An electrical generator that pressurizes and ignites ultracite, then harvests energy from the resulting heat. The process creates an unpleasant harmonic noise that disturbs nearby people.</BioferriteGenerator.description>
  <BioferriteShaper.label>ultracite shaper</BioferriteShaper.label>
  <BioferriteShaper.description>A work bench used to craft ultracite products. It uses heat and electromagnetic stimulation to soften ultracite long enough for a worker to shape it into complex forms and combine it with other materials.</BioferriteShaper.description>
  <BioferriteHarvester.label>ultracite harvester</BioferriteHarvester.label>
  <BioferriteHarvester.description>When placed near a holding platform, this device extracts mineralized biomass from the held specimen and refines it into ultracite. Larger specimens generally produce more material, but the process makes them harder to contain.</BioferriteHarvester.description>
  <ShardBeacon.description>A black technological fragment mounted on an ultracite pedestal. Focused through the ultracite, it stabilizes local occult interference and improves nearby ritual work.</ShardBeacon.description>
  <VoidSculpture.label>omen sculpture</VoidSculpture.label>
  <VoidSculpture.description>An unsettling sculpture made from ultracite. The material's unusual properties improve the quality of nearby occult rituals.</VoidSculpture.description>
  <Apparel_DisruptorFlarePack.description>A utility pack that shoots disruptor flares. On impact, the flare burns a capsule of ultracite, creating a bright flash and a local interference pulse. This stuns unusually sensitive targets, reveals hidden ones, and leaves a burning light source for a time.</Apparel_DisruptorFlarePack.description>
  <Gun_HellcatRifle.description>A versatile assault rifle with good range, decent power, and good accuracy. It also includes an ultracite-powered mini-burner unit that produces a short burst of flame from pressurized ultracite charges.</Gun_HellcatRifle.description>
  <VoidMonolith.label>black monolith</VoidMonolith.label>
  <VoidMonolith.description>A monolith of unknown age, purpose, and workmanship. Its smooth surface is etched with lines that twist in unsettling patterns.</VoidMonolith.description>
  <VoidStructure.label>black structure</VoidStructure.label>
  <VoidStructure.description>A warped structure made of jagged, oil-dark metal-like pieces. It emits a disturbing vibration and seems to kill nearby plant life.</VoidStructure.description>
  <VoidNode.label>storm node</VoidNode.label>
  <VoidNode.description>A roiling sphere of unstable energy suspended by nearby machinery. It appears to be one part of a larger atmospheric or geological phenomenon.</VoidNode.description>
  <Shard.description>A scavenged fragment of black, highly advanced machinery. It can be built into devices that produce unusual electrical, chemical, and psychological effects, though its full workings remain unclear.</Shard.description>
  <Plant_TreeHarbinger.description>A gnarled tree that grows fleshy tissue around an ultracite-rich core. It can feed on corpses and raw meat, and if well fed the grove will continue to spread.</Plant_TreeHarbinger.description>
  <HarbingerSeed.description>The seed of a harbinger tree. It can be planted to grow a new tree, which will consume corpses or meat placed nearby.</HarbingerSeed.description>
  <Metalhorror.description>A predatory cryptid made of metallic filaments, blades, and surgical-looking growths held together by a dark circulating fluid. Reports suggest it can remain hidden inside a host before emerging violently when threatened.</Metalhorror.description>
  <Revenant.description>A gaunt humanoid cryptid known in frontier folklore for stalking isolated settlements and returning to the same victims night after night. Witness accounts describe it as difficult to track, but flares, fire, explosives, and EMP can reveal it.</Revenant.description>
  <Sightstealer.description>Emaciated humanoid cryptids with sharp, curled claws formed from ultracite growth. They are fragile, but use camouflage and ambush to close on their victims before striking.</Sightstealer.description>
  <Noctol.description>A large nocturnal cryptid covered with an oil-black carapace and armed with claws formed from ultracite growths. Bright light irritates it and slows it considerably.</Noctol.description>
  <Gorehulk.description>A massive cryptid with swollen, irregular anatomy and dense keratin spines. It can launch these spines at range, though its awkward body is less effective in close quarters.</Gorehulk.description>
  <Devourer.description>A large burrowing cryptid with a toothed maw and a powerful leaping strike. It is known for swallowing prey whole and digesting them with unusual speed.</Devourer.description>
  <Chimera.description>A huge cryptid resembling a distorted mix of bear and other animal features. Its origin is unclear, but field reports are consistent about its aggression and physical strength.</Chimera.description>
  <Bulbfreak.description>A foul-smelling cryptid mass made up of smaller fused organisms linked by a shared nervous system. It is slow and comparatively easy to kill, but may break apart into smaller attackers when it dies.</Bulbfreak.description>
  <Toughspike.description>A tough, man-sized cryptid with two spiked limbs and a hardened carapace. It throws sharpened keratin spikes and is most dangerous at range.</Toughspike.description>
  <Trispike.description>A man-sized cryptid formed from several fused organisms. Its limbs can remain active after death, causing the body to split into smaller attackers.</Trispike.description>
  <Fingerspike.description>A dog-sized cryptid with a single spiked limb. Despite its short legs, it moves quickly and closes distance well.</Fingerspike.description>
  <Dreadmeld.description>A huge tunnel-dwelling cryptid formed from multiple fused organisms around a loosely shared nervous system. It uses its massive claws to dig through rock and is most often encountered below ground.</Dreadmeld.description>
</LanguageData>