<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as Centurion overseeing Legion operations at Techatticup Mine. [PAWN_pronoun] manages slave labor and defends strategic mining positions with tactical precision.</FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Adult.title>Centurion at Techatticup</FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was taken into the Legion as a child during tribal assimilation. [PAWN_pronoun] adapted quickly to military discipline and showed tactical aptitude.</FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Child.title>Legion conscript</FCP_Backstory_Alexus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Antony_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as the Legion's primary arms merchant at The Fort. [PAWN_pronoun] trades weapons, armor, and supplies with Legion members and approved visitors. [PAWN_nameDef] maintains good relations with Caesar's forces while turning a profit.</FCP_Backstory_Antony_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Antony_Adult.title>Legion arms dealer</FCP_Backstory_Antony_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Antony_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a merchant family, learning the value of goods and the art of negotiation. [PAWN_pronoun] could spot quality weapons and armor from an early age.</FCP_Backstory_Antony_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Antony_Child.title>Trader's apprentice</FCP_Backstory_Antony_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as Centurion overseeing the Legion's slave operations at The Fort. [PAWN_pronoun] manages the capture, breaking, and assignment of slaves with cold efficiency. [PAWN_nameDef] views slaves as resources to be exploited.</FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Adult.title>Legion Slave Master</FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up navigating dangerous canyons and learning to track and capture prey. These skills would later serve [PAWN_objective] well in a different kind of hunting.</FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Child.title>Canyon survivor</FCP_Backstory_Canyon_Runner_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] commands Legion forces at Dry Wells, enforcing Caesar's will with brutal efficiency. [PAWN_pronoun] is ruthless in combat and shows no mercy to enemies or incompetent subordinates.</FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Adult.title>Centurion of Dry Wells</FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up learning to enforce order through strength. [PAWN_pronoun] believed in harsh discipline and total obedience from an early age.</FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Child.title>Wasteland enforcer youth</FCP_Backstory_Centurion_Severus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as a Cursor, a Legion scout and messenger. [PAWN_pronoun] explores ahead of Legion forces, gathering intelligence and relaying orders. [PAWN_nameDef] moves quickly through hostile territory.</FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Adult.title>Legion scout</FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was always fast on [PAWN_possessive] feet and quick-minded. [PAWN_pronoun] delivered messages across dangerous terrain with speed and reliability.</FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Child.title>Swift messenger child</FCP_Backstory_Cursor_Lucullus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] commands Legion forces at Camp Nelson with ruthless efficiency. [PAWN_pronoun] is known for brutal tactics including crucifying NCR prisoners. [PAWN_nameDef] enforces discipline through fear and violence.</FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Adult.title>Centurion at Nelson</FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a harsh tribal environment where only the strong survived. [PAWN_pronoun] learned early that violence and intimidation were the keys to power.</FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Child.title>Brutal tribal youth</FCP_Backstory_Dead_Sea_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] commands a contubernium (squad) at Camp Nelson. [PAWN_pronoun] enforces discipline among legionaries and coordinates small unit tactics. [PAWN_nameDef] aspires to earn promotion through battlefield performance.</FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Adult.title>Squad leader at Nelson</FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in the Legion's training camps. [PAWN_pronoun] learned combat skills and tactical basics, preparing to lead small units.</FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Child.title>Legion youth</FCP_Backstory_Decanus_Severus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] leads Legion raids against NCR positions, particularly targeting Camp Forlorn Hope. [PAWN_pronoun] is a skilled tactician who keeps NCR forces under constant pressure through coordinated attacks.</FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Adult.title>Centurion at Forlorn Hope</FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised within the Legion from early childhood. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in combat training and absorbed Legion philosophy completely.</FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Child.title>Legion raised warrior</FCP_Backstory_Gaius_Magnus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Karl_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] serves as Decanus at Cottonwood Cove, a Legion river outpost. [PAWN_pronoun] manages ferry operations and oversees security along the Colorado River approach to The Fort.</FCP_Backstory_Karl_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Karl_Adult.title>Decanus at Cottonwood Cove</FCP_Backstory_Karl_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Karl_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a tribe conquered by the Legion. [PAWN_pronoun] proved [PAWN_possessive] worth in combat and was selected for military training.</FCP_Backstory_Karl_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Karl_Child.title>Tribal warrior youth</FCP_Backstory_Karl_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Otho_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] manages the Legion's mongrel war dogs at The Fort. [PAWN_pronoun] breeds, trains, and maintains these vicious animals used for guarding and combat. [PAWN_nameDef] understands his beasts better than most people.</FCP_Backstory_Otho_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Otho_Adult.title>Legion mongrel master</FCP_Backstory_Otho_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Otho_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up around dangerous wasteland creatures. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to understand their behavior and train them through a mix of discipline and reward.</FCP_Backstory_Otho_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Otho_Child.title>Beast handler child</FCP_Backstory_Otho_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Picus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] operates as a Frumentarius embedded at Camp McCarran. [PAWN_pronoun] passes as an NCR civilian while gathering intelligence and sabotaging operations. [PAWN_nameDef] must maintain [PAWN_possessive] cover at all costs.</FCP_Backstory_Picus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Picus_Adult.title>Deep cover agent</FCP_Backstory_Picus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Picus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was always watching, always listening. [PAWN_pronoun] learned to gather information and read people's intentions before speaking.</FCP_Backstory_Picus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Picus_Child.title>Observant youth</FCP_Backstory_Picus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Silus_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] operated as a Frumentarius until [PAWN_possessive] capture by the NCR. Now held at Camp McCarran, [PAWN_pronoun] faces interrogation while maintaining loyalty to Caesar. [PAWN_nameDef] knows too much to give up easily.</FCP_Backstory_Silus_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Silus_Adult.title>Captured spy</FCP_Backstory_Silus_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Backstory_Silus_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] learned early that lies and misdirection could be as effective as weapons. [PAWN_pronoun] practiced assuming different personas and hiding [PAWN_possessive] true nature.</FCP_Backstory_Silus_Child.description>
  <FCP_Backstory_Silus_Child.title>Deceptive child</FCP_Backstory_Silus_Child.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] earned the rank of Centurion through valor in battle. [PAWN_pronoun] commands a century of legionaries and is responsible for pacifying the Phoenix area. [PAWN_pronoun] is a skilled tactician and respected by [PAWN_possessive] troops for leading from the front.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Adult.title>Centurion</FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in Legion territory and raised according to Caesar's strict code. [PAWN_pronoun] excelled in military training and showed natural leadership abilities from an early age.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Child.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Child.title>Legion Youth</FCP_Character_Backstory_Aurelius_Child.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] founded Caesar's Legion after being captured by the Blackfoot tribe. Using [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of Roman history and tactics, [PAWN_pronoun] united dozens of tribes under one banner. [PAWN_pronoun] is a brilliant strategist and charismatic leader, though [PAWN_pronoun] suffers from a brain tumor that causes periodic weakness.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Adult.title>Caesar</FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Child.description>Born Edward Sallow, [PAWN_nameDef] was raised by the Followers of the Apocalypse after [PAWN_possessive] parents died. [PAWN_pronoun] spent [PAWN_possessive] youth studying history, linguistics, and philosophy in the Boneyard, developing a sharp intellect and an obsession with ancient Rome.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Child.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Child.title>Follower Acolyte</FCP_Character_Backstory_Caesar_Child.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Adult.description>Known as the Monster of the East, [PAWN_nameDef] rose to become Caesar's most feared military commander. After personally executing [PAWN_possessive] entire tribe for cowardice, [PAWN_pronoun] joined the Legion and became legendary for [PAWN_possessive] brutality and unstoppable combat prowess. [PAWN_pronoun] leads from the front, breaking enemy lines through sheer violence.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Adult.title>Legate</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into the Hidebarks tribe in the savage lands east of the Colorado River. As a youth, [PAWN_pronoun] witnessed [PAWN_possessive] tribe's brutal traditions and learned that strength and fear were the only currencies that mattered in the wasteland.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Child.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Child.title>Hidebarks Tribesman</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lanius_Child.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] commands Caesar's elite Praetorian Guard. [PAWN_pronoun] is a veteran warrior who has served the Legion for decades, earning [PAWN_possessive] position through unwavering loyalty and battlefield skill. [PAWN_pronoun] is responsible for Caesar's personal safety and the training of the Praetorian Guard.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Adult.title>Praetorian Commander</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was one of the earliest tribes assimilated into Caesar's Legion as a child. [PAWN_pronoun] was trained in the ways of the Legion from a young age, learning discipline, tactics, and absolute loyalty to Caesar.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Child.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Child.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Character_Backstory_Lucius_Child.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Adult.description>[PAWN_nameDef] leads the Legion's Frumentarii, the elite intelligence and infiltration corps. Known as "Mr. Fox," [PAWN_pronoun] is a master of espionage, sabotage, and psychological warfare. [PAWN_pronoun] operates behind enemy lines, sowing chaos and gathering intelligence for Caesar's campaigns.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Adult.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Adult.title>Frumentarius</FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Adult.title>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] showed exceptional intelligence and cunning from a young age. When [PAWN_possessive] tribe was absorbed by the Legion, [PAWN_pronoun] was selected for special training due to [PAWN_possessive] quick mind and natural talent for deception.</FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Child.description>
  <FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Child.title>Tribal Scout</FCP_Character_Backstory_Vulpes_Child.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Acolyte_of_Mars.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an acolyte of Mars, spreading the word of Caesar, the son of Mars, through the lands occupied by the Legion. While [PAWN_pronoun] essentially was something in between a priest and a messenger, [PAWN_nameDef] truly thought [PAWN_pronoun] had a divine mission. [PAWN_pronoun] was gifted with words and where [PAWN_pronoun] spoke, the people listened.</FCP_Legion_Acolyte_of_Mars.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Acolyte_of_Mars.title>Legion Acolyte of Mars</FCP_Legion_Acolyte_of_Mars.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Administrator.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a Legion administrator, tasked with overseeing the logistics that are required to hold together such an innumerable army as the Legion. As such, [PAWN_pronoun] had a talent for numbers, administration and other things most legionaries viewed as the work of profligates.</FCP_Legion_Administrator.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Administrator.title>Legion Administrator</FCP_Legion_Administrator.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Arizona_Trader.description>Not all who lived in the domain of Caesar were part of his army. Many of the inhabitants of more civilized settlements within Legion domain remained relatively free. As a matter of fact, many traders preferred operating in Legion territory, as they managed to keep the roads safe from raiders. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of those merchants, traveling around Arizona, New Mexico, Utah and Colorado and dealing with the Legion on a regular basis.</FCP_Legion_Arizona_Trader.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Arizona_Trader.title>Arizona Trader</FCP_Legion_Arizona_Trader.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Born.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in Legion territory as a child of civilians. [PAWN_pronoun] enjoyed a relatively uneventful childhood, until the day the Legion decided [PAWN_possessive] labour was needed in a nearby encampment and [PAWN_pronoun] was taken from [PAWN_possessive] parents by force, never to see them again.</FCP_Legion_Born.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Born.title>Legion Born</FCP_Legion_Born.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Caravan_Child.description>The vast territories the Legion had conquered during a short timespan led to a growing demand in trading caravans. [PAWN_nameDef] grew up traveling the length and width of the southern parts of the wastelands and learned much on the dusty roads.</FCP_Legion_Caravan_Child.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Caravan_Child.title>Legion Caravan Child</FCP_Legion_Caravan_Child.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Carrier_Slave.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was used as a human beast of burden to carry around massive amounts of materiel. [PAWN_pronoun] was treated like cattle for most of [PAWN_possessive] life. Needless to say, that such cruel treatment left deep scars in [PAWN_possessive] soul.</FCP_Legion_Carrier_Slave.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Carrier_Slave.title>Legion Carrier Slave</FCP_Legion_Carrier_Slave.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Centurion.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was an elite soldier of Caesar’s Legion. Unrelenting and fearless in battle, [PAWN_pronoun] was awarded with the rank of centurion. There were few who could match [PAWN_pronoun] in close combat and [PAWN_nameDef] used [PAWN_possessive] abilities to crush anyone foolish enough to stand in the Legion’s way.</FCP_Legion_Centurion.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Centurion.title>Legion Centurion</FCP_Legion_Centurion.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Coin_Minters_Child.description>Like many other larger political entities, Caesar had his Legion mint coins adorned with his profile. [PAWN_nameDef] was born to a minter and enjoyed a relatively peaceful childhood, as the Legion left [PAWN_possessive] family be, due to the rarity of the skill provided by them.</FCP_Legion_Coin_Minters_Child.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Coin_Minters_Child.title>Coin Minter’s Child</FCP_Legion_Coin_Minters_Child.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Colorado_Kid.description>[PAWN_nameDef]’s family came from Colorado. The mountainous state brought forth many skilled miners, builders, and craftspeople, most of which have found employment within the Legion. Those unwilling to do so freely were usually enslaved and put to work anyway.</FCP_Legion_Colorado_Kid.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Colorado_Kid.title>Colorado Kid</FCP_Legion_Colorado_Kid.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Cook.description>As cynical as it may sound, [PAWN_nameDef] was a rather lucky slave. [PAWN_pronoun] was tasked with the preparation of meals for [PAWN_possessive] Legion camp, which absolved [PAWN_objective] from most of the hardest, most exhausting labour. Truth be told, [PAWN_nameDef] wasn’t even that good a cook, but the Legion’s contempt for luxury ensured that that wasn’t an issue.</FCP_Legion_Cook.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Cook.title>Legion Cook</FCP_Legion_Cook.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Cunning_Whelp.description>From [PAWN_possessive] birth, [PAWN_nameDef] was smaller and weaker than [PAWN_possessive] peers. It was rare for the Legion to let such children live, but [PAWN_nameDef] was one of the lucky few, mainly due to the fact that [PAWN_pronoun] had other skills and qualities than raw strength, [PAWN_pronoun] was cunning.</FCP_Legion_Cunning_Whelp.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Cunning_Whelp.title>Cunning Whelp</FCP_Legion_Cunning_Whelp.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Decanus.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a decanus in Caesar’s Legion. It was [PAWN_possessive] duty to lead the rank and file legionaries in battle. [PAWN_nameDef] has been a decanus for many years and yearned for a chance to ascend to the rank of centurion.</FCP_Legion_Decanus.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Decanus.title>Legion Decanus</FCP_Legion_Decanus.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] early childhood in a small settlement somewhere in the south-western part of the former USA. One day Caesar’s Legion raided the settlement, razing it to the ground and enslaving the survivors. [PAWN_nameDef] was taken as a slave and spent the remainder of [PAWN_possessive] youth in a cage, like an animal.</FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Child.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Child.title>Enslaved Child</FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Child.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Tribal.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into one of the many tribes which were conquered and subjugated by the Legion. The utter obliteration of the tribe’s culture and traditions left [PAWN_objective] shaken and traumatized.</FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Tribal.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Tribal.title>Enslaved Tribal</FCP_Legion_Enslaved_Tribal.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Flag_Staff_Kid.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born and raised in Flag Staff, the capital city of Caesars Legion. While Two Sun served as Arizona’s main trade hub, Flag Staff was the beating heart of the Legion itself.</FCP_Legion_Flag_Staff_Kid.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Flag_Staff_Kid.title>Flag Staff Kid</FCP_Legion_Flag_Staff_Kid.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Frumentarius.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a frumentarius. As one of the elite intelligence officers [PAWN_nameDef] serves as the mighty Caesars eyes and ears and is tasked with subtle missions, like infiltrating the enemy’s society or gathering intelligence behind enemy lines.</FCP_Legion_Frumentarius.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Frumentarius.title>Legion Frumentarius</FCP_Legion_Frumentarius.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Gladiator.description>[PAWN_nameDef] fought frequently in the fighting arenas, often located at the centre of Legion camps. [PAWN_pronoun] has won many battles in the arena, leaving [PAWN_possessive] opponents bleeding out in the dust. [PAWN_nameDef] wore [PAWN_possessive] many scars with pride.</FCP_Legion_Gladiator.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Gladiator.title>Legion Gladiator</FCP_Legion_Gladiator.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Healer.description>While the Legion shunned most forms of modern technology, including many types of medicine, someone had to keep the Legionaries in fighting condition, patching them up if wounded or putting them down for good if deemed too weak to fight again. [PAWN_nameDef] never got any kind of real medical training but proved to be quite resourceful with needle and thread, as well as several herbal concoctions of questionable quality.</FCP_Legion_Healer.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Healer.title>Legion Healer</FCP_Legion_Healer.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Healers_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef]’s mother was a healer in the Legion. While the Legion did not have access to high-tech medicine due to their refusal to use modern technology, the Legion’s healers managed to cook up various poultices, ointments, and other herbal remedies. [PAWN_nameDef] learned a good deal about healing from [PAWN_possessive] mother.</FCP_Legion_Healers_Child.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Healers_Child.title>Healer’s Child</FCP_Legion_Healers_Child.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Hunter.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a trusted enough warrior, to receive advanced hunting equipment. With [PAWN_possessive] trusty rifle, [PAWN_pronoun] prowled through the wasteland, always on the lookout for brahmin, bighorners and other game to fill the bellies of the hungry legionaries at the camp.</FCP_Legion_Hunter.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Hunter.title>Legion Hunter</FCP_Legion_Hunter.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Legionary_Child.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born as the child of a Legionary, as were most children within the Legion since Caesar demanded a child-quota from his soldiers to bolster his army’s ranks.</FCP_Legion_Legionary_Child.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Legionary_Child.title>Legionary Child</FCP_Legion_Legionary_Child.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Magister.description>While the Legion did not put much emphasis on education, there still was a need for someone to teach the values of the Legion to the younglings. [PAWN_nameDef] was in charge of educating the soon-to-be Legionaries. Through [PAWN_objective] they learned how a Legionary had to speak, as well as the most essential things about the Cult of Mars.</FCP_Legion_Magister.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Magister.title>Legion Magister</FCP_Legion_Magister.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Miner.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was part of a tribe, which was only recently subjugated by the Legion. [PAWN_possessive] tribe lived in the Rocky Mountains, where they lived in caves and canyons. As such they were skilled miners and [PAWN_nameDef] was put to work as a miner for Caesar’s Legion.</FCP_Legion_Miner.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Miner.title>Legion Miner</FCP_Legion_Miner.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Peasant.description>While [PAWN_nameDef] wasn’t technically a slave, [PAWN_pronoun] still lived within Legion territory, where [PAWN_pronoun] had to work the land. A large proportion of [PAWN_possessive] produce was confiscated by Legion administrators after each harvest, but [PAWN_nameDef] was still content since Caesar’s warriors kept the raiders at bay and didn’t harass [PAWN_objective] otherwise.</FCP_Legion_Peasant.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Peasant.title>Legion Peasant</FCP_Legion_Peasant.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Praetorian.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a member of the esteemed praetorian guard, tasked with the protection of none other than the almighty Caesar himself. [PAWN_pronoun] became part of this elite group by challenging and defeating one of the praetorians and took great pride in the fact that few other’s within the Legion would ever be so close to their infallible leader as [PAWN_pronoun] was. Of course, this position was not representative in nature, [PAWN_pronoun] had to be a formidable fighter, capable of dispatching any would-be assassins sent after Caesar.</FCP_Legion_Praetorian.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Praetorian.title>Legion Praetorian</FCP_Legion_Praetorian.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Promising_Youngling.description>Like many other children, [PAWN_nameDef] was born in a Legion war-camp. [PAWN_pronoun] grew faster, taller, and stronger than most other children in the camps and showed great promise during the excruciating trainings, much to the pride of [PAWN_possessive] tutors.</FCP_Legion_Promising_Youngling.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Promising_Youngling.title>Promising Youngling</FCP_Legion_Promising_Youngling.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Purchased_Slave.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born as the child of a Legionary, as were most children within the Legion since Caesar demanded a child-quota from his soldiers to bolster his army’s ranks.</FCP_Legion_Purchased_Slave.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Purchased_Slave.title>Purchased Slave</FCP_Legion_Purchased_Slave.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Raised_by_Priestess.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised by a Priestess of Mars and enjoyed a relatively (by Legion standards) pampered childhood and a somewhat formal education.</FCP_Legion_Raised_by_Priestess.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Raised_by_Priestess.title>Raised by Priestess</FCP_Legion_Raised_by_Priestess.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit.description>The Legion’s reckless way of war and the consequently high casualties meant that they were always in dire need of new recruits. [PAWN_nameDef] was one of those recruits. While [PAWN_pronoun] didn’t have much combat experience, [PAWN_pronoun] was eager to prove himself in the eyes of [PAWN_possessive] decanus and fought ferociously.</FCP_Legion_Recruit.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_a.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into the Legion, raised from childhood to see Caesar as a god and the Legion as the only true way forward. [PAWN_pronoun] trained with spears and rifles from an early age, learning discipline, obedience, and the art of war. Now of age, [PAWN_pronoun] stands among the fresh recruits, eager to earn [PAWN_possessive] place in the ranks through blood and conquest.</FCP_Legion_Recruit_a.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_a.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit_a.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_b.description>Caesar is not just a warlord, he is a prophet, a divine ruler destined to unite the wasteland. [PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a Legion-controlled settlement, where the words of Caesar were absolute truth. When the time came to serve, [PAWN_pronoun] took up arms with fanatical devotion, ready to purge the weak and spread Caesar’s will.</FCP_Legion_Recruit_b.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_b.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit_b.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_c.description>Once, [PAWN_nameDef] belonged to a nomadic desert tribe, skilled in survival and warfare. But weakness is not tolerated. When [PAWN_pronoun] was cast out for failing [PAWN_possessive] people, death seemed certain. Instead, the Legion found [PAWN_pronoun] and offered a place among the recruits. In the Legion, failure means death, but success means power. [PAWN_pronoun] swore never to fail again.</FCP_Legion_Recruit_c.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_c.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit_c.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_d.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up under the New California Republic, believing in democracy, law, and order. But as the NCR spread, corruption and weakness spread with it. When the Legion came, [PAWN_pronoun] expected death. Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] was given a chance to serve something stronger than the crumbling NCR. Now, with a sword in hand, [PAWN_pronoun] fights against the very nation [PAWN_pronoun] once called home, convinced that Caesar’s way is the only way forward.</FCP_Legion_Recruit_d.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_d.title>Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit_d.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_e.description>The Legion destroyed [PAWN_possessive] town. [PAWN_pronoun] should have died with the rest. Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] was given a choice: submit and fight for Caesar or be wiped away like the rest of [PAWN_possessive] people. With nothing left, [PAWN_pronoun] chose the Legion. At first, it was just survival. But as the years passed, [PAWN_pronoun] began to understand the Legion’s strength. The weak are burned away, and the strong endure. [PAWN_pronoun] will never be weak again.</FCP_Legion_Recruit_e.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_e.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit_e.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_f.description>Some people join the Legion for survival. Some join for loyalty. [PAWN_nameDef] joined because [PAWN_pronoun] loves war. The Legion offered something that no other faction could, unlimited opportunities for battle, slaughter, and conquest. [PAWN_pronoun] fights not for Caesar, not for glory, but simply because it’s what [PAWN_pronoun] does best.</FCP_Legion_Recruit_f.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Recruit_f.title>Legion Recruit</FCP_Legion_Recruit_f.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Scavenger.description>Unlike the NCR, the Legion couldn’t rely on a strong industrial centre to supply them with enough weapons and ammunition to supply their ever-growing army. [PAWN_nameDef] was a scavenger for the Legion, who’s main task was to scavenge pre-war buildings for weaponry. As the Legion generally was a rather low-tech faction, they favoured weapons that were easy to maintain and repair and rugged enough to keep their functionality in the hazardous wasteland.</FCP_Legion_Scavenger.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Scavenger.title>Legion Scavenger</FCP_Legion_Scavenger.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Scout.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a Scout in Caesar’s Legion. [PAWN_pronoun] job was to explore new areas for the Legion to conquer. [PAWN_nameDef] is well-trained with the weapons of the Legion and always eager to show his prowess in battle against the enemies of the son of Mars.</FCP_Legion_Scout.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Scout.title>Legion Scout</FCP_Legion_Scout.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Scribe.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a scribe in service of Caesar’s Legion. [PAWN_possessive] task was to write done orders, sometimes from Caesar himself, and send them on their way through the Legion’s domain and beyond. Some Legionaries rumoured, that [PAWN_pronoun] secretly wrote poetry, but there never was any proof for these allegations.</FCP_Legion_Scribe.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Scribe.title>Legion Scribe</FCP_Legion_Scribe.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Sentry.description>Being a sentry wasn’t seen as a very honourable task by most legionaries. It was a task mostly left to the less experienced legionaries and recruits. [PAWN_nameDef] wasn’t particularly fond of guard duty, but the horrifying punishments the Legion enacted upon those who neglected their duties were motivation enough to keep [PAWN_objective] focused and obedient.</FCP_Legion_Sentry.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Sentry.title>Legion Sentry</FCP_Legion_Sentry.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Slave.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was a slave of Caesar’s Legion. [PAWN_pronoun] was put to backbreaking work by [PAWN_possessive] masters. It was a bleak life full of violence and toil, but it made [PAWN_nameDef] tough and resilient, albeit wary of others.</FCP_Legion_Slave.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Slave.title>Legion Slave</FCP_Legion_Slave.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Smith.description>It was expected of each and every Legionary that he was capable of maintaining of his equipment. However, it was [PAWN_nameDef] to craft the equipment at first. [PAWN_pronoun] was a proficient smith, able to craft the Legionaries distinctive armour out of old sport equipment and other salvage. [PAWN_possessive] abilities made [PAWN_objective] popular within the Legion’s encampments, as no warrior, no matter how skilled, can fight for long without good gear.</FCP_Legion_Smith.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Smith.title>Legion Smith</FCP_Legion_Smith.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Talented_Hunter.description>Early in [PAWN_possessive] life, [PAWN_nameDef] showed a great talent for hunting. These skills were fostered by the Legion, as food was scarce in the Legion camps and the hides of the beasts [PAWN_pronoun] slayed could be used to craft many useful goods like waterskins, tents and other necessities.</FCP_Legion_Talented_Hunter.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Talented_Hunter.title>Talented Hunter</FCP_Legion_Talented_Hunter.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Taskmaster.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was tasked with ensuring discipline and obedience among the recruits and slaves of Caesar’s Legion. While [PAWN_pronoun] was feared among [PAWN_possessive] subordinates for [PAWN_possessive] brutal methods and high expectations, [PAWN_nameDef] always felt a sense of pride for the younglings [PAWN_pronoun] shaped into Legionaries.</FCP_Legion_Taskmaster.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Taskmaster.title>Legion Taskmaster</FCP_Legion_Taskmaster.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Two_Sun_Dweller.description>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in the Arizonian town formerly known as Tucson, which was renamed to Two Sun at some point after the Great War. Two Sun was known as a major trading hub in the southern parts of the American wastelands and an important stop for people travelling to the wastelands of what once was Mexico and vice versa. [PAWN_pronoun] learned a lot about bartering during [PAWN_possessive] time in the sprawling city.</FCP_Legion_Two_Sun_Dweller.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Two_Sun_Dweller.title>Two Sun Dweller</FCP_Legion_Two_Sun_Dweller.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_a.description>[PAWN_nameDef] has fought beside greatness. From the early days of [PAWN_possessive] service, [PAWN_pronoun] caught the attention of a powerful Centurion, serving as a personal enforcer, executioner, and right-hand warrior. In battle, [PAWN_nameDef] was the one sent to break the enemy’s resolve, to cut down officers, champions, and cowards alike. With [PAWN_possessive] Centurion now dead, [PAWN_pronoun] fights on, not just to honor the fallen, but to one day rise to that same position of power.</FCP_Legion_Veteran_a.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_a.title>Legion Veteran</FCP_Legion_Veteran_a.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_b.description>Some battles end in an hour. Others last years. When Caesar ordered a campaign deep into NCR-controlled territory, [PAWN_nameDef] was among those sent on the grueling march. Months without resupply. Constant fighting. Watching entire centuries wiped out. [PAWN_pronoun] survived it all and returned to tell the tale, scarred, hardened, and more devoted than ever. Those who survived became Veterans, forged into warriors beyond pain or fear.</FCP_Legion_Veteran_b.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_b.title>Legion Veteran</FCP_Legion_Veteran_b.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_c.description>The battle for Hoover Dam was a test, one that many Legionaries did not survive. But [PAWN_nameDef] was among the few who stood victorious, cutting through wave after wave of NCR defenders. Even when the battle turned against Caesar, [PAWN_pronoun] refused to flee, choosing to hold ground until the last possible moment. Now, [PAWN_pronoun] fights not just for conquest, but for revenge, to see the NCR shattered and Hoover Dam taken once and for all.</FCP_Legion_Veteran_c.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_c.title>Legion Veteran</FCP_Legion_Veteran_c.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_d.description>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up under the New California Republic, believing in democracy, law, and order. But as the NCR spread, corruption and weakness spread with it. When the Legion came, [PAWN_pronoun] expected death. Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] was given a chance to serve something stronger than the crumbling NCR. Now, with a sword in hand, [PAWN_pronoun] fights against the very nation [PAWN_pronoun] once called home, convinced that Caesar’s way is the only way forward.</FCP_Legion_Veteran_d.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_d.title>Legion Veteran</FCP_Legion_Veteran_d.title>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_e.description>The Legion destroyed [PAWN_possessive] town. [PAWN_pronoun] should have died with the rest. Instead, [PAWN_pronoun] was given a choice: submit and fight for Caesar or be wiped away like the rest of [PAWN_possessive] people. With nothing left, [PAWN_pronoun] chose the Legion. At first, it was just survival. But as the years passed, [PAWN_pronoun] began to understand the Legion’s strength. The weak are burned away, and the strong endure. [PAWN_pronoun] will never be weak again.</FCP_Legion_Veteran_e.description>
  <FCP_Legion_Veteran_e.title>Legion Veteran</FCP_Legion_Veteran_e.title>
</LanguageData>