<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VEE_AnimaPearls.description>A smooth, lustrous pearl formed within anima blossoms, faintly humming with psychic resonance. Anima pearls can be consumed to increase psychic sensitivity for some time.</VEE_AnimaPearls.description>
  <VEE_AnimaPearls.label>anima pearl</VEE_AnimaPearls.label>
  <VEE_ButtercupFlower.description>A beautiful wild flower.</VEE_ButtercupFlower.description>
  <VEE_ButtercupFlower.label>buttercup</VEE_ButtercupFlower.label>
  <VEE_Cenote.description>A deep, water filled sinkhole carved into the stone. The surface appears calm. Due to its depth, it can't be filled.</VEE_Cenote.description>
  <VEE_Cenote.label>cenote</VEE_Cenote.label>
  <VEE_Cenote_Small.description>A deep, water filled sinkhole carved into the stone. The surface appears calm. Due to its depth, it can't be filled.</VEE_Cenote_Small.description>
  <VEE_Cenote_Small.label>small cenote</VEE_Cenote_Small.label>
  <VEE_Coral.description>A colorful, calcified colony of tiny marine organisms, forming intricate reef structures teeming with life.</VEE_Coral.description>
  <VEE_Coral.label>coral</VEE_Coral.label>
  <VEE_DayBoomshroom.description>These mushrooms produce volatile chemicals as a defensive measure. They can be harvested for chemfuel. However, this must be done with extreme caution, as the mushrooms can explode if they're destroyed.\n\nGlitterworld researchers have used genetic material from boomshrooms to bioengineer a number of chemfuel-producing animals.</VEE_DayBoomshroom.description>
  <VEE_DayBoomshroom.label>light-resistant boomshroom</VEE_DayBoomshroom.label>
  <VEE_DayPsilocap.description>A fungus that gives off hallucinogenic spores. Standing next to them is enough to produce mild hallucinations. Psilocaps can be harvested and ingested to produce a vivid sensory experience that increases the user's mood.</VEE_DayPsilocap.description>
  <VEE_DayPsilocap.label>light-resistant psilocap</VEE_DayPsilocap.label>
  <VEE_DayWillowgill.description>A tall spindly slow-growing mushroom with gills that droop like a willow tree.</VEE_DayWillowgill.description>
  <VEE_DayWillowgill.label>light-resistant willowgill</VEE_DayWillowgill.label>
  <VEE_DeadlifeVent.description>A sinister geyser that exhales eerie, ash-like dust, capable of reawakening the dead under its influence.</VEE_DeadlifeVent.description>
  <VEE_DeadlifeVent.label>deadlife geyser</VEE_DeadlifeVent.label>
  <VEE_DenseSnow.description>A heavy, compacted layer of snow that resists movement and muffles sound. Can be mined to remove it.</VEE_DenseSnow.description>
  <VEE_DenseSnow.label>solid snow</VEE_DenseSnow.label>
  <VEE_DriftwoodChunk.description>A sun-bleached fragment of wood, smoothed by waves and time, carried ashore from some distant and unknown origin.</VEE_DriftwoodChunk.description>
  <VEE_DriftwoodChunk.label>driftwood</VEE_DriftwoodChunk.label>
  <VEE_DryWheat.description>An amber cereal plant that takes almost an entire growing season to come to fruition. This wheat has been subjected to drought conditions for too long and has wilted away.</VEE_DryWheat.description>
  <VEE_DryWheat.label>dry wheat</VEE_DryWheat.label>
  <VEE_Filth_Seashells.label>seashells</VEE_Filth_Seashells.label>
  <VEE_ForgetMeNot.description>A beautiful wild flower.</VEE_ForgetMeNot.description>
  <VEE_ForgetMeNot.label>forget-me-not</VEE_ForgetMeNot.label>
  <VEE_Gorse.description>A spiny, evergreen shrub covered in bright yellow flowers. Its thick, tangled branches provide shelter while resisting wind and harsh conditions.</VEE_Gorse.description>
  <VEE_Gorse.label>gorse</VEE_Gorse.label>
  <VEE_Heather.description>A low, flowering shrub with dense clusters of tiny blooms. It carpets the landscape with muted colors and weathers wind and exposure with ease.</VEE_Heather.description>
  <VEE_Heather.label>heather</VEE_Heather.label>
  <VEE_InertPitGate.description>A massive, foreboding hole that connects the surface with a dark network of underground caves. It is possible to climb down into the caverns below.</VEE_InertPitGate.description>
  <VEE_InertPitGate.label>pit gate</VEE_InertPitGate.label>
  <VEE_JadeChunk.description>A chunk of jadeite. It can be deconstructed to acquire some jade.</VEE_JadeChunk.description>
  <VEE_JadeChunk.label>jadeite chunk</VEE_JadeChunk.label>
  <VEE_Knapweed.description>A robust, weedy, wild plant.</VEE_Knapweed.description>
  <VEE_Knapweed.label>knapweed</VEE_Knapweed.label>
  <VEE_Loosestrife.description>A beautiful herbaceous perennial wild plant.</VEE_Loosestrife.description>
  <VEE_Loosestrife.label>loosestrife</VEE_Loosestrife.label>
  <VEE_Mangrove.description>A salt-tolerant tree adapted to life in brackish wetlands. Its tangled roots anchor it in shifting mud and provide shelter for aquatic life.</VEE_Mangrove.description>
  <VEE_Mangrove.label>mangrove</VEE_Mangrove.label>
  <VEE_Mangrove_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a mangrove tree has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Mangrove_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Mangrove_ChoppedStump.label>mangrove chopped stump</VEE_Mangrove_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Mangrove_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a mangrove tree destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Mangrove_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Mangrove_SmashedStump.label>mangrove smashed stump</VEE_Mangrove_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.description>Advanced ancient electronics, compacted over time. Can be mined for useful advanced components.</VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.description>
  <VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.label>advanced compacted machinery</VEE_MineableComponentSpacer.label>
  <VEE_MineableJadeite.description>A silicate mineral in the pyroxene family that is one of the two forms of jade.</VEE_MineableJadeite.description>
  <VEE_MineableJadeite.label>jadeite</VEE_MineableJadeite.label>
  <VEE_ObsidianChunk.description>A chunk of obsidian. It can be deconstructed to acquire some obsidian.</VEE_ObsidianChunk.description>
  <VEE_ObsidianChunk.label>obsidian chunk</VEE_ObsidianChunk.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.description>Clumps of vines that burst through the soil to bloom into beautiful flowers. Believed to be part of great collective roots that spread deep under the terrain which occasionally breach the surface to pollinate. The attractive qualities of the flowers encourage humans not to remove them.</VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.label>anima bell</VEE_Plant_AnimaBell.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.description>Thorny, fast-growing vines infused with faint anima energy. Their barbs are humming softly to the touch.</VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.label>anima brambles</VEE_Plant_AnimaBrambles.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.description>A short shrub. Does talk, but only when you're not around.</VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.label>anima bush</VEE_Plant_AnimaBush.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.description>A delicate, softly glowing flower that blooms near anima trees, resonating faintly with psychic energy. Can be harvested to acquire anima pearls.</VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.label>anima heart blossom</VEE_Plant_AnimaHeartBlossom.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.description>A withered anima tree whose bark has hardened into a gray, lifeless shell under relentless pollution. Its psychic presence is muted and distorted, yet a stubborn echo of anima still clings to the husk, refusing to fully fade.</VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.label>anima husk</VEE_Plant_AnimaHusk.label>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.description>Pale, twisting roots shot through with a soft inner glow, drawn from anima-touched soil. Can be harvested for wood.</VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.description>
  <VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.label>anima root</VEE_Plant_AnimaRoot.label>
  <VEE_Plant_BarrelCactus.description>A large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VEE_Plant_BarrelCactus.description>
  <VEE_Plant_BarrelCactus.label>barrel cactus</VEE_Plant_BarrelCactus.label>
  <VEE_Plant_BeavertailCactus.description>A large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VEE_Plant_BeavertailCactus.description>
  <VEE_Plant_BeavertailCactus.label>beavertail cactus</VEE_Plant_BeavertailCactus.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ChollaCactus.description>A large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VEE_Plant_ChollaCactus.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ChollaCactus.label>cholla cactus</VEE_Plant_ChollaCactus.label>
  <VEE_Plant_DatePalm.description>A tall palm thriving along warm coasts, bearing clusters of sweet, energy-rich fruit. Its deep roots and flexible trunk help it withstand salt spray and coastal winds.</VEE_Plant_DatePalm.description>
  <VEE_Plant_DatePalm.label>date palm</VEE_Plant_DatePalm.label>
  <VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.description>An anima-touched tree. It lacks the psychic potency of a true anima tree, but still hums faintly with psychic life.</VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.description>
  <VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.label>anima tree</VEE_Plant_FakeAnimaTree.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Fern.description>A shade-loving plant with broad fronds that spreads across damp forest floors and sheltered ground.</VEE_Plant_Fern.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Fern.label>fern</VEE_Plant_Fern.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood.description>A hardy tree adapted to grow on volcanic ground. It is among the first plants to colonize cooled lava, helping life return to the black stone.</VEE_Plant_Firewood.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood.label>firewood tree</VEE_Plant_Firewood.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a firewood tree has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.label>chopped stump</VEE_Plant_Firewood_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a firewood tree destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.label>smashed stump</VEE_Plant_Firewood_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.description>A twisted, weathered pine shaped by wind and poor soil. Its gnarled branches and sparse needles give it a rugged, enduring appearance.</VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.description>
  <VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.label>gnarled pine tree</VEE_Plant_GnarledPine.label>
  <VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.description>A grand anima-touched tree. It lacks the psychic potency of a true anima tree, but still hums faintly with psychic life.</VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.description>
  <VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.label>grand anima tree</VEE_Plant_GrandAnimaTree.label>
  <VEE_Plant_HedgehogCactus.description>A large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VEE_Plant_HedgehogCactus.description>
  <VEE_Plant_HedgehogCactus.label>hedgehog cactus</VEE_Plant_HedgehogCactus.label>
  <VEE_Plant_HoodiaCactus.description>A large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VEE_Plant_HoodiaCactus.description>
  <VEE_Plant_HoodiaCactus.label>hoodia cactus</VEE_Plant_HoodiaCactus.label>
  <VEE_Plant_JuniperBush.description>A hardy, low-growing bush with aromatic needles and dense berries. Its branches twist and spread, enduring harsh winds and exposed conditions.</VEE_Plant_JuniperBush.description>
  <VEE_Plant_JuniperBush.label>juniper bush</VEE_Plant_JuniperBush.label>
  <VEE_Plant_Laurel.description>An evergreen broadleaf tree with dense foliage and aromatic leaves, well adapted to mild, humid climates.</VEE_Plant_Laurel.description>
  <VEE_Plant_Laurel.label>laurel tree</VEE_Plant_Laurel.label>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a laurel tree has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.label>chopped stump</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a laurel tree destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.label>smashed stump</VEE_Plant_LaurelTree_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_MysticCap.description>A small, vividly colored mushroom with a faintly iridescent cap. Can be harvested for raw fungus.</VEE_Plant_MysticCap.description>
  <VEE_Plant_MysticCap.label>mystic cap</VEE_Plant_MysticCap.label>
  <VEE_Plant_OrganPipeCactus.description>A large cactus native to arid Earth environments. Though it is not a tree, it yields a small amount of fibrous material that can be used like wood.</VEE_Plant_OrganPipeCactus.description>
  <VEE_Plant_OrganPipeCactus.label>organ pipe cactus</VEE_Plant_OrganPipeCactus.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.description>A hardy coastal tree with spiraled leaves and exposed roots, adapted to wind, salt, and shifting sand.</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.label>screw pine</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.description>A stump left behind after a screw pine has been felled. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.label>chopped stump</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_ChoppedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.description>The remnants of a screw pine destroyed by damage. It's ugly. The stump can be extracted but yields very little usable wood. Left outdoors, the stump will deteriorate in time.</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.description>
  <VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.label>smashed stump</VEE_Plant_ScrewPine_SmashedStump.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.description>A huge rare tree with warm, skin-smooth bark and long iridescent leaves. Infused with bioluminescent micro-organisms, ancient anima trees develop a unique form of psychic symbiosis with surrounding lifeforms.\n\nIf a person (psycaster or not) meditates near an ancient anima tree, it will grow anima grass around its base. Once enough grass is grown, it becomes possible to carry out a psychic linking ritual with the tree and upgrade a person's psychic powers. Only tribal peoples know the secret of this ritual. Tribal psycasters are also able to draw psyfocus from ancient anima trees while meditating to them.\n\nAncient anima trees' psychic properties are weakened if artificial structures are placed nearby. They refuse to be caged or studied, and must remain part of nature.\n\nMost tribes believe that ancient anima trees are not simply trees, but are rather the physical extremities of a single world spirit.</VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.label>ancient anima tree</VEE_Plant_TreeAnima_Ancient.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.description>A temperate-biome tree known for its thin, white, paper-like bark.</VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.label>auburn birch tree</VEE_Plant_TreeBirch_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.description>A common medium-sized tree, easily identifiable by its distinct three-pointed leaf.</VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.label>auburn maple tree</VEE_Plant_TreeMaple_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.description>A hardwood tree. Oaks take a long time to grow, but their wood is so strong that 'oak' is used as a metaphor for strength across many cultures.</VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.label>auburn oak tree</VEE_Plant_TreeOak_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.description>A softwood tree that grows very fast. Unfortunately, its wood is weak and so it yields less useful material than hardwood trees.</VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.description>
  <VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.label>auburn poplar tree</VEE_Plant_TreePoplar_Auburn.label>
  <VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.description>A small anima-touched tree. It lacks the psychic potency of a true anima tree, but still hums faintly with psychic life.</VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.description>
  <VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.label>anima sapling</VEE_Plant_YoungAnimaTree.label>
  <VEE_RadioactiveBarrel.description>A rusted barrel leaking discarded nuclear fuel.</VEE_RadioactiveBarrel.description>
  <VEE_RadioactiveBarrel.label>radioactive barrel</VEE_RadioactiveBarrel.label>
  <VEE_RawDates.description>Raw dates. Nice to eat, even when raw. They are sweet, nutrient-rich fruit harvested from date palms. They keep well in warm climates and provide a reliable source of energy.</VEE_RawDates.description>
  <VEE_RawDates.label>dates</VEE_RawDates.label>
  <VEE_RotstinkVent.description>A foul geyser that intermittently belches clouds of corpse-born miasma, choking the air with the stench of decay.</VEE_RotstinkVent.description>
  <VEE_RotstinkVent.label>rotstink geyser</VEE_RotstinkVent.label>
  <VEE_Sinkhole.description>A sudden collapse in the ground forming a deep, unstable pit, often exposing bare rock beneath the surface.</VEE_Sinkhole.description>
  <VEE_Sinkhole.label>sinkhole</VEE_Sinkhole.label>
  <VEE_SmokeVent.description>A smoldering fissure that intermittently exhales thick, acrid smoke, reducing visibility and choking the lungs.</VEE_SmokeVent.description>
  <VEE_SmokeVent.label>smoke geyser</VEE_SmokeVent.label>
  <VEE_SmoothedJadeite.description>A silicate mineral in the pyroxene family that is one of the two forms of jade.</VEE_SmoothedJadeite.description>
  <VEE_SmoothedJadeite.label>smoothed jadeite</VEE_SmoothedJadeite.label>
  <VEE_SulfurVent.description>A naturally-occurring break in the ground from which sulfuric gases escape. The gas produced on these fissures stinks of rotten eggs.</VEE_SulfurVent.description>
  <VEE_SulfurVent.label>sulfur fissure</VEE_SulfurVent.label>
  <VEE_ToxicVent.description>A volatile fissure that periodically spews noxious green gas, poisoning the air and sickening anything that breathes it.</VEE_ToxicVent.description>
  <VEE_ToxicVent.label>toxic geyser</VEE_ToxicVent.label>
</LanguageData>