<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GutWorms.label>rad worms</GutWorms.label>
  <GutWorms.description>Parasitic worms found in irradiated soil and contaminated food throughout the wasteland. They consume nutrients in the gut alongside the host, causing severe malnutrition even in those who eat regularly. Common in settlements with unfiltered water or improperly preserved food.</GutWorms.description>
  <FibrousMechanites.label>cloud pustules</FibrousMechanites.label>
  <FibrousMechanites.description>A skin irritation acquired through exposure to a mysterious cloud fallout. The residue forms dense fibrous deposits throughout connective tissue and produce visible subcutaneous pustules. The infestation temporarily enhances physical capacity but causes worsening pain as the load increases.</FibrousMechanites.description>
  <SensoryMechanites.label>cloud lung</SensoryMechanites.label>
  <SensoryMechanites.description>A respiratory infestation acquired through inhaling mysterious cloud fallout. The residue lodges in the respiratory tract and nervous system, initially sharpening the senses before progressively overloading neural pathways. Worsening pain and sensory interference are the hallmarks of an advancing infection.</SensoryMechanites.description>
  <Plague.label>new plague</Plague.label>
  <Plague.description>A viral infection endemic across pre-War America. Spreads rapidly once established, overwhelming the immune system within days. Without treatment, most infected individuals die. Standard medicine can suppress the virus, while advanced medical protocols can eliminate the infection entirely.</Plague.description>
  <Malaria.label>bloatfly fever</Malaria.label>
  <Malaria.description>A parasitic infection transmitted by bloatfly bites. The parasites incubate in the bloodstream for days before symptoms appear. Bloatfly fever is rarely lethal on its own, but causes recurring fever episodes that significantly reduce the victim's capacity for work. Common in low-lying areas where bloatfly populations are dense.</Malaria.description>
  <SleepingSickness.label>bayou fungus</SleepingSickness.label>
  <SleepingSickness.description>A slow-spreading fungal infection originating in radioactive stagnant water. The spores progressively saturate neural tissue, causing deepening fatigue and diminished cognitive function. Recovery is slow. Common near stagnant water and dense organic decay.</SleepingSickness.description>
  <ScariaInfection.label>scorched plague</ScariaInfection.label>
  <ScariaInfection.labelNoun>a scorched plague infection</ScariaInfection.labelNoun>
  <ScariaInfection.description>A bacterial infection derived from the Scorched Plague pathogen. The bacteria erode self-control progressively as they reach saturation. Without treatment, the host will eventually descend into a berserk Scorched state. The infection can be halted at any stage with standard medicine.</ScariaInfection.description>
  <Abasia.label>shell shock</Abasia.label>
  <Abasia.description>Shell shock is a severe psychosomatic breakdown triggered by exposure to the unrelenting violence of modern combat. The nervous system, overwhelmed by the sensory assault of weapons fire, explosions, and close-quarters killing, shuts down voluntary motor function as a defensive response. The patient is physically unharmed but cannot walk — the commands the brain sends to the limbs no longer arrive.
Recovery occurs naturally as the mind and neural pathways slowly repair, though the process takes time. A specialized surgical procedure can restore motor function immediately by reconstructing the broken pathways.</Abasia.description>
  <Abasia.descriptionShort>A psychosomatic breakdown caused by extreme combat trauma, leaving the patient unable to walk despite no physical injury.</Abasia.descriptionShort>
  <VFED_Invisibility.description>A stealthboy cloak granted by the Stealthboy device. It affects nearby observers, making their brains unable to perceive this individual even if their eyes remain unaffected.</VFED_Invisibility.description>
  <VFED_Invisibility.label>stealthboy cloak</VFED_Invisibility.label>
</LanguageData>
