<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Outpost_Border_Post.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in patroling faction's border, searching for illegal trespassers and smugglers. Once the violator is caught, he is fined or imprisoned. After which a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Border_Post.description>
  <Outpost_Border_Post.label>border post</Outpost_Border_Post.label>
  <Outpost_Circus.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in organizing artistic and recreational events for wanderers, caravans and natives in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Circus.description>
  <Outpost_Circus.label>wandering circus</Outpost_Circus.label>
  <Outpost_Construction_Site.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in providing construction workers for temporary employment to other factions in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Construction_Site.description>
  <Outpost_Construction_Site.label>construction workers outpost</Outpost_Construction_Site.label>
  <Outpost_Embassy.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in negotiating with other factions. Once the negotiations are successful, goodwill of that faction will increase.</Outpost_Embassy.description>
  <Outpost_Embassy.label>embassy</Outpost_Embassy.label>
  <Outpost_Field_Hospital.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in producing medical supplies for colony. Alternatively can sell them and provide medical help to wanderers, caravans and natives in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Field_Hospital.description>
  <Outpost_Field_Hospital.label>field hospital</Outpost_Field_Hospital.label>
  <Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in providing mercenary services in exchange for silver. Once mission is over reward will be delivered at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.description>
  <Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.label>mercenary camp</Outpost_Mercenary_Camp.label>
  <Outpost_Prison.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in keeping prisoners and their rehabilitation. Get payment with silver for holding prisoners from other factions. Can force to work, recruit or enslave colony prisoners. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Prison.description>
  <Outpost_Prison.label>prison</Outpost_Prison.label>
  <Outpost_Ranch.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in livestock handling and gathering their products. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Ranch.description>
  <Outpost_Ranch.label>ranch</Outpost_Ranch.label>
  <Outpost_Restaurant.description>Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in producing meals supplies for colony. Alternatively can sell meals to wanderers, caravans and natives in exchange for silver. Once an ample amount is collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.</Outpost_Restaurant.description>
  <Outpost_Restaurant.label>restaurant</Outpost_Restaurant.label>
</LanguageData>
