<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <VEE_Hail.description>Hail reduces the accuracy of ranged weapons, extinguishes fire, and slows people down.</VEE_Hail.description>
  <VEE_Hail.label>hail</VEE_Hail.label>
  <VPE_RadioactiveFog.description>A Nuclear reactor's meltdown has freed a cloud of radioactive material. This fog will hinder ranged attacks until it dissipates.</VPE_RadioactiveFog.description>
  <VPE_RadioactiveFog.label>radioactive fog</VPE_RadioactiveFog.label>
  <VPE_Hurricane.description>Extreme wind will cause a slowdown to everyone not under the roof.</VPE_Hurricane.description>
  <VPE_Hurricane.label>hurricane</VPE_Hurricane.label>
  <VPEH_Bloodstorm.description>Mystical downpour of blood, caused by forbidden hemosage psycast. While non-hemogenic individuals are choking on blood, sanguophages regenerate hemogen and can cast psycasts without worrying about psychic heat.</VPEH_Bloodstorm.description>
  <VPEH_Bloodstorm.label>bloodstorm</VPEH_Bloodstorm.label>
  <AM_Facilities.description>There is no weather in facilities.</AM_Facilities.description>
  <AM_Facilities.label>facilities</AM_Facilities.label>
  <VQE_AncientSilo.label>ancient silo</VQE_AncientSilo.label>
  <VGE_DustCloud.description>A dense cosmic dust cloud has drifted across your sector, shrouding your gravship in particulate haze. Visibility is almost zero, and targeting systems are struggling to lock onto anything. The dust will eventually clear as the cloud drifts away.</VGE_DustCloud.description>
  <VGE_DustCloud.label>dust cloud</VGE_DustCloud.label>
  <VGE_ToxicDustCloud.description>A drifting cloud of highly toxic cosmic dust has enveloped your gravship. Microscopic particulates are seeping into every exposed space, corroding surfaces and poisoning the crew.</VGE_ToxicDustCloud.description>
  <VGE_ToxicDustCloud.label>toxic dust cloud</VGE_ToxicDustCloud.label>
  <VQEA_AncientComplex.label>ancient complex</VQEA_AncientComplex.label>
  <VEE_DustStorm.description>A choking wall of wind-driven dust sweeps across the land, reducing visibility, slowing movement, and scouring anything left exposed.</VEE_DustStorm.description>
  <VEE_DustStorm.label>dust storm</VEE_DustStorm.label>
  <VEE_FertileRains.description>Unusually nutrient-rich rainfall is sweeping across the region, boosting plant growth for its duration.</VEE_FertileRains.description>
  <VEE_FertileRains.label>fertile rain</VEE_FertileRains.label>
</LanguageData>
